[2025 Chungnam location incentive
production support project]
[Woo Jihan]
[Shin Jeongyou]
[Min Dohee]
[Seo Seunghyeon]
[Always Meet Again]
Are you done drawing?
Yes.
Hey, look ahead when you're riding.
Look ahead.
Hey, you might injure yourself.
I was looking ahead.
Let's go.
Jang Hyeseong, wake up.
It's time to move.
Hey, Jang Hyeseong!
Hey, the door is open. Come in!
It's really open.
Hey, what's with your state?
What happened?
Urgh...
I just woke up.
I've been nocturnal.
Seriously.
That's why
you've got to wake up now.
Wake up.
Let's drink some beer.
[Episode 1: You, whom I draw again;
you, whom I meet again]
I got into trouble.
Are you getting married?
That's not trouble.
That's boring.
Really?
Let me tell you
something interesting then.
You
will be coming
to our school!
Wow!
Isn't that great?
Why would I be going there?
Here's the thing.
The art room of our school
needs to be renovated.
I'm in charge of it.
While I was busy being delighted...
Hey, the teachers in my school
all look at your social media accounts.
So I went,
"Oh!
Jang Hyeseong is
my childhood best friend!
I can invite him
to be a special lecturer."
That's the trouble I got into.
Hey, we were high school classmates.
How did we become childhood friends?
Hey, we've seen
everything about each other—
that's childhood friends.
It doesn't matter whether
we met in middle school or high school.
Whatever.
Anyway...
Just once...
No.
Just once, please.
No!
To be honest,
you made me become an art teacher too.
You're being stubborn again.
Hey. It's not like I...
threatened you
to become an art teacher.
Well...
No.
It's still all because of you.
Anyway,
you must come.
You'll feel better too. It's good for you.
Why?
I feel great now.
You will feel even better if you go.
I've moved schools.
To where we had many beautiful memories—
Seongjin High!
S-Seongjin High?
Yes.
You haven't been there since graduation,
right?
I haven't gone to school with you
like this in forever.
Hey.
That's not called going to school
but to work.
You rascal!
That's not important!
What matters is
we will be
going to school together
like this for the first time in a long time.
Also...
You must be there tomorrow.
Huh?
Hey.
I haven't decided yet.
You punk.
Wow.
We were so energetic
when we were young.
I'm sorry.
Not for you!
You were terrible at sports!
Hey, I'm not that bad.
Okay?
I'm completely masculine, okay?
Yeah, right!
Hey. Anyone could tell
you're only good at drawing.
How about this?
Let's go one round.
Right now. Let's go!
Oh,
gosh!
Is it 'cause I haven't drunk in a while?
Why does my head hurt?
Gosh...
My head hurts so much.
You...
Hey, I can't.
I gotta go rest up.
You coward.
What are you talking about?
Hey. I have to work tomorrow.
I gotta take care of my health.
Hey, office workers
care about their health.
Gosh.
Anyway,
it's tomorrow.
See you in school,
Mr. Jang.
Hey!
I—
Gosh.
So darn stubborn.
[Lee Woojin]
I was going to go this year.
[Seongjin High School]
They're all so youthful.
I used to have such a good time too.
Hyeseong.
You're so annoying.
How is it?
It feels good to be here
and you're inspired, right?
Gosh.
Hyeseong
was quite naive back then.
What are you talking about?
Go in quickly!
What's wrong?
Huh?
It's nothing.
Let's go.
As you can see,
different people
can feel different
about art—
it's something without
a model answer.
Do you have any questions?
Go ahead.
Do you have a girlfriend?
No.
You're so handsome. Why not?
Well...
There's no one who likes me.
And I don't want to be
in a relationship either.
Why?
I really want to date.
Are there
any other questions?
Any question's fine.
This is not a question,
but I'm going to apply
for a fine arts college.
I was wondering
if you could sketch a portrait
in front of us?
I just want to know
how the professionals do it differently.
Uh...
Sketch...
Well,
my specialty is different.
I need tools too.
I'm afraid I can't do it without those.
There are some in the art room.
In that case...
Next time...
Next time,
I'll show it to you.
Wow.
It's been a while.
[Seongjin High School] [2005-2010]
[Artwork submitted for fine arts college]
Wow.
I drew these too?
What happened?
My head...
The bell's ringing.
I'm going to be late.
What's going on?
Is it broken?
Hello?
Hello! Is anyone outside?
I'm locked inside!
Hello!
Open the door for me!
Is there someone in here?
Oh?
Yes!
I suddenly can't open the door.
You can't go in here.
What?
Well,
I've never heard about that.
It's written on the door.
Well...
Can you open the door for me first?
Wait.
I can't open it.
It's completely locked.
Huh?
What do I do?
Oh?
Hey...
Hey!
How can you just leave?
Hey! Open the door!
[Lee Woojin]
Let's go.
Lee Woojin?
You know me?
Huh?
Yeah.
You saw me on Cyworld?
Are you really Lee Woojin?
Of course.
Is someone pretending to be me?
No.
That's not what I meant.
Why are you here?
'Cause you called out to me.
What?
You called out
saying the door was locked, no?
Wait.
I'm not asking about that.
So are you coming out or not?
If you want to, I'll help you.
If you don't,
I'm leaving.
Yes!
I'm going out.
But...
Then...
step up on that chair.
What's going on?
Aren't you coming out?
Huh?
Yes.
I'm going out.
Thanks.
I'm dreaming, right?
What?
What are you doing?
You're not dreaming.
Huh?
If it's not a dream, what's...
Hey, Woojin.
The transfer student is missing.
What are you doing?
Wearing a uniform?
What's going on?
Wait, why are you all
wearing school uniforms?
What else should we be wearing?
Who is he?
I don't know.
[Jang Hyeseong]
It says Jang Hyeseong.
Jang Hyeseong?
He's the transfer student.
Hey, you're that transfer student, right?
Hey, your homeroom teacher
found you missing
so we were sent out to look for you.
Transfer student? At this age?
What's wrong with him?
I don't know. He's weird.
Hey!
You guys are weirder.
Huh?
Strange transfer student,
let's go.
You're in Class 3, just like us.
Let go! Jeez!
At my age,
why would I be going to school with you?
How old is he?
Is he a repeat student?
Who knows?
But in any case,
he doesn't seem like an ordinary person.
What's going on?
This isn't a dream?
Taejun must be pulling my leg.
No, what about Woojin then?
My goodness.
There are people
still listening to cassette tapes now.
July.
August.
It's a Wednesday, indeed.
Whatever.
I need to see Taejun first.
Where are you feeling unwell—
Huh?
It's class time.
Sister?
Why are you here?
What's with your getup?
Get...
Getup?
Do you want to die?
What are you doing here during class?
Are you skipping class on your first day?
Also,
I told you to call me
the school nurse in school.
Go to class quickly.
Wow.
But you really...
look 10 years younger.
What are you talking about?
But honestly,
you look like you're in your 20s.
What do you mean?
Hey, I'm really young.
I'm in my 20s.
How could you be in your 20s?
You're in your 40s.
I believe this can bring hope and energy
to Korea in 2008.
In the summer of 2008,
we'll be cheering
for the national athletes
who will write an amazing chapter
-with this song full of passion here.
-2... 2008?
2008?
Is it 2008 now?
What else? 2018?
What's wrong with you?
Are you sick?
Sister.
I went back in time.
You must be very sick.
No, no.
T-Today...
No, yesterday Taejun...
Well...
He invited me to be a special lecturer.
So I came to school today
to give students art lessons
and help them understand art.
But the students
told me to sketch a portrait.
I said I couldn't.
Then I went to sketch—
Sister.
I think I found the way back.
Go back? To where?
Go back to class quickly.
Quickly!
Go!
Go back to class!
Uh...
I'm going back.
I'm really back in time?
But why?
Why did I go back to the past?
Whatever.
I can go back soon anyway.
What?
Damn it.
It's locked again.
Oh, yes, the window.
Huh?
I already told you that you can't go in there.
What's going on?
Were you waiting for me?
Why would I be?
Then why are you still here?
Why are you here again then?
Well...
Can you open this?
You're so weird.
You went through so much to come out.
Why do you want to go back in again?
I left something important
in it.
Is that so?
I'm afraid I can't help you this time.
This is locked too.
Hey!
What do I do?
Just wait then.
Until when?
Until the renovation's done.
What?
[Lee Woojin]
Lee Woojin.
Did you call me back?
Class Rep!
The class teacher is calling for you.
Oh.
I think it's about the transfer student.
Hey, your shoelaces are loose.
I'll go first.
See you later.
Okay.
Let's go.
Hello?
Hello! Anyone there?
Help me!
Help me out!
I'm locked inside!
Hello!
[Always Meet Again]