[2025 Chungnam location incentive
production support project]
[Woo Jihan]
[Shin Jeongyou]
[Min Dohee]
[Seo Seunghyeon]
[Always Meet Again]
Lee Woojin.
Did you call me back?
Why would I?
I was going to go play basketball.
Wanna join?
Come out if you want to.
Why did I come back here
and meet you again?
I must
go back.
I barely managed to forget you.
Hey, pass!
Transfer student.
Are you okay?
You don't look well.
I like...
[Episode 2: My Heart beats
for My First Love Again]
I like...
Suddenly?
Oh.
I mean, like, I'm fine.
So don't worry.
You don't look well though.
[Lee Woojin]
Did this happen before?
Goodness.
I knew something was wrong
when you last came here.
Are you sure this is the only wound?
Did you hurt your head?
No.
I was just confused.
That's not right.
You seem crazy.
How much longer will it take?
Almost done.
Oh!
I need to go to the teachers' office.
Here's a Band-Aid. Do it yourself.
Wait for me here.
If anyone comes,
tell them I'll be back soon
and just wait. Okay?
Hey!
You have to finish what you started.
I'll be right back.
So irresponsible.
School nurse.
Didn't you say you weren't hurt?
Well...
It was fine just now.
It just suddenly hurt.
One should take care
of their health when they're young
so they won't suffer when they're old.
Have you been old before?
Of course...
not.
Adults just always say that.
The school nurse
went to the teachers' office.
She said she'll be back soon.
Okay.
You need the spray, right?
What?
For your wrist, right?
How did you know?
It's normal for someone
who plays basketball
to hurt their wrists.
You seem to know
I often hurt my wrist.
Do you...
like me?
What are you talking about?
Is that not it?
Then how do you know me so well?
I don't.
You say you don't,
but actually you know me well.
Did you put the Band-Aid on?
Nurse!
Since you're back, I'm leaving.
Thank you!
You should put on the Band-Aid first!
I don't want to get involved with him,
but why does it keep happening?
I'll bring it to him.
We are classmates.
Oh.
Can you?
Yes.
Thank you.
I should avoid him from now on.
Do I really have to avoid him like this?
I'm so hungry.
This place is full of memories.
Hello.
Give me a can of coke.
I'm hungry.
2,500 won.
I'll pay with my phone.
What?
We only take cash here.
Wait.
Do you...
take this too?
You're not an elementary school kid.
How could you bring counterfeit notes?
I didn't see you eating during lunch.
Well,
I wasn't hungry then.
And you say you're not hungry?
You're full of lies.
That's not it.
I'll find out if we meet more often.
Meet who?
You.
Why?
We're classmates. Can we not meet?
You...
don't want to see me?
This alley
is still the same.
Oh?
Wow, I heard this place
was gone after we graduated.
How interesting.
Oh!
Wow!
Gosh, I used to...
I used to come here all the time.
The minced meat sauce here
is super good.
Skipping class
on his first day of transfer.
How interesting.
I'm hungry.
Gosh.
Why does it have to be a 50,000 note?
I can't even use it.
Gosh.
But this place is still the same.
Done painting already?
Yeah.
This is for me, right?
No.
I'm going to keep it.
Why?
This is your first time drawing me.
Give it to me.
You can just draw again.
No.
This is my first time drawing you.
I want to keep it.
Huh?
What do you mean?
You're over if I catch you.
This place is nice.
How did you know this place?
Well...
Somehow we ended up here.
Have this.
Wow!
Thanks.
Oh.
This.
The school nurse asked you to put it on.
Let me see.
Does it hurt?
Is it okay?
I...
thought about it.
About what?
I'm sure
you like me.
You're so suspicious.
I don't like you.
You like me.
No.
Doesn't seem like you don't like me.
I said I don't.
So I was right.
Huh?
What?
I knew it.
Hey, what are you hiding?
What...
can I be hiding?
You're really suspicious.
Did you do something wrong to me?
I guess.
How could you do that to someone you like?
Anyway,
I'll keep an eye on you.
Don't.
Hey. You liked me on your own accord.
I can do things on my own accord too.
I'm leaving.
See you tomorrow.
Oh,
be careful of your wound.
See you at school tomorrow.
Since I'm here,
it's okay if I stay a little longer,
right?
Water.
Oh?
When one's upset, they got to drink beer.
Hey, are you crazy?
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
You little brat.
Right.
Hey.
I knew something was wrong with you
at school.
Did you get a heatstroke?
Well...
Sister.
Well,
do you know when
the art room's renovation will be done?
How did you know about that?
Well,
can you ask the art teacher
and get me the key to the art room?
What?
What for?
I ran an errand for someone today
and left my sketchbook there.
Buy a new one.
That sketching book
is quite important.
I need it.
Seriously.
I'm always in the infirmary.
I'm not familiar with the art teacher.
Hey, just wait
until its renovation is done.
I'll be fine in a few days.
I need it quickly!
As a school nurse,
you can't even help me with this?
What?
You're so useless.
Goodness.
What can you even do at school?
How dare you!
He's so rude.
[Jang Hyeseong]
You know the test
is coming up, right?
I'll score according to the success rate
of free throws.
Try your best, okay?
-Okay.
Let's go!
I'm depressed.
I can't score any of them.
I can definitely get full marks.
You're so annoying.
By the way,
is the transfer student
good at basketball?
Taking a basketball test at this age...
How speechless.
We
won't show mercy
to the transfer student.
Go and practice.
Okay.
Let me help you.
Relax your wrist.
The angle should be like this.
And...
Throw hard.
Okay.
Try it.
Wow!
Hey, I got it!
Well done.
Gosh.
[Lee Woojin]
What?
With this ball, it'll definitely go in.
[Lee Woojin]
What's different about it?
Because I always use this to shoot.
That's because you're good at it.
If you don't trust me, try it.
Your hand
should be here.
Relax your wrist.
And
as for the angle...
It should be like this.
And then
toss hard.
Okay.
Try it.
Wow!
Hey!
It went in!
Hey, I told you it'd go in.
It's different from before.
Of course.
It's all thanks to me.
Is it really because of you?
Of course.
Do you want bigger changes?
How?
I'll teach you how to play basketball.
I'm sure you'll get everything in
in the future.
Hey, I'll go get the ball.
Hey—
Is this really okay?
Really?
But if
it can really be changed...
Are you ready?
Huh?
Yeah.
In the next five minutes,
try to get the ball from me.
You can do it, right?
Hey!
Are you kidding me?
Huh?
Of course!
I'm afraid it won't be that easy.
All right, start!
Darn it.
You're quite interesting.
Hey, wait. Let's take a break.
You're already tired?
Hey, what "already"?
It's been 50 minutes.
Didn't you say 5 minutes?
That's 'cause you couldn't
get the ball from me.
Whatever.
I can't do it.
Hey, are you giving up
on the test?
Even if I don't do
that test,
it won't affect my life in the future.
What are you talking about?
You make it sound like you're an adult.
Hey, to be honest,
it's not that I'm like an adult—
I'm just old for real.
What are you talking about?
What if you really get old in the future?
In the future?
In the future...
what kind of life
do you think you'll live?
Well...
There's nothing I really want to do.
I might
just live like this with you.
Why?
I just think hanging out with you
is quite fun.
In that case,
shall I just stay here?
Here?
Yeah.
By your side.
If not, are you running away?
The basketball class isn't over yet.
[Lee Woojin: You did well today.
See you at school tomorrow.]
You did well today.
See you at school tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Tomorrow...
Is this okay?
Really?
Is he already asleep?
You're tired already?
It's understandable he slept early.
Good night, Jang Hyeseong.
Hello.
What are you doing?
Did you sleep well?
These songs are pretty good.
What are you doing here?
I was going to wait till you woke up.
Why were you waiting for me?
I couldn't wake you up
because you were asleep.
But I couldn't bear
to leave you alone more.
Aren't you getting off?
We already missed our stop by one stop.
Hey, wait!
If you're lucky,
you might make it in time.
It's okay to be late once in a while.
Being late once
won't affect your future life.
Hey.
We're almost there.
Let's go!
Hurry!
[Seongjin High School]
Hey!
Wait, wait.
I can't do it anymore.
No more.
Whoever's late pays for snacks.
Out of nowhere?
That's more fun.
Hey!
This is cheating!
Come quickly!
Okay, 10 seconds left.
Hyeseong.
I'll transfer the opponent's defense
to the left,
and you pass the ball to the right.
Okay?
Hyeseong.
Hey!
Woojin!
Hey, Woojin!
Hey...
Are you okay?
Hey, I'm sorry.
I'm fine.
You didn't do it on purpose.
Are you okay?
Let's go to the infirmary.
Yes, I'm fine.
Hey, I'm fine. Don't worry.
I'll be back soon.
Sir,
we're going to the infirmary.
Okay, go with him.
Yes.
Go back to your positions.
But why would things like this
happen as it did?
Let's go.
Hey!
What are you doing?
I thought I was fine being the one
bearing the burden.
Are you okay?
[Always Meet Again]