[2025 Chungnam location incentive
production support project]
[Woo Jihan]
[Shin Jeongyou]
[Min Dohee]
[Seo Seunghyeon]
[Always Meet Again]
Hey,
are you OK?
Yup!
I'm OK.
Pass me the yellow.
I asked
for the yellow.
Oh, yellow...
Hyeseong.
Are you
maybe
color-blind
or color-weak?
What?
Let's take a break.
OK.
Lee Woojin!
Jang Hyeseong!
Wow.
So you're doing the mural here.
Yeah.
Why?
I'm joining you.
But the art teacher asked us to do it.
I just asked the art teacher
for permission.
He said we can do it together.
What?
The three of us together?
Yeah.
Can't I join?
Why must you join?
Because I want to do it with you too.
But I don't want to.
Hyeseong, what about you?
Hey.
Come on.
This is unlike you.
What?
I've always been like this.
OK, sure.
But the mural stuff was already decided
with the art teacher earlier.
Oh.
It wasn't decided, actually.
He just agreed because the bell rang,
and everyone was
waiting for the class to end.
It was decided that it's the two of us.
Oh...
Really?
Do you think so too?
Think about it, it'll be faster
if the three of us do it!
Also,
I'd be of great help.
I'm quite artistic, you know?
No need.
We'll manage this mural.
Aren't we friends?
Wouldn't it be nice to do it together?
You guys are so mean.
But, well...
since you insist on doing it yourselves,
there's nothing I can do.
Fine then.
[Episode 6:
[Shaken Relationships]
What Taejun did threw you off, right?
Hmm?
He isn't usually that stubborn.
He's as stubborn as can be.
Is he?
Well, maybe not yet.
Hmm?
Anyway,
I'm fine.
From Taejun's perspective,
it's understandable.
His perspective?
How so?
Well...
Woojin
will die in a week.
Jang Hyeseong!
Forget it.
I'm the idiot for
entertaining your nonsense.
He's your best friend,
but you've been hanging out a lot with me.
So,
it was a valid crash out.
Crash what?
Oh, um...
It means he's upset.
It's slang.
Foreign slang.
I see.
OK.
When you see him at school,
buy him a Coke
and hear him out.
He must be quite troubled right now.
What's there to be troubled about?
I'm not doing all that.
Anyway, I get what you mean.
As long as you're fine with it,
I'm fine too.
Because what's important to me
is you.
[A guide to national and public
art schools in France]
[Seongjin High School]
Hey.
At this rate,
it'll be done soon, don't you think?
Yeah.
Speed is important,
but quality is more important.
No.
There's something more important.
What is it?
That we're doing this together.
Yo, the mural is
progressing fast, huh?
Looks like you're really planning on
applying to art school.
Did you come here to ask that?
No.
I came to see if he went missing
out of the blue again.
Or if
he's harming you in any way.
Hey.
I'm here to check if you're safe!
What are you saying?
Why would he do that?
Well,
he's been weird from the start.
Hey.
What's your problem?
What did I do?
I'm doing this for your sake!
Oh, please. Don't give me that.
You're just pissed off
that I'm close to him!
No, I'm not!
It's really for your sake...
You have no idea how crazy he is.
He's not right in the head.
Why are you targeting someone innocent
for no reason?
Him, innocent?
When he's so full of crap?
Woojin.
Hey.
Full of crap?
How is he full of crap?
Hey.
Do you know what he said?
He said that a week later, you...
Forget it.
I'm the idiot for
playing right into his hands.
Woojin.
It's OK.
Hey, Park Taejun.
Let's talk.
What's the deal with you lately?
What?
Don't play dumb.
Hey.
You always called me your best friend.
But I guess we're not now, huh?
What?
I mean,
you seem to trust him more than me.
Why do you keep speaking in riddles?
Just spit it out.
If I tell you,
will you even believe me?
No matter how I try to convince you
that he's crazy,
you'll still be on his side!
Because you like that bastard.
You're right.
I do like him.
So what?
How does it affect you?
It doesn't affect you at all,
so why do you keep picking on him?
I'm not picking on him!
I'm just worried about you!
Because we're friends!
That's why.
Worried?
That makes no sense.
Yes.
I know it sounds crazy, I do, but...
But I just keep
having the feeling that
he'll put you in danger!
Hey, Lee Woojin!
Hey.
Stop it.
Taejun!
Wait, listen to me.
You'll fight with him
at school in two days.
And in a week...
He'll really die in a week.
I know!
I wished what I'm saying is nonsense.
But you'll soon see
that I'm telling the truth.
What you said
is actually true?
Let's go.
Sigh.
F**king hell.
You'll fight with him at school
in two days.
It must just be a coincidence.
And in a week...
He'll really die in a week.
But if
he's speaking the truth...
And when you do believe me,
please help me out.
Please help me.
I have to save Woojin.
This is insane.
How the hell can I help him?
Hey.
Why did you throw this in the trash?
No, I...
[A guide to national and public
art schools in France]
Eunha.
I'm thinking of pushing back
my study abroad.
What?
Hey.
You said you wanted to study abroad,
so Mom and Dad took the time to ask around
and prepare for it despite being busy,
but now you're backing out?
Well, I...
There's something I have to do here.
So please help me.
No, I...
I just transferred schools not long ago.
I didn't think
it'd be processed so quickly.
Also, don't you think
it's better if I go abroad
after I finish high school?
After all this time
when you've been begging to go ASAP?
Hey.
Are you dating?
Huh? What are you saying?
Me? No way! Ha.
No, I just think...
What?
Eunha.
Do you believe in fate?
Like, how they say
everyone has a predetermined fate.
Do you think that's real?
For example,
that when you die is predetermined.
Or like it'd be
impossible to prevent the death
even if I go back in time
and try to change things?
What have you been up to lately?
Don't try to change the subject
and be honest.
I've just been...
hanging out with my friend.
Which friend?
Lee Woojin.
Lee Woojin?
The guy in the infirmary that day?
Yeah.
Eunha.
Anyway, he and I
have something to deal with.
Let's postpone my study abroad.
Park Taejun?
Hey.
Why are you here?
I'm going to
take your word for it.
Really?
But if it turns out to be a lie,
I'll give you hell.
Hey.
Thank you so much.
I still don't completely trust you.
I'm only going along with this
because Woojin is my best friend.
So,
what do I have to do?
If what you said is true,
won't Woojin
be in grave danger soon?
Right.
Here's a list.
Don't miss anything.
[To-Do List:
Make sure Lee Woojin doesn't ride his bike.
Remind Lee Woojin to watch out for cars.]
[Never leave Lee Woojin alone.
Make sure Lee Woojin
doesn't go to my art cram school.]
It's nothing hard.
Got it.
Now, there's no way he can ride his bike.
Hey.
Just in case,
let's add one more lock.
What's this?
Why are there two locks?
Three?
No, it's four. Ugh.
-Watch out!
What are you two doing?
Be careful.
Seriously, what's wrong with you two?
-Watch out!
Why are you suddenly making a fuss?
Seriously, why do you keep following me?
Just in case you fall down.
Am I a toddler?
In case you bump your head somewhere.
Are you kidding me?
Still, do you have to
follow me to the restroom?
We aren't following you.
We're here to use the restroom.
Yeah, me too.
Why are you two acting crazy?
Are you seriously not leaving?
What if you suddenly run into danger?
You're more dangerous to me.
Get out!
Go, now.
No, wait! Hey! Stop!
I feel less stifled without one of you.
Can I sit?
Sure. Sit.
Hey.
When did you and Taejun
get so close?
He's your best friend.
We should get along.
Right.
There's no harm in getting along.
Woah.
The Jang Hyeseong's room.
Is this the room of a future artist?
Don't tease me. It's nothing special.
Hey, um...
Give me your bag.
Stop fussing.
Where should I put it?
No, no.
Give it to me.
Stop it.
-Should I just jump out of the window?
-Hey, hey!
Put it over there.
Over there?
Yeah.
Can I look around your room?
You're already doing it.
Yes.
I was just informing you.
Um,
want to eat something
before doing homework?
Of course.
I'll be back soon.
OK.
Right.
Don't touch anything dangerous.
You...
Be careful.
What's gotten into him?
Is the light bulb faulty?
Hey!
[Always Meet Again]