[2025 Chungnam location incentive
production support project]
[Woo Jihan]
[Shin Jeongyou]
[Min Dohee]
[Seo Seunghyeon]
[Always Meet Again]
Isn't that
Woojin?
Right. Why is he there?
Hey, Lee Woojin!
Woojin!
Huh?
What happened?
Where'd he go? What's going on?
Jang Hyeseong...
[Episode 8:
Transcend Time]
Are you OK?
Jang Hyeseong...
Hey, Woojin.
Woojin!
Lee Woojin!
[Lee Woojin]
No way.
I came back just like that?
[We're here!]
It wasn't a dream.
[Park Taejun]
Taejun?
Hello?
Hey, the great artist Jang!
Your exhibition is tomorrow.
How's the prep going?
What?
My exhibition?
Yeah.
What's with that reaction?
Is the prep not going well?
Oh. No, no.
It's going well.
But...
I'm sorry I suddenly disappeared that day.
What?
What do you mean?
I mean, I'm sorry I disappeared
during the break of
my special lecture at your school.
What are you talking about?
Are you doing the special lecture?
Didn't you say "never in a million years"?
Did you change your mind?
Huh?
Nice! Then wait for me
to get off work.
Let's talk over some chicken and beer.
I've got to go to class.
See you later.
Hey.
Wait! Hey!
Wait, what's going on?
I'll look for it and get back to you ASAP.
Woojin!
Hey, Lee Woojin!
Jang Hyeseong?
Wait right there!
Is he still living here?
Who are you?
Uh...
Is there a person named Lee Woojin
still living here?
There's no such person here.
The loser pays for snacks.
Hurry up!
Let me help you.
This is still here?
I had...
a great time today.
Yeah.
Me too.
We're done.
I couldn't have done it alone.
I could only finish it thanks to you too.
What I want to draw?
There is something
I want to draw.
Me?
You want to draw me?
You're the theme for my art.
I want to draw you too.
Then let's draw
our backs.
If I keep it a secret for you,
what's in it for me?
Because what's important to me
is you.
Woojin.
Let's stay away
from each other from now on.
What are you talking about,
out of the blue?
We...
must meet again.
Please be alive.
Please.
Hey, Jang Hyeseong!
Oh? It's not locked.
Why do you always bang on the door
instead of ringing the bell?
Because it opens when I knock!
Let's have a drink to celebrate.
By the way,
don't forget what you
promised on the phone.
What?
You said you'd give a special lecture.
You wouldn't agree
no matter how I begged you before.
Why the change of mind?
What?
Is it because you heard that
I'd been transferred
to our high school,
the peak of our youth?
What on earth changed
and what didn't?
What?
What changed?
Huh?
No, nothing.
Um...
I have something to ask you.
Woojin...
Uh, what?
How's Lee Woojin?
The wheel of time seems to be
spinning as usual,
but my time
is still stuck on that day.
There's nothing!
Lee Woojin...
Where have you been?
[The Trace of Time]
[Salute to the world of artist Jang Hyeseong]
Hey, Jang Hyeseong!
I knew you'd be late.
Why are you so late?
I had somewhere
to stop by.
Are you sure you didn't sleep in?
All right.
Shall we meet them now?
Meet them?
Today will be
another beginning for you.
Get ready.
Another
beginning...
Congratulations.
You're so handsome.
Thank you.
Please smile.
Hello.
Congratulations on your exhibition.
Oh. Thank you.
I've been looking forward
to your exhibition.
I'll enjoy it.
Thank you for coming to my exhibition.
Excuse me while I take this call.
Hello?
You didn't find him?
OK.
Mr. Jang.
Can we take a photo with you?
Oh, sure.
Thank you.
1, 2, 3!
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Mr. Jang.
Yes?
You know about the interview, right?
Uh, yes.
I'll come pick you up when you're ready.
OK, thank you.
[Lee Woojin]
Woah.
It's a basketball.
[Lee Woojin]
Thank you.
It's nothing.
How's it nothing?
I can't give you anything like this.
[Lee Woojin]
Mr. Jang, it's time for the interview.
Mr. Jang!
Lee Woojin.
Woojin.
Here.
Hyeseong asked me to give it to you.
Hyeseong?
Yeah.
Hyeseong
always thought of you.
Woojin.
When you read this letter,
I'd have either gone abroad
or vanished for a while.
Sorry for leaving
without saying goodbye.
Every moment I spent with you
was like a gift to me.
I wanted to protect you,
hoping you'll live a happy life.
Even without me by your side,
keep smiling
and keep living well.
If we ever meet again...
No, we will meet again.
Jang Hyeseong.
We must meet again.
When we meet again,
you should smile at me
like nothing happened.
I love you,
Lee Woojin.
From Hyeseong.
[Always Meet Again]