[2025 Chungnam location incentive
production support project]
[Woo Jihan]
[Shin Jeongyou]
[Min Dohee]
[Seo Seunghyeon]
[Always Meet Again]
Eunha!
Woojin went to the hospital?
Woojin?
Oh, him.
You were together last time too.
Looks like you've gotten close.
Is he badly injured?
I just asked him to go take an x-ray.
He broke something?
Hey.
It's normal for boys
to get hurt while playing basketball.
Why are you so shocked?
They'll contact me soon,
so don't worry too much.
Might as well go to this place.
[Art Room]
Give it back before the break ends.
Are you telling me to go now?
Yes.
I have to return it as soon as possible.
[Art Room]
[Episode 3:
Feelings That Can't Be Suppressed]
If nothing changes...
No—if it can't be changed,
it's better to leave here.
What's going on?
Why is it still the same?
Hey.
I drew the same thing as I did last time.
What's wrong?
Hey, sketchbook.
Let me back.
What's going on?
This doesn't work too?
Hey, you...
Is it because it's not complete?
Okay.
That's enough, right?
What's going on?
This doesn't work too?
What am I supposed to do? Gah!
Hey, Jang Hyeseong.
Woojin is in the hospital
because of you.
I know.
Be careful next time.
You got into trouble on your first day.
Because of you, the class teacher
calls me over every break time.
I'm sorry.
Also,
it seems like
you're getting close to Woojin.
He's my best friend...
So let's get close too.
Oh...
Sure.
Okay!
This is great, right?
Gosh.
That's so unc of you.
Unc?
What does that mean?
Well...
Nothing.
It's something
you probably don't understand.
There's nothing I don't understand.
Let's say you do then.
I just want to be alone now.
Can you leave me alone?
Gosh. What's wrong?
Is something bothering you?
Then consult me.
Tell me.
I can take care of everything.
I said I wanted to be alone.
Hey.
Actually, you want to
get close to me too, right?
I understand.
No.
What do you understand?
You haven't changed at all.
Of course I understand.
You can't tell me that directly,
so you're putting it in a vague way.
All right.
Let's go
to the snack shop now.
Let's go get a can of coke
and have a deep chat.
I don't want to become your friend,
Taejun.
You two seem close now.
Woojin!
Hey, are you okay?
Are you okay?
You have a fracture?
It's just a minor injury.
I wanted to take this opportunity
so I asked the doctor
to give me a plaster.
I'll be fine in a few days.
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
No, it's not your fault.
I was being unreasonable.
No, it's my fault.
If you feel sorry,
buy me something from the snack shop.
A patient needs nutrition.
Buy whatever you want.
Whatever I want?
Yeah.
Sure.
I eat a lot.
Let's go.
Hey! Hey!
Weren't we going to the snack shop?
Let's go together!
There's a reason
why you're so bad at sports.
Huh?
You're so talented in drawing.
There's no need
for you to be good at sports.
You're exaggerating.
Hey, just major in art.
I'm hopeless.
Just draw something.
I only know how to draw stickmen.
Then just draw those.
That's...
Is there anything you want to draw?
Fill your drawing paper with that.
What I want to draw?
I got it—
what I want to draw.
All right, did you practice well today?
Before the next class,
hand in your sketchbook
with what you want to draw.
For the theme—like I mentioned just now—
it's freestyle.
So,
I don't want to see how technical
your drawing is,
but how much sincerity
you put into your painting.
Don't think too much.
No need to feel stressed.
Sir.
You're making us feel more stressed.
Just give us a theme.
This is too difficult.
Nah, nah.
You're doing well.
That's all for today.
See you next time.
-Okay.
I've decided on the theme.
What is it?
But I don't know how to draw it yet.
So I need your help.
Me?
By the riverside we went to last time.
I taught you how to play basketball.
It's only fair to return the favor.
What—
You'll help me, right?
Oh!
You looked so reluctant,
but it looks like you came well-prepared.
I don't know how to teach you.
So I hope you can get inspiration
from nature.
I don't want to draw nature.
I want to draw a portrait.
Hey.
It's hard for a beginner
to draw portraits.
That's why I'm asking you to teach me.
Fine.
Who do you want to draw?
It should be easier to draw
if you have their characteristics.
Let me see
if there are any characteristics.
I just like to
look at you.
What characteristics
do you think you have?
Me?
You want to draw me?
Mmhmm.
You're my subject.
But I'm going to draw a stickman
for your body.
Just drawing your face would be
hard enough.
Sure, I guess.
It's up to the painter.
Okay.
I'm going to
draw according to what I feel,
then you give me some suggestions.
Hey, hey!
You should start sketching with a pencil.
I want to paint the background first.
Then the level of completion—
The teacher said he wanted
to see our sincerity
instead of the level of completion.
Fine.
Do what you want.
Speaking of,
what are you drawing?
Well, I...
-If you don't know, start with the background.
-Hey!
I haven't decided on what to draw yet.
Don't think too much.
Just decide while drawing.
You're really...
But...
-Don't you think this color is better?
-Hey!
Just draw your own!
What's yours and mine between us?
If we draw together,
we can help each other—that's nice.
You call that helping?
Mmhmm.
Is that so?
Well, then...
Why?
Hey.
I'll help you too!
Hey!
It's ruined!
Stop it!
It's ruined for real!
Hey, are you sure it can be washed off?
Yeah.
Hey, it's not coming off.
It comes off.
Really?
Yeah.
Hey!
What was that!
Gosh!
It's not coming off.
Do you need my help?
Is that enough water?
Hey, don't do it.
Don't!
Hey, the water...
Hey!
Stop it!
Sorry!
Stop it, stop it!
Can it really be washed off?
Yes.
Try this.
A lip balm?
Yeah.
Thanks.
I have something for you too.
What is it?
Give me your hand.
[Lee Woojin]
Wow, a basketball!
Thank you.
It's nothing.
Don't say that.
I can't give you anything like this.
Thanks to you, I had fun today.
Me too.
By the way,
is your hand okay?
You mean this?
It's just a minor injury.
It's not my first time getting hurt.
Taejun is quite worried about you.
He's always worried.
Isn't it because of his good friend?
We are indeed best friends.
We've been close since middle school.
Then why don't you
hang out with him these days?
Hmm?
You've been hanging out with me lately.
That's because...
it's most fun when being with you
these days.
I feel happy when I'm with you.
Am I the only one who thinks that?
Even if
you feel bored and unhappy
hanging out with me,
as long as you don't dislike it,
don't go anywhere
and stay with me
just like you are right now.
Then I'll make you happy
and find it fun.
Got it?
Let's go.
Are you okay?
You can't be with me.
Hey, what's wrong?
No.
I said no.
Hyeseong!
Hey, Jang Hyeseong!
Wow.
Why was that car driving so fast?
That could've gone down bad.
Hyeseong.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Oh...
Nothing.
It was really dangerous just now.
It's the green light.
Let's go.
[We almost got into an accident crossing the road.
The same thing happened. What should I do?]
[Lee Woojin:
I had fun today. See you tomorrow.]
I had fun today.
See you tomorrow.
You're home safely, right?
[You're home safely, right?]
[Sent]
[Lee Woojin:
Of course. Good night.]
Of course.
Good night.
From now on,
I need to keep a distance from him.
Hey!
I saw Woojin in person
yesterday.
What?
Gosh.
I'm so envious.
I want to see him,
but I haven't been able to.
How was he?
Does he really
shine
really bright?
I mean.
He was so handsome.
-He's a complete prince charming.
-A complete prince charming?
-Yes.
-How much so?
The coolest prince charming on earth.
The coolest prince charming on earth?
No—in the universe.
In the universe?
The kids' taste nowadays...
Forget it.
Hyeseong.
How about we keep a distance
from each other from tomorrow?
Okay.
Just today.
Hey.
Oh!
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Hey.
I just did.
Why didn't you tell me earlier!
Hey.
Let's go.
What's this?
Don't you feel uncomfortable?
Change into this.
Oh...
Thanks.
Here.
Don't look.
Don't look. Raise it up.
Where did you get these clothes?
I had them just in case.
I sweat when playing basketball.
Is your MBTI J?
J?
What's that?
Well...
Someone who's well-prepared
is a J...
What does that even mean?
I'm done.
Thanks.
If you're thankful,
go to the snack shop and buy me something.
Why was the car driving so fast?
[We almost got into an accident crossing the road.
The same thing happened. What should I do?]
Okay.
Just one more day.
Not just the snack store,
I'll pay for all today's expenses.
All?
Yeah.
Sure.
-Hello.
-Welcome.
Thank you.
Wow.
This is interesting.
You've been to a place like this before?
Order whatever you want.
It's on me today. Don't feel burdened.
Bruschetta?
What's that?
Are you...
a second-generation
chaebol?
No, I mean,
I'm a capable adult...
wannabe.
It's okay to spend a bit more now.
Looks like
you're quite confident making it
as an artist.
Right?
Sounds good.
I'm going to order
everything I want.
Sure.
But it seems like
this is a place people come for dates.
Huh?
We...
What's next on this date?
Wow! Wow!
Gosh.
Did you see that?
Amazing.
Is this really
your first time playing bowling?
Yeah.
It's fine.
Actually,
I've never been to restaurants
like just now before either.
I'll teach you how to play.
Okay.
Put your hand back.
Hold the ball like this.
Hey.
I'll do it.
Mine is red, right?
Yeah.
Good luck.
Wow!
-Amazing!
-Wow!
Oh.
I'm sorry.
-Wow.
-You're good.
Let me go again.
Wow, a photobooth.
Hyeseong.
Hmm?
Shall we wear headbands for the photos?
Huh?
Wear this.
Hey.
I'm wearing this.
Must I wear it?
Didn't you say you'd do anything I want?
Put it on and come in.
Hurry up.
Are you serious?
Come in quickly!
Okay, I'll listen to you for today.
I'll listen to you.
Okay, it's starting.
What should we do?
One, two, three.
Butterfly net.
Butterfly net?
One, two, three.
[We're here!]
[Hyeseong]
I'll draw you thick lips.
Don't!
Draw it on yourself!
[Woojin] [Hyeseong]
[We're here!]
Hey, it came out well.
What's all this?
-I like this.
-I don't!
I think this one came out well.
This is terrible.
Hey, you spent too much today.
Let's go dutch.
What are you talking about?
I said it's my treat today.
Is that so?
I'll treat you next time.
Gosh.
I had so much fun today.
Yeah.
I've never had so much fun.
Never?
Really?
Yes.
Because I'd go to art class
every day after school.
Wow.
Hey, you'll definitely
get into a fine arts college.
There's no reason you won't.
If I do, I will just live my life drawing.
Is that not the future you want?
It was.
Not anymore?
No, so...
What's that?
-So...
-You're drunk.
Huh?
Hey!
That's the art teacher
and the school nurse, right?
-Right?
-Be careful.
Hey!
Hide!
Why?
Shh!
That school nurse...
is my sister.
Sister?
Your blood sister?
Yes.
Well...
I can't let her find out
I didn't go for art class today.
Hey!
What are you doing?
You two don't look alike.
Anyway,
keep this a secret
from the others.
I can keep it a secret.
But what do you offer in exchange?
Huh?
[Always Meet Again]