[2025 Chungnam location incentive
production support project]
[Woo Jihan]
[Shin Jeongyou]
[Min Dohee]
[Seo Seunghyeon]
[Always Meet Again]
No, so...
What's that?
Huh?
Hey!
That's the art teacher
and the school nurse, right?
-Right?
-Be careful.
Hey!
Hide!
Why?
Shh!
The school nurse...
is my sister.
Sister?
Your blood sister?
Yes.
Well...
I can't let her find out
I didn't go to art class today.
Hey!
What are you doing?
You two don't look alike.
Anyway,
keep this a secret
from the others.
If I keep it a secret,
what do you offer in exchange?
Huh?
I know a nice draft beer place.
Let's go.
How nice.
What are you talking about?
Let's go.
I'm leaving.
Oh...
Go ahead.
Uh...
Wow...
Today is finally over.
[Lee Woojin:
I had fun today. Good night.]
I had fun today.
Good night.
[Mmhmm, good night.]
[Sent]
Mmhmm.
Good night.
Are you free tomorrow?
[Lee Woojin: Are you free tomorrow? Let's draw together.
The art homework deadline's coming up.]
Let's draw together.
The art homework deadline's coming up.
You're going to your art class
tomorrow anyway.
[Lee Woojin: You're going to your art class tomorrow anyway.
So let's do our homework together.]
So let's do our homework together.
[Lee Woojin: See you at the usual place
at 3 p.m. tomorrow.]
See you at the usual place
at 3 p.m. tomorrow.
[Lee Woojin: See you at the usual place
at 3 p.m. tomorrow.]
[New Message]
[Okay.]
[Sent]
Okay.
[Episode 4: The Truth that Came Late]
What's going on?
Did something happen to him?
[The subscriber
you're calling is not available.]
[Please leave a message after the tone.]
Gosh.
Gosh!
I'm going crazy.
Didn't you say you were going out today?
Me?
Where can I go?
Sister.
Are you
dating the art teacher?
What?
Hey.
What...
What are you talking about?
I mean...
The rumor has already spread.
What?
That rascal...
It's all your fault.
How is it my business?
You were the one
who told me to get
the key to the art room.
That's why this happened.
I didn't know this would happen.
Right?
Besides, you can just date other men.
From what I know,
you'll have many men in the future.
The problem is they're unreliable.
I'm afraid you'll fall for them.
How do you know?
I just know.
So...
just be cool about it.
Hey!
How can I be cool about it?
My heart hurts.
Your heart hurts?
Sister.
This is about my friend.
He likes someone.
But for some reason,
he keeps trying to hide his feelings
and avoid them.
Do you think this friend
is more heartbroken
or that person?
You have someone you like?
Hey!
I already said it's my friend.
If he likes them,
why is he hiding from them?
Well...
He likes him,
but he always causes trouble
to that person inadvertently.
So he's in a lot of pain.
If it's so painful,
it's better to clear it up
as soon as possible,
before the love gets too deep.
Don't you think
that's better
for both parties?
I'll be right back.
Since it's so painful,
it's better to clear it up
as soon as possible,
before the love gets too deep.
Yes.
It's not too late. Let's end it.
I'm sorry,
Lee Woojin.
Did something happen yesterday?
Hyeseong.
Hey, Jang Hyeseong.
What?
Why didn't you come yesterday?
I did.
What?
When?
I was a little late.
But you weren't there.
Then why didn't you call me?
I thought you might have left
because you got tired.
We'll meet at school anyway.
I asked you out yesterday
to do our homework together.
Ah.
Let's do our homework
at home by ourselves.
We don't need peer evaluation anyway.
What?
What's wrong?
What do you mean?
You're being weird suddenly.
I'm weird to start with.
You said I was weird when we first met.
You know that's not what I meant.
Something's bothering you, right?
I've just gotten tired of you.
What?
I mean, that happens.
As you live,
you can take a liking to someone,
but you can also get tired of them.
I don't believe what you said.
Did I do something wrong?
No.
Oh.
I guess you woke me up?
Hey.
Why are you like this suddenly?
Hyeseong.
I'm sorry for just now.
Got it.
Hey, Taejun.
Huh?
I need your help.
With what?
The PE teacher said
the basketball test...
Hyeseong.
Let's talk.
Let's go to the snack shop.
Me?
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
Wow.
He's so good at drawing.
Hey!
How could you look at
other people's stuff without asking?
Then why did you draw me
without asking?
Tired of me?
How can I believe that
after seeing this?
I just...
thought you were a good model.
You're lying again!
You drew me because you like me.
'Cause you like me!
No.
No?
It's all me.
Don't you feel the same as me?
Why are you suddenly denying it?
Why...
Why do you keep avoiding me
and pushing me away?
Yes.
I like you too.
But...
we can't get any closer.
You said you liked me, so why?
Because it's dangerous
for you to be with me.
It was like that last time,
and it's the same this time.
It won't change.
What are you talking about?
What danger?
What won't change?
Woojin.
Let's stay away
from each other from now on.
I'll let go
of my feelings for you.
Hey!
Ouch!
Oof...
What?
I'm back?
All of a sudden?
To come back, I have to tear this?
But I didn't want to come back like this.
[Lee Woojin]
Let's stay away
from each other from now on.
I'm sorry.
Darn it.
Didn't he say
he was going to the art room?
He's not answering his phone.
Where did he go?
Hello?
Hey, where are you?
Break time is over.
What are you doing?
It's hard to explain.
I'm not at school right now.
What?
Where are you?
Hey, Jang Hyeseong.
Jang Hyeseong!
Sister?
Why are you here?
What about school?
How did you know
I went to school?
[Cheongmyeongwon Memorial Hall]
I'm sorry.
I don't know
how to tell you this.
Actually,
I've been secretly coming here every year
without you knowing.
Why would you come here?
Woojin
didn't get into an accident
in front of the school gate.
Then where was it?
It was at the entrance
of your art class—
when he was on his way
to look for you on a bicycle.
What?
Then why did you tell me
he had a car accident
on his way to school?
I thought it would be better
if I kept it from you
that he got into an accident
looking for you.
If you knew,
it'd be very difficult for you.
But...
I feel guilty
hiding it from you,
so I come here every year,
asking Woojin for forgiveness,
apologizing to him.
Eunha!
I'm sorry.
I didn't want you to have a hard time.
So all this time,
to avoid meeting you here,
I've always arranged
for you to be elsewhere.
This year it's school.
Last year it was a health checkup.
The year before last...
So every year, Taejun and you...
Taejun knows too?
I'm the only one who didn't know.
Everyone but me—
the person involved—knows?
I'm sorry.
I did it for your sake.
For my sake?
I'm the only one who doesn't know
about the truth of Woojin's death.
You call this for my sake?
That's why I kept it from you.
I didn't want you to blame yourself.
I should!
He died because of me!
What would hiding this change?
Are you okay?
You can't be by my side.
Hyeseong.
You're quitting school?
What are you talking about?
I'm leaving tonight.
What?
I'm going to study abroad.
All of a sudden?
You never talked about that.
I thought it'd be better for me
to go earlier.
Still, how could you
leave without saying goodbye?
What's there to be in a hurry about?
I should be.
If I just waste my time here with you,
I'll fall behind.
What?
Dating you
won't do me any good.
Hey.
Do you think drawing
is more important than I am?
Yeah.
Sorry.
I'm sorry for lying to you.
But it's all in the past.
If you live well,
he will rest in peace.
You said he would rest in peace?
Even if you are sad,
nothing will change.
No.
What if I say I can change it?
Eunha.
Do you have a pen or pencil?
Pen?
So suddenly?
Do you?
Hey, Jang Hyeseong!
I can change everything.
[Lee Woojin]
Lee Woojin.
I'll definitely save you this time.
[Lee Woojin]
I'll let go of
my feelings for you.
Hey!
Hyeseong?
Where did he go?
[Always Meet Again]