[2025 Chungnam location incentive
production support project]
[Woo Jihan]
[Shin Jeongyou]
[Min Dohee]
[Seo Seunghyeon]
[Always Meet Again]
Is the light bulb faulty?
Hey!
What were you thinking!
What if you got hurt?
Huh?
The light bulb seemed faulty.
It looks fine.
I know...
Hey, Taejun, wait.
Hear me out first.
You'll fight with him at school
in two days.
Two days later,
he'll get hurt
while changing a light bulb.
The location's changed,
so why is this happening？
What did you say?
No, nothing.
[Episode 7:
What's Our End?]
Really?
Gosh, that was close.
Luckily he didn't get hurt.
That's a relief.
But why'd it happen at your house?
I know, right?
By the way,
I've been wanting to ask you something.
How'd you know
something would happen
to Woojin?
It's not that I don't trust you.
But logically...
I believe you from the bottom of my heart.
But to be honest, logically,
it's hard to understand,
isn't it?
Right?
What's going on?
I'll tell you...
I'll tell you when it's over.
When it's over?
What?
What's over?
After Woojin gets through the week.
O-Oh...
OK.
Jang Hyeseong.
What secrets are you two whispering about?
Huh?
What secrets? No way.
Nothing of that sort.
Yeah... You're here.
I'll leave you two to finish the mural.
I'm off.
Oh, OK. Bye.
-Good luck with the mural.
-Thanks.
The old Park Taejun is back.
Yeah.
Oh, um...
Do you want to go on a trip?
Hmm?
I mean, the vacation is short.
Let's go on an overnight trip
at someplace fun
and have some good food.
Woah...
I'd love that.
Let's bike there.
Uh...
Biking's a bit dangerous.
Hey.
What's dangerous about biking?
We'll just be careful.
I'm so excited.
Then,
you must be really careful.
Of course.
You're here.
What took you so long?
My bike was locked up by someone.
L-Locked up?
Wait till I get my hands on who did it.
Let's go.
Hey.
You must be super careful.
Don't mess around or anything.
Are you my mom?
What's with all this nagging?
Hey, I'm a great biker.
Just be careful yourself.
Let's go.
Please let us get through today safely.
Ah! This is nice!
Hey.
Look over there.
It's totally submerged.
Someone should be living there too.
There's no way someone lives there.
Hmm?
Hey!
Ho!
You've got ice cream all over your face.
I had...
a great time today.
Yeah.
Me too.
Hyeseong.
Hmm?
I had so much fun today.
I'll never forget this trip.
Me too.
Let's come again.
Can we?
Why not?
We can just come if we want.
Yeah.
I hope we can come again.
Hmm?
If I can stop your death...
If I stop your death...
I won't
leave you behind again.
But
if I can't stop it...
I'm leaving soon.
What?
Where are you going?
To study abroad.
What?
All of a sudden?
You know
my dream is to be an artist.
I'm leaving to fulfill my dream.
But it's so sudden.
I should have told you earlier.
Sorry.
Is this trip just
to make your last memories with me
before you leave?
No, it's not like that.
When are you leaving?
Soon.
What?
I'll tell you
when it's decided.
Are you really leaving?
You're really leaving?
So this is really to commemorate our end.
It's not that.
Then why are you...
leaving all of a sudden?
If I can change your fate,
we will
definitely meet again.
Don't answer if you don't want to.
We...
must meet again.
Will you come back?
If you're still alive.
What do you mean?
No, I mean...
If I live
a good life there
and you live your life well here,
won't we get to meet again?
Lee Woojin!
Where did he go now?
Hey.
Where were you?
Just to buy breakfast.
How could you disappear
without telling me?
I was so worried!
You were sleeping so well, so...
Hey, I'm not a kid.
No, I...
Why are you so worried about me?
If you're so worried,
why are you leaving me so suddenly?
Hey.
No, I just...
I don't want you to be in danger.
Fine.
Thanks for the concern.
You must be hungry.
Let's eat.
Before you leave,
we'll finish the mural, right?
Hmm?
Since you're going abroad.
Yeah.
We said we'd finish it together.
I was planning to finish it today anyway.
OK.
To you,
this mural is just
a tiny fraction of your art, right?
Hmm?
I want to
see your art.
You've seen it before.
Not the mural.
Not stuff you drew in school.
Serious drawings and paintings of yours.
Art so spectacular
that warrants you going abroad
and leaving me.
I think I'll be able to
accept your leaving
after seeing them.
So show them to me.
Won't I get to see them
at your art cram school?
Let's stop by there today.
What?
Woojin didn't
get into an accident
in front of the school gate,
but at the entrance
of your art cram school,
when he was on his way
to look for you on his bike.
Hey!
No.
Why?
You don't want to show them to me?
No, that's not what I meant...
The art cram school is closed
until tomorrow.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Then let's go the day after tomorrow.
I really want to
see your art.
Yeah.
OK.
He suddenly wants to
go to my art cram school.
Didn't you say he mustn't go there?
Yes, he mustn't.
Not even the vicinity.
But I'm busy
at home today. I can't be with him.
So you should
stay with him for the entire day.
Yeah.
I was thinking of
finishing the mural today anyway.
Right, also, um...
Thank you for believing me.
Believe what?
Uh.
Yeah, Eunha.
Yes, believe me.
I'll get home safely. Haha.
Don't worry.
See you at home.
OK.
Ha, goodness.
Hey, it's crazy
how my sister still sees me as a kid.
Let's go.
We have to finish the mural.
Yeah, sure.
We're done.
We are.
It's really done.
Never thought I'd get to do a mural.
I couldn't have done it alone.
I could only finish it thanks to you too.
So, you're
leaving now?
Hmm?
Since the mural's done.
Not yet.
Then when?
When should I start
getting mentally prepared?
Don't tell me
you're going to
vanish out of the blue again?
Just now...
To be honest,
I heard everything
just now.
He suddenly wants to
go to my art cram school.
Yes, he mustn't.
Not even the vicinity.
No, listen...
Why do you never tell me the whole truth?
About studying abroad,
you also kept it a secret
and just suddenly informed me.
You say you like me,
so why do you keep
taking me for a fool?
-No, it's not like that.
-At the very least,
you should give me
a chance to say goodbye.
Am I asking too much?
Did I ask you not to go?
I just...
I just want to see your art,
so I can remember you with it.
So I can reminisce about you
while looking at your art,
and engrave you in my heart.
Go.
Your study abroad and whatnot.
Your feelings;
your thoughts...
I can no longer make sense of them.
Actually,
it doesn't matter whether
we have a future or not.
As long as I can keep Woojin safe,
as long as I can stop his death,
that's enough, isn't it?
[To-Do List: Make sure Lee Woojin
doesn't go to my art cram school.]
Tomorrow is the last day.
Just get through tomorrow safely...
You don't need to know
why I'm doing this.
All I want
is to keep you safe.
[Art Cram School]
Didn't you say he wouldn't come?
Still,
just in case.
Hey!
He's saved.
Really?
OMG!
We finally made it.
Thank goodness.
I know.
Let's go.
You can tell me now, right?
Tell you what?
About Woojin's death.
You said you'd tell me
how you foresaw everything when it's over.
Well, that's...
Isn't he safe now?
Tell me.
What? Are you not going to tell me?
Actually, I'm...
from the future.
What?
I'm serious.
How did you get here?
Through a time machine?
Through this sketchbook.
Gosh, you've really got a screw loose.
-Huh?
-You wacko.
Hey, I'm s-serious.
Oh?
Isn't that
Woojin?
Right. Why is he there?
Oh?
Hey, Lee Woojin!
Woojin!
[Epilogue]
I don't know why, but your smile
always looked sad to me.
Was it because I sensed
that you'd leave me?
If you were going to leave,
why've you been so nice to me?
It's fine.
Go.
[Live your own life.
Stay healthy.]
Live your own life.
Stay healthy.
Like you,
I'll build my future well too.
By then, I'll...
search for you.
We'll meet again.
[Always Meet Again]