[2025 Chungnam location incentive
production support project]
[Woo Jihan]
[Shin Jeongyou]
[Min Dohee]
[Seo Seunghyeon]
[Always Meet Again]
Lee Woojin.
Eat this.
Sigh.
Screw that Jang Hyeseong.
When he shows up again,
he's dead meat!
Hey.
How could you say that
about someone who's missing?
And he's been gone
for three whole days.
His family's already reported him
missing or as a runaway anyway.
Why are you so worried?
Wait,
are you...
Never mind.
What is it?
Nothing.
I'll come again tomorrow morning.
Didn't you say
he suddenly showed up in the art room?
Then this time, I'm sure
he'll suddenly show up somewhere again.
Don't worry too much.
I'm back.
Alright.
This is my last chance.
I must change things,
no matter what.
[Episode 5:
Be With You No Matter What]
Woojin!
Hey, Lee Woojin!
Jang Hyeseong?
Wait right there!
What...
happened to you?
Thank goodness
I get to see you again.
What are you talking about?
You were the one who vanished.
Where did you go?
What happened?
I'm sorry.
What do you mean?
Did
something happen to you?
No, nothing.
Then why did you suddenly...
I...
I'm sorry for what I said that day.
It's OK.
I know you didn't mean it.
I'm...
going to stay by your side.
To keep you safe from danger,
I will protect you.
Why'd I be in danger—
You won't.
I'll make sure you're safe.
In any case,
I'd like that.
See you tomorrow.
It's really late.
Go on in.
Get home safely.
OK.
Hey, Jang Hyeseong!
Where have you been?
I need to talk to you.
Showing up out of thin air,
and now you want to talk?
Hey.
Did you apologize to Woojin?
Because of you, Woojin's been...
I know.
He must've been really worried.
I'm sorry to you and Woojin.
Is this what you wanted to say?
Please help me.
This might be hard to believe,
no,
you won't believe me,
but you have to.
It's the only way Woojin can live.
What?
Woojin...
will die in a week.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I told you you wouldn't believe me.
But please believe me.
We must keep Woojin alive.
Jang Hyeseong!
Are you serious?
Forget it.
I'm the idiot for
entertaining your nonsense.
Taejun!
Wait.
Listen to me.
You will fight with him
at school tomorrow.
Two days later,
he'll get hurt
while changing a light bulb.
And in a week...
He'll really die in a week.
For heaven's sake,
stop with this nonsense,
you crazy bastard!
I know!
I wished what I'm saying is nonsense.
But you'll soon see
that I'm telling the truth.
And when you do believe me,
please help me out.
Please help me.
Taejun.
I have to save Woojin.
You're insane.
To-do list...
[To-Do List]
Make sure Lee Woojin
doesn't ride his bike.
[To-Do List]
Remind Lee Woojin to watch out for cars.
Never leave Lee Woojin alone.
Make sure Lee Woojin
[To-Do List]
doesn't go to my art cram school.
Let's just
get through this week safely.
Huh?
Why are you here?
To go to school with you.
Are you sure
nothing happened?
Of course.
I just want to go to school with you.
Yeah?
Let's go.
Hey,
we're having class in the art room today.
Let's get moving.
Art class, your favorite.
Yeah.
Guess the construction's done.
Don't you want to go there?
You said you left
something important there.
Finally.
No, I don't need it anymore.
Hmm?
But we're screwed.
We didn't do the homework.
I know.
Because someone stood me up.
Sorry.
It's OK.
We'll just apologize
to the teacher together.
OK.
Let's go.
Aren't you leaving?
What are you doing?
I'm looking at you.
What?
You asked me to.
[Won't you look at me?]
Hey, that's...
Why'd you read it now?
How can you take back what you gave?
Calm down. Give it to me.
-No!
-Give it to me.
No!
Hey, give it to me!
Stop right there!
Bleh! I don't want to!
I can catch you anyway.
Careful. You'll get hurt.
Here. Have it.
You knew I'd wrestle it out of you
anyway, right?
It doesn't matter.
Since I'm smart,
everything's stored in my head.
Pfft.
This is so embarrassing.
The bell's about to ring.
Let's go.
Alright, let me see what you've drawn.
Wow.
This is interesting.
Yeah?
Good job.
This is very original.
Right?
Good brushwork too.
Good job.
What about you two?
Did you just draw in your minds?
-I'm sorry.
Did I insist on a completed work?
You should've at least drawn something.
-I'm sorry.
I'm sure you are. Tsk.
What are you trying to express?
It's great now,
but it'd be even better if
you could give it a bit more depth.
OK, that's all for today.
Oh, right.
Before you leave,
I have an announcement to make.
Anyone want to
participate in an
environmental beautification art project?
I need two volunteers.
No one?
If you're into art,
this is a great opportunity.
Me!
Jang Hyeseong?
Yes.
Right, you're
planning to apply to art school, right?
Yes.
Great.
If you do a good job,
I'll make a note of it
in your school report.
OK?
Thank you.
Well, no one else?
Sir, I'd like to do it with Woojin...
Sir!
Me!
Park Taejun?
Yes.
Hey.
This isn't your thing anyway.
It is my thing.
It is?
Yeah.
Then...
will you do it with Taejun?
But I want to do it with Woojin.
Let's finish it together this time.
Sure.
OK, I'll do it with him.
Taejun, are you OK with that?
Yes.
If I keep at it,
I'll get my chance someday.
It's settled then.
Jang Hyeseong and Lee Woojin will do it.
-OK.
See you next class.
Thank you, sir.
You just decided for me?
I'll help you.
It's a deal.
Let's go. Come on.
Let's sit here.
Ah.
Here.
Thank you.
By the way,
have you done a mural before?
Yeah.
Oh, um...
Not for now.
Not for now?
What do you mean?
Well, I mean,
we're going to do it soon.
Is there anything
you want to draw?
Me?
Of course, it has to be...
you.
I want to draw you too.
Then
let's draw us.
Us?
Yeah.
Draw the two of us.
OK.
I think it'll take at least a week.
Hmm?
So for the next week,
we have to stick together.
Oh.
OK.
Got it.
It'll take a long time to draw faces.
How about drawing backs instead?
Backs?
Yeah.
Our backs.
Don't you think
that will look sad?
Isn't it hopeful if you see it
as us moving forward?
Feels like a positive spin on it.
As they say,
art is open to interpretation.
OK then.
Let's draw
our backs.
Hey.
Are you OK?
Yup!
I'm OK.
Pass me the yellow.
Here.
I asked for the yellow.
Oh, yellow...
Hyeseong.
When I draw the defense to the left,
make a pass to the right.
Hey, Hyeseong!
Mine is the red ball, right?
Yeah.
Hyeseong.
Are you
maybe
color-blind
or color-weak?
What?
Let's take a break.
OK.
Lee Woojin!
Jang Hyeseong!
Wow.
So you're doing the mural here.
Yeah.
Why?
I'm joining you.
But the art teacher asked us to do it.
I just asked the art teacher
for permission.
He said we can do it together.
What?
The three of us together?
Yeah.
Can't I join?
Why must you join?
Because I want to do it with you too.
But I don't want to.
Hyeseong, what about you?
Hey.
Come on.
This is unlike you.
What?
I've always been like this.
[Epilogue]
Where on earth did he go?
The person you have reached
is not available.
Why do you even have a phone?
Woojin.
Where's my baby brother?
Hey, Taejun.
Eunha.
Have you
met Hyeseong?
Ah...
Yeah.
Why did he go there?
He was at school a minute ago.
I know, right?
But
Hyeseong
suddenly disappeared.
What?
Where did he go now?
I don't know.
He just suddenly disappeared.
What?
[The late Lee Woojin]
Where
did Hyeseong go?
Sigh.
At the moment, my vision turned white,
and then Hyeseong suddenly disappeared.
Something's off.
Woojin!
Hey, Lee Woojin!
Jang Hyeseong?
This time,
I won't lose you again.
[Always Meet Again]