WOULD YOU LIKE TO MEET
YOUR NEXT BOYFRIEND?
EPISODE 1
THE FUTURES OF YOU AND ME
2 WEEKS AGO
I'm home.
I said I'm home.
Initiating home mode.
There's no place like home.
There are 24 hours in a day.
Six hours of sleep.
Ten hours of work.
COMMUTING: 2 HOURS
Time spent commuting and eating…
EATING: 1 HOUR
Take out all of that, plus washing up,
and I'm left with…
WASHING UP: 1 HOUR 30 MINUTES
…just three and a half hours.
Enough to watch a movie or two, at best.
I don't waste those precious
three and a half hours on just anyone.
An ordinary day like today,
with no plans or special events…
So warm.
Days like these are the best kind for me.
Off to sleep now.
Initiating sleep mode.
When the brief happiness ends,
my body is thrown back
into the bustling world.
The circle route train is arriving.
Last summer in the Philippines
was the best.
I wish I could go swimming.
When is summer coming?
Excuse me.
Yes?
I think that kid just…
Damn, that little rascal!
Doors opening.
Doors closing.
Hello.
Hey.
Come on.
That won't work.
Okay.
What's his deal?
Doors opening.
Doors closing.
UNREGISTERED ID
Please try again.
Producer?
Hello.
-You're here.
-Hi.
Congratulations.
-What for…
-Congratulations.
Thank you.
As always,
another perfectly punctual arrival.
Your commitment to never being early
is truly impressive.
Is it Park Kyeong-nam's birthday today?
Oh, that?
-He signed an adaptation deal.
-Again?
Just come to dinner. The director
is treating us to beef because of that.
Company dinner?
I actually have plans today.
Plans, you say?
Just say you're going vegetarian instead.
Mr. Park will be coming, won't he?
He's the man of the hour.
Even he wouldn't sit this one out.
Are you really not coming?
The director is totally miffed
that you've been skipping dinners lately.
It's not like I'm the only one. That guy…
Producer Park always skips them too.
You have a point.
He's a tiny bit less personable than you.
Don't you think he's so charming?
Huh?
Leave her be.
She's been fangirling over Kyeong-nam.
-Fangirling?
-Yes.
After much deliberation,
I've decided to give liking him a go.
What are you talking about?
You've decided to what? Why?
He's so handsome.
Smells good too.
Oh my.
Eun-ju, you've still got much to learn.
About what?
"Never date someone on your own turf,
even with a knife at your throat."
No one told you that?
Well, I never said I wanted to date him.
You'll know when you know.
-Good luck, Eun-ju.
-Oh dear.
PARK KYEONG-NAM
Here is the requested feedback
on your team's proposal from last week.
Oh, right.
Weaknesses.
The protagonist lacks compelling appeal.
An insufficient grasp
of the fantasy genre.
Disconnected characters
and unclear themes.
The story offers
neither universality nor plausibility.
Strengths. None worth mentioning.
Hey, Cho!
Hey, I'm not done talking to you!
Well,
I'm done working here.
-Wait, Mr. Cho!
-Hey! You're quitting?
-That's right!
-Come on now.
-Let go.
-You know how he is!
-I don't care.
-Just think it over.
No. Move aside!
Mr. Cho! Wait a minute. Mr. Cho!
Is he seriously leaving?
Why are you all looking at me?
I didn't do anything wrong.
Did he really go? What do we do now?
JI-YEON
We really need to meet up today.
I'm serious.
What's up with her?
Hey.
Seo Mi-rae!
It took me ages to get here.
Did you call me here
just to drag me around shopping?
Of course not.
You know I know your lifestyle.
I called you here to address
a very serious and important issue.
Issue? What is it?
An Da-yeong's wedding.
What are you wearing?
Huh?
You're not just going to send her money
and be done with it, are you?
I mean, I'm busy with work and all--
Hey! All the more reason to go.
You should be there, dressed to kill,
to show everyone that you're going places!
I'm going places?
I mean, that's how you should look.
All our classmates are gonna be there.
You can't just sit and watch You-mi
and Se-june pull that lovey-dovey crap.
Breaking them up isn't an option,
but you should still strut your stuff.
"I'm totally doing well right now."
"I'm at my peak."
Hey, it's been forever since we broke up.
Besides, I have nothing to brag about.
Hey, this one looks decent.
Go try this one on.
Hurry up!
It's not even Kim Se-june's wedding.
She's so dramatic.
Don't you dare return that.
I'm so gonna get you.
Oh, please! You're making it sound
like you bought it for me.
Hey, I'm an art teacher.
You think I'm rolling in cash?
I wish I could get you stuff like that.
Mi-rae, you poor thing.
Hey, why would you say that?
I'm doing well. I'm happy, you know.
Aren't you lonely?
Not one bit.
You don't think about guys at all?
For real?
Would my company give me a raise
if I got myself a boyfriend?
Doubt that.
Doesn't that mean dating someone
would only tire me out more
and make me poorer?
Getting physically tired
isn't the only problem.
You know how mentally exhausting it can be
if you end up with an immature guy.
Then find yourself a mature guy!
Or someone exactly like you.
What, a guy like me?
Yeah!
-You know, your kind.
-What kind?
You don't exactly bother others,
but you come off as kinda
standoffish.
Date a guy like that.
Damn.
I'm done working here.
Wait, Mr. Cho!
-You know how he is.
-I don't care.
What are we gonna do without you?
Whatever. Ask the director!
Hey! Are you out of your mind?
Why would I do that?
A person's got to be personable.
That's what makes us human.
So you know how I feel about you!
Hey, I'm home.
I said I'm home!
Initiating home mode.
God, I must have been out of my mind.
Are you serious?
Oh my God.
What a shame. Mr. Cho was so close
to becoming team leader.
Was it because of Yun Song?
Man, who's going to take that on?
PLANNING TEAM 2
Did they find a replacement?
Will Team 1 be taking over?
Word is,
they're considering
Park Kyeong-nam or Seo Mi-rae.
What? I get Park Kyeong-nam.
But Mi-rae?
She's not even in charge of Yun's genre.
The romance producers
are refusing to do it.
Mi-rae's schedule is lighter right now.
Good morning.
What? What is it?
What?
Me? Me? Me?!
Morning, everyone!
Good morning!
Good morning.
Still, Park Kyeong-nam's been doing
better than you lately.
The director might assign him
instead of you.
Well, you never know.
Who knows what the director is thinking?
Don't worry about it.
Oh God.
Ms. Yun!
Please open the door, Ms. Yun!
Ms. Yun! Please give me the final files!
Ms. Yun!
YUN SONG
WEBTOON "THE MAN TO KNOW"
EPISODE 21
UPLOAD COMPLETE
Like a flu virus that slips past
even the raging white blood cells,
Yun Song, back in the day,
completely took over my daily life.
YUN SONG
Yes, Ms. Yun.
Ms. Seo?
Ms. Yun, are you crying?
Did you see the comments?
The things they wrote about me!
Ms. Yun, it's 3:00 a.m. right now.
These hateful comments won't stop
until I die, will they?
But why should I?
Why should I be the one to go?
You sons of bitches!
No!
Absolutely not.
IN
Director, it's Seo Mi-rae.
Yes, come in.
I happened to pass by Raturer Macaron
after having lunch.
I know how much you love…
I see you were also here, Mr. Park.
Yes. I also happened
to pass by that place.
Take a seat. We can talk together.
God, that's sweet. Too sweet!
-Have some coffee.
-Okay.
This coffee you got… You got…
-Yirgacheffe.
-You got Cheffe!
Right, Cheffe.
Man, I didn't realize
how sociable you guys are until today.
I need to talk to you about--
Now!
An opportunity like this
won't ever come around again, okay?
Make your case for why
you should be put in charge of managing
Yun Song, Naemo's number-one author.
Right. I'd first like to--
Even though you two heartlessly declined
to attend any of the dinners,
this is no place for personal grudges.
I'll decide based solely on your skills.
So just relax. And speak up.
What I'm saying is,
the right person to manage
our top author is none other than--
I'll step aside.
I may have joined Naemo a bit earlier,
but Ms. Seo's shown she's capable
of managing authors and planning projects.
No matter how I think about it,
I think you should grab that opportunity.
All right, then.
No. I wouldn't dare take the place
of someone so competent
and manage Ms. Yun for the second time.
You're being too modest.
Mr. Park gets a hit
out of every author he manages.
He'd be perfect for Ms. Yun.
Besides, in his own words,
my projects have
no strengths worth mentioning.
Ms. Yun's already set the whole table,
so there's not much to worry about.
Wow, then you should sit at that table
and dig in.
Enough.
So, neither of you wants to do it.
That's the gist of it, no?
Fine, I get it.
But still,
how can you work in the webtoon business
with so little passion?
You guys worship work-life balance,
don't you?
Forget it. We're all done here.
Seo, you manage her.
What?
I noticed
you were only managing six authors.
But--
Besides, you're the one who directed Yun
toward romance when she started out.
Yes, but I ended up handing it over
to a different producer.
You know it's not my genre.
Actually, I don't.
Then I'll consider this matter settled
and take my leave.
-I have a meeting to attend.
-Sure. Go ahead.
All right.
I'll leave you to it.
Excuse me.
A meeting just magically popped up?
Off you go.
You call that a meeting?
How did it go?
So it's you?
Park Kyeong-nam showed up
with a whole box of macarons.
-Wonder who tipped him off.
-What?
Hey, it wasn't me.
Well, so,
how long will you be
in charge of Ms. Yun Song?
-Dunno.
-How long?
Until she collapses from exhaustion.
Mi-rae, you've got this.
Don't let it get you down.
You just need to get the jump on her.
Like that will work with Yun Song.
Some pasts come back to you,
reborn as the future.
Didn't I tell you?
My sister's friend works
at Dongseoyang Law Firm.
-I'm heading there tomorrow.
-You just got back?
-Stupid online trolls.
-What?
-I'm gonna confront them this time.
-Be quiet. Ms. Yun's on the phone.
Settlement? Not on your life.
-Does she ever sleep?
-I have money.
-I'm calling my sister now.
-She's really something.
She hung up!
I'm really going crazy.
Are you sure you can come tonight?
You bet. It's your birthday.
The advertisement we talked about,
is it a go or not?
You don't need to worry too much.
Of course I need to worry.
We're talking money here.
I'll sort it out, Ms. Yun.
I've been so busy writing.
I can't do anything, let alone eat.
Do you know how hard that is?
I know how hard it must be.
-Can I take a break this month?
-What?
But you already took a break last month.
Why do those damn trolls keep
driving me crazy over every little thing?
It's so frustrating!
Don't mind those hateful comments.
SE-JUNE
The person you are calling is unavailable.
Please leave a message.
SE-JUNE
12 MISSED CALLS
Crap!
Oh no.
Come on!
That's how my romance became a past
that would never come back.
Forget clocking out on time.
You'll be lucky to catch the last train.
Didn't you get a bald spot here before
from stressing about Yun Song?
Let's see if it's grown back.
-She did?
-I think it was around here.
-Was it this side?
-It's gonna fall out again anyway.
Hey, guys. Cut it out.
You had something to tell me, Hye-bin?
Oh, yeah…
Will you be attending
the meeting with the author?
That hurts!
My goodness, I'm sorry! I didn't mean to.
Miss, are you okay?
-She's so pretty!
-Yes. You've gotten prettier.
What a glow-up.
Have you lost weight?
What the heck?
Hey, I told you not to return that outfit.
-I didn't return it.
-Then why didn't you wear it?
No reason. I didn't feel like it.
There's no point in looking good today.
-But--
-Seo Mi-rae!
Hey, you only answer Ji-yeon's calls!
Didn't think I'd see you.
I heard you were busy.
It's so nice to get together.
How have you been?
I've got so much to tell you.
Let's talk over drinks later.
Let's go.
Please welcome the groom!
The cliché of awkwardly running into
your ex at a mutual friend's wedding
never happened, after all.
Today's true star will be entering now.
Please welcome the bride.
Da-yeong!
-Congratulations!
-Beautiful.
Congratulations!
Congrats. Be happy!
You look great together!
You look like a goddess!
She was stunning, wasn't she?
-Yeah.
-She really was.
We'll be having drinks later.
You're coming, right?
Definitely. I'll make sure
to bring Mi-rae along.
-Good.
-Be right back.
You'd better come this time.
-Got it.
-You always skip out.
You-mi!
You-mi! Congratulations!
-Is that You-mi?
-Where?
Hey, you!
-Did you hear? She's getting married.
-Really?
-I am.
-No way!
-Is Se-june still in America?
-Yes. He's coming next week.
Hey, when you get married…
A girlfriend who would be the envy of all,
and a sparkling diamond ring on her hand.
He managed to show off what he had
without even showing his face once.
-Congrats!
-I'm happy for you.
You're even prettier.
Is it the engagement glow?
Stop it! You're all pretty.
I'd love to carry my kid like that
after I get married.
You wanna get married?
-I'm sure I will someday.
-To whom?
Whatever. I'm sure
you'll find someone someday.
Hey, what's up with you?
What do you mean?
Why are you talking like that?
Every time we bring up the future,
you always start with "I."
Have you ever said "we" first?
We haven't met in a while.
Looking forward to catching up tomorrow.
Are you freaking kidding me?
I'd forgotten about this.
Seriously, why are you all
doing this to me?
THE MAN TO KNOW
EPISODE 107
HOW DARE YOU…
MAKE A MOVE ON MY FAMILY?!
SQUEEZE
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU DISAPPOINT ME, AUNT
So she's gone even more off the rails
since the last time.
Naemo's most popular webtoon
for three years running,
Yun Song's The Man to Know.
A chaebol romance featuring Choi Si-woo,
the third-generation heir of SY Group.
Of course, he's just as disrespectful
as he is handsome,
with the classic and clichéd selling point
of only being soft with the female lead.
It's a romance-action hodgepodge mixed
with all the intrigue of a chaebol family.
The main romance plot is so clichéd
that Hans Christian Andersen would rise
from the grave and sue her for plagiarism.
While in Cebu
for a resort construction project,
Choi Si-woo goes surfing one morning,
is swept away by the waves,
only to be rescued by Eun Na-ra,
the female protagonist on vacation,
and falls in love with her.
THE MAN TO KNOW
YS is such a has-been.
Waste of money.
Treat your folks to dinner instead.
How is this number one?
Naemo fell off. Fire YS already.
Manage your authors better.
Great fix for low BP.
It got me all worked up.
YS should quit Instagram first.
I feel sorry for her fans.
YUN SONG
Yun Song debates with readers again.
Yun Song faces backlash
after posting targeted message.
Fans angered by popular author
Yun Song's unprofessional hiatus.
Here for snacks?
No, I just…
That annoying jerk.
That selfish jerk.
That self-centered jerk.
-Ms. Seo.
-Yes?
How long are you gonna be on that?
Just five more minutes.
Sure.
Lovely weather today.
Ms. Seo, about the handover
of Ms. Yun's work…
Oh, right. Who's handing over to me?
From Mr. Park.
Sorry?
Mr. Park?
What was this doing here?
Did you miss it because it's so small?
I'm here for the handover.
Oh, the handover.
Five minutes.
Conference room.
-Five minutes?
-Yes.
All right.
It has the lowest ratings,
but the sales are still steady.
We have three ad deals remaining.
Let's move one to a branded webtoon
by next month.
The CTR is pretty good,
so we can push that point
when contacting future clients.
Bet you feel great after dumping
this ticking time bomb on me.
Could you take a look
at the file I'm sending you?
Man, look how neat his nails are.
Not a single cuticle in sight.
-Ms. Seo.
-Yes?
Please accept it.
Okay.
This is the feedback my team has shared
with Mr. Cho on The Man to Know so far.
-Take a look if you need to.
-Okay.
And…
PARK KYEONG-NAM SENT A MESSAGE
SAUNA COUPON
What's this?
Mr. Cho said you'd need it.
I don't need it.
I'll be sleeping at home, no matter what.
Okay. Sure.
Anyway, that's all for the handover.
Any questions?
No.
Right, then.
Time for lunch.
Is it already?
Today's your first meeting with Yun.
Let's go. I'll treat you to unadon.
You're the best.
-Let's go.
-Let's go!
Eating ginger makes me nauseous
for some reason.
She just doesn't get it.
Ginger is what makes unadon so great.
You got that right!
I'm starving. We could've ordered in.
Seo Mi-rae!
Ms. Yun! You're here early.
We can eat together before our meeting.
I'm right on time, aren't I?
You guys go on ahead!
Come on. I'm hungry!
-Bye, Mi-rae.
-I'm hungry.
Enjoy your meal, Ms. Yun.
It's so good.
-Worried about working with me?
-Sorry? Not at all.
If Cho hadn't gotten sick,
we would have kept going.
It's such a shame he's so frail.
It was our first reunion in a while,
and she was still as clueless as ever.
It's been three years. Let's crush it.
Sure. I look forward to working with you.
If it weren't for you,
things wouldn't have worked out for me.
You would've managed fine without me.
That's true.
The female lead being constantly tormented
by her in-laws' disapproval,
only to have Choi Si-woo swoop in,
acting all cool, to save her…
The readers are getting
a little tired of that.
Recently, the aunt-in-law
has been a bit too…
Good grief.
You want the super-rich, swoony male lead
to drop the cool act?
That wasn't the point.
The constant disapproval of the family--
Why do the readers complain
but keep reading anyway?
Because they just expect me to give them
something to complain about.
Goodness, this is the kind of thing
I was worried about.
Sorry?
What do you mean?
I know you're smart and all,
but we both know we don't really vibe.
Then you could've told the director
you didn't want to work with me.
I mean, it won't be an issue
as long as we figure things out as we go.
Just like old times.
Please give me the final files!
Ms. Yun!
I'm sorry to bother you.
A guest would like to see you, Ms. Yun.
-Is that so? Sure.
-All right.
-Please come in.
-Hello.
-Hi. How have you been?
It's been a while.
This is Producer Seo Mi-rae,
who will be in charge of Ms. Yun.
Right.
-Hello.
My name is Min Jun-young.
-I'm Seo Mi-rae. Great to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
-Have a seat.
-Thanks.
So, there's this new dating simulation
that DU just launched,
and Choi Si-woo was used in it.
Ms. Yun's already met him
a few times over the contract.
If it's a dating simulation,
is it like a game?
It's more like a dating app than a game,
and more realistic.
So what is it called?
Boyfriend on Demand.
See that? I told you she was like this.
She always cringes
at the slightest sign of cheesiness.
-No, that's not it. I--
-That's okay.
Everyone reacts the same way you do.
I wanted to meet you today, Ms. Yun,
because our planning team loved
your character so much.
They suggested using the male leads
from your other works as well.
-The male leads from my other works?
-Yes.
That's understandable,
given Choi Si-woo's popularity,
but the others aren't all that cool.
You could call them Si-woo knockoffs.
-Well, they are!
-Isn't she just hilarious?
What she means is…
Some of us did say other characters
might not have as much impact as Si-woo,
so I just wanted to hear your thoughts
before making a formal proposal.
In that case--
Then how about using the second male lead?
-Yes, that's--
-Second male lead?
Yes, so…
In her works, the lead and the second lead
always have such different charms,
so the female lead wavers
until the very end.
Yes.
Take Hong-ju from Bloodsucking Boyfriend.
He was so popular that you ended up
having to kill him off.
That's right.
Did the Team Leader Say That?
has a final episode rating of four.
Fans of the second lead review-bombed it.
Right.
You could use the second male lead
in your app with this tagline.
"It's your turn to make him the lead."
That would create quite a buzz,
don't you think?
Wow, I love it!
Man, that's just, wow…
"Make him the lead!"
Nice, huh?
Doors opening.
Ms. Yun, please answer your calls
going forward.
Bye now.
-Answer them, please!
-Yeah.
Hi.
Did you have a good talk
with the director?
I did, yes.
Ms. Seo?
Do you have time for a quick chat?
Excuse me?
A product reviewer?
Yes. It's nothing serious, really.
You just need to give us a review
after using the app for a month
with the equipment provided.
I'm not exactly sure
what I should be reviewing.
It's a dating app,
so you'll be reviewing your dates.
Your thoughts on your dates
and what you liked or disliked about them.
So is it more like role-playing
than an actual date?
Very realistic role-playing.
You're not into cheesy stuff,
is that right?
Yes.
Our goal is to captivate
people like you as well.
That, and you seem consumer-savvy.
Our app is in beta service,
so we're in dire need of quality feedback.
You will be compensated,
so think it over and get back to us.
I'd get paid for this?
Of course.
You'd be putting in your valuable time.
"Boyfriend on Demand."
"Sync your phone with the device."
Transmitting user information
to the device.
"Place the ring on your head
and assume a comfortable position."
"The ring will automatically adjust
to the user's head"?
"You are invited to the world of wonders."
Personalization process complete.
Place the ring on your head
and assume a comfortable position.
Press the red button on the device.
When you press the button, the ring
will light up and begin connecting.
What's going on?
It's cold!
I can…
I can breathe.
What the…
Wait a second.
THE MAN TO KNOW
This is…
This is Choi Si-woo.
Congratulations, Ms. Seo Mi-rae,
on meeting your first date!
Are you okay?
Subtitle translation by: Daham Yoon