[This drama is a work of fiction.]
[Any resemblance to real persons,
places, or events is coincidental.]
[Scenes with child actors and animals
were filmed safely]
[under professional supervision.]
We should bury the recording.
Yeah.
We're killing this project here.
Pull everything tied to
Park Jae Sang and Oh Kwang Jae.
And shelve the recording release.
Understood.
With the chairman involved,
it's too risky to keep pushing.
I'll reach out to Park Jae Sang
and put the project on hold.
And
bring me a Plan B.
Got it.
The number you have dialed is not available.
Why isn't he picking up?
Leech.
What the...
[Episode 6]
Hey!
I said I'm not doing it.
I'm through with all the expose crap.
I told you, it's over!
There's really no copy left?
Park Jae Sang's the one who has it.
How many times must I repeat myself?
It's not with me!
Looks like there's nothing here.
I ran the IP and combed every server.
Nothing's surviving on the web either.
What are you doing?
What?
I said, what are you doing?
That's gasoline?
Are you insane? What the fuck is this?
Look, I'll...
I'll convince Director Lee myself, okay?
Enough of this.
Even if you all pull the broadcast,
Park Jae Sang isn't backing down.
Where are you hiding Park Jae Sang?
Just one hour, please.
Yes, understood.
Jae Sang.
I'm so sorry.
What would it take
for you to let this go?
You want forgiveness?
I want to see you destroyed, too.
To be stabbed in the back the same way...
and to experience the same pain I went through.
I've been suffering, too.
I was desperate and blurted it out.
I never thought it would...
actually happen.
Please forgive me.
So, Jae Sang...
The recording...
can't you just bury it?
This was about the recording?
My whole life fell apart,
and all you care about is your image?
Then deal with it.
That's exactly what I'm after.
Talking to you is pointless now.
I'm done trying.
What?
I'm sick of pretending around you.
So you're pushing this to the end?
Alright. Bring it on.
Hey.
Please don't say
you believed we had a future?
You pictured us walking down the aisle?
What a complete idiot.
Just die. Just die!
That's Chu Sang Ah, right?
He's going to kill her at this rate.
What's he doing?
Somebody needs to call the police.
He's lost his mind.
- Isn't he killing her?
- Somebody has to step in.
- She'll be dead if this keeps up!
- Please, someone call for help!
Somebody help!
Hey, Park Jae Sang!
Let go of her! I said let go!
Don't come closer!
Is that a knife he's got?
What's going on?
- Someone call the cops.
- Out of my way!
Get out of the way!
Shouldn't somebody grab him?
You alright?
Put the cameras down!
I told you, quit recording!
Just record it.
Oh no.
Is he just trying to scare her?
What if she ends up dead?
What's going on?
- We should report this.
- Who is that?
[Sang Ah]
The call could not be connected
and was forwarded to voicemail.
Record your message after the beep.
Hang up when you're finished.
You met with Choi Ji Ho, right?
Find anything else?
Choi Ji Ho doesn't have any copies.
The recording leak's been called off.
All that's left is Park Jae Sang.
Where the hell is he?
We've narrowed it to the motel area.
I'll send the pinpoint once it's locked.
Sang Ah's been unreachable since yesterday.
Do you know anything?
I'll look into it.
Last night...
Sang Ah was with you, wasn't she?
You're supposed to observe and report.
But last night, you went too far.
Why pull something like that now?
You're the one who pushed me to this.
Were you listening in on us last night?
I sent you after Park Jae Sang,
not to spy on me!
What's got you this shaken up?
I mean, of course.
You let your precious wife
carry a murder on her back. And now it's out.
- Scared, right?
- I warned you, know your place.
You've been using Sang Ah all along.
Hey.
You caught a bit of our talk,
and now you're flapping your lips.
My patience for taking you in
and looking after you has its limits.
Isn't it me you really need right now?
Want me to kill him?
Park Jae Sang.
We're done here.
Stay away from me and Sang Ah for good.
Piece of shit.
Made up your mind, Chairman?
I'm going to stoke the fire.
Executive Director Kwon?
Quick on the uptake, as usual.
Mr. Bang.
Thank you.
For what?
Just thank you.
Thank you.
What exactly did you pull
for the old man to collapse
right after you walked out?
The way the will reads now,
WR lands in my hands on its own.
Tough break, huh?
I don't need you anymore.
So you're telling me,
with the will as it stands,
I might come out on the losing end?
[Leaking WR Group info means]
According to the Chairman's revisions,
should WR's secrets get out
and tarnish the Group,
[losing all rights and shares, instantly]
every right and share of that heir
will be stripped away.
You'd better kill that story immediately.
And that's precisely
why I'll be adding gasoline to your fire.
What the hell is he doing?
Because that's become...
my way of protecting my shares.
Mr. Kwon.
If that's how you play it, I'll go all in.
If something tarnishes Chairman Kwon's name,
you're fine with that?
My father beat me
every day until I turned twenty.
The Group's honor, who cares.
I'll make up scandals just to expose them.
So...
I'll set the whole thing ablaze.
Just watch.
You think the card I'm holding
just brings down the Chairman alone?
What card?
The Oh Kwang Jae file.
Press,
cabinet members, moguls, all tied in.
If that file comes out, can you survive it?
The moment my wife speaks publicly,
my name will be cleared.
The grounds are more than sufficient.
Get me that nomination as promised.
But...
what's the point of surviving on your own?
When Chu Sang Ah falls, you fall with her.
You're both tied to the same rope, right?
Looks like a Doberman needs putting down.
The Changjo Party has revealed
it's weighing the withdrawal
of Bang Tae Seop's bid.
[Changjo Party Holds Urgent Nomination Review]
We're reviewing his nomination status.
As moral standards are the priority,
we'll establish the facts
and deliver our stance shortly.
[Prosecutors Mull Calling In Bang Tae Seop]
Looks like the prosecution's reopening
the Oh Kwang Jae case.
[Citizens Urge Revival of Oh Kwang Jae Case]
The ruling should come in a few days,
[Chu Sang Ah, Murderer]
and whether Park Jae Sang's recording
[Hold Bang Tae Seop Accountable for His Lies]
is released will be the key element.
[Look Into All Parties Connected!]
We have breaking news.
[25,345 Demand the Case Be Reopened]
Chu Sang Ah was assaulted by Park Jae Sang
[Conduct a Thorough Probe for the Truth]
in Deokyang-dong earlier today,
[Prosecution Must Revisit This Case Now]
and the clip is circulating on the web.
[Citizen Footage, Park Jae Sang's Rampage]
Park is seen strangling Sang Ah on video
[Ex-Convict Park Menaces Sang Ah and Escapes]
and waving a blade at her manager.
The violent attack was captured on film.
[Sang Ah's Life Not in Danger, Sources Say]
Authorities are reviewing CCTV footage
[Authorities Hunt Park Jae Sang Using CCTV]
to locate the suspect on the run.
[Murderer: Chu Sang Ah]
Once the footage came out, some sympathy
[Quit the show. We see through the setup]
for Chu Sang Ah did surface,
[She deserved it. Should've gone harder]
but the general online reaction was brutal.
[Drop dead, Sang Ah! Maybe then we'll forgive]
The studios and sponsors who hired her
are gearing up for massive penalty suits.
[The Truth Behind the Oh Kwang Jae Murder]
I can't pull back from this any longer.
This evening at 8:30,
I'm going to expose
Sang Ah's actual voice
recorded seven years ago,
to everyone linked to Oh Kwang Jae's death.
I'm laying it all bare.
[Sang Ah]
[Live broadcast launches at 20:30]
Where are you?
You saw that?
I'll take care of it,
so...
No...
This is our punishment right now.
You told me this when you proposed.
That we're the same kind of people,
that we can't do without each other.
Right.
We really are the same kind.
A pair of hypocrites.
- Sang Ah, listen...
- Vowing to avenge Han Ji Soo,
I'm a fraud for exploiting Park Jae Sang,
and you, who covered up that case
to shield me, you're a fraud, too.
Alright.
If this is the price we're paying,
let me fight it off.
Between us and Park Jae Sang,
either we or he
has to die before this is over.
So I'll shut him down, even if he has to die.
I'll handle him on my end,
you take care of things on your side.
I'll call you back.
Where are you?
[Park Jae Sang]
Didn't I say to scrap the release?
Those are the client's instructions!
You'll get the agreed sum. Now where are you?
[Live broadcast launches at 20:30]
Money's meaningless to me now.
Why do you all just exploit me
and throw me out?
There's no turning back now.
I'm putting everything out. We all burn.
Darn it.
[Live broadcast launches at 20:30]
[The Truth Behind the Oh Kwang Jae Murder]
Got a lock on Park Jae Sang?
[Live broadcast launches at 20:30]
Narrowed it down to two motels.
I'll go to that area and wait,
let me know once you pin it down.
Sure.
Room 1708. She left the key.
- And the name?
- Han Ji Ah.
Thank you.
[To Jeong Won]
- What's going on?
- Oh no.
Jeong Won.
If you're the one reading this,
I owe you an apology first.
Everyone has turned away from me,
and I have no place left to turn.
Maybe by doing this,
the world might forgive me
and finally trust me.
Thank you for having faith in me,
and for giving me comfort.
Goodbye.
[Location found. 89-1 Chungnyang-ri,
Doryang-gu, Seoam. Rm 304]
Seriously.
It's already 8. What's the plan?
Are you able to block Park Jae Sang?
Skip the excuses.
Use every means you have
to track him down and stop him now!
Understood?
Yes.
I've sent a team out to sweep the area.
We'll track him down before it airs.
Darn it.
[Park Jae Sang]
[Live broadcast launches at 20:30]
[89-1 Chungnyang-ri, Doryang-gu, Seoam. Rm 304]
- You're here? Check it, quick.
- Yes.
[Live broadcast launches at 20:30]
[Park Jae Sang]
[The Truth Behind the Oh Kwang Jae Murder]
[Live Chat]
- Bang Tae Seop!
- Mr. Bang!
- Ms. Chu...
- A quick word, please!
Mr. Bang, what happened?
Just one statement, please!
Bang Tae Seop!
- A comment, please!
- About Chu Sang Ah...
- Mr. Bang!
- Wait.
Chu Sang Ah...
Was a patient named Chu Sang Ah checked in?
Hold on, please.
Emergency patient, clear the way!
Please, move aside!
Move!
Sang Ah!
This is breaking news.
Chu Sang Ah's former bodyguard, Park Jae Sang,
has been found dead.
Given no apparent criminal evidence,
authorities are leaning
toward self-inflicted harm.
Park was released in February after serving
his term for the Oh Kwang Jae murder.
[Convicted Killer Park Jae Sang Dead at Motel]
Since his release, via a popular MeTuber,
he'd been insisting on his innocence.
Right, sir.
I've been sitting here for hours now,
and there's no word on her status.
Nothing new since.
From the mood on Chu Sang Ah's side,
it doesn't look like she's faking.
Right.
That's not it.
Every doctor and nurse here is on lockdown.
So...
I wrote up a death piece
and a survival piece,
and I'm ready to run whichever applies.
Aren't you Bang Tae Seop?
Prep the statement right away.
And you keep the comments clean.
[Operating Room]
Understood?
She lost quite a bit of blood,
but we've finished the initial treatment.
She should be out of danger.
Is she awake yet?
She hasn't woken up yet,
so we'll have to keep a close watch.
Doctor,
in that case,
how soon before she returns to normal life?
We should move him to the OR right now.
Check his vitals.
They keep dropping.
Tae Seop, what do we do?
What if Dad doesn't pull through?
When he decided to take the company to court,
I should've stopped him
from going through with it.
That piece of shit prosecutor
put the whole thing on Dad.
Tae Seop.
What's wrong with you?
Hey.
Pull yourself together.
You alright?
No wonder you're losing it.
What a cursed life you've got...
Dad wasn't enough, now it's your wife.
Think back to then.
Meeting a celebrity, of all places,
at a prosecutor's office.
I had a bad feeling from the start.
When you told me about the wedding,
the fortune teller I visited warned me,
you two are destined to be each other's ruin.
I should've dragged you out of it then.
Enough.
Hold on.
What on earth made her do it?
She must've felt wronged.
But then what about you?
Gosh.
It was eating me up so much
I visited that fortune teller recently.
I told you not to blow the allowance
I give you on fortune tellers.
No,
this time it's different.
Just hear me out.
Your destiny takes three big hits
because of your wife.
The first one's behind you,
with two more on the way.
I think this right here is one of them.
If divorce isn't on the table,
picture yourself caught in a tidal wave.
Don't try to brace yourself.
Bend with it, or you'll snap.
- Got it?
- Yeah, I got it.
Look at you, what a mess.
What are you doing?
Hold on, stay still. Get over here.
You're at a pivotal moment right now.
Looking too ragged isn't going to cut it,
but with your wife in this condition,
appearing too put-together won't do either.
Leave it all up to me.
Oh, you poor thing.
Who did this to you?
Oh, Tae Seop.
Put these on. I packed fresh ones for you.
Thanks.
Look after Sang Ah,
and don't forget about yourself either.
I'll get going now.
As long as the Chairman holds on
till the election,
we have a chance to raise the shares.
As I've said before,
if we secure the next frontrunner early,
with an early reform of the insurance law,
the WR Life shares will flow to you...
No matter what,
keep him alive.
I'll try everything I can, but...
I'm not asking you to keep him alive forever!
The presidential race,
actually, after the election,
just keep him alive another month or two.
You'll receive anything you request,
and I'll meet every single demand.
Answer me.
Right, of course.
Keeping him here, it'll leak everywhere.
First thing tomorrow,
we'll transfer him to my home discreetly.
You two will be making
your rounds there from now on. Got it?
Understood.
[VIP Room]
[Authorized Personnel Only]
Chu Sang Ah.
Nice show you put on.
Nice shot.
["Pre-Live Tragedy,
A Truth Lost in the Shadows"]
[Former Guard Park Found Dead Post-Expose...
Police, "Exploring Every Angle"]
[Chu Sang Ah Left Comatose, Sending Shockwaves]
[Eyes are on the mystery
of Park Jae Sang's death]
[Something's off about Park Jae Sang's suicide.
He was literally on a live stream]
[Isn't Chu Sang Ah
kind of innocent in all this?]
[So why did Park Jae Sang end up dead, then?]
Look, now that things are like this,
try to get a little food down.
Should I get you chicken feet or something?
Hey.
What?
The whole thing was an act, right?
Being discovered at just that timing,
ending up here
where Director Jang is easy to sway.
Was a single thing here by chance?
How could you do this kind of thing?
Without consulting me even once!
So...
Is that how you chose to deal with it?
You can't seriously think
that I'm the one who killed him?
No...
I trust that it wasn't you.
I need to believe that.
Damn it.
Do you know how scared I was
that something would happen to you?
I was terrified too.
Have any idea how alone I felt
before I made this kind of decision?
Whatever methods we used,
you did your part, I did mine,
and we stopped ourselves
from falling off the cliff.
That's all that matters.
I'm sorry.
I was in a state of shock,
and I saw no other escape.
Right...
Maybe I'm the person who drove you to this.
I tried my hardest to keep you safe,
but perhaps my approach was misguided.
No.
We simply took different paths.
You did nothing wrong.
I'm sorry.
Kwon Se Myeong's condition looks serious.
Once the funeral takes place,
the structure hands WR to Kwon Jong Uk,
and Director Lee will find a way
to wage all-out battle against Kwon Jong Uk.
Whether we become
collateral in this conflict once more
is something we'll have to watch.
You still have to reclaim your nomination,
and I have to get back on track.
Let's start by flipping public opinion.
For the second segment of Newsroom,
a high-profile figure from the Doyak Party,
Assemblyman Son Guk Won, is with us
as today's special guest in the studio.
- Hello.
- Yes, hello.
I'm a Doyak Party assemblyman
and presidential candidate, Son Guk Won.
In the New Year's interview, the opposition...
So, the next presidency is Son Guk Won?
[Shaman Moon]
- A 92% likelihood.
- Bringing it up like...
The earthly signs align in a triple bond,
taking hold of executive authority,
while the three clash formations
[Son Guk Won]
command military strength,
with the people's support,
and the metal feeding water
signifies governance,
which can be read as national authority.
His fate and the nation's destiny
are a perfect match.
You could say the victory is already his.
Okay. I'll be in touch again.
[Choi Ji Ho]
It's me.
Yes, Director.
Didn't you say
we had bait stashed for a diversion?
Right, there are a couple.
Where do you intend to deploy them?
I'm looking to reel in Son Guk Won,
but the mess he's made is just too massive.
Do we have a plan that can match that level?
Since his old scandals were already massive,
to pull this off...
[Practice Room Logs, Unreleased Footage]
we'll need a long-game hot-cold approach.
Plus, if this is election-grade,
it'll require serious funding, right?
Forget about the money.
Prepare a tentpole scenario.
[Breaking,
Bang and Chu Press Conference at 10 AM]
Wait a second.
[Breaking,
Bang and Chu Press Conference at 10 AM]
This couple...
they make for entertaining targets.
Hello.
I'm actress Chu Sang Ah.
To begin,
for Park Jae Sang, who is no longer with us,
I offer my deepest condolences.
Though the Oh Kwang Jae incident
[Chu and Bang Couple, Urgent Press Conference]
left us beyond repair,
at one time, he was
someone I considered family.
Following his release, I did all I could
to restore my bond with Park Jae Sang,
but consumed by rage and vengeance as he was,
there was no getting through to him.
As the situation grew worse,
harm reached my family and my company,
and despite my appeals of innocence,
not a single person trusted my words.
So even if it had to be this way,
I wanted to prove I'm innocent.
All that bad acting every single day,
but that's Oscar-worthy, honestly.
What happened to Park Jae Sang is tragic,
[Chu and Bang Couple, Urgent Press Conference]
but I'm glad the misunderstanding
is cleared at last.
To all who stood
by Bang Tae Seop and me through it all,
I express my gratitude once more.
After this case, we've been through
endless suspicion and scrutiny,
but I vow that we never commissioned a murder
or concealed any wrongdoing.
As a result, Chu Sang Ah endured
devastating harm to her reputation
and crippling financial losses, and I as well
[Live Chat]
was at risk of having
my Changjo Party nomination revoked.
[Always rooting for you from afar, Chu Sang Ah]
[Chu Sang Ah did nothing wrong]
What gullible, pitiful idiots.
Good morning!
Oh, dear Mother.
On the verge of losing it all,
and the Bang couple just
knocked you down again.
Hey!
Don't bring a dog in here!
My Petit here
outranks you by bloodline.
You're constantly getting beaten by those two,
and still you babble about seizing WR.
My nerves are shot right now,
so close your mouth
and get out while I'm being polite.
Hey.
You're nothing but a stray
who latched on to mooch,
while I'm
the sole thoroughbred successor
of this household's bloodline.
I'm not incapable of tearing you apart.
I'm simply holding back.
Aren't you going to get rid of this thing?
Not "this thing." Petit.
Shit.
Even if you end up kicked to the curb,
don't drag our family through the gutter.
Come here. Goodbye, Mother.
That son of a bitch...
Not "son of a bitch." Petit.
Get out. Get out!
We were ruthlessly targeted and pursued.
The people who persecuted us
wielded their influence as a tool
to prey on the weak for their own greed,
manipulated the press,
and even resorted to killing.
Killing? What do you mean by that?
What's he getting at now?
Yet even with all their plotting,
we refused to go over the edge.
We're ready to fight once more.
Citizens,
I ask you to put your faith in us once more,
and stand behind the fight
we're about to carry forward.
I humbly implore you.
I'll put that tentpole plan
together personally.
Glamorous, fierce, and sensational.
Ms. Chu, any serious health concerns?
What's the scale of the liabilities?
What are your next steps from here?
What drove Park Jae Sang
to end his life, in your view?
- Chu Sang Ah!
- A comment, please!
- Ms. Chu!
- A statement, please!
Please, just one comment!
- Did you have Park Jae Sang murdered?
- Ms. Chu.
Ms. Chu!
From the CCTV footage obtained on-site,
we believe Park Jae Sang was killed by someone.
The outside cameras show
clear evidence of a woman entering,
yet the interior CCTV in this building
contains no trace of her.
Somebody wiped the trail clean.
Want me to kill him?
Park Jae Sang.
So?
What is it you're curious about?
You were close with Park Jae Sang,
and you'd been seeing him
up until recently.
Does anyone come to mind?
We have a scheduled appointment,
so let's wrap this up.
Did he not suggest suicide at the cafe?
Are you dismissing the chance of foul play?
Is there anyone you'd point to?
- Just one comment, please.
- Ms. Chu.
Ms. Chu.
The battle's already broken out.
[Candidate No. 2 Bang Tae Seop]
It's not getting any easier.
I must look like a fool to you.
It's not that you need me.
Now you'll die without me.
What I can't possess, I'll shatter.
I'll see this through to the very end.
Put your faith and money in me,
and there'll be no regrets.
Chu Sang Ah.
Can I borrow her for just one night?
After coming this far,
what's left but to break?