Where are you going?
Nowhere in particular.
You know, Kanda-san...
Don't you have plenty of
other people besides me?
Huh?
Those are all just one-night stands.
Haven't you met anyone decent?
Well...
It's hard to say.
So?
What's he like, this guy you mentioned?
Hmm.
He loves soccer,
but he quit for a while.
He said he's starting up again, though.
An athlete, huh?
Sounds nice.
He's got dreams.
Yeah.
He has his worries
and gets depressed sometimes,
but even then, he's just so... dazzling.
He's a really sincere person.
So you're saying you aren't?
You know the answer
to that better than anyone.
Should we...
call it quits?
No.
I'm sorry,
Akira.
"Contrast"
(Episode 3: A Festival Night of Jealousy and Secrets)
Oh, by the way,
I've decided to join the soccer club.
That's great!
Wait, they'll let you join this late?
Yeah, the coach knows I used to play.
That's awesome, right?
Totally. I'll come watch your games.
Well, I mean...
our team is pretty weak.
And I might not even
get to play right away.
Don't worry about it.
I'm sure you'll be on the field in no time.
It's not that easy.
Then let's all go together!
Good idea. Let's do it.
Yeah, let's go.
I'll bring Senkawa-kun along too.
Huh?
Wait, Senkawa?
Who's that?
Kanata's friend.
Isn't Senkawa-kun in Class 1?
That's the honors class.
What? You have friends in the smart class?
Yeah... something like that.
Impressive.
Alright, everyone, back to your seats.
Oh, morning, Teach.
You say "Good morning."
Morning...
Honestly, if you can't even give a
proper greeting when you're older...
(Akira: You're either
at cram school or home, right?)
(Kanata: So you're
home today?)(Akira: Yeah.)
(Want to go there next time?)
Oh, for crying out loud.
What is this?
What are you doing?
Making yakisoba.
The seniors are running
a stall at the festival.
This is a trial run.
Oh! The one where everyone
volunteers every year?
That's the one.
Want some?
Don't mind if I do.
Looks delicious.
I heard the news.
You're going back to soccer?
Yeah.
Pretty much.
Oh...
What's with the "oh"?
Here.
Thanks.
Time to eat.
It's good!
Really good.
Well,
I guess I can talk soccer
with my big brother again.
Huh?
Man, what a relief.
I was actually pretty worried.
Don't go saying you're
quitting soccer anymore.
Got it?
I know, I know.
I won't say it again.
Good.
I'm gonna eat too.
Let's dig in.
No, you're seriously a genius.
- For real?
- For real.
- I like you.
- Whoa, a confession!
Keep it down!
Huh?
Nakano-san?
What are you doing?
Thank you.
Oh, but... I'm sorry.
Is it really a no?
These...
I made them for you, Kanata.
Please take them.
Thank you.
Here he comes! Hide!
Is she gone?
Yeah, she's gone.
Hey, wait.
Who's this?
Oh.
This is Senkawa-kun.
The friend of Kanata's I mentioned.
The smart one?
This is Jun.
He went to middle school
with Kanata and me.
Oh.
Um...
What's going on with Kanata?
Oh, he just got confessed to.
Oh?
Kanata is
actually pretty popular.
It's definitely his looks.
But he won't date anyone, will he?
Probably not.
Hey, Senkawa-kun, tell him he's
gonna get cursed if he keeps this up.
Okay...
Man, that was close.
Mizuki, you're such a bad liar.
What? Me?
You're so obvious.
So that's how it is.
Mizuki will probably ask
you to come watch the game.
Yeah.
I'll be there.
But I don't think I'll
be playing right away.
Everyone's getting ahead of themselves.
If I just sit on the bench the whole time,
it's gonna be so embarrassing.
You'll be fine.
Good luck.
Thanks.
Oh, Akira.
Do you like sweets?
They're okay.
I got some cookies.
They're really good.
These...
Can I have one?
Hmm? Sure.
I have plenty.
See?
I heard you're quite popular.
Huh?
What, did you hear something again?
Not exactly "heard"...
Well, I guess.
It was Mizuki.
And Jun.
What?
Wait, why?
When did you talk to Jun?
I just happened to see Nakano-san
and said hi.
Jun was with her.
Whatever, it doesn't matter.
A confession...
I heard you turn everyone down.
I guess so.
Yeah.
Why?
I mean, you've probably
got a lot of reasons.
Yeah.
Even if I tried dating them,
I wouldn't feel the same way.
I guess I just find it
all a bit of a hassle.
I see.
So
It's easier to be with
someone I can just relax with.
I've dated people like that before,
but I think I'm done with that for now.
I'm sorry,
Akira.
Come to think of it,
we've never met up outside of school.
Oh?
No, I mean...
Once practice starts, I
won't have much free time.
Since we'll be practicing every day.
Oh.
Then, want to go somewhere?
Oh, really?
Yeah.
I have extra classes starting soon,
so it'll be hard for me to get away too.
If you're free, I'd love to go.
Awesome!
Of course I'm free. Let's do it.
I've been dying to go somewhere.
You're overreacting.
Going out and all...
But wait, is it really okay?
What?
You know...
Finals.
If our grades are too low,
we have to take those
makeup classes, right?
If you're joining the soccer club,
you can't afford to fail.
Crap.
Oh... right.
I
Completely
forgot about that.
Ugh...
What am I gonna do?
Seriously, what do I do?
Ugh, I can't do this.
Nothing is sinking in.
Kanata.
You're getting distracted again.
But there's so much to cover!
And honestly,
when am I ever gonna
use these math formulas?
Once I'm out in the real world,
as long as I don't look like
an idiot, that's enough, right?
Don't start with that.
Do you want to join the soccer club or not?
No, I do.
Of course I do.
Then focus.
You use factoring here.
X cubed is negative 64, so...
Keep the left side as it is.
Then, 64 on the right is...
4 cubed.
So the answer is...
X equals one-fourth.
Get it?
Uh, can you say that again?
Here.
Huh?
Is this for me?
Yeah.
You were working hard.
Thanks.
You're a lifesaver, Akira.
I'm glad you're smart.
It's not that big a deal.
It's not like I'm top of the class.
It's plenty for me.
Spoken like a true honors student.
You seem like the type
who's good at "indoor" stuff.
That doesn't sound like a compliment.
Really?
But you know,
having Akira tutor me like this...
I'm probably the only one, right?
Well,
I guess so.
Yeah.
What?
Hmm?
How do I put it?
It gives me a bit of a superiority complex.
You look so quiet on the outside,
but you listen to such hardcore music.
I like knowing things about
you that no one else does.
What's that supposed to mean?
Just that you're an interesting guy.
Oh.
(Community Festival)
A festival?
Want to go?
Eh.
Not really.
Aw, why not?
Why? Well...
No particular reason.
I'm asking because it's you, Akira.
Hey, Akira.
Let's go to the festival together.
But...
Aren't you going with your school friends?
Yeah.
But I think it'd be more fun with you.
Let's all go together.
And then
the two of us can sneak away.
But...
You'll probably just end up disappointed.
Huh?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Never mind...
Stop overthinking it and let's go.
Come on.
(Enjoy Autumn to the Fullest)
(Community Festival)
Whoa, this is huge.
Yeah.
Should we get some food first?
I think my brother's team has a stall.
Okay.
Let's go.
Whoa...
Wait, look at the dog!
Hey there.
So cute.
What's with this weird unicorn?
They have soccer games too.
Oh! A shooting gallery! Want to play?
Hmm? Accessories?
Yeah.
This is cool.
A bracelet?
A soccer player I like wore
one like this on social media.
I see...
I'm getting hungry. Let's go.
Thanks for your business!
Oh, you're actually working.
Hey, Kanata.
Oh, this is my brother, Yuito.
I'm Akira.
Nice to meet you.
- Can we get some yakisoba?
- Sure, you want some?
Two, please.
That'll be 700 yen.
You're charging me?
- Well, yeah, obviously.
- Cheapskate.
I am not.
- Fine, fine. 700 yen.
- 700 yen.
Let's eat.
Look, red ginger.
Whoa.
Mmm.
- It's good.
- Yeah.
I got the Blue Hawaii one.
Yeah, this is good.
- I got orange.
- Let's eat.
That looks like fun.
- Yeah.
- It's so lively.
I want to try the shooting gallery later.
- Let's do it.
- Can we?
- This is really good.
- Yeah, it is.
Want a bite?
Ah.
Good, right?
Dammit!
- So close!
- This is too hard.
You can do it! One more time.
Here goes.
Oh!
Nice!
You hit it!
Can I have this?
Yes! Not sharing with you!
What?
Just kidding, here.
- Whoa, you're so good!
- That was cool.
Can you teach us?
Oh, so that's how you do it.
Amazing!
Oh, wait.
Wait, isn't this hard?
This weird guy is gonna try now.
Come here.
Come here... ah.
There you go.
Aw, so cute.
Hello.
That was fun.
Thanks for today.
For what?
For bringing me to the festival.
I'm glad I came.
Do you remember?
A while back,
you said talking things
out helps clear your head.
Yeah.
I remember.
I was really happy then.
That you were willing to listen to me.
So if
you're ever worried
or feeling lost, Akira...
you can talk to me too.
Kanata.
Why do you think I'm interesting?
What do you mean?
If you knew
everything about me,
you'd definitely find me boring.
Oh?
Just knowing you is interesting enough.
I've never met anyone like you.
Kanata.
Yeah?
Can I see your hand for a second?
Why?
Just give it here.
Huh?
Now we're matching.
You remind me of the color light blue.
So this is for you.
Wait, but I haven't paid you back yet.
For the tutoring and the snacks...
I've already gotten plenty from you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
But why light blue?
Hmm...
It just suits you.
I see...
Kanata, you'll catch a cold sleeping here.
Kanata?
Hmm?
Just think of it as recharging.
What's that supposed to mean?
(Next Episode)
Were our faces a bit too close back then?
Are you sleepy?
Consider it a reward for working hard.
This time,
why don't you pretend to be asleep too?