(All characters, places,
and organizations are fictional.)
(Children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
Hello.
Do you know me?
You're CEO Mari Yoon.
Is it true
you made a lobbyist offer to Belen?
I'm not recording.
Without your consent,
I won't release it either.
How did you find out?
Did someone at the hotel leak this?
Absolutely not.
The rumor that Lee Woo Seul is your son.
Have you heard it?
That's ridiculous.
This is the first I'm hearing of it.
That's why I'm asking.
Someone gave me a tip.
What are you trying to confirm?
Belen? Lee Woo Seul?
What publication are you from?
Sungwoo Daily.
I'm Geum Ba Ra from the culture desk.
I've also covered Lee Woo Seul.
Did you happen to see the article?
It's not like I even live in Korea.
How is Director Park Sang Jik doing?
He retired last week.
He had some health issues.
What's wrong?
Ms. Yoon?
Are you all right?
You're a reporter from where again?
Geum Ba Ra from Sungwoo Daily.
What were we talking about?
She's old enough to have already left
the orphanage,
so on a hunch,
I searched all the self-reliance centers,
and Kim Jin Ju was the only person
who matched.
A woman?
Yes, and she's exactly 27.
Thank you.
Good work.
Was it because I was thinking
about Momo too much?
But why did CEO Yoon all of a sudden...
How did you score the Mari Yoon interview?
I just got lucky.
(Manager, Self-Reliance Program)
Hello, sir.
- Hey, it's been a while.
- Yes.
You might want to brace yourself for this.
Someone came by asking
for your contact information.
He said you might be
his long-lost daughter.
Who was it?
He said he's lived abroad for a long time,
so you'll have to meet him
to hear the details for yourself.
Should I text you the number?
Yes, please.
He seemed like a nice person.
You can arrange to meet him here
at our office if you want.
Thank you.
- Hi.
Kim Jin Ju!
A student with pierced ears?
What's this?
Sir.
Please give me back my earrings.
When I was left at the orphanage,
they said these were in the blanket
I was wrapped in.
If I wear them around,
I was hoping my parents might see them.
That's quite a fantasy you've got there.
If I make an exception for you,
what about the other students?
I'll let it slide just this once.
Even if they did see them,
do you think they'd say
they were the ones who abandoned you,
and it was nice to see you?
And he calls himself a teacher.
I'm jealous.
I don't have anything like that, you know.
I feel like it'd be better
if I at least had a keepsake like that.
I'd feel less like I was just abandoned.
But was there any love in it?
Spicy rice cakes,
blood sausage, fried food...
And add an egg.
This is Kim Jin Ju.
Is now a good time to talk?
Hello?
Is this Kim Jin Ju?
Yes.
Did Kim Min Hyeok, the manager
at the Self-Reliance Center, brief you?
Yes.
Can we meet today?
I get off work late. Is that all right?
That's fine. I don't mind how late.
How about around nine, then?
Where should we meet?
All right, quiet on set, please.
We're about to roll.
All right, ready.
Action!
- Cut! It's no good.
- Let's do it again.
I need to talk to you for a sec.
Are you here for a story?
- Yes.
- My birth father showed up.
He wants to see me.
I'm meeting him
in the Sera Hotel lounge later.
Can you come with me?
I'm too nervous to go alone.
I have an interview
with Jin Yi Han after this.
How did he contact you?
I guess...
all the kids who suffered
because of Ye Jeong...
will say she got what she deserved.
As her mother, I'm to blame too.
If only I'd known
how she was behaving at school,
I would've met with the kids she hurt,
even belatedly, and apologized.
I should've tried to make it up to them,
but I didn't.
But it's too late for regrets now.
I don't know what to say.
I feel terrible about it too.
It must be karma.
They say you reap what you sow,
and it seems like
the skies are truly watching.
The saying "spare the rod,
spoil the child" is true too.
The reason I wanted to see you...
My father-in-law agrees to this as well...
How would you feel about
becoming part of our family?
We'd make it official, legally.
To put it plainly, we want to adopt you.
That day you came to our house...
left such a deep impression on me.
I just couldn't stop thinking about...
how well you turned out,
even without parents.
If only Ye Jeong were
half as wonderful as you...
I know you won't see us as parents yet,
or yourself as our daughter,
but we'd grow on each other over time.
We'll be your safety net.
That's what we want to do for you.
This isn't just out of a desire
to atone for Ye Jeong's awful behavior.
We're not doing this just
to ease our own conscience.
We've genuinely grown to care for you.
I'm not as good a person
as you think...
I have many shortcomings,
and you might be disappointed.
Could you be worse than Ye Jeong?
I never imagined she was going around
acting like that.
Now that she's cut us off and left,
I'm trying my best not to think about her.
I just hope that, wherever she is,
her spirit is repentant.
So what are you going to do?
Should I even need to ask?
This is what we always wished for.
Well, good for you.
You're getting sophisticated parents
from a loaded family.
I'll still look out for you.
How?
By buying me a nice meal once in a while?
They know you well, so I'm sure
they'll care about you too.
They came to volunteer last week
and acted all friendly with me.
They're planning to keep volunteering,
you know.
And that's supposed to erase
all the pain we suffered?
They're just doing it
to ease their own conscience.
Either way, they're people to look up to,
aren't they?
They should've just raised their kid right
in the first place.
Was Tae Ye Jeong even human?
So this is how...
our friendship ends.
Why would it end?
It won't.
We'll just be living in different places.
But that "different place" is
a completely different...
You're becoming the legitimate daughter
of a lawyer at a top Seoul firm.
You'll get to enjoy everything
that Tae Ye Jeong had,
and our paths in life will diverge.
I'm happy for you.
Congratulations.
This is such a surprise.
It feels like a dream.
I really hope he's my dad.
Are you Kim Young Jun, by any chance?
Yes.
Have you had dinner?
We can get a simple meal here.
Have you eaten?
(Gimpo International Airport)
What about the name Kim Jin Ju?
It's just what I was named,
and what I've always been called.
Was there a necklace with the baby's name,
by any chance?
When I left her with a close friend
in Japan,
I put it around her neck.
I do have an earring.
A single pearl earring.
- A pearl earring?
- They said it was in my baby blanket.
So it's not me?
No, I don't know.
Someone could've swapped the gold necklace
for a pearl earring.
It's a 14-karat gold post with a pearl.
It's not expensive.
Did you ever hear anything
about coming from Japan?
Me?
No.
Anything at all, no matter how small.
There used to be a church
in Myeonghui-dong...
affiliated with the Nua Children’s Home.
It was sold after the pastor passed away.
I was apparently left in their baby box.
I heard most of what I know
from that church.
Some kids were left by parents
who couldn't afford to keep them,
and others were there to escape
abuse from their parents.
Was there anything else in your blanket,
like a note?
Nothing besides the earring...
Blood type?
Type A.
I'm Type A too.
If I were the one left in Japan,
wouldn't I be in an institution
somewhere in Japan?
After looking into it,
someone brought her...
to Korea right away.
We should get tested to be sure.
Okay.
Didn't you check my texts?
The ceiling is leaking.
I called management,
but they said the owner was abroad.
If this is uncomfortable for you,
I'll go to a hotel.
When you decided to become an actor,
how did your parents react?
My father didn't speak to me for a month.
We'll just have to wait and see.
My car isn't being delivered
until next month.
I can take the subway.
See you Monday at ten, then.
Okay.
Drive safely, please.
Will do.
I'll be pretty busy through next week,
so let's aim for the week after next.
But if you'd just reconsider...
Mind if I sit here?
I was with a client too.
I just saw them off.
Was that an interview with Jin Yi Han?
- Yes.
- Why were you so chummy in the interview?
You barely made eye contact with me
during my interview.
But you couldn't take your eyes off
Jin Yi Han.
Am I supposed to look away
while he's answering my questions?
Why the sudden formality?
I suppose I'm just on edge.
Are you on edge, or are you embarrassed?
Because I saw right through you?
This is just like the old you.
- You're joking around again.
- I'm not joking.
If I didn't know better,
I'd have thought he was your boyfriend.
Let's do some serious drinking.
Tomorrow's the weekend.
A bottle of 25-year Dickel, please.
Right away, sir.
Isn't that crazy expensive?
Isn't that heavy?
What if it is?
You have a driver's license, right?
I've decided on your birthday gift.
When's your birthday?
You'll celebrate it at some point,
won't you?
Since when are we close enough
for you to buy me a car?
How could you say that?
You're disappointing me
on so many levels today.
Did you pick this place?
- No.
- Don't you think he has a thing for you?
Of course not. I'm just a reporter.
You're a reporter, but also a woman.
You really run hot and cold sometimes.
That's a hurtful thing to say.
I'm not just talking about right now.
Last time we were here,
you just ditched me and left.
- I had an urgent assignment.
- Don't make excuses.
I'm not that clueless.
Back then...
Put yourself in my shoes.
Let's say I...
(Ba Ra)
The person you are calling is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone.
What if I only had eyes
for Director Shin Ju Shin?
Since he's with Momo,
wouldn't I seem pathetic to you?
Pathetic?
Now you get it.
You're saying you thought
I was pathetic back then.
It's different.
I'll drink it straight.
It is completely different.
How much does it take you to get drunk?
- I don't know.
- Meaning you can hold your liquor?
Or you've just never drunk enough
to find out?
You have to let your guard down
to get drunk,
and I've pretty much never done that.
I've even faked being drunk when I had to.
I'm an expert at
secretly dumping my drinks.
Don't do that tonight.
This is too good to waste.
Hey.
Yes?
I just felt like calling you.
You won't let your guard down,
even with me?
It's not like you're a stranger to me,
and I'm not drinking because it's work.
When...
are you the happiest?
I'm happy...
- right now.
- Besides right now?
- What about you?
- Me too. Right now.
- It's nice.
- But I'm happy.
It's just "nice" for you?
Coming from me,
"nice" is the highest praise.
Shin Ju Shin...
is someone women would fall for.
Do you like Director Shin too?
Yes.
He's got it all.
His father passed away,
but he's the son of the esteemed Chairman.
As the Chairman's son?
How about...
we trade houses?
When I was at your place,
it felt so comfortable and cozy.
I feel like I'd sleep well there.
It's not really my place.
Technically, it's An Hee's.
Having trouble sleeping?
I wouldn't call it insomnia.
After living in such a big villa,
you'd feel cooped up.
Besides, if you're alone,
it'll probably be the same everywhere.
Slow down.
Worried I'll get drunk and come on to you?
I'm worried it'll be hard on you.
A hangover is the least of my worries.
Don't worry. I don't act out when drunk.
I've seen enough of it to be sick of it.
I bet you making a scene
would be something to see.
- To me, no matter what you do...
- Don't make me cuss at you.
Go ahead.
I'll even let you hit me today.
- There's nothing I like here.
- What?
Want me to order you spicy rice cakes?
A long time ago,
I was standing outside a supermarket...
Go on.
I went there to eat snacks
to make myself feel better...
after my teacher hurt me,
but I couldn't buy anything.
I saw all the other kids there
with their moms.
And another was holding
their grandma's hand.
In front of all those happy kids,
I felt so pathetic and small.
We'll stop by a convenience store
on the way.
You should either get a puppy
or find someone.
There is no need to force
myself into a relationship.
It'd help you relax and sleep better.
If I can't sleep, I read or play games.
- There's plenty to do.
- I'd love to get a puppy.
You must be lonely.
Want me to get you one?
I can't just leave it alone all day.
That would be cruel.
Why don't you move in with me?
I'm not kidding. I've got spare rooms.
Aren't you going to get married?
You want people to think
we're living together?
We would be.
We decided we'd live like family.
So let's do it.
Are you worried it'd ruin
my marriage chances?
I'll just have to move out
again eventually.
What woman would be okay with that?
I'd basically be getting kicked out then.
I don't want things to end
like that between us.
Having a puppy is nice
for the companionship,
but I want to be able to say "I love you."
I've never been able to.
Come to think of it, me neither.
Not even to your parents?
Or to James?
You really don't get guys, do you?
To my own brother?
There's so much I don't know.
The hardest part for me
after my mom passed away...
was never telling her I loved her.
Not even once.
Or rather, I didn't.
I never thought she'd
pass away so suddenly.
Then tell her now, in your heart.
Like a prayer, every night
before you go to sleep.
I'm sure she'll feel it.
The prayer from her loving son.
You think she'll feel it?
Yes.
If it were me, I'd stay by my son's side
and protect him, even as a spirit.
Let me pour you a drink.
You're not just anybody.
Say that again...
one more time.
You're not just anybody.
So we have something special, right?
I'm definitely getting drunk tonight.
You want to say "I love you" to a puppy?
Yes. Someone to love and care for.
I wish I had someone like that in my life.
Wouldn't I be a better choice...
than a dog?
I love you.
I didn't mean it.
A dog only has eyes for its owner,
and they never waver.
They're animals that deserve to be loved.
What am I to you?
I'm very clear on what you are to me.
Clear in what way?
That I'm definitely like a little sister,
six years younger?
Something that will never change.
So you don't want to be
a distant benefactor,
but someone closer to me?
That's right.
Anyway, a true bond is
something that doesn't change.
Just like the bond
between a parent and child.
What, are we family now?
In TV shows, when a mom says to her kids,
or a daughter to her mom,
"I love you,"
I've always wondered what that felt like.
I love you.
I'll always love you,
my sweet girl.
Today's the day we confessed
our love to each other.
Remember this.
Long time no see.
My gosh.
He's someone I'm interviewing.
He was a senior in my college club.
- And your name, sir?
- Ha Yong Joong.
I'm Yoo Seon Oh.
We just finished round one,
and this is round two for us.
We haven't met, have we?
Your friends are waiting for you.
Keep in touch.
We're in the same business,
but I never see you.
Sure.
Then.
Wait a second.
Are you that...
WorldNet?
- Yes.
- It's an honor.
(Taewon Daily, Yoo Seon Oh)
I don't have a business card on me...
- How about a picture instead...
- He's being interviewed.
I'm a huge fan of Lost Knights.
You owe me a meal.
- Yes, anytime...
- You promise?
- Okay.
- She's our witness.
- Until then.
- Right.
Let's have a proper drink next time.
- Keep the bottle for us. Check, please.
- Yes, sir.
- Should we go see Ju Shin?
- You should go.
- Together.
- Why would I go?
Ju Shin needs to accept you
as my little sister now.
Would you like that if you were him?
Why wouldn't he?
He said he doesn't tolerate people
crossing boundaries.
Ju Shin said that to you?
He summoned me once.
Get in.
You should call him first.
He might be asleep.
With us, showing up unannounced
gets you an even bigger welcome.
We need to establish your place with us.
That may be true for you, but it's rude.
Trust me on this.
Then at least text him.
Careful. It's slippery, you'll get hurt.
I don't feel like it. You go in alone.
Director Shin.
Since you're getting married,
you'll be getting a lot of press.
I got a suit that would look great on you.
I got it at cost.
I've only seen you in a suit a few times,
but with my professional eye,
I thought there was some room
for improvement.
Jin Ju.
- Hurry up. I have to get to a wedding.
- Yes, sir.
What should I wear?
The press is going to swarm the place.
My boss sent me to give you this.
Take it back. I can't accept this.
My boss is just a very generous person.
This is way too much.
They say even fish can't live
in water that's too pure.
Are you trying...
to lecture me?
I got the suit.
We should grab a meal sometime.
(We're ready for surgery.)
Did your interview run late yesterday?
Are you sure he's your dad?
I hope so.
He's so young.
He said he was 20 when I was born.
We're scheduled for a DNA test on Monday.
- What's he like?
- I bet he was a real looker in his day.
- He's single.
- Sure he's not a con artist?
Nowadays, it's gotten more sophisticated.
What could he possibly con me out of?
It's not like I have anything.
We'll do the test, and if it's negative,
I'll just say goodbye,
and that will be it.
But...
My heart just...
Shoot. I have to go.
If your boss is calling, then this...
No, it's my manager.
He's got a short fuse...
I'll see you later.
(Hospital Director, Shin Ju Shin)
(Kim Jin Ju)
(I got the suit...)
Thank you for the suit.
Are you free for dinner tonight?
Can you do dinner tonight?
Yes, Director Shin.
- Kim Jin Ju?
- Yes.
Did you have lunch?
I just had some snacks
at my friend's place.
You must be hungry, then.
What about you, Director Shin?
You're friends...
with Geum Ba Ra?
Yes.
Are both of you still single?
A boyfriend.
Right.
So what do you do for fun?
I enjoy my work.
Ladies first.
They're Baccarat glasses.
Since you just moved here from abroad,
I figured you might not have anything.
And these are things you'll need.
Clients, gallery owners, and reporters...
will all be dropping by your studio
frequently now.
Have you tried this?
Mr. Kim.
Aren't you lonely?
Isn't everyone a little lonely?
The character for "person..."
shows two people...
leaning on each other.
It's only natural for us
to rely on each other to get by.
That's what my mother used to say.
I...
at least have my beautiful daughter.
Are you offering...
to be my friend?
Just...
a friend?
Someone I can confide in.
How about me?
Have you tried this?
This wine is on a whole other level.
It's from my private collection.
You know, you really play favorites.
- To CEO Ju Yeong Ae...
- Hyun Ran Hee.
What do you think you're doing?
- Mr. Kim.
- I'm...
Kim Young Jun.
Did you forget my name too?
I...
Are you...
No way. Absolutely not.
I was in a car accident in Germany.
A bad one.
- You completely forgot all about me.
- Did you...
get a whole new face?
Let's just say you forgot about me.
But did you also completely forget
about the child you abandoned?
How can you live so carefree
with a clear conscience?
- Who says I abandoned her? She had a dad.
- I don't want to speak with you.
And I hope I never see you again.
Wasn't his name Pyeon Seung Jae?
The one whose father was a doctor.
I heard from him that you went to Japan.
What about our child?
In Germany?
The daughter of the woman
who worked for our family for ages...
moved to Japan, did very well,
and opened a big restaurant.
She was born at our house.
I think I remember hearing that.
I gave her the baby and went to Germany,
but had an accident upon arrival.
My recovery took a long time,
but I was determined to make it through.
After ten years, I tried to contact her,
but I couldn't get to her.
I was worried, but I trusted her
to raise our daughter well.
After everything our family did for her.
A few years ago, I went to look for them,
but her restaurant was gone.
So I asked around
at the neighboring shops.
They told me she had died
just days after I left.
- Why?
- It was her Yakuza boyfriend.
It was a crime of passion, apparently.
And our daughter?
Did something happen to her?
All I could find out was
that she was brought back to Korea.
When? Who brought her back?
There was a Korean lady at the eatery.
She brought her back...
What was her name?
How would I know?
I was only there one night.
All I remember is she had a round face.
There were no records of her?
I had no idea.
I just thought she was in Japan,
living a good life.
So, is that woman raising her, then?
I went to the police,
but there was nothing they could do.
So, grasping at straws, I hired a PI.
He said he couldn't make any promises.
If she's alive, right now she'd be...
You never even registered her birth?
Are you blaming me now?
You just dumped her on me...
when my family was falling apart,
and then disappeared.
She'd always adored me,
so I assumed she'd raise her well.
I had a necklace made
with her name and put it on her.
What name did you use?
Her paternal grandmother's.
The characters for Jin and Ju.
Kim Jin Ju?
Don't tell me it's that Kim Jin Ju.
Hello?
No, it can't be.
Hello.
Yes, I'll check with the gallery.
There's a wrapped painting in my room.
It's next to my desk. Go get it.
Okay.
Is she new?
Momo's new stylist. She started last week.
- Is she trustworthy?
- Yes.
- Momo's new stylist.
- Kim Jin Ju?
Did you run a background check on her?
No.
You need to.
You can't be too careful these days.
She could leak information.
- Is she discreet?
- She's quiet and seems composed.
You know how many people
talk behind your back.
You can't judge a book by its cover.
That sponsored bracelet
that went missing last year...
I'm sure that was an inside job.
What do her parents do?
I don't know that...
It's good, isn't it?
Yes.
Is James treating you well?
- Yes.
- Where did you work before this?
I worked under Park Min Ja.
You don't need to use honorifics
for her when you speak to me.
Does Park Min Ja outrank me?
Yes.
Order a Coke.
Everyone has Coke with pizza, right?
I don't really drink soda.
Good. If you're next to Momo,
constantly sipping on things like that,
how difficult do you think
that makes it for her?
She's dieting like her life depends on it,
even when she has such a big appetite.
So, what do your parents do?
Are they divorced?
I grew up in an orphanage.
Don't worry, CEO Hyun.
I hired her because she's a hard worker,
and you know I'm a better judge
of character than anyone.
I wouldn't pair Momo with just anyone.
We'll have to wait and see.
How she's always walking on eggshells...
She's better than some clumsy fool.
I fear she's a wolf in sheep's clothing.
Mom, you can be a little too
suspicious of people.
(Momo)
Tell Jin Ju to come up before she leaves.
You'll get an upset stomach. Slow down.
Have some milk with it.
Mom, did you just get here?
No.
Then did you make these yourself?
It's not like making a sandwich
takes that long.
Jin Ju, your hair is so lovely and thick.
Let me compare.
My hair just keeps getting
thinner with age...
Mom.
Look at how thick it is.
Why are you so tense?
You're making me uncomfortable.
Nice earrings.
- Drink up.
- I'll take my time.
Are you a lightweight?
I can't drink much...
My driver will take you home.
I couldn't possibly take your ride, sir.
I live nearby.
I'm going to walk to sober up anyway.
Were they a gift?
They said they were in my baby blanket.
Do you resent your parents?
I'm sure they had their reasons.
That's a wise way to think about it.
Did Momo ever give you
a hard time at work?
Not at all.
She was a total nightmare.
Are you managing to save any money?
- I am.
- What for?
To get your own place?
First, I want to take a trip.
Where to?
- Japan.
- For the food? Shopping?
Both.
Lots of expenses will come up.
(DNA Analysis Report)
(DNA Test Report)
Here.
It's a gift certificate.
- No, I couldn't.
- I had it lying around.
I don't need it.
Go on, take it. It was a gift.
But you already treated me
to such a nice dinner.
Thank you.
So is the job a good fit for you?
Yes.
(DNA Test Report)
(Subjects: Kim Young Jun, Kim Jin Ju)
(Paternity Probability: Non-match)
I have plenty of great paintings,
you know.
I mean, we're not talking
about a couple of grand here.
Then just consider it a loan.
Keep it on your wall for a few years.
- Mr. Ha.
- Yes?
Would you rather take this back
and continue...
your relationship with Yong Joong and me?
Or should I take this piece
and we call it quits today?
Give it here. I'll take it back.
Manager Yoon, take this back to my office.
Goodness, I'm no match for you,
Reporter Geum.
It's okay to let your junior win
every once in a while.
What do you mean, junior?
Even your rejections are clever.
- Some drinks, please.
- Yes, sir.
Don't you feel peckish?
Shall we order something?
It's the perfect time for a snack.
What are you in the mood for? My treat.
Especially after the huge spread
you gave me last time.
- My pleasure.
- Me too.
How about some jokbal?
On second thought,
that's not really fitting for you.
- I'm willing to try it.
- Wait, you've never had jokbal?
No.
Let's go with lamb and hummus instead.
- But you can't get that delivered.
- I'm James.
Is Jin Ju out on assignment?
I should've told you
That I loved you
That without you
I can't live on
That I love you
I should have said it
But I hesitated
And my love is gone
I gave you my heart
I gave you my tears
And I gave you my dreams
But you drifted away
My love is far away
What do I have to do, go pray at a temple?
I just can't give her up. I can't.
Everything...
All of it...
(Geum Ba Ra)
Hey, Ba Ra.
Have you been drinking?
A little.
Are the results not a match?
Not a match.
With my luck, who was I kidding?
I really had my hopes up all weekend.
And I was so happy.
- Go to bed.
- You pathetic fool.
Pathetic or not,
I'm still...
your biggest fan.
That venomous witch.
Careful. It's slippery, you'll get hurt.
Where does it hurt? Is it your spine?
Your tailbone?
I don't know.
Ju Shin's here.
Sorry.
Are you shocked?
Shocked about what?
I'm going.
(Available)
- Myeonghui-dong, please.
- You should get off first. It's closer.
Myeonghui-dong, please.
See? Just listen to me from now on.
Is there a convenience store nearby?
They're everywhere.
Don't worry about it.
Sir, the Itanic Palace, please.
No, Myeonghui-dong, please.
Right here, please.
What looks good?
- I'll get fat if I eat this at night.
- You need to gain some.
If you get fired for gaining weight,
you've got me to lean on.
Then I'll get ice cream, too.
It's the first day
since we confessed our love,
but this is a pretty weak celebration.
It's plenty.
So I'm your number one, right?
I'm happy being third.
James, Momo, and then me.
Whatever.
There's a taxi.
Go on.
Sweet dreams.
Isn't that the story? The broke girl
who's all alone snags the prince?
Your bones look fine.
Is it a sprained ligament then?
Should I get some physical therapy?
We need to know how much production costs,
like talent fees, have spiked.
We need concrete figures,
not just what the PR people are saying.
Get some solid quotes...
from production company CEOs
or top executives.
- Understood.
- Kwon Woo Seok.
- Sir?
- Are you giving me an eye test?
You're fast, but why have there been
so many typos recently?
I'm sorry, sir.
I know Director Park Tae Won at Juplus.
Want an introduction?
I would really appreciate that.
- Tuesday. The highlight of my week.
- Because of the black bean noodles?
It's better than most Chinese restaurants.
I heard the Friday special
at the Shinpyeong Daily is beef bone soup.
Hello?
Looks like she's got a boyfriend.
The caller ID says
"Manager Kim, Self-Reliance Center."
He knows the exact date
you were brought to Minjin Church.
How old is he?
He was born in 1968.
His name is Kim Gwang Cheol.
If he's your biological father,
then you were never Geum Ba Ra,
but Kim Ba Ra all along.
I heard from Manager Kim
at the Self-Reliance Center.
My name is Geum Ba Ra.
(Kim Gwang Cheol)
Hello?
(Just got your text.)
Hello.
(From the center...)
(You live in Seoul?)
Yes.
(When are you free?
I'm available right now.)
(Just tell me where, and I'll head over.)
(It won't take me more than an hour.)
Does the ER have an orthopedist?
(Kim Gwang Cheol)
Geum Ba Ra?
December 21, 1999,
at Minjin Church?
Yes.
Are you ready to order?
Coffee.
An Americano?
- Yes.
- Hot?
No, iced.
I'll have the same.
I looked into it,
and on that day, two babies...
Yes...
(Doctor Shin)
When will you stop being so formal?
It's going to become a habit.
It'll become a habit.
Reporter Geum
is going to be devastated. This is awful.
- What are we going to do?
- Are you sure about this?
But you know how people
can have a change of heart.
- Having second thoughts?
- I can have you all fired! Hey, Lee Shim!
- Park Soo!
- You want me to be honest?
You should be,
especially with a good drink like this.
Don't you know what people look for
in a marriage prospect?
I don't. All I know is love.
- Have you actually said "I love you?"
- Of course I've been in love.
If you get adopted,
that lady won't volunteer anymore, right?
She said she'd keep coming.
Think it through so you have no regrets.
- I won't.
- I was away at "school" all this time.
You know what I mean by "school," right?
- Kim Jin Ju.
- Yes?
Ever think about getting on
an operating table?
I don't know who'll be the first
to read this, but...
What do you think of me?
Not as chairman of the orphanage
or the hospital director,
- but just as a man?
- I couldn't possibly...
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)