(All characters, places,
and organizations are fictional.)
(Children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Episode 3)
Who...
am I? What's your name?
A mirror.
It hurts...
What are you doing?
You're beautiful.
I'll make sure you never get old.
- You'd hate to get wrinkles?
- Wrinkles of the heart.
I don't care about wrinkles on your face.
Tell me.
Your name.
What am I supposed to say?
It hurts...
Does it hurt?
You...
want to...
die?
Don't cry.
You succeeded,
and that's all that matters.
You did it.
You worked so hard.
Goodbye.
This is how I live.
I should've brought some fruit.
- I have milk.
- How's Momo?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
I'm sure she's recovering well.
James said he hasn't heard
anything either.
It's weird, isn't it?
- Why don't you text her?
- You think I haven't?
But you can go see her.
What? How can I just show up
when she hasn't asked me to?
- She's at Dr. Shin's getting treated.
- For seven months?
Then just how serious is it?
Was she completely unconscious
at the time of the accident?
No one at her agency is talking.
They just say she's recovering.
Is that why you're here?
If her condition were bad,
Director Shin would've fallen apart.
Ms. Hyun also had a couple of fittings
and seemed perfectly normal.
Are you leaving?
Hey.
Don't you have anything to say to me?
About what?
You don't know?
It's just that...
I was hurt because I felt like
you started pulling away from me.
You were hurt?
Yes.
For dinner, I want French Toast
and a Caprese Salad.
Okay?
Caprese Salad.
French Toast.
Get lost...
Get lost.
Is Director Shin still coming
on Wednesday as planned?
There are barely any wrinkles.
I'll look great as long as I dress well.
There.
No.
Excellent. Even I have to admit, I look...
mid-thirties?
When is your birthday, Mr. Ha?
I asked Manager Yoon,
but she wouldn't tell me.
I don't take cakes from my employees.
That's too much sugar.
But still, for us...
Jin Ju, do you drink?
A little.
Should we do the wine pairing?
It's been a while.
Natasha's airport look was great today.
I learned from the best.
I can't take all the credit.
You have to have a natural gift for it.
Should I call you Mr. Ha?
Or do you prefer "Sir?"
Call me whatever you want.
To be honest,
neither of those really suit you.
Then what, you want to call me honey?
- You're like a celebrity.
- I'll take that as a compliment.
Of course. I mean it.
This is so delicious.
This is so delicious, Yong Joong.
They have good pairings here.
Is that birthday on your ID your real one?
You don't know?
No.
- What about Reporter Geum Ba Ra?
- It's the same for Ba Ra.
We even entered the orphanage
on the same day.
Really?
You'll just have to find
yourselves good husbands.
- You think that's possible?
- Where there's a will, there's a way.
They say the deity grants at least one
of your most earnest wishes.
Then why are you still single?
Because I was too busy
taking care of my young brother.
Mr. Ha Yong Joong.
He's ridiculously handsome.
Though he's not quite as handsome
as Director Shin Ju Shin.
You clearly don't have an eye for men.
Whether it's looks or anything else,
Yong Joong is way better.
To each their own, I guess.
But Mr. Ha didn't get far academically,
did he?
What does a formal education matter?
It's his character that's important.
Besides, Yong Joong is smarter
than people with PhDs.
He reads a lot.
It's so tender.
I'll take you out more often.
Is Reporter Geum Ba Ra seeing anyone?
- I have no idea.
- How could you not know?
You said you're practically sisters.
I get the feeling
she's not interested in marriage.
The ones who say they're not interested
in marriage are always the first to marry.
What's Ba Ra's ideal type?
Are you thinking of
setting her up with someone?
You're not thinking of Mr. Ha, are you?
Of course not.
Get lost.
I can't stand the sight of you.
I said, get lost!
Who the heck are you?
Momo, come on. Let Mommy get some sleep.
You're dead meat.
Coffee, and make it weak.
(Post)
What's this?
She's pretty, right?
I thought she might be your type.
(Post)
Looks like she's had work done.
- Nearly everyone gets work done now.
- But you haven't. You're all natural.
- That's because I'm broke.
- You want some?
No, you're perfect just the way you are.
It's not because
I won't give you the money.
"Perfect..."
Is that the right word for a face?
It's more than just being pretty.
Only in your eyes.
She said she's interested in me?
- Yes.
- A PhD likes a middle school dropout?
A high school dropout, to be exact.
- Just meet her once.
- Do you think we'd be a good match?
Yes.
Personality-wise? Our backgrounds?
- She asked me to set you two up.
- I was just asking.
No, you weren't.
You're going to get married, right?
Yes, of course I am.
She comes from a good family,
and she has a great personality.
Plus, she has that foxy look guys go for.
What kind of look do you have, Ba Ra?
I'm clueless
when it comes to women's looks.
Is gaming all you know about?
Pretty much.
Of all the men I know,
aside from our Advisor,
no one is as savvy as you.
You're filled with mature knowledge.
I'll take that as the highest compliment.
It's true.
So when knowledge matures,
does it become wisdom?
You may be half-joking with me,
but I only ever mean what I say.
I don't joke around with just anyone.
How about the Sky Hotel Lounge?
Forget it.
Is the Sky Hotel Lounge okay?
So, is she ready to get married
as early as next month?
That's up to you.
How many cups of coffee
is that for you today?
Four?
That's enough.
Drink something healthy and nutritious.
At least when you're with me.
If this goes well, how about some Chalet?
Is "Eruchal" the thing these days?
I'll deck you out from head to toe.
Clothes by Chalet, shoes by Rugati,
a bag by Evua.
Or an all-Chalet look?
I don't want you to call me
anything different.
Even when we get older,
can't you just keep calling me
what you always have?
I'll take that over all
the designer gifts.
A long time ago,
the first time we met,
in front of the supermarket.
You mean, "Hey, kiddo?"
You're the only person...
who called me that way,
as far as I can remember.
Yong Joong.
We...
seem to really click.
Am I sexy, too?
Turns out, honesty can be sexy.
And you are being
seriously sexy right now.
(James)
- Hey, James.
- Are you out?
Yeah, at a local café with Ba Ra.
You're on speakerphone.
Hey, Reporter Geum.
- Hello.
- So what did my brother get you?
What did he buy you?
Not even a teddy bear this time.
He just said Korean stuff is better.
- I'll get her a bag tomorrow. I'm broke.
- Make sure you get it.
By the way, Reporter Geum,
have you spoken with Momo recently?
- No.
- Is it possible she hasn't woken up yet?
- Why?
- You didn't hear from Reporter Geum?
Momo supposedly passed out scuba diving,
but now she's completely off the radar.
You startled me.
- Are you on a diet?
- I ate way too much yesterday.
It's weird saying this, but...
- Go on.
- I think you would've made a great woman.
- A compliment on my cooking or an insult?
- A compliment.
But there are way too many side dishes.
I don't eat like this when I'm by myself.
You're really getting old.
You used to stuff your face late at night,
and still grill meat at dawn.
Now that you're pushing 50...
I'm a light sleeper.
Why didn't I hear your car pull up?
Because you're old.
Your hearing is the next thing to go.
- Your eyes are already going, too.
- You think you'll stay young forever?
- No.
- You're really asking for it.
I took a cab because I drank.
Is something wrong at the company?
Maybe something's wrong with Momo.
Is that what's bothering you?
Yesterday,
I just felt like having a drink.
Forget Momo and focus on your own life.
I'm dying to hold a niece or nephew.
That's my wish, too.
Is it that hard for you to move on?
Why wouldn't I be able to?
It's just that I'm concerned, that's all.
Why would you be concerned?
She's your best friend's fiancee.
I wouldn't be
if they were happily married.
You think I've only known Ju Shin
for two years?
And it feels like he's hiding something.
I looked into it,
and her decompression sickness is severe.
You can bet Director Shin is taking
the best possible care of her.
Here, take a container of this kimchi
to Ba Ra.
I don't know her address.
You don't know her address?
Burn it. I'm not taking it.
(Nua General Hospital)
Momo, get a grip.
Walk like you're okay.
(Republic of Korea passport)
Director Shin, you know Geum Ba Ra, right?
Yes.
I think Ba Ra is digging around
for information on Momo.
It looks like she even met with
the scuba instructor.
I'm not writing an article, I promise.
You know me better than that, Manager Oh.
CEO Hyun said she's doing perfectly fine.
Have you seen her since the accident?
- I haven't.
- Does that make sense?
She told me not to worry, so...
- If you meet with CEO Hyun...
- I've already texted her,
but I got no reply.
So?
I just thought you should know
since it's about Momo.
Doesn't it seem strange to you too?
With your reporter's intuition.
Like you say,
what if Momo is in some kind of...
worst-case scenario,
what are you going to do then?
When it comes to the heart...
Shin Ju Shin has a cold side.
To put it nicely, he's just rational.
And it's not like they're married.
In that situation, I wonder how long
he can keep looking after her.
He's bound to get worn out.
And it's not like he has a low-stress job.
And you wouldn't get worn out?
Slow down.
You've never really been in love,
have you?
And for you, that's Momo?
What's so great about her, anyway?
Is it because she's a celebrity?
Lee Ye Rim, Hong Mi Jeong,
and Jeong Chun Hee are celebrities, too.
I've met them all at gatherings.
You can't really explain...
a person's feelings, you know?
If the situation is really that serious,
and Director Shin
eventually gives up on her...
are you saying you're going to take
responsibility for her?
For her entire life?
How noble of you.
To Mr. Ha and his undying love.
You're not being yourself today.
You're so cynical.
How well do you even know me?
What is it that I don't know? Tell me.
Other than that I was an abandoned orphan,
you know nothing about me.
You weren't abandoned.
It must have been an impossible situation.
I can tell by looking at you.
I can tell it's in your blood.
You've got good character.
My name...
Who gave you that name?
How would I know?
But I think...
It's just a guess...
I'd rather not say.
Are you mad at me?
I thought you'd understand.
I don't like how you're addressing me.
Don't call me Mr. Ha. It feels impersonal.
It's not like we have that many employees.
You should meet Director Shin,
find a way to see Momo for yourself,
and settle this once and for all.
I have an article to write.
I'll get going.
- Excuse me?
- Yes.
No, go ahead and finish your drink.
(Available)
How's Momo?
I don't want her to see me like this.
She's the same.
Don't let your mind run wild.
I'll wrap this up without any issues.
How are you going to wrap it up?
How did your seminar presentation go?
It was fine.
- I'm sorry. I came empty-handed.
- Don't be silly.
This is all very confusing, isn't it?
You'll get used to it. Eventually.
You should go. You must be tired.
Sometimes when I look in the mirror,
I can't tell if I'm Momo
or if I'm looking at her.
(Yong Joong)
Momo...
How can I live without seeing her?
(Ba Ra)
(Send me your address...)
(Where do you live? Are you asleep?)
(Yong Joong)
Are you still mad, kiddo?
What book is that?
("Mouth Management")
Come on up.
- Is this a bad time?
- I can't eat out. I have surgery later.
We were all in disbelief
when your father passed so suddenly.
- Were you there?
- As the orphanage's representative.
So many people came to pay their respects.
Honestly, my mother's death was harder.
I was just a kid.
Am I making you uncomfortable?
Do you mind if I get this to go?
I usually have late lunch.
This is my first meal of the day.
Are you going around investigating Momo?
- I heard about it.
- From who?
- It's not an investigation. It's...
- For a story?
Or as a concerned friend?
I heard you two were pretty close.
I'm just worried.
I haven't heard from her in so long.
Her phone is still turned off,
and Jin Ju said she had an accident...
It wasn't that serious an accident.
She's out of the country.
She was exhausted,
so I told her to take a break.
She'll be back soon enough.
About me and Momo dating...
Did you hear it from Kim Jin Ju?
I can't reveal my sources.
It wasn't Jin Ju.
We're both too busy to see each other.
We just run into each other at gatherings.
And even that was only once in a while.
You know my father was very proud of you,
don't you?
Running the foundation...
He found it so worthwhile.
If you ever need help with anything,
let me know.
- I don't.
- You never know.
Don't be so sure.
By the way,
I saw you interviewed Ha Yong Joong.
He's been a friend of mine
since we were kids.
He also played the double bass
at the appreciation gala.
Why did you leave so early that night?
I was running a little late
because I had an emergency surgery,
and I saw you were leaving.
I remember because of your ivory coat.
My mother used to wear an ivory coat
a lot.
Please tell Momo I said hi.
I'll take it to go.
Pack it for her to go. The sandwiches.
I can't relay the message.
You should tell her in person.
Hello?
- Yes?
- Where've you been? Haven't you seen it?
- The article on Momo's engagement.
- Where did it run?
Got it.
The inevitable has happened, Momo.
Did you already know about this, sir?
("Exclusive, Momo's Secret Engagement!")
("Fiance is Director Shin Ju Shin
of Nua Medical")
("Exclusive, Momo's Secret Engagement!")
(Two families have met.
Yet, there is no official announcement.)
(Surprised by his handsome looks,
belying his director title...)
(Innocent looks that belie his title...)
(and even more surprised
by his fresh-faced youth)
(We interviewed Director Shin and heard
the full story of their romance.)
- Is this for real?
- We need to publish by eight o'clock.
- Hey, over there.
- This is it.
("Exclusive Interview with Momo's Fiance,
Director Shin Ju Shin")
I just met with Director Shin Ju Shin
and posted the interview.
You interviewed him?
- Yes.
- When?
- I was with him when you called earlier.
- You should've told me then!
I knew you'd pull through.
Yes?
I just met with Director Shin Ju Shin.
He said Momo's fine
and that she's gone abroad to rest.
That's a relief.
Did you see the article?
Yes.
Can you toss me a decent engagement photo?
You must've taken some, right?
A really nice one of the two of them.
Ju Shin would kill me.
His picture's already out there
and the story went viral.
Do you have any idea
how much my boss chewed me out?
All because I was trying to be loyal
and keep it a secret...
I won't reveal my source, of course.
People will just assume
it was leaked by the wedding studio.
- If I can't make up for this...
- All right, fine.
What's with the sudden change of heart?
You've been ignoring
all my calls and texts.
It's not a change of heart.
Then what is it?
I'm sorry.
I'll be more respectful from now on.
- Director Shin Ju Shin!
- Just give us one comment!
- I have an interview with Mr. Shin!
- He has patients to see.
- We're reporting from Momo's house.
- Please just open the door!
- We're from CBS News!
- Come on, please open the door!
- Please, just open the door!
- Just open up!
This will only take a moment!
What are you doing?
Go back inside.
Who am I?
I...
The one you're referring to...
Who is that?
Don't you miss me?
You don't remember me?
I don't know.
Get lost.
You get lost.
You're so dead.
How can you say that to me, your mom?
(Surgery Center)
What am I going to do?
They won't stop ringing the bell,
so I had to turn off the intercom.
For now, there's no other way...
but to endure it.
So we endure it, and then what?
They broke up?
I'll think about it.
Let me think about it.
I guess you have no other choice.
Then just announce it tomorrow.
I won't have any time for a while.
And that'll just stir up
another huge mess.
If you're so busy, why'd you
even do that interview with Sungwoo Daily?
I didn't give them an interview.
She's a reporter, all right.
I heard she was snooping around
like she was onto something.
So I called her in
and gave her the runaround, but...
And that's what she wrote?
Yes.
Hello. We met before
at the exhibit with Momo.
I'm from the culture desk
at Sungwoo Daily.
I could tell she was something else.
(Sungwoo Daily)
(Director Shin Ju Shin)
Yes, Director Shin.
Did I have an interview with you today?
I'm sorry.
I'm in the middle of writing the article.
Can I call you back when I'm done?
Another story about us?
Yes, a follow-up piece.
Geum Ba Ra.
Yes, Director Shin.
You're biting the hand that fed you?
And you, of all people,
are going to take it even further?
- After you read the article...
- Don't write anything else.
Rather than let other outlets
write sensationalist garbage,
it's better to release
a well-written story based on the facts...
and help both of your images.
That is my professional opinion.
And who are you to make that call?
An interview that never happened.
That's what's fiction, an outright lie.
I'll make sure you have nothing
to worry about.
Is that what they taught you
at the Nua Orphanage?
I wasn't taught anything there.
You should have a shred of conscience.
You'll stop at nothing...
I'll call you when I'm finished.
Goodbye.
("Rumors of Momo's Broken Engagement,
Couple Not in Contact")
("Momo's Representative on Rumors:
'No Comment,' A Puzzling Response")
("Scoop:
Momo's Fairytale-like Secret Engagement")
("Momo's Fairytale-like
Secret Engagement")
(Geum Ba Ra)
Hello?
This is Geum Ba Ra.
Because of this exclusive interview
that never happened,
all the other news outlets
are in an uproar.
May I state my opinion?
At the end of the day,
it's true that you two are engaged.
It's a reporter's calling
to report the truth.
I'm asking why you published
a fabricated story.
What did Momo say?
Just answer my question.
As you said,
When the Chairman treated me to dinner
after I got into college,
he told me I was the face
and the pride of Nua Orphanage.
Everyone at my company knows
I grew up in an orphanage,
so I have to work harder than the others
just so they won't dismiss me.
That's how I survive in this business
without getting crushed.
If I succeed and make a name for myself,
you think you'll never need a favor
from me, Director Shin?
You think I don't have connections
in the media?
I've more than I know what to do with.
I'm sure you do.
But I'm not just a typical connection.
When you get down to it,
you could call me family.
Part of the Nua Foundation family.
Please, just think of it
as giving me a leg up.
You have every right to be upset.
And for that, I apologize.
To be honest,
I knew about your engagement for a while.
You heard it from Kim Jin Ju, didn't you?
I'm on the Culture Desk, so I have sources
at the salons that celebrities frequent.
I get all kinds of intel from them.
It's fast and accurate.
I'll let it slide this time.
Don't you dare stab me in the back again.
I promise.
You owe me one.
I wouldn't be where I am today
without the Chairman and you, Director.
I will be sure to repay everything I owe,
including this.
I don't care if you're a reporter
or the head of a media company,
You do not cross the line with me.
Yes. I'm sorry.
You can go now.
Yes, sir.
Is there anything you want to eat?
Who am I?
(To my dearest Momo,)
My dearest Momo.
If it weren't for you,
I would've left this world
a long time ago.
That I have to leave you like this...
this mother who is leaving you now...
I hope you can understand and forgive me.
I could never let you see,
but at some point,
I find it hard to even breathe.
For no reason at all,
every day was filled with despair...
and sorrow.
I tried to hold on a little longer,
but in place of this weak,
pathetic mother,
you have Director Shin,
someone who cherishes you...
and loves you so dearly.
I can leave now, because I trust him.
Please, let me go without any tears.
I feel deeply sorry...
to Dr. Jung,
who tried everything...
to cure the sickness in my soul.
To my many acquaintances,
I can see all their faces now.
My dear daughter,
don't be foolish like me...
and don't bury yourself in your work.
From now on, learn to enjoy life a little,
and always try to keep your spirits up.
Please, live a long and healthy life.
Live well, for my sake too.
The good deeds I wasn't able to finish...
Do plenty of them with Director Shin.
I don't want to be buried
in the cold, dark ground.
Please have me cremated.
I love you, my daughter.
(Paul Kim)
(Incoming Call)
This is Paul Kim.
Hi, I'm calling about the painting
you sold to CEO James Ha of Lim Company.
Yes.
I'm an acquaintance of CEO Ha's.
I found the mood of that painting
so unique and refreshing.
I assume you have other pieces
at your studio?
- I do.
- I'd like to purchase one. May I stop by?
My studio is on the outskirts of Seoul.
That's fine.
It's only one hour at most with traffic.
Do you have the address?
Could you give it to me?
It's open. Come on in.
Paul Kim?
Yes.
Hello. Sorry I'm a bit late.
The drive up here is just beautiful.
Please, have a seat.
You don't have any of your work
on display?
No, I don't.
They're in my studio
and on the second floor.
- All I have is coffee.
- Coffee is perfect.
No espresso, I presume?
I'm just kidding.
He surely is an artist.
He's middle-aged,
but not an ounce of fat on him.
This is delicious.
It's German coffee.
I heard you were based in Germany.
Yes.
I wasn't sure what to get you,
so I came empty-handed.
You really didn't have to.
There's nothing I need.
I just meant some basic necessities.
He's so stoic, like a Zen monk.
I'm Hyun Ran Hee, by the way.
(CEO Hyun Ran Hee)
He must have heard of me.
Do you do photography as well?
Sometimes.
So you must go out on photo shoots.
When I have a block or feel drained.
There's hardly any information
on you out there.
When did you return to Korea?
Seven months ago.
So you knew CEO Ju before that?
Yes, back in Germany.
So CEO Ju sought you out?
Yes.
After seeing my work
at the Hong Kong Art Fair.
The Hong Kong Art Fair? When was that?
That was two years ago.
I missed that one.
No wedding ring, either.
By any chance,
is this a painting of someone
in your family?
Your wife?
It's just that the feeling
I get from it...
is so profound.
I don't have any family.
Single? How attractive.
When did you start focusing on people
as your subject?
It's been a while.
Clients love it.
These heartfelt paintings.
This place is perfect for a studio.
So, are you back for good?
I am.
Why don't I plan a solo exhibition
for you?
Is it because of CEO Ju?
Mother's Gallery?
We're in talks.
I'll take this with me today.
She hasn't changed a bit.
(Paul Kim)
If you find her,
tell her...
that her mom was so, so sorry.
You have to find her. No matter what.
(One Missed Call, Ran Hee)
If you find her,
tell her...
that her mom was so, so sorry.
You have to find her. No matter what.
(Ran Hee)
The person you have called is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Hyun Ran Hee.
You've worked so hard.
And you're still so young.
Still in your prime.
That girl just wouldn't listen.
I warned her over and over
that it was dangerous.
Is this my karma?
Even if it is, it can't be helped.
Hello, is this the Immigration Office?
I'm calling to check if an acquaintance
of mine has left the country.
I can't let you know
as it's personal information.
Not even if I come to the office?
It wouldn't make a difference.
I see.
It's 911. What's your emergency?
- I...
- Please state your emergency.
Hurry. Please come quick. It's my mom...
We had a few calls.
Mr. Oh Young Sik woke up in distress.
He's intubated,
so he couldn't express himself clearly.
Remifentanil didn't work.
So we used Propofol, and he settled down.
When we started Precedex for sedation,
his blood pressure dropped slightly...
(Conference Room)
Hello?
(Nua General Hospital ICU gets top rating
in quality assessment!)
We can run a check,
but it's logged in the immigration system.
Who is it?
- A celebrity.
- Which one?
I'll tell you,
but you have to stick your neck out.
If I stick my neck out and lose my job,
are you going to take responsibility?
- You won't be fired for this.
- Get forensics to Momo's house, now!
What's going on at Momo's?
What happened? An accident?
Don't you know me?
You're the one who called me a pit bull.
It looks like Momo's mother
committed suicide.
We still have to investigate, though.
- Why?
- How would I know?
What about Momo?
Apparently, she's the one who called 911.
(Forensics)
(Sungwoo Daily)
(Headline)
("Hyun Gallery CEO Hyun Ran Hee
Found Dead")
("Momo Called 911")
(Reporter Geum Ba Ra)
("Hyun Gallery CEO Hyun Ran Hee
Found Dead")
(Momo discovered the body and called 911.)
(Reporter Geum Ba Ra)
(Doctor Shin)
No way. This can't be happening. How?
- What is it, sir?
- She's relentless.
Momo...
James, doesn't your company sponsor Momo?
- Yes.
- Can you introduce me?
I didn't realize you were his best friend.
I made a complete fool of myself.
- I'm Ha Yong Joong.
- I'm Momo.
I can't believe it.
She got all that work done on her face,
- and she looked so happy.
- Hyun Ran Hee is the one who died.
Things are not what they seem.
Just take it for what it is.
No need to overthink it.
Loosen your tie before you go.
I wonder where my daughter is
and if she's growing up well.
He was the one who saw the good in me
when I felt worthless.
- Yong Joong.
- They didn't even do CPR.