DOCTOR SHIN
THIS IS A FICTIONAL PRODUCTION
ALL NAMES, LOCATIONS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND CASES ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED SAFELY
WITH PARENTAL PERMISSION
EPISODE 2
MR. HA YONG-JUNG IS WAITING FOR YOU
AT YOUR OFFICE
When did you get here?
What happened to Momo?
Who told you?
That's not important right now.
Was it a diving accident?
She's much better after oxygen therapy.
What's her room number?
Nobody can visit her, except for her mom.
She hates showing her bare face.
She's an actress, after all.
Your snowman looks too sexy.
6 MONTHS BEFORE MOMO'S ACCIDENT
Have I...
changed that much?
That you don't even recognize me?
I guess you didn't miss me at all.
Check if it's good,
then write up a quick piece and post it.
SUNGWOO DAILY
Let's see the article.
How did it come out?
Where is it?
I don't see your article.
It'll run in the weekend edition.
Oh, the weekend edition?
Man up, you punks.
Don't pick on the weak.
He earned 100 billion won
from making one game.
Must be nice.
- A hundred billion.
- Who?
Ha Yong-jung,
the developer of Lost Knights.
I doubt that it's true.
No, it's for real.
HA YONG-JUNG'S LOST KNIGHTS
HITS 3.5M SALES WORLDWIDE IN 1 MONTH
No way.
Let's go.
I've put on an inch, right?
You still look like a model.
I've wrapped a painting
in my office beside my desk.
Yes, sir.
She must be new here.
She's been Momo's stylist since last week.
I hope I made the right purchase.
Have you heard of Paul Kim?
He used to be based in Germany.
Did you buy it directly from him?
You have a lot of baggage.
Are you moving back from overseas?
Yes.
Where were you staying?
Hello.
The article came out nicely.
I appreciate it.
Do you need any help, sir?
Not at all. You can go home.
Hello.
I guess you haven't heard yet.
I had to fly to the US
because my father passed away suddenly,
so another journalist,
Ms. Geum Ba-ra, interviewed you instead.
HA YONG-JUNG'S LOST KNIGHTS
HITS 3.5M SALES WORLDWIDE IN 1 MONTH
CULTURE DESK, JOURNALIST GEUM BA-RA
Bow!
Get ready to fight!
Ready, set, go!
SUNGWOO DAILY
JOURNALIST, GEUM BA-RA
This is Ha Yong-jung.
Are you Geum Ba-ra,
who was in 4th grade
at Minjin Elementary 16 years ago?
Yes. It's me, Yong-jung.
Yes. It's me.
Can I call you right now?
I'll call you in ten minutes.
GEUM BA-RA
Hello.
You're all grown up, kiddo. Amazing!
Why didn't you tell me yesterday?
Because I was there to work.
So you knew it was me.
How could I forget you?
I did.
Unbelievable.
If you were here right now, I would...
You would?
I would've flicked your forehead.
Up until now,
I thought I was texting Journalist Kim.
I thought so.
My goodness.
When did you grow to be so big?
- I haven't changed a bit, have I?
- No.
An-hui hasn't changed, either.
- How is he?
- Great.
- Is he married?
- No.
Let's meet up. You're off now, right?
I was just about to.
See you tonight with An-hui.
If you're busy, we can even meet late.
I'm free tonight.
Let me call An-hui.
What do you feel like eating?
I'll make a reservation.
Just act natural and keep talking.
Could you smile a bit?
Yes, that's perfect.
You're kidding, right?
You've never been to Paris?
No, I'm serious.
I've never been out of the country.
I was busy working all through college.
Perfect.
Could you stand up for me?
I thought you were
brought up like a princess.
I guess I was mistaken.
Would you like to see them?
We can delete them if you want.
I don't mind as long as you don't post it.
Could you send them to my phone?
You still have your baby features.
I couldn't reach An-hui on the phone.
He must be busy.
What does he do
that he's too busy to pick up?
Guess.
I know he joined the UDT
for military service.
He's so stubborn. Was he okay there?
Yes.
Does he work at an office now?
He works as Chairman Mo's bodyguard.
As a bodyguard?
I can't think
of a more perfect job for him.
Order everything you want.
The course meals are great here.
They're not too big.
The tasting course?
Yes.
- What about wine?
- Next time, with An-hui.
- Sure.
- How would you like your steak?
Medium, please.
Should I get the fish so we can try both?
So, would you like grilled
blackthroat seaperch with caviar?
Yes, please.
I know it's just water, but cheers.
I still can't believe it.
It feels like the impossible has happened.
Are you heading to Italy tomorrow?
I was supposed to leave today,
but I pushed it back for you.
Oh, wow.
When did you grow so tall?
Since sixth grade.
You were such a baby.
Are you disappointed
I'm not a baby anymore?
No, I'm just amazed.
You were so tiny
that you looked like a preschooler.
I was actually insecure about that.
Well, I was insecure about everything,
but my height bothered me a lot.
Is it okay
if I ask you this?
Were you ever adopted?
I almost was, but it fell through.
What happened?
It's a long story.
You had a best friend back then.
You mean Jin-ju?
Yeah, how's she doing?
She studied fashion
and still works in the field.
So things worked out well for everyone.
You have a boyfriend, right?
Why do you think I do?
I actually avoided
asking you that question.
Are you seeing anyone right now?
Why did you avoid it?
I didn't want you to think
I was making a move
during a professional interview.
I answered all your questions honestly.
I had no time to date.
But you have more time now, right?
I'd be open to dating
if the right person came along.
Do you have anyone in mind?
Let me know what you're looking for.
Come on, you're hilarious.
I'll think about it.
But no journalists.
Why not?
You're sitting in front of one now.
Yeah, but before that,
you're like a little sister to me.
So where do you live now?
In an apartment in Myeonghui-dong.
It's a small place.
By yourself?
Of course.
Is An-hui seeing anyone?
He almost married into a rich family,
but it didn't work out.
Did her parents disapprove?
After serving in the UDT,
he worked as a bodyguard
for Mo Group's daughter,
and she fell in love with him.
Was she pretty?
Oh, come on.
An-hui only likes pretty girls.
He's all about the looks.
Anyway, go on.
She even wanted to marry him,
so he got fired.
Hey, lighten the mood a little.
No, you can stay seated.
I apologize, sir.
I had no choice.
You couldn't have stood around
and watched your boss
get humiliated like that.
Come on. Let me pour you one.
I'm not much of a drinker, but sure.
Hop in, Ms. Journalist.
Where are we going?
Don't ask.
An-hui's.
Just kidding, maybe next time.
It'll take 10 minutes without traffic
and 30 with traffic.
The more I think about it,
the more I'm shocked.
How could you keep such a straight face?
You know what I was thinking?
"Should I make a move on her?"
I'm so happy and proud
to see you thriving,
but a part of me is...
a little sad.
What if I didn't recognize you
and had made my move?
Would you have kept playing me like that?
Absolutely not.
What do you mean?
I know you don't mean it.
No, I mean it.
No, you're kidding.
What if I really mean it?
How should I put it?
You're what people would describe
as insanely charming.
You're smart,
classy, polite,
but hard to read at the same time.
Are you describing yourself?
You agree, then?
That you always keep your guard up.
I don't do it on purpose.
I had to be like this.
You know how I grew up.
I'm not blaming how you grew up.
I'm just thankful.
I want to thank the universe
for letting you grow up so well.
Did you ever think of me?
I did.
Whenever I thought of An-hui.
And you? Did you ever think of me?
- I did.
- Did you?
Should I pound An-hui a few times?
He's a bodyguard.
I'm as good at beating people as he is.
Remember how we
took over the neighborhood?
Why did you drop out of high school?
Because I liked fighting
more than studying.
I didn't drop out. I was expelled.
Why didn't you write that?
You knew the truth.
My baby looks even prettier
when she smiles.
I missed you, Yong-jung.
I was...
so desperate to see you again.
Dear Lord,
is this an answer to my prayers?
Do you still play the contrabass?
I see marriage in your future.
You'll find someone.
When?
In five years.
But...
your bride will be young.
Very young.
How young?
She could be...
your daughter.
That'd be the dream.
Dr. Shin.
Hi, could I have Momo's number?
You didn't meet her?
I did, but she had to leave soon
for a shoot.
I see.
I mean, she's a huge star.
She's always busy.
Did she not like Dr. Shin?
I'll give you her manager's number.
No, I want Momo's number.
I can't.
Do you know how hard it was
to get her to see you?
I'm Shin Ju-sin. I'll take care of it.
That's not what it's about.
I don't want her to get mad at me.
Mr. Ha Yong-jung's car has arrived.
Didn't Yong-jung go to Italy?
I thought so, too.
You should ask Ms. Hyun yourself.
Okay.
Bye!
Bye.
- At 11 o'clock tomorrow?
- No, today.
Did my housekeeper let you in?
Your mother gave me the code.
She said she was at an art fair.
I'm getting shy.
I've never really done this.
You can stop, then.
I don't like flowers.
Not all women like flowers.
What do you like, then?
Nothing.
I hate watching them wilt.
I've probably thrown away
truckloads of them by now.
Good night.
Your mother won't tell me your number.
I told you I was a mama's girl.
I need her permission for everything.
I'm really tired.
Let me walk you to your door, then.
I thought all women liked flowers.
No, you just dated the same type.
Isn't he leaving?
Just as I expected.
I knew you'd be hard to approach.
That's a first.
No, people just didn't tell you
to your face.
I've never really been into women.
I didn't ask.
Is that a line from a TV show?
TV shows are based on reality.
Do you think that's a good thing?
A good thing?
I mean, are you proud of it?
That you're not obsessed with women?
I don't like getting attention.
I'm tired of it.
Bye.
Humans become
honest about their feelings at night.
I want to get married.
To whom? To me?
Yes.
That's random.
Give me a chance and some time.
I'll do my best.
You think you're being honest?
Not at all.
You're just impulsive.
Nobody's told me that.
They wouldn't say it to your face.
I'll try not to think
you see me as an easy target.
Quite the opposite.
You should go.
I'll forget about this right now,
so no need to kick yourself over it later.
I don't think I'll ever be doing that.
I've never regretted anything.
You can't be so sure.
And I'm seeing someone.
You said you were single in the interview.
You're not the type to lie, are you?
I sometimes do, to journalists.
Have you eaten?
Just a few snacks.
Then let me order some food for you.
I'm an actress. It's too late to eat.
You're still human.
You act to put food on the table.
Just quit.
No need to starve yourself.
Your body's also made of chicken breasts
and vegetables, though.
I'm not picky about what I eat.
I was born with good metabolism.
Lucky you.
Have some fruit, at least.
Do you not have any?
Should I get some for you?
Fruits are not allowed at my house.
Ms. Hyun doesn't allow it?
No, I don't.
In case you'd eat too much?
Yes.
I know you don't agree,
but I feel bad for you.
No, I feel bad for myself, too.
I would've wanted to marry you,
even if you were divorced.
I don't care
if you're dating ten other men.
See you.
Why are you getting so casual
all of a sudden?
Give it.
If you're throwing it away.
I'm not.
I'm not attracted to your fame or beauty.
And when my father told me
you were Ms. Hyun's daughter,
I wasn't particularly intrigued.
Twentieth floor.
This doesn't seem like your place.
It's my father's.
But he passed away.
That was what I heard.
When you were nine.
An-hui told me.
You even remember that?
I was going to prank you.
Oh, my!
My goodness.
You two know each other?
Did you just get home?
I told you not to bring this stuff home.
Oh, I forgot we had that.
I sometimes need it for my indigestion.
Is that Ms. Hyun?
Oh, it must be a delivery.
Do the deliverymen
usually ring the doorbell?
Oh, right. They don't.
It must be one of your fans.
But I don't see anyone there.
Go and check.
Who could have sent this?
You didn't order them, did you?
Maybe one of your fans brought it.
But how did they get in the building?
Oh, gosh, I need to use the bathroom!
MILK ICE CREAM, YOGURT DRINK
He's not bad.
Looks aren't everything.
You should tell him that about me too.
Why did you tell him the gate code?
He's not just anyone.
He's Dr. Shin's son.
How could I not tell him?
Ms. Moon can still read her script well
without glasses,
and she's seven years older than you.
She's single and doesn't have a kid.
How's that relevant?
Enjoy your acting career for now,
and get married in about ten years.
- He'd wait for me?
- No, with someone else.
All the good ones will be gone by then.
Maybe a man about five years younger?
After marrying your dad,
I looked like I was in my 50s
until I got these surgeries.
You're really something else.
Plastic surgeons are only getting better.
Maybe no one will look old anymore.
That could happen.
It's not bad to get old
as a famous actress.
- You mean it?
- Yeah.
But you love your life.
Yeah, I loved it.
But...
End it when he texts you.
Don't give him any hope.
And don't lead him on.
Hello?
I'm from Nua Hospital,
on behalf of Dr. Shin,
the head of surgery.
Door opening.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Enter the first three digits
of your gate code.
I put the flowers in a vase.
I chose them with care
while thinking of you, after all.
My mother passed away five years ago.
And she told me
to give these to the love of my life.
I wanted to show
how sincere my love was for you
with something meaningful,
and these were the only things
I could think of.
Please accept them.
I won't ask for anything in return.
I didn't have any new patients
admitted yesterday.
But I did get two calls.
One was for Orthopedics,
and the other seemed unrelated
to severe trauma.
I got a call from an ambulance in Gangnam
at around 11 p.m.
about a woman in her thirties
who had fallen down
and was vomiting blood.
It seemed like viral syndrome,
so I told them to contact
the Emergency Center.
As you can see,
the patient's toe and ankle are broken.
Only her ankle was severely injured.
But what's confusing
is that we found
this trace in the frontal lobe.
Now, whether this was a bleeding risk--
It's calcification.
I love mornings.
It's the only time I can actually eat.
Is it that hard?
You said it was hard for everyone.
When we film scenes with food,
other actors just pretend to eat,
but I actually gorge myself.
I go crazy.
The scenes of you eating
in The Girl's Prayer really were the best.
My ring fits you?
It's not yours.
It was a gift.
From whom?
Don't tell me it's from Dr. Shin.
Is it?
Why did you take it?
I told you to end things!
He's really determined, huh?
He's getting way ahead of himself.
But I can't believe
you're falling for just some jewelry.
It's a lot.
You can't even get
full price reselling them.
So return them.
When is your manager coming?
What if they don't get delivered?
It's not a difficult surgery,
so rest assured.
Thank you.
Momo's here to see you, Doctor.
Any more patients?
We have two more.
Tell her to wait.
- To wait?
- Yes.
Will do.
You can head in now.
Sorry for not offering you
anything to drink.
I'm here to return these.
It's too much.
Have you never
given a gift from your heart?
I have.
Then why?
This is too much.
A gift from the heart
doesn't have ulterior motives.
I didn't realize catching attention
could be an ulterior motive.
You didn't finish college.
I know you didn't finish
your acting degree
at Hankuk University.
My mother never finished college, either.
She married my dad
in her second year of college.
She had me at 23.
She was such a courageous and wise person.
I always thought of her
when I lay down to sleep.
Now, there's one more person I think of.
I want to do everything with you.
And I don't.
Give me a chance.
Does my opinion not matter?
I'm going to scream.
I'm sure many have told you
you had so many layers.
You're full of different layers.
That's just your fantasy.
What you see isn't everything.
I like women who are wise.
I'm sure all the female doctors here
fit that description.
No, not women who are just book smart.
I mean in love.
Someone with a warm soul
in their heart.
I don't have a warm soul.
But I can feel it.
How could I ignore that?
You're all I can think about.
How do I make it stop?
Tell me if you know how.
Do you only care about your feelings?
What about mine?
You've starved enough
to prove yourself as a talented actress.
Now, you can study,
do whatever you want,
and eat as much as you want
without worrying about gaining weight.
I'll love you, no matter how big you get.
Just keep your brain sharp.
Let me be your everything.
I can promise you that. I swear.
I know I can be a responsible husband.
I'm sure of it.
Let's live a normal life
as husband and wife.
That's all there is to love.
FATHER
I have to answer. It's my father.
Yes, Doctor.
I can't.
A friend's mother
is coming to the ER soon.
Hello.
Oh, my.
Is your father with you?
No, he had dinner plans.
May I join you?
Sure, I'm alone.
I guess you come here
to work out from time to time.
I don't come that often.
Momo loves the ocean so much.
Allow me
to tell you while we're here.
I'd like to get to know Momo
on a deeper level.
What did Momo say?
- She said no.
- Oh, gosh.
Really?
She said she's seeing someone,
but I think she's lying.
No, she might not be.
She doesn't even have time to sleep.
She's lost all her friends,
aside from the colleagues she works with.
I feel bad for her, as a mom.
She should be having fun.
What did your father say?
I haven't told him.
And I'd like your help.
Of course I'd be more than happy to help.
I'm meeting someone
at the restaurant here.
But I'm not sure
your father will approve of this.
My father's always respected my decisions.
You two are close.
Yes, but this is different.
See you around.
Yes, ma'am.
YOU HAVE A GUEST
Who?
Okay.
Please follow me.
Hey.
I didn't know you were off work.
I should go and see your father,
but I'm nervous.
Why?
He'll be happy to see you.
I got something for you and Dr. Shin.
I got my permanent contract.
They're just something small.
That'd be unnecessary.
I'll tell my father that you came by.
Where are you working?
The Lim Company.
I see. You got into James's company, huh?
Yes, I was an intern there for two years.
Whatever it is, just return it.
I can't.
Didn't you get it at a mall?
I got it over a week ago.
It's not much, but please accept it.
Don't lick your lips.
They say people
who lick their lips are dishonest.
But I'm not.
Who says you can get married?
Why do I need your permission?
I'm 24, the perfect age to get married.
Most people get married at 33 or 34 now.
You're not even dating.
You only saw him a few times.
You married Dad six months after you met.
You're at the peak of your career,
and you can stay on top of your game
for another ten years.
You think getting married is nice?
I won't know until I get married.
Enjoy your youth while you have it.
Date around for a bit.
I don't have time for that.
Guys like him are rare.
I'll regret it if I lose him.
There are plenty of fish in the sea.
But how many are actually decent?
And how can you be sure
that someone compatible and decent
will keep pursuing me?
You still need to date around first--
I've already decided.
Am I nothing to you?
It's not like we become strangers
if I get married.
Or do you want me to stay with you
and grow old alone?
Ju-sin is 33.
I'm 46.
He's only 13 years younger than me.
And he's my son-in-law?
It makes me feel so uneasy and awkward.
I have to get married early to have kids.
It's lonely to be an only child.
I want two or three kids.
You want me to become a grandmother at 46?
Thank you.
And please, no need to be formal with me.
I'll take my time.
What did your father say?
He was happy.
No, not that.
Dress up. It's an important day.
Your father isn't the type
to like a TV star for his daughter-in-law.
Quite the contrary.
He was happy for us.
Do you really have to steal Momo from me?
I'm sorry.
Just think of it as gaining a son.
There's no reason to rush.
Why not date for a few years?
Momo's signed a lot of contracts, too.
But it's not a breach of contract.
I asked for legal advice,
and her agency said
it might help with her reputation.
But you already know.
Why don't you get engaged first?
The driver has arrived.
Okay.
May I see your hand?
Do you read palms?
I'm not always right,
but Momo's father left me too soon.
Sir.
Listen carefully, Ba-ra.
What you experienced today
will happen over and over.
And I'm leaving in two years, too.
You're your only guardian.
So what do you have to do?
Are you just going to get a snack
and cry after getting beaten, like today?
Today's the last day you cry.
You're 11 now. You can't cry all the time.
Make sure to eat, even if it's hard.
Drink water if you have to.
You have to grow.
Middle school kids will bully you
even more for being a tiny orphan.
Your whole class will bully you.
You have to stay strong.
They might even try to do
something awful to you.
I'm going to teach you
how to defend yourself.
Do you want to learn or not?
Harder!
That's nothing. Harder.
That's it.
Harder!
Let me go!
You little!
Come here!
Hey!
Ba-ra!
Listen, all of you.
Get up.
I'll let it slide this time,
but don't mess with us again.
I won't let you go easy next time.
Life is short.
The world is full of great things,
so why waste your life being despicable?
You're all despicable.
You damn orphans.
What did you just say?
I don't think
I heard you right.
I said, you damn orphans.
We don't have anyone to protect us.
Getting into the slightest trouble
can get you expelled.
Don't hurt anyone,
unless they're beating you up.
I'll make you
regret this someday.
You'll be weeping in regret,
maybe even in utter misery.
What are you, a fortune-teller?
Disgusting.
You think you can lecture me
when your own parents abandoned you?
I'll make sure
I teach her a lesson one day.
By the way, I didn't brush my teeth today!
Hey, Ba-ra!
Even your own parents didn't want you!
Don't you want to know who they are?
If I were you,
I'd look everywhere for them.
Babe!
What happened to your face?
I got hit.
Who did this to you?
Was it a guy?
A girl.
Why, you little...
How dare you touch my baby?
What the hell are you looking at, huh?
She needs to be put in her place.
Strip her.
Do something!
Hold her in place.
Are you wearing a torso guard?
Damn, that's impressive.
Look at those abs.
You could even have two men on you.
It's so soft yet firm.
Damn.
That's a nice one to grind on.
Did you work your abs every night
instead of your thighs?
What are you doing?
Take my lady home safely.
Babe!
Get her!
Fucking bitch!
Wait, step aside.
Today's a turning point in your life.
Let me make you a woman today.
What the hell?
Ba-ra!
Damn it...
An-hui.
Don't worry about me anymore.
You can rest in peace.
I'm going to sell this house
and donate the money in your name.
Come visit me every year
on your commemoration day.
I'll make you some kimchi fried rice.
Your favorite.
PRESENT
Welcome back.
DOCTOR SHIN
Tell me.
- What's your name?
- How do I answer that?
You can't really explain
why you like someone.
Momo lost consciousness while diving,
but no one's talking about it.
And nobody's seen her since.
What if Momo's really hurt?
This must be very confusing.
You'll get used to it over time.
Why do you like her?
You've never been in love, have you?
The news about Momo is finally out.
Geum Ba-ra.
Is this how you repay my kindness?
Her phone's been off for a while,
and Jin-ju told me about the accident.
Excuse me...
Yes, we're listening.
What's going on? Did something happen?
She called emergency services herself.
Subtitle translation by Kim Min-sun