[Translate By Machine]
None
General He, have a good journey
General He
None
Have a good journey
Wei Qilin
None
You are a big traitor who is worse than a pig or a dog.
Wei Gou fled out of fear of crime.
None
He deserves to fall off the cliff
family
None
General He also died in battle yesterday.
Beat this Wei dog together
None
Beat the Wei dog Beat the Wei dog
burn him
None
Let him go down and apologize to the two generals.
what are you doing
None
you are the one
Kill King Naganobu’s female general
None
Yes, it's her
It's Lady Fan
None
Madam Fan, what are you doing?
We're going to burn this Wei dog
None
He is not a Wei dog
Fan Niangzi
None
We admire you as a woman
Kill King Chang Xin without fear of life and death
None
But why did you do it for Wei Qilin?
The great traitor speaks
None
What do you mean?
Why do you speak for Wei Qilin?
None
He's not, he's not a traitor
Today is the death anniversary of General Xie and General He
None
you do this
With the entire Jizhou Army
None
The entire Yanzhou army is the enemy
Sorry, generals
None
But he's really not like that
Stop talking nonsense here
None
enough
Houye Houye
None
Let's go
I haven't paid homage to General Xie yet.
None
I really want to worship
You have to speak for Wei Gou
None
You don't deserve to pay homage to the general
Our Xie Jiajun will never agree
None
right
Never agree
None
get out get out
line up
None
Mr. Hou, what are you doing?
Lord Hou, she just got wet
None
Xie Jiajun and Yanzhou Army obeyed the order
kneel
None
two generals
Have a good journey
None
Changyu
Feeling better?
None
Folk girl Fan Changyu
I’ve met Mr. Hou
None
You just
What do you call me?
None
Marquis
Thinking about it for so long
None
Just figured this out
Juhouye
None
But it’s really a struggle
If Mr. Hou feels that he is alive,
None
You and I are from the same school
You can call me Junior Sister
None
An important place in the Marquis's mansion
It's my boudoir again
None
Lord Hou, please respect yourself
i may know
None
what do you mind
But you should also know
None
nothing in this world
Can make you and me live apart
None
If this matter is great
will make you
None
I can’t be the head coach of Yanzhou Army?
Am I qualified to be the head coach of the first army?
None
It's all up to me
It has nothing to do with anything or anyone
None
including you
What Mr. Hou means is
None
Everything in this world
Just like military affairs
None
It's all up to Mr. Hou alone.
It's late at night
None
I still need to recover from my injuries
Mr. Hou, please come back.
None
Wei Xiang
Tutor
None
Look, look, look
This man is old
None
The disciples have big ideas
Can't govern anymore
None
This discussion is related to Jizhou’s military power
Everyone will use their own merits to fight without any selfish opinions.
None
I hope Mr. Wei won’t take it seriously.
If the master feels that he is old,
None
You can learn from Tao Taifu in those days
rapids retreat
None
To this day, both the government and the public
Even His Majesty
None
Only thinking about his good
It's better than being seventy and still not working
None
Rely on the old and sell the old
Can't govern
None
He's still crazy
The Battle of Lucheng defeated General He
None
General He is among the deceased
Strongly recommend Li Huaian as Sima
None
Now the military power of Jizhou has fallen by the wayside
I'm afraid Wei Yan won't be arrogant for a few more days.
None
As long as the Marquis of Wu'an still garrisoned in Lucheng,
This power of soldiers and horses cannot be ignored
None
this
This is Wei Yan's confidence
None
Mother
I will never play the traitor game again.
None
All are children
know what
None
people in this world
a few more
None
Can you really tell the difference between loyal and traitorous?
Know right from wrong
None
It’s time to eat
Okay, let's go eat
None
father and mother
What the hell is going on?
None
Enter
Lao Fan
None
boss
Lao Fan
None
Generals
This is
None
so many days
Can General Fan drink?
None
Yes, brothers have been waiting for so many days
I have long wanted to come and celebrate
None
Yes or no
What General Fan?
None
You guys are trying to discredit me.
General Fan is the great general in our eyes
None
You are the one who killed King Changxin
Retaking Chongzhou is just around the corner
None
After this
There's no battle to fight at all
None
That's right
Drink quickly
None
Come on, come on, boss
pour on pour on
None
To Lao Fan
Then I would like to thank you all
None
Sister
drink
None
Sister
That Mr. Li is looking for
None
Let him come in
I'm afraid it's not very convenient.
None
Sister, you’d better go out and take a look quickly.
Mr. Li, what are you doing?
None
Huai'an is ashamed
Today I specially bear the thorn to apologize to Miss Fan.
None
One of his crimes
When the rebels attack the city
None
Miss Fan is afraid that I will act on my own initiative
knock me out
None
I don't understand this
Instead, he spoke harshly to you when you were seriously ill.
None
This is unjust
The second crime
None
The dispute between me and the girl
Cause others to misunderstand you
None
Damage the girl's reputation
This is disrespectful
None
Please also invite Miss Fan
Answer me with a whip of thorns
None
Otherwise I wouldn’t have the face to meet the girl
I don’t even have the face to meet Mr. He
None
Mr. Li, don’t worry about it
Mr. He is very kind to me
None
I can understand your situation at that time
Get up quickly
None
Huai'an is ashamed
Unexpectedly, I have been practicing in the northwest for a long time
None
But my mind is not as good as yours
Mr. Li will be in chaos if he cares about you
None
Don’t be so hard on yourself
I knocked you unconscious
None
I was wrong too
Let's pay for each crime
None
Even if the two are cleared
stand up
None
Order troops and generals
Riding to fight
None
I touch this
Peeping is a puppy
None
I want to draw the highest
Look at my Shuangtian card
None
Look at my four pairs of candied haws
Do you think I won?
None
I won
Who won this card?
None
Uncle, uncle, look
who won
None
Double heaven pressure and purity
Emperor Guan Wanguan
None
Baoer wins this game
Come, come, come, come, come
None
Play one more game, play one more game
good enough
None
Then I will draw the thunder card and blow you up.
I want to draw the queen card
None
Come, come, come
Don't run, don't run
None
own people
Baoer
None
Ning Niang
fairy sister
None
Mom, you are finally back
I miss you so much
None
Mom misses you so much too
Shopkeeper Yu
None
you are back
It's Changyu girl
None
I asked General Xiaoqi to send me back.
She said that no one from Lin An can be left behind.
None
I
Also from Lin'an
None
Changyu, this kid is really capable.
Before, I had Changning and Baoer
None
Send it back
This is back again
None
Just come back, just come back
This home finally has a corner to fill.
None
Yeah yeah
why are you still here
None
What
Walk
None
Say it quickly
My father-in-law, Marquis Wu'an, said that military affairs are busy.
None
Can't come
Don't have to wait anymore
None
Father-in-law will not announce the decree again
I'm afraid I'm going to be late.
None
That’s all
No more waiting
None
Then
Let me announce these first two things first
None
Why did you drag me here?
I'm stewing meat
None
Why did you come?
There are so many people
None
Coming
How long will this declaration take?
None
I watched the shadow puppet show
Proclaiming the decree is just a matter of a while.
None
But I don’t know why it takes so long
It's me in front of my grandfather's mourning hall
None
I didn’t kneel for that long
It's so bad that my knees are numb now.
None
Get out of here
my stew
None
The edict arrives
All the soldiers received the order
None
His Majesty said
Chongzhou rebels
None
Luanyin Rivers and Mountains
Insulting people
None
Jizhou Muhe Jingyuan Kuang helped Sheji
Kill the rebels
None
Died in battle and died heroically for his country
Sacred Heart has mercy
None
In memory of his service
He was given the title of General Kuangzheng
None
Funeral with national ceremony
To show his loyalty and comfort his heroic spirit
None
Announcement to all the world’s envoys
Jizhou Zhenwei Captain Li Huaian
None
Stay calm in times of crisis
Success in raising the city
None
Feng Jizhou Sima
Reward Li Huaian and his men
None
Two hundred taels of gold and eight hundred taels of silver
Thank you Lord for your kindness
None
Jizhou soldier Fan Changyu
Fan Changyu
None
Where did Lao Fan go?
Fan Changyu
None
I have no idea
Fan Changyu
None
Jizhou soldiers died
Fan Changyu
None
Kill King Chang Xin in front of the battle array
Make miraculous achievements
None
Granted him the title of Commander of the Heroic Cavalry
Official rank from fifth grade
None
Reward Fan Changyu and his subordinates
One hundred taels of gold and five hundred taels of silver
None
fifth grade
Remembering that the Jizhou Army cannot live without a leader for a day
None
Order Sima Li Huaian as the master
Xiaoqi Captain Fan Changyu assisted
None
Jointly take charge of the military power of Jizhou
To reassure the troops
None
Therefore, it is clearly stated
Want to know
None
Let Li Sima take over the order on your behalf.
Thank you Lord for your kindness
None
Congratulations to Li Sima
Father-in-law comes from afar
None
Tired of traveling and traveling
If you don't dislike it
None
Please take a break
please
None
Congratulations, congratulations, congratulations
The boss has become an official
None
Great, Lao Fan is now an official.
Lieutenant of the heroic cavalry
None
five hundred taels
Our family has been in the palace for so many years
None
I have never seen such an unbecoming soldier.
Just them
None
How to beat King Chang Xin?
Captain Fan is there
None
Come and go
Go, go, go
None
Fan Duwei
Before, we were too blind to recognize Mount Tai.
None
How offended
Offended, offended
None
what do you call me
Captain Fan
None
Where is Lao Fan?
Congratulations to Lao Fan
None
Congratulations
Congratulations sister
None
Become an official
What official
None
Lieutenant of the heroic cavalry
Official appointed by the emperor
None
fifth grade
Talk about since the founding of the People's Republic of China
None
There has never been a woman
Can you be such a great official?
None
There's one more thing
The county official will see you later
None
First you have to kowtow three times
Only then do I dare to talk to you
None
How faceless you are
real
None
My sister is really a female general now
Let’s follow the boss from now on
None
Don’t eat spicy food every meal
Popular
None
That means you can have whatever you want
But remember
None
We are taking advantage of Lao Fan
From now on I won’t be called Jin Yuanbao, Lao Fan.
None
My name is Jin Changsheng
They also changed their names
None
Full of teachers
right
None
The army is full of courage
that's great
None
Today I'll treat you all to stew
Come on
None
Let's help
Come, come, come
None
Sit down quickly
Go sit over there
None
OK OK
Sister, let me help you get the bowl
None
The boss sits
Come on, let me pour the wine
None
Come
Bring it over
None
good
Come
None
thank you thank you
bring it on
None
Come, come, come
Not too much
None
Just two big bowls
Send it over
None
Come on, generals
Eat well and drink well
None
Such a big portion
Eat well and drink well
None
I'll fill it up for you
I'm afraid Li Sima is very disappointed.
None
I originally thought that General He would leave
This military power
None
I will go to your Li’s house naturally.
Unexpectedly, half of it was robbed
None
This little thing won't let me down
It's you, Mr. Hou
None
Jizhou’s military power is so important
Why would you leave it to someone with no experience?
None
In the hands of a young lady with no background
Didn't you take it upon yourself to repay the favor to the court?
None
this is the result
I repay Mrs. Fan's merits
None
It's to protect her
And I will definitely protect her
None
My family's child
I don’t need you as an outsider to protect me.
None
Uchiko
I remember that Mrs. Fan had Yan Zheng as her daughter-in-law.
None
It's not you Xie Zheng
Even if it is correct
None
You also wrote and left the book
Madam Fan has no engagement with you today
None
Lord Hou, why do you have to deceive yourself?
Don’t forget Li Sima
None
Your engagement with the eldest princess has been concluded
Two boats
None
This is not what a gentleman does
Xie Qi has delivered Yu Qianqian safely
None
Officail website =dramacool.club=
It's Tao Taifu
None
He insists on staying
I refuse to go back to Beijing no matter what.
None
Official reinstatement
If he doesn't go back
None
I'm just afraid that the Holy Emperor will be unhappy
What are you afraid of?
None
The Holy One is always on the wall
Hugging thighs everywhere
None
besides
The imperial court handed over military power to Lady Fan
None
I'm afraid it's the result of the fight between Wei Yan and Taifu Li
these two people
None
Check each other
Let's just let go
None
Fan Changyu poses no threat to them
It's better than having the military power taken away by me
None
This Li Huaian is so smart
As a result, both parties took advantage of it.
None
These two old foxes
The abacus beads are beating loudly
None
We all heard it clearly in Jizhou
It seems so
None
Lady Fan is like a child holding gold
Walking in the busy city
None
There's big trouble
I'm here
None
she won't be in trouble
what to do now
None
Divide half of the military power
Madam Fan doesn’t get the slightest advantage
None
I'm afraid he's still a scapegoat.
The master's side must also be unhappy.
None
Grandfather clearly wanted to take advantage of Mrs. Fan
Sabotage Wei Party's plan
None
But it doesn't matter, you can just use the plan
I'm Li Huaian
None
Can also become Lady Fan’s backer
Be obedient
None
Lieutenant of the heroic cavalry
The reward is one south and two taels, and the reward is five hundred taels of silver.
None
Ancestors
This is enough for Changyu and Changning to spend a lifetime
None
This is nothing
Fan Duwei
None
Now he can command half of Jizhou’s military power.
little brother
None
After you go back
Can you please tell our parents Yu?
None
Although he was promoted to captain
But there is a saying among the people
None
You can't stop being a spoiled man
What a bad husband and a bad wife
None
Don't interrupt
When it was so difficult for Changyu
None
It’s recognition that Yan Zheng is with her
I walked through it with support
None
Later, she was drafted and taken away by the army.
This affection
None
People are incomparable
Don't let her learn that
None
A heartless girl who turns her back on wealth and refuses to recognize anyone else
Heartless man
None
old man
Why are you like the ladle of water?
None
Ladle after ladle
What are you talking about?
None
Then you are wrong
You haven't asked someone to correct you yet, have you?
None
uncle aunt
Don't worry
None
Sister Changyu is not such a person
I will definitely go back and tell Captain Fan
None
With my family Hou
Good brother's
None
Yan Zheng also wants to come back safely.
The family should be in order
None
Yes, everyone in Lin'an is waiting for him.
What you two said
None
Xie Qi will definitely bring it
Unexpectedly, the eldest princess
None
Chaochao traveled thousands of miles to come to the northwest to endure hardships
It’s for the headmaster of Luyuan Academy
None
It's for him that you and I agree
Li Sima Lai stayed in Jizhou and refused to return to the capital.
None
Could it be that you want to be married in Xiao?
Lady Fan and Marquis Wu An were married in a fake way
None
Fan Duwei and I are Pao Ze
Very innocent
None
The mountain leader and I once fought together
It’s a righteous comradeship
None
Captain Fan is here
If innocent
None
What made Sima so flustered?
You really care about your comrades.
None
Princess, don’t laugh at me anymore
Mr. Gongsun
None
A joke won't work the second time.
Unexpectedly, His Highness and Li Sima were also here.
None
It's because Xiaosheng is abrupt.
Bunkan
None
The medicine has been changed
Pay more attention to rest recently
None
I have something else to do
I'll go first
None
Don't move, count down to five
His Highness doesn't want to see you
None
Your Highness
Your Highness stays
None
Your Highness
Listen to me, Your Highness
None
Stay away from the eldest princess
Your Highness
None
That's it, Your Highness
Close the door and listen to my explanation
None
Your Highness
Can you leave?
None
I won't leave
If you don't walk, your feet will be broken.
None
Are you okay?
Let me see
None
It's okay
You lied to me again
None
I just want to say a few words to you
Princess, tell me
None
Do you have any feelings for Li Huaian?
There is a fart
None
Not only does I have no interest in him,
Not interested in you either
None
This is what you came to me to say
Don't you have anything else to say?
None
actually i
Gongsun Shanchang
None
If you have no interest in me
Don't come to me again
None
My mouth
Why can't I say it out loud at the critical moment?
None
Sister, come on
Lao Fan
None
Why are you so distracted today?
Are you coming again?
None
Come
Sorry Mr. Li
None
Fan Duwei
I came here today because I have something I want to discuss with you.
None
That son-in-law is annoying
This Li threshold
None
more annoying
Mr. Li, please come back.
None
I'm in a bad mood today
Your first appointment as captain
None
Need to understand the regional military situation as soon as possible
I just hope this marked map can help you
None
If there is any confusion
Wenjing is willing to analyze
None
Some people really like to take advantage of opportunities.
I guess my son-in-law is in trouble.
None
That's the case
Thank you very much, Mr. Li.
None
If you don't want to hear it, you can leave.
No, no, no
None
We can't go
here we go
None
Who protects the captain's name?
good
None
Have dinner
This sentence is well written
None
It's getting late
How about this today?
None
There are too many things involved recently
I'm afraid I won't be able to accompany you these days
None
But I hired the best mentor in Jizhou for you
as your staff
None
I believe you will become more and more like a captain.
Then thank you Mr. Li
None
Taking advantage of the enemy's plan
The micro gap must be multiplied wherever it is
None
Small profits must be obtained
I know this
None
It means I saw the thief's sheep
Take it away easily
None
Make another mutton soup
That's right too
None
And this
I know this too
None
Kill with a borrowed knife
It means that I was killed with a knife on the battlefield.
None
I immediately borrowed other people's weapons
Kill the calf with a click
None
You don’t have to use your own strength
You go and seduce others.
None
Let them help you destroy your enemies
It can prevent you from consuming your own strength
None
Understood
Then I really know about watching the fire from the other side.
None
this is in our town
Rich people
None
You can watch the fireworks very close
But we children from poor families
None
It can only be far, far away
Very far far far away
None
go watch fireworks
it it it
None
it's not a matter of fireworks
this this
None
Pass
gentlemen
None
What does this mean by pointing at wood and cursing ghosts?
Pointing at mulberry and scolding huai
None
Elegant and upright person
What is elegance
None
Changyu
gentlemen
None
How's it going today?
Fan Duwei is extremely intelligent
None
learn by analogy
is a talent
None
Well taught sir
Don't dare
None
That’s it for today
farewell
None
Mr. Sun Tzu, I know the art of war.
Can you teach me more tomorrow?
None
Sun Tzu and his grandfather’s art of war
farewell
None
hurry up
Let’s find another gentleman
None
clear
Master Liu is tired
None
my protégé
All are outstanding generals
None
Li Sima is completely relieved
don't worry don't worry
None
please
Master
None
Sir you
Can't read all the words
None
You'd better hire another Gao Ming
Master Master Master Master
None
There is really nothing I can do
farewell
None
adult
Find here again
None
Please rest assured, Sima
Education without distinction
None
gentlemen
I'm just so poor
None
I can't teach you even a little bit.
husband
None
Is there anyone who can’t teach?
Little talent and little learning
None
Please Li Sima, please raise your hands and stand up.
Spare my life
None
Get up sir sir
This is the person to teach
None
It can't be Captain Fan, right?
gentlemen
None
Fan Duwei’s reputation
It has spread throughout the city
None
All my subordinates have joined in for an hour.
I'll teach her myself
None
How come it is like this
Fan Duwei did it
None
You're both still hurt.
They also learned martial arts skills.
None
All internal injuries
It's getting late
None
help me up
I still have to teach her
None
Just take a rest
Let’s not teach Fan Duwei any more.
None
This is the art of war
Don’t we have to do it step by step?
None
Right?
Learn the art of war
None
first time meeting
Teaching can teach you a good year
None
li adult
Changyu
None
Mr. Li, no, no, no, no.
li adult
None
Mr. Li, I’m really sorry.
Otherwise, I should learn it slowly by myself.
None
you say
My adoptive father is so powerful
None
At first, he wanted to take me on as his disciple.
Is he older?
None
My old eyes are dim
On Lady Fan
None
Must have great wisdom
Tao Taifu must also like this in you
None
I can't compare
I think too
None
otherwise
I'd better ask my adoptive father to teach me
None
Just don't harm his old man.
Why can't you learn?
None
It seems that he is really not good at reading.
I'm in the margin of the paragraph
None
Wrote a red note
Take your time and read it when you have free time
None
It's stormy
The cock crows endlessly
None
Seeing a gentleman
Yunhu is not happy
None
What does this poem mean?
means
None
It's raining heavily
The rooster crows in panic
None
It happened in the midst of all kinds of chaos
Eyes turn slightly
None
But I saw her at a glance
like
None
Clear away the clouds
A beam of light hits me
None
Overflowing with warmth
feel happy
None
Teach me how to speak honestly
I just remember it
None
Chi doesn't know what he is doing