There are so many people today
None
Quite lively
yes
None
Sister
You said you wished you could
None
Being with Mr. Hou every day
Why do you have to come and join in the fun?
None
I came to Beijing and he cheered me up
He returns in triumph this time
None
Of course I want to come and join in the fun.
Song Yan, Department of Internal Affairs, Ministry of Rites
None
Carrying out etiquette and enlightenment
However, there is no official status
None
Dereliction of duty
Immediate dismissal
None
Repatriation to place of origin
never use
None
Coming, coming, coming
Sister, come and see
None
You don't come over
I won’t go if there’s anything interesting to see.
None
Marquis of Wu'an Marquis of Wu'an
Look at this Marquis of Wu'an
None
Marquis of Wu'an Marquis of Wu'an
Look at me, look at me, Wu Anhou
None
Marquis of Wu'an
Look at me, Wu Anhou
None
stop
Sister
None
Why don't you throw one in too?
Didn't bring it
None
Throw one away
Which of you is wearing a veil?
None
Did you bring it?
What's the point of throwing the veil?
None
Come
Let me give you a try
None
See if I don't knock you out
What are you doing? What are you doing?
None
I
you you you what you
None
Who threw away the hair tie?
Could it be that Marquis Wu An has a sweetheart?
None
There are so many girls throwing silk handkerchiefs along the way
Marquis Wu'an didn't even take a second look.
None
Whose daughter is this?
Isn't that General Hairpin?
None
It was indeed General Fan
Our General Fan is really a woman who cannot stand before men.
None
No wonder he is the only one favored by Marquis Wu'an.
What's so great
None
Our marquis goes to war
He is not a person who sticks to petty love affairs.
None
that is
That one of you who kills pigs?
None
Not worthy at all
Not worthy
None
We, General Hairpin Flower, will fight at home for ten meetings
Captured King Chang Xin and made many military exploits
None
Stop being so sentimental to me here
that is
None
Stop being so sentimental
Our brother is very brave
None
I won’t accommodate you, a pig-killer.
It's you, you loser butcher
None
What's so great
Our sister has a great record
None
I won’t marry a warrior like you.
Why are you talking, Wufu?
None
We just want to look good
Can you please stop making noise?
None
that is
God is unfair
None
This man is older
My memory is not good either
None
today
I actually forgot to bring your favorite osmanthus cake
None
Come today every year
Look at my father and mother down there
None
You're living a peaceful life, right?
Come and piss them off once a year
None
This has been hidden for several days
Finally want to show up
None
Today is your mother’s death anniversary
Let’s talk about the killings later.
None
No matter how big a thing it is
We have to wait until we finish paying homage to your parents.
None
bring it on
The prime minister drinks up the dead soldiers
None
Not afraid
Do I want you to pay with blood?
None
Your mother is watching from here
Why would I embarrass you here?
None
Disturbing her peace
to this day
None
Prime Minister Wei finally knows how to cherish your sister.
seventeen years ago
None
You turned back to Beijing on the way to mobilize troops
Have you ever thought about it
None
my father and mother
Will die because of your hasty decision
None
I'll tell you again
seventeen years ago
None
I was ordered to return to Beijing to quell the chaos.
Yeah
None
Then do you dare to stand in front of my father’s and mother’s memorial tablets?
Make a poisonous oath
None
Okay, now that we’ve talked about it~
today
None
Let me share a few words with you sincerely
I will raise you
None
I just want you to be
The future of the Xie and Wei families
None
Brilliant and charming
To protect the peace of Dayin
None
so
I worked hard to cultivate you
None
cultivation
It's just a matter of forging a suitable blade.
None
It's just that you never thought of it
this blade
None
will eventually point to yourself
And you
None
He's the one who messed with our family.
Those who destroy the peace of the country
None
Beguiled by the enemy's daughter
Disloyal and unfilial
None
Why did you mention to me the importance of family and country?
Today I will make you do it in front of your parents
None
Cut off with Fan Changyu in two pieces
No more connection
None
what qualifications do you have
Say these words to me here
None
I raised you for seventeen years
Isn't it enough?
None
this
Do you agree?
None
Still don’t recognize it
I agree
None
as your uncle
Follow your father's duty and your mother's orders
None
today
Family law is up to you
None
tell him
how to be punished
None
According to clan rules
Disloyal and unfilial
None
One hundred and eight lashes
good
None
Every whip today
I'm willing to suffer
None
I should return your flesh and blood
But from today on
None
Stop talking about the kindness of upbringing
Disgusting words like that
None
Come
Obviously my ancestor
None
Yin Shi Liufang
Train children and grandchildren
None
learn the original meaning
Thirty-five
None
thirty six
Thirty-seven
None
thirty-eight
thirty-nine
None
forty
ninety-nine
None
One hundred and four
Words correct
None
you shouldn't have come
I shouldn't have come
None
And you
Knowing that Wei Yan was in the cemetery
None
Why did you come alone?
Why be whipped?
None
General Fan broke into the Xie family cemetery without permission
But it's against etiquette.
None
I am not only General Fan
Also Mrs. Hou
None
Why can't you come?
This marriage requires the order of the parents
None
matchmaker's words
Plus
None
Where are the three media and six people?
As for getting married
None
Even the name is fake
How can this marriage be taken seriously?
None
I have received one hundred and eight lashes
You are not qualified to make decisions for me
None
A marriage certificate is just a piece of paper
Only I recognize
None
That's called a marriage certificate
let's go home
None
etc.
Kneel down
None
Parents are generous
Fan's Changyu
None
Lin An people
When the child's life is at stake
None
saved by her
When the child's heart is as dead as water
None
be loved by her
My son has been on the battlefield for more than ten years
None
Never feel like I'm still alive
to her
None
Just feel that this world is worth it
Dare to tell parents’ souls in heaven
None
This woman
My lifelong companion
None
Never be negative
Till death do us part
None
Never be negative
Till death do us part
None
Prime Minister
Zheng'er
None
What's wrong with you
Why was it hurt so badly?
None
It's okay, aunt
This is Fan Changyu
None
my wife
aunt
None
Hairpin General
I have heard of your reputation for a long time
None
When my life hangs by a thread
It was she who saved me
None
both of us
Determined for life
None
Till death do us part
By the way, Changyu
None
Hurry up and help Zheng'er apply the medicine
Zheng'er is coming
None
It’s very cold and dewy today
Why did the lady come here?
None
The concubine saw the sweet-scented osmanthus cake prepared by the prime minister
Forgot to take it
None
So hurry up and deliver it to Mr. Xiang
Zheng'er's mother used to like sweet-scented osmanthus cake
None
The prime minister misses his sister
I send sweet-scented osmanthus cake every year
None
This year will certainly be no exception
Give
None
This box is uniquely crafted
Could it be that it was made by a famous artist?
None
Then I must eat more every day
Fang deserves it
None
The brotherly friendship that hurts the hand
Sweet Osmanthus Cake
None
Don't eat too much
yes
None
they match so well
Even if Zheng'er's parents are under Jiuquan
None
Will also be happy
fifteen twenty ten
None
drink wine
What kind of bullshit game is this in your hometown?
None
Gudu lost all night
Come again
None
fifteen twenty ten
drink wine
None
hurry up
master
None
have something to say
There are no outsiders here
None
There is a letter for you
I already knew that Xie Zheng would not give up searching for the truth.
None
What kind of bullshit uncle-nephew relationship?
It seems it's time
None
Come here with me
What's going on so late?
None
I have prepared a surprise for you
The gorgeous clothes I prepared for you
None
how
you are crazy
None
This is the queen's phoenix crown
be a lonely queen
None
Mother's love for the world
Stand shoulder to shoulder
None
rule the world
So what about the queen?
None
You just want to find someone to sleep with
When you wake up from Huang Liang's dream, someone will be with you
None
What's wrong
dislike
None
That's it
do i like it or not
None
What does it matter
Don't let me kill someone alone
None
Do not kill if you are alone
Gu Ye has already promised you
None
Don't hurt that little kid anymore
What do you want Gu to do?
None
Only then do I want to be a lonely queen
kneel before me
None
beg me
You want me to kneel down to you
None
Gu Ke is the Nine-Five Lord
What's the matter
None
Not happy
I beg you
None
be a lonely queen
I'm waiting for the day I become queen
None
will be soon
Stop making trouble
None
Give me back the tiger charm
Marquis
None
Madam, what's wrong?
Help back to room
None
Don't make any noise
yes
None
Madam, do you want to go and have a rest?
The slave monument is here to serve you.
None
I'll do it
You can go down now
None
If there is nothing important
Don't bother
None
yes
Changyu
None
I received these one hundred and eight lashes
It can be justified
None
Three matchmakers and six beauties have married you.
It turns out you have already thought about it
None
To redeem yourself in this way
Changyu
None
I will marry you
Good
None
No need to marry again
You have long been mine, Fan Changyu’s.
None
mother concubine
don't want
None
mother concubine
Officail website =dramacool.club=
None
let me die
This is enough to feed and clothe you for a lifetime.
None
Then take this baggage
Delivered to the General's Mansion intact
None
Then leave the capital
The further away the better
None
never come back
Madam, won't you come with me?
None
His eyes are everywhere here
I can't leave
None
If I leave
This hospital will only kill more people
None
Go quickly
woke up
None
careful
thank you
None
always stay with me
You took so many whips for me
None
How could I not accompany you?
I always thought
None
This Wei Yan hates me
It's because when I was a child
None
Greedy that plate of sweet-scented osmanthus cake
Giving my mother the opportunity to hang herself
None
I have always resented myself for this
But later, regardless of whether I took Jinzhou to take revenge
None
Or should I be the Marquis of Wu'an?
I can only dream
None
That disgusting scent of osmanthus
And my mother’s skirt hanging from the rafters
None
I'm still the same
crybaby
None
never changed
I'm here now
None
I can protect you
do you know
None
You were injured at that time
When you came out from Lin'an to look for me
None
I'm thinking about it in my heart
What kind of revenge is there?
None
No more reporting
don't want to see you cry
None
But later
I thought again that my surname is Xie
None
My father is Xie Linshan
I don't even remember what he looks like
None
But I can still remember
After he was disemboweled
None
The chest that was barely sewn up with needle and thread
I still remember him
None
Sixty-seven arrow-shaped wounds
Words correct
None
I never blamed you
Wei Yan is your uncle
None
I have raised you for more than ten years
Now the grace has been repaid
None
It's time to take revenge
Don't let others make mistakes
None
torture ourselves
good
None
it's time
The palace banquet three days later
None
I enter the palace in person
Bring out the maid witnesses from the palace
None
I help you
Come in
None
Mrs. Houye
Hai Dongqing brought back a set of chess records from the palace
None
After Mr. Gongsun cracked
I wrote this to Mr. Hou
None
What's wrong
Wei Yan once had an affair with his concubine
None
This woman
My lifelong companion
None
Never be negative
Till death do us part
None
Third brother and my dearest brother
Show your confidence and look good
None
Missing each other so much after parting
Every pair of mirrors for dressing
None
The injury of your joy
Flowers and butterflies dancing in the garden
None
But no one shares it
Elders in the family
None
Marriage agreed
Qunxiang Jiji
None
Two races having sex
Six rites are not for you
None
Lamb Goose General Preparation
Everything is ready now
None
Only missing your companion
Never be negative
None
Till death do us part
Third brother kisses
None
See words as face
The oracle arrives suddenly
None
Call into ban
The body is ordered by the king
None
Last resort
Notes from Third Brother Recalling the Past
None
love words
Every word is haunting
None
Just like the ear
In the past you gave me hairpins
None
Fragrance lingering on temples
As if yesterday
None
The greatest regret in the world
There is nothing better than falling in love without being able to stay together
None
From now on, I will be trapped in a golden cage
My heart is always flying with Bai Yunfei
None
If you see Yannan crossing
Just send you a letter
None
Yoon
Cry before departure
None
grandfather
Someone coming
None
Catch my good brother
What do you mean?
None
After the palace banquet
Brother will understand
None
Grandpa, you are pretending to be sick.
Where is the threshold of literature?
None
Do you know where you lost?
Those who achieve great things need to make prompt decisions
None
Not swayed by any emotions
You are so kind
None
It is destined to be difficult to achieve great success
I am for my country
None
Grandfather is doing it for personal gain
I'm destined not to be like my grandfather
None
desperate
you are confused
None
The loyalty of our Li family for so many years
what got
None
What did you get in exchange?
come this far
None
Already riding a tiger with difficulty
We must protect the emperor and his grandson's succession
None
Even if he is not Renjun
Even if we draw our bows, there will be no turning back.
None
Bunkan
There are thousands of people from our nine Li clans
None
If you continue to be so close and distant, I will never tell you
No distinction between inside and outside
None
It will only make our entire Li family suffer.
Let Dayin's national foundation be shaken
None
Since ancient times, those who succeed are princes and those who lose are bandits.
Self-interested
None
Only then can one sacrifice his life for the country
You
None
read
Read Qianfu
None
without my order
The eldest son is not allowed to go out
None
yes