Lord Wu has arrived
None
Previously in the Jinluan Hall
Just meet the general face to face
None
I am concerned about the general’s execution of the rebel king Naganobu.
I admire you so much
None
I'm lucky tonight
I would like to propose a toast to the general first.
None
please
There are so many generals
None
yes
General Fan is young and promising
None
Famous everywhere
A talent
None
Able to kill King Changxin
It's really amazing
None
yes
I would like to offer a toast to General Fan.
None
Keep drinking it
The pig-killer will definitely make a fool of herself
None
Don't care about her
Why hasn’t the eldest son arrived yet?
None
Another toast to General Fan
Taifu heard that his teacher had a heart attack recently.
None
Can it get better?
much better
None
I miss you very much
good drinker good drinker
None
The pig-killing woman uses her power to bully others
It’s unspeakably painful to wait.
None
Don't wait and see
I'll have a few drinks with you guys
None
Good things come in pairs
You must have fun today
None
Let me toast the general again
Come
None
Didn’t your Majesty give me a banquet today?
You are the disciples of Prime Minister Wei
None
Why only frequently
How about a toast to General Hairpin?
None
Is it possible
It’s because you look down on me
None
Mr. Hou was joking
General Fan arrived first
None
Everyone just wants to have some fun
The lower official Jinghou returned with a great victory
None
Marquis
You and I are ministers of the same palace
None
Why is this necessary?
Mr. Fang, right?
None
As the Minister of Household Affairs
Is it your responsibility to regulate food at the border?
None
So what
Almost led to civil unrest in Jizhou
None
I haven’t held you accountable yet
You look like a human being
None
you
Today is to celebrate the Marquis
None
Don't talk about business
Mr. Fang spilled his wine all over his body
None
Go down and rest first
Lord Marquis please
None
The prime minister is coming soon
Go, go, go
None
Lord Marquis takes leave
This is really unreasonable
None
The great master is here
The fun has just begun
None
You and I look slowly
I'm afraid you'll start a fight
None
You value these salaries too much
These people all have deep feelings
None
And I feel three points lower than myself
Don't dare to make trouble in a high-profile manner
None
Don't worry, I'll leave soon
Gongsun will cooperate with you
None
Take a seat
His Majesty arrives
None
Welcome Your Majesty
Taifu recovered
None
great kindness
Your Majesty, I would like to thank you for your concern
None
I am ashamed, veteran
Prime Minister Wei has been working hard these days
None
This is always the case
Not that it's hard
None
It's Taifu
Pay attention to your health
None
The combination of work and rest is
thank you thank you
None
Both my dear friends are the pillars of the country.
Today can be regarded as a double happiness
None
I am very happy
This time the Chongzhou rebel rebellion was put down
None
Marquis Wu'an survived a narrow escape
Taking credit for greatness
None
The four northwest prefectures were also fortunate to be guarded by Marquis Wu'an.
Only then can we be safe
None
I specially give the Longquan Sword to the Marquis of Wu'an
This sword was made by Emperor Taizu of Dayin
None
Go up and kill the faint king
Execute ministers
None
To show my heart
Presented
None
This Longquan sword
It really lives up to its reputation
None
Go up and kill the faint king
Execute ministers
None
It's a good sword
However, the minister’s heart is concerned about the country
None
loyal to duty
This Longquan sword is too valuable
None
No one is worthy of you except Your Majesty
Marquis Wu'an's loyalty
None
I already know it
Today's shrine banquet
None
My beloved, you will never return until you are drunk.
Thank you, Your Majesty
None
I'm going to change clothes first
His Majesty temporarily withdraws
None
His Majesty the Emperor
His Majesty
None
Princess Palace
Instruct His Highness
None
The palace banquet is about to begin
Don't waste time
None
Your Highness forgive me
The slave didn’t do it on purpose.
None
You, you bastard, you
No problem
None
Today is the celebration banquet hosted by the emperor’s younger brother for Marquis Wu’an
Don't get angry
None
you
You go down first
None
yes
This is an old slave who was not strict in his discipline. Please forgive me, Your Highness.
None
I have to go back and change clothes.
I miss Wu'anhou and the emperor's younger brother
None
There should be no blame
This, this, this
None
Her Royal Highness the Princess
Your Majesty is still waiting for you
None
Xie Zheng Wei Yan
Their nephews are all the same
None
They never took me seriously
Damn it
None
They all deserve to die
That being the case
None
Then don't blame me for not giving you a chance
My dear friends, this atmosphere is not right.
None
Watch the music and dance
drink up
None
Tutor
His Majesty
None
Do I, Dayin, still have to rely on me?
Of course
None
I, Dayin, will live forever
It all depends on His Majesty’s holy candle alone.
None
What would you do if you didn't have me in this world?
Right?
None
yes yes yes
This drunkard has no distinction between high and low.
None
The emperor drank too much
Bragging
None
Similar to Uncle Zhao
Wei Xiang
None
male
Found it
None
The eldest princess has already been brought out
Placed in Qingyuan Palace
None
Don't say
Your outfit suits you quite well
None
Thank you Mr. Hou
little chamberlain
None
Put that plate of snacks over here
All my dear friends, have you finished drinking?
None
you
Forgive me, Lord Marquis
None
Is Wu'anhou okay?
No problem
None
You stupid slave
How dare you collide with my Marquis Wu An?
None
Pull me down and punish me
yes
None
Your Majesty, please calm down.
At this palace banquet
None
It's better not to see blood
So as not to ruin His Majesty’s interest
None
Still the Marquis of Wu'an is generous?
Go down
None
OK
Marquis Wu'an has already begged for mercy for you, this stupid slave.
None
Why don't you thank me quickly?
Thank you, Your Majesty
None
Xie Wuanhou
What are you doing standing still?
None
Ye Ling, Marquis Wu An, went down to change his clothes.
yes
None
Thank you, Your Majesty
emperor of japan
None
Seems a little excited
cheers
None
Prime Minister stays
Heard about the Battle of Lucheng
None
Thanks to Mr. Xiang for adjusting the food in time
What to transport
None
The last general will replace
Frontier soldiers who died in battle
None
Border residents who died in vain
Here's to you
None
Fan Changyu
Are you toasting or are you rude?
None
Go on
Toast of course
None
If our Prime Minister hadn't taken action,
Just afraid of Lucheng
None
It will be Jinzhou seventeen years ago
Unable to mobilize troops
None
There is no food either
He died at that time
None
I'm afraid it's not just General He
Marquis Wu'an is afraid that he will be like General Xie
None
Tragic death on the city wall
Disemboweled by the enemy
None
I am a pig killer
I'm afraid the outcome will be nothing compared to nothing.
None
Wei Qilin, the traitorous minister
This wine
None
Shouldn't we respect it?
The real person is an official
None
Have a clear conscience
But General Fan
None
Indeed not as good as Wei Qilin
Prime Minister
None
Where is Marquis Wu'an?
The Marquis wants to wake up and sober up.
None
Went towards the Royal Garden.
find him immediately
None
Report to me
yes
None
Fan Aiqing
I also want to toast you
None
Dear friends, thank you for your hard work.
Since I ascended the throne
None
Fortunately, civil and military cooperation
Kuangfu Sheji
None
Only I, Dayin, can have today’s peace
I can’t be considered as living up to the inheritance of my ancestors.
None
I dare not call myself a wise king
But tonight
None
All my dear friends, please be my Dayin’s peace
Drink this cup together
None
His Majesty the Holy Spirit
Your majesty is wise, your majesty is wise.
None
What a fatuous emperor?
You're here
None
I brought the person
empress
None
The sweet-scented osmanthus bloomed
empress
None
The sweet-scented osmanthus bloomed
Bring people here from the cold palace
None
It's not easy
empress
None
on fire
After the fire that year
None
Everyone in the palace is very taboo about this place
So it's safer to hide people here
None
But her whole body
delirious
None
nonsense
And have no clue
None
on fire
empress
None
General Wei Zhonglang
Why are you back again?
None
The queen asks you to run quickly
You run quickly
None
Run quickly, run quickly
Lost
None
Who is the empress?
empress
None
The queen is pregnant
Your Majesty, you cannot hit her
None
Both mother and son will die.
The sweet-scented osmanthus bloomed
None
It’s Concubine Shu Qi
It smells so good
None
This Qingyuan Palace
It was the residence of Concubine Shu before.
None
I planted a lot of sweet-scented osmanthus back then
Osmanthus fragrans
None
empress
Osmanthus fragrans
None
empress
I want to use osmanthus to make incense
None
It smells so good. Who lit the incense?
Who lit incense for the empress?
None
Fell into a trap
Hold your breath
None
Wu'anhou
You and that palace maid have been intoxicated by the aphrodisiac.
None
anyway
You can't escape the crime of filth and chaos in the palace.
None
If you are interested
Just surrender quickly
None
As long as you are obedient
Our Lord
None
I will definitely leave a way for you to survive.
Marquis of Wu'an, Marquis of Wu'an
None
No matter how brave you are
Presumably there is no way to escape
None
This is a clever trick to catch a turtle in an urn, right?
General Fan, help me
None
Your Highness's hiding place must be discovered.
She originally asked me to stay near Qingyuan Palace
None
However, not long after Mr. Hou entered,
Li Xiang led people to surround it.
None
So the servant hurriedly came to report the news
I'm going to Qingyuan Palace
None
You go find Mrs. An
But His Highness said it
None
Never let the Dowager Empress know
I'm just afraid something big is going to happen
None
Only Concubine An can take charge
Go quickly
None
yes
Come on, come on, come on
None
You all come together
Isn’t this person already poisoned?
None
Why are you so good at fighting?
Words correct
None
stand up
Words correct
None
What's going on?
Changyu
None
Why is it so hot?
Why is your hand injured?
None
Changyu
It's too dangerous here
None
come over
quick
None
Go and seal the palace gate
An assassin has broken into the Royal Garden
None
yes
His Majesty
None
Dear Sir, I respect you
Tutor
None
Wei Xiang
Come and love me
None
Where are my Marquis Wu'an and General Hairpin Hua?
All gone
None
Your Majesty is not well
His Majesty
None
Marquis Wu'an was immoral after drinking.
He actually kidnapped a palace maid
None
Desire to do evil
The slave tried to stop
None
But he was beaten out by Wu Anhou
presumptuous
None
Framing an important official of the imperial court
Do you know what the crime is?
None
The slave saw it with his own eyes
Don't dare to make false accusations
None
His Majesty
Is there some misunderstanding in this?
None
It’s better to see is to believe
The master is right
None
You bitch slave
How dare you frame my loyal ministers and good generals?
None
Dear friends
I am here
None
Come and see with me
yes
None
Prime Minister Wei won't come with me to see
I have something important and I need a vote, Your Majesty.
None
The situation is urgent
You can't stop me
None
Master Li's palace banquet has begun
No trespassing without purpose
None
Violators will be dealt with according to palace rules
We are also following orders
None
Please forgive me, Mr. Li.
This is the royal badge given to me by the Holy Emperor to enter the palace of the Li family.
None
I was also invited to be on the list
This is not allowed either
None
Go over there quickly
Go
None
There, there, and there
Search them all carefully for me
None
Calling you useless trash
You are such a big group of people
None
Can't find it
Search carefully for me
None
Supervisor Li is not in good condition, something has gone wrong over there.
not good
None
The oriole behind
Why are you standing there?
None
Didn't you see the fire?
This is because Marquis Wu An wants to destroy the corpse and eliminate all traces of it.
None
Go and put out the fire. Go and put out the fire.
yes
None
this
How could such a good person cause such a big fire?
None
A chamberlain heard
A palace maid shouted that she was a thief
None
Wait until the subordinates arrive
only saw
None
Who did you see?
I saw Marquis Wu An escaping from the palace.
None
He also injured someone
Supervisor Li led his men to chase him.
None
run away
How could you let him escape?
None
His Majesty
Then Xie Zheng not only fornicated the harem
None
I still want to destroy the corpse and eliminate all traces of it
Should be arrested immediately
None
If you encounter resistance, shoot to death.
His Majesty
None
dowager
His Majesty
None
Shu'er is still inside
Shu'er
None
dowager
Shu'er
None
dowager
What are you doing to stop me?
None
Go and save people quickly
The eldest princess is still inside
None
Why are you still standing there?
Why don't you go put out the fire quickly?
None
yes
Go quickly
None
Shu'er
toffee toffee
None
dowager
The fire is too big. You can't go in by yourself.
None
Princess, you better take care of yourself
My own body, concubine
None
Stop talking and let me save you
Wait
None
Gongsun Yin
shut up you
None
and you
How dare you call me that?
None
His Majesty
As soon as this happened
None
I'm just afraid of the Yanzhou Army to which Marquis Wu'an belongs.
Military morale is unstable
None
And that one
General Hairpin who left the table midway
None
Where is the Jizhou Army?
We also need to take action early.
None
So what do you want to do, Mr. Li?
Your Majesty, please allow me to have full authority to handle this matter.
None
Shu'er
The pile of soldiers in front passed by
None
Let's run into the corridor
Don't move
None
Changyu
I like you
None
someone
i really like you
None
who is there
Where are the people chasing me?
None
stop
When has it been?
None
Shu'er
Her Royal Highness the Princess
None
Shu'er
Princess Shuer
None
Shushu'er is out of breath
She, she, is out of anger, Shu'er
None
Quickly announce the imperial physician
yes
None
Shu'er
The eldest princess serves as a witness
None
if still alive
Xie Zheng has room to turn around
None
The man who set fire
What a cruel heart
None
besides
And there's more
None
Gongsun Yin
You are insulting the innocence of the eldest princess
None
Make him unable to live in peace after his death
what do you want to do
None
dowager
Someone once taught me
None
This method can save his life
Let me ask you, is your reputation important now?
None
Life is still important
Save, hurry up, save
None
His Majesty
You are bold
None
What kind of behavior do you have?
Humiliate the eldest princess in public
None
Where is the dignity of such an official?
yes
None
Someone comes and captures him
Let me see who dares to move
None
I killed too many people in the first half of my life
I am here to eat fast and chant Buddha's name
None
Just to save my only daughter
If you can't even save Shu'er's life,
None
I don’t mind killing a few more
The commander of the Jinwu Guards obeys orders
None
The end will be in
Guard all entrances and exits
None
If even half a word of what happened today spreads out,
Someone present has an idea
None
All must die
Take orders
None
Officail website =dramacool.club=
follow me
None
Everyone listens to the concubine
Gongsun
None
I order you to save her
If you can't save Shu
None
You have to die too
Shu'er
None
Shu'er, wake up
Shu'er
None
His Majesty
Although Gongsun Yin saved Her Royal Highness the eldest princess,
None
But this does not prove
Xie Zheng is not guilty
None
Is it an accomplice?
His behavior needs to be determined through interrogation.
None
this
Save the eldest princess tonight
None
He's the imperial doctor from the imperial hospital
No one named Gongsun has ever been here before
None
What does Mrs. An think?
Exactly
None
Today's events
That's it
None
right
That's it
None
This ends today's matter
Shu'er
None
His Majesty
No trace of the thief has been found yet
None
Expanding search scope
Is Your Majesty looking for me?
None
you two
Why are you two together?
None
Why are Aiqing's clothes wet?
I fell drunk into the lotus pond
None
Fortunately, General Hairpin came to his rescue.
Someone coming
None
Go and put some clean clothes on Mr. Hou.
Prepare another bowl of ginger soup
None
yes
Wu'anhou
None
There is a fire in Qingyuan Palace tonight
The eldest princess almost died
None
Someone testified
All because you held the palace maid hostage and caused trouble in the palace
None
I still want to destroy the corpse and eliminate all traces of it
What's your explanation?
None
I beg your Majesty to take a closer look.
Marquis Wu'an is the thief
None
you
I am a thief
None
Aren't you Jinwu Guards catching thieves?
Why is there a second thief?
None
Your Majesty's thief was caught
Bring up
None
yes
Your Li family
None
What a great drama about killing relatives for justice
How could it be you
None
My grandson wanted to confess his feelings to the eldest princess today.
I didn't expect it would cause such a big misunderstanding.
None
It also alarmed His Majesty
Please punish me
None
this
I am the one going to see the eldest princess today
None
Not Marquis Wu'an
Your Majesty, please take a closer look
None
tonight
Why are there so many abruptness and misunderstandings?
None
I am as curious as Your Majesty
I've always had a good drinker
None
I don't know why
I get drunk right now after just one drink
None
Could it be the wine given by His Majesty?
Too strong
None
Those are all fine wines that have been stored in the palace for a long time.
Naturally it will be a little stronger
None
This wine is all
Li Xiang, the slave, prepared it himself
None
Right?
Could it be that you have a different intention?
None
this
good
None
this matter
All done by one slave
None
All because
Marquis Wu'an had insulted his slaves many times before
None
He also cut off one of the slave's ears
so
None
That's why the slave always holds a grudge
want to take this opportunity
None
frame him
The fire in the princess palace
None
It was you who put it too
enough
None
A slave betrays his master
Your Majesty was also enslaved by this person
None
Deceived
His Majesty
None
Someone clearly set a trap tonight
Want to frame Chen and Wu'anhou
None
I was born as a pig butcher
Don't understand any big reason
None
Ke Chen kills the enemy at the border
After many battles, he did not die
None
Now go home
But he was framed by the people around him
None
Your Majesty, please
Tutor
None
Or Wei Xiang
Tell me about this
None
state-owned law
Li Xiang guilty
None
Nature has laws to deal with
This matter has nothing to do with others
None
His Majesty
I don’t know about the Longquan Sword that your Majesty gave me.
None
Can be counted
natural arithmetic
None
you
Your Majesty bestowed upon me the Longquan Sword
None
I will take care of your majesty.
Thank you, Your Majesty
None
Dear friends
They are all my humerus ministers
None
They all made great contributions to Dayin
Tonight's business
None
I will definitely investigate thoroughly
Find the person who did the voting
None
Severe punishment without mercy
It's getting late
None
Dear friends, please come back
Walk
None
grandfather
Li Xiang
None
Wei Xiang
Why don't you go home?
None
seventeen years ago
The late emperor also did this once
None
You and your family
It’s so random
None
last time
If the person here is the late emperor
None
Does the Prime Minister dare to do this to the late Emperor?
Otherwise, Your Majesty
None
How to ascend the throne
Such a long opening
None
You have to go to the hospital
what are you doing
None
Calm down