leaf
None
General Houye's mansion has arrived
Changyu, what are you doing?
None
I miss you
Changyu
None
Don't do this
Calm down
None
Mr. Hou's injury is too serious
So you guys can stay here and watch
None
I'm going to find a doctor
It's useless to see a doctor for this thing.
None
Why is it useless
Why a woman?
None
I don't understand this
Got it
None
I'll go to Goulan Courtyard to find one right away.
What are you looking for?
None
Inside you
I can't explain to you
None
How many of you
Find some sensible people
None
in these four corners
Keep a distance
None
Don't let anyone get close to you
I understand it’s brother
None
go ahead
What about me?
None
Just stop causing trouble and come with me.
Not that
None
I found you
We can't keep fighting
None
You need to know more about life
Which aspect?
None
You calm down first
I'll go find the doctor
None
who I am
Fan Changyu
None
It seems there is no need for me to take action.
This is better
None
The way of heaven is natural
Imperial physician
None
You didn't even look at you
You are the imperial physician
None
Or am I an imperial physician?
I
None
I already told you that you don’t need to see a doctor for this kind of thing.
Why don't you hire a doctor?
None
It's a waste of time
Go, go, go
None
both of you
Walk
None
So what is life?
The emperor got a slap in the face
None
It was not in vain that Gu sent him a big fire.
It's a pity
None
Or let Wu Anhou and Fan Changyu escape the disaster?
Your Li family has a thief
None
Why don't you punish me well?
My grandson
None
Being temporarily bewitched by Wu Anhou and Fan Changyu
Ruined today's plans
None
All this guilt
I bear it for him
None
Too much words
In this way
None
It can be considered isolated.
The possibility of cooperation between Wu Anhou and Qi Sheng
None
Moreover
Give it back to the pig-killing woman
None
Prepared a big gift
If Wei Yan knew
None
You will definitely be very happy
What is it?
None
That's when
The Tiger Talisman of the Northwestern Troop Movement
None
This is the appetizer
The banquet is yet to come
None
please
good
None
please
The properties of the medicine have not been resolved yet
None
I can't do it anymore
I have to get some sleep
None
daughter
Look at me picking a lot of sweet-scented osmanthus
None
Zheng'er is awesome
Let's wait for a while
None
How about using these to make some osmanthus candy?
good
None
smell
daughter
None
Here comes Zheng'er
Come sit down and eat sweet-scented osmanthus cake
None
finally
see you again
None
With you now
To have someone who knows and cares for you
None
My mother is relieved
Remember
None
Mom’s favorite food
This is the osmanthus cake
None
What's wrong
Having a nightmare
None
fine
Just dreaming about some childhood things
None
Changyu
Just let you follow me like this
None
After all, I treated you poorly
Wait until I settle down
None
I will definitely make up a wedding for you
you didn't treat me poorly
None
I am willing to marry Xie Zheng
It can be said that he just joined my family.
None
That was a great wedding too
We haven't signed the divorce papers yet.
None
Don't deny it
admit account
None
One time marriage
Never change for life
None
This is coming to Beijing
It’s really a wave of ups and downs.
None
I just want to hurry now
Clear Daddy's name
None
Hurry back to Lin'an
Live an ordinary life
None
But what happened last night
I'm afraid it's not that simple
None
rest assured
I already have countermeasures
None
Take your time
I thought I would never see you again
None
I thought I was going to die there
Okay, okay
None
Am I not by your side?
Stop crying
None
last night
Did you take care of me here all night?
None
yes
You didn't even get a break
None
then how could you
You saved me yesterday
None
You rush into that sea of ​​fire
I'm afraid you'll die inside
None
Okay, okay, you must be hurt.
Let me take a look
None
Okay, okay
you are weak now
None
Just stop talking
listen to me
None
before
I'm always submissive
None
but this time
I want to say to you
None
after
no matter what happens
None
I will always be by your side
And I can only take care of you
None
This tiger doesn't fit the bill
Fake
None
Prince
This tiger charm is real
None
Prince Chengde and General Xie can't hold on for long.
Jinzhou is in danger
None
For the sake of the country and the country and the thousands of people,
Please send troops to rescue quickly
None
general
Enter
None
What's the matter
Return to the general
None
Guard Jin has been waiting outside the door for a long time.
Make sure you go find him when you wake up
None
knew
you go
None
There is a letter here
Need your help
None
Written by Sister Qian
Tiger Talisman
None
where did it come from
last night
None
There is a messenger
Died at the door of our general's mansion
None
Help
Come quickly
None
dead
You guys bring weapons
None
Look around for anyone suspicious
yes
None
That dream just now
Could it be that somehow
None
God also wants to seek justice for my father.
general
None
There is someone named Thirteenth Niang who wants to see you
Thirteen daughters
None
I'll go with you
No
None
I want to talk to her alone
That bitch has already used the tiger talisman
None
Gave it to Fan Changyu
deal with it
None
yes
You were not drunk that day
None
I love you so much
why are you doing this to me
None
every time i think
You will not leave alone
None
Will I be willing to be alone with you?
This is always the result you are waiting for.
None
Lonely love is so cheap
I can only be ruined by you
None
that's not love
It's possessiveness
None
It's control
I'm going to be the emperor right now
None
No more lonely
you will not be queen
None
you are nothing
I don't care about being a queen at all
None
without you
I will live better
None
If you dare, strangle me to death
Are you okay? Are you okay?
None
I beg you
please tell me
None
As long as you don't leave alone
what do you want
None
I'll give it all to you
i don't want anything
None
I just want to leave you forever
You forced me to do this
None
bring it
yes
None
This is made of fine steel
Swords and axes are all cutting incessantly
None
If you want to escape
One of our hands must be cut off
None
you are crazy
you are really crazy
None
you can't escape
this life
None
You are all alone
I didn't expect you to be alive
None
What do you want from me?
Reward Sui Yuanqing for excellence
None
Now it seems
I'm the only one left who still remembers to avenge him.
None
This is for you
Sui Yuanqing gave it to me
None
And this
I'll leave you a way to survive
None
Take this to find Fan Changyu
I'll give you one
None
Certificate of investment
I gave you the Tiger Talisman
None
He is also dead
I guess
None
He just wants Qi to be
Fall into a place of no return
None
What about you?
what do you want
None
I once thought
You and Xie Zheng are my enemies
None
you killed my brother
Xie Zheng destroyed my Qingfeng Village
None
Later I felt
He cheated on my feelings
None
Let me and Qingfeng Village
Falling into a place of no return
None
But it wasn’t until today that I realized
There are many causes and effects of grudges in the world
None
Revenge can never be fully avenged
Killing and killing
None
Also endless
I leave the Tiger Talisman to you.
None
Take the head, please.
I don't need it anymore
None
You can leave him a whole body
thank you today
None
I will order someone to show you a new way
You will be free from now on
None
Just treat it as
Repaid Ning Niang's kindness
None
But the grudge between you and me
Finish it after I come back
None
I hope to see you next time
you are still alive
None
This is from Sister Qian
I dreamed about dad last night
None
When I woke up I saw this tiger charm
But I don't understand why
None
Why did King Changxin slander my father?
Jinzhou was defeated
None
The deaths of hundreds of thousands of soldiers
Why does it have to be blamed on my father?
None
My parents have obviously been anonymous for more than ten years.
why
None
Why do you still have to be killed?
I want to prove my father's innocence to the world
None
your dad
There are also the Jinzhou soldiers who died in vain
None
All need an explanation
But now
None
Just this pair of tiger charms
It can't be proven at all
None
The initiator of all this was Wei Yan
That crazy palace maid who knew about it
None
Already died in the fire
Nothing can be left in Qingyuan Palace
None
Everyone involved in this matter
They have all been silenced by Wei Yan
None
The crazy official girl’s former master was Concubine Shu
What is the relationship between Concubine Shu and Wei Yan?
None
There were rumors in the palace that they were having an affair.
What happened back then?
None
Are there any clues?
That Qi Sheng
None
Will Qi Sheng know anything?
Don't worry yet
None
Even if Qi Sheng knows anything
He didn't dare to say either
None
He's been a puppet for decades
I have long been afraid of Wei Yan.
None
I definitely won’t dare to pursue it.
now
None
Want to bring down Wei Yan
Let him plead guilty
None
Only hard ones
I called him uncle for more than 20 years
None
I know his character very well
Just afraid
None
He has already started to raise troops
Don't worry
None
I will summon all the main forces of Xie Jiajun
Give it back to your father
None
I want to give my father justice
We have finally reached this point.
None
In this case
Then act in advance
None
Pass the order
Send troops back to Beijing immediately
None
yes
obey orders
None
You regard Fan Changyu as a criminal
News about Wei Qilin's daughter spread
None
The sooner the better
yes
None
Hairpin General
Those who tamper with the drums
None
According to the regulations, you must first parade on the streets to show the public
Let the people criticize and discuss
None
Fang has to beat the drum to clear up the injustice
it's her
None
Come and see everyone
it's her
None
She is the daughter of the traitorous minister
There is no good person in your Wei family
None
My father died in the battle in Jinzhou
Make her pay with her life
None
What nonsense are you talking about?
Mouth full of feces
None
What nonsense are you talking about? Is there any evidence?
Stop talking nonsense
None
My sister is innocent
Father
None
Mother
Unfilial child
None
May the spirits of the two elders be in heaven
forgive children
None
beat her to death
I'm going to tear your mouth apart by talking nonsense again
None
Great traitor
Wei Qilin
None
Press grain and grass
disloyal
None
Ruining the lives of 100,000 heroic souls
beat her to death
None
call me
beat her to death
None
Sister
Lao Fan
None
Who threw it
Well smashed
None
It's not over, right?
stop
None
My father is Wei Qilin
But he is not a traitor
None
He was wronged
That was your father, your father killed you
None
Of course you said he was innocent
that is
None
hit her
It's not over, right?
None
beat her to death
Officials handling cases
None
Idle people waiting to retreat
Back
None
are you okay
Officail website =dramacool.club=
None
you fart
Hairpin General
None
I think he's a traitor general
Shut up
None
Have all of you seen it with your own eyes?
You confirm what you heard and saw
None
Is that the truth of the matter?
We will accompany you too
None
the rest of the way
I go by myself
None
Take this step
But there is no way out
None
let me go
I am Qingping County
None
Fan Changyu, Xigu Lane, Lin'an Town
This trip
None
Come here to complain
accuser
None
If what you tell is false
That's deceiving the king
None
Immediate execution without pardon
Have you thought clearly?
None
Think clearly
My trip
None
sue the world for injustice
Wei Qilin
None
You are a big traitor who is worse than a pig or a dog.
Traitor feeds the dog
None
Let him feed the dog
hit him
None
Second, the king is not clear
who is beating the drum
None
His Majesty
It’s General Hairpin who beats the Dengwen drum
None
He said he wanted to file a complaint
Didn’t Mrs. Li say that
None
Can Xie Zheng and Fan Changyu be used to deal with Wei Yan?
This is a crapshoot for him
None
This is all a knock on Denwen's drum.
three reports
None
Traitors are in power
I am Fan Changyu
None
Today I want to avenge my father.
Zheng'er
None
This is the sweet-scented osmanthus cake made by my mother.
you have to remember
None
My mother’s favorite food
This is the osmanthus cake
None
The third brother's personal greetings are as good as his face
Waiting for your triumphant return and letter
None
The concubine is probably pregnant
I just wish there was an afterlife
None
You are a commoner
I am a Mulan boat
None
Rong Yin's last work
Turns out to be brother
None
Return to Beijing halfway
Jinzhou fell
None
So Linshan’s death
It was also caused by my brother.
None
Zheng'er
The current situation is turbulent
None
The soldiers of the Xie family threatened each other with their lives
Asking my brother to reveal the truth about the Jinzhou case
None
My mother was caught in it and she couldn't help herself.
Maybe only one death
None
Only then can this dispute be settled
I would also like to use this to awaken my brother’s conscience
None
Let you live
Zheng'er
None
Don't miss me
Mom can’t grow up with you anymore
None
Mother
Unfilial child
None
I didn’t understand until so late
Your good intentions
None
Stop knocking
The eldest princess arrives
None
Imperial younger brother
His Majesty
None
Royal sister
I know what you want to say
None
But at this time
This is not the time for you to talk about sisterly love
None
The emperor must go to court
To listen to the opinions or grievances of subjects
None
Changyu’s grievances
It has been amplified by those who are interested
None
This matter is now known to the whole world
Emperor brother, you can't hide from me
None
Imperial younger brother
You designed to frame Xie Zheng
None
Almost hurt my life
I haven't settled this matter with you yet.
None
But if you can show your imperial momentum
Call the shots and clear up the grievances
None
I'll cancel this matter with you
Imperial younger brother
None
Those who value themselves
Show off the momentum of your ninth-five-year-old master
None
Are you going to be a puppet emperor all your life?
Someone coming
None
Summon Fan Changyu to see him in court
Chongde Hall
None
I'm going to be the emperor
The unjust case in Jinzhou seventeen years ago
None
Wei Qilin was framed
Today, I, Fan Changyu, am willing to risk my life
None
implore the emperor
justice
None
This is Wei Qilin
The tiger talisman that went to Chongzhou to ask for help
None
this is the truth
But at that time, King Chang Xin
None
He said the tiger charm was fake
Refusing to send troops
None
This led to the Jinzhou tragedy
visible
None
Someone deliberately delayed the military plane
Xie Jia Wei Jia
None
They were all framed
If found to be true
None
Fan Aiqing
How do you want me to punish you?
None
This is a fake
Simply shameless
None
Why do you say it's false?
Why
None
Just by the people present
The only one who was present at the tragedy
None
Only the truth
You said this thing is real
None
What evidence is there?
Although the last general is a new general who has just marched to fight,
None
But also know
All tiger charms must be kept on file
None
There is a mark as evidence
Can be compared
None
All paper files
They were all destroyed by the fire seventeen years ago
None
How could there be such a coincidence
It's such a coincidence
None
Still know the truth
Why are you obsessed with this?
None
just because
That's just selfish of yours
None
This is
Revealed the woman’s true identity
None
Your Majesty, please take a look
Wei Qilin escaped from battle
None
die a violent death
The only fish that slipped through the net
None
it's you
Wei Changyu, daughter of Wei Qilin
None
Wei Yan
Stop confusing the public here.
None
I, Fan Changyu, have no shame in my heart
Wei Changyu
None
Not subject to national law at that time
I came to the court today to confuse the public.
None
Attempting to disrupt our country in Dayin
His heart can be killed
None
His Majesty
The truth is that today I want to impeach this remnant of the Wei family.
None
punishable by death
To sacrifice this
None
Jinzhou City’s one hundred thousand officers and soldiers are the spirit in heaven
Who is the remnant?
None
My Lords
If my father is really a wicked person
None
General He Jingyuan, a close aide of Prime Minister Wei
Why do we correspond with him?
None
And want to protect the lives of my two sisters
I would like to ask Mr. Wei
None
If my father
He really became a traitor
None
Who is the last beneficiary?
who is
None
General Fan is right
I'd like to ask
None
A case that year
Who is the biggest beneficiary?
None
Hear Your Majesty
The tragedy of Jinzhou seventeen years ago must be re-examined
None
This case concerns my father Xie Linshan
Prince Chengde
None
And one hundred thousand heroic souls
If the investigation is restarted
None
How can I be absent?
This country's revenge has not been avenged
None
Unresolved family feud
today
None
But you ask for credit for this sinner’s daughter
The matter of burning the palace has not yet been resolved
None
You still defend it
Could it be
None
Do you also have a disobedient heart?
Having a disloyal heart
None
I'm afraid it's someone else.
this letter
None
It was the letter for help that Concubine Shu wrote to Wei Yan.
Wei Yan has an affair
None
Returning to Beijing without permission
Throw Jinzhou soldiers in front of the battle
None
final
Cause catastrophe
None
Thief shouts "Catch the thief"
Wei Yan
None
You are the biggest traitor in the Jinzhou War
There are also our people in the Jinwu Guard.
None
This palace gate can be broken down without attacking
I have already spread the news to Qintian Prison
None
There have been droughts and floods over the years
It's all dragon vein rebellion
None
Caused by improper succession
Succession is what the people want
None
The wishes of the ministers
good
None
Seventeen years
I finally returned to this place