this letter
None
It was the letter for help that Concubine Shu wrote to Wei Yan.
Wei Yan has an affair
None
Returning to Beijing without permission
Throw Jinzhou soldiers in front of the battle
None
final
Cause catastrophe
None
Thief shouts "Catch the thief"
Wei Yan
None
You are the biggest traitor in the Jinzhou War
This is Qi Rongyin’s letter
None
seventeen years
you should have forgotten
None
Let me read it for you
Third brother
None
Shut up when you see the words
Wei Changyu can fight if he wants to
None
Don't insult the innocence of the deceased woman
It seems that Prime Minister Wei still has someone he cares about.
None
seventeen years ago
My mother wrote this letter
None
Hidden in the candy box you gave her
so many years
None
You have done all the bad things
That's why you feel so guilty
None
I don’t even dare to touch this candy box.
Dare I ask Prime Minister Wei?
None
These seventeen years
Have you ever confessed to my father
None
Have you ever been pitiful?
Thousands of dead soldiers
None
Have you ever mourned
My sister who committed suicide helplessly
None
seal of approval
Counterfeit Tiger Talisman
None
Do you just want to discredit the truth?
Because of this, Prime Minister Wei believed
None
Are there still few mouths that have been exterminated?
If Concubine Shu knew something under the spring
None
Shut up for your evil deeds
Don't mention her
None
I want to confirm whether this tiger charm is real or fake.
Not difficult either
None
The tiger talisman is an important weapon of the country
Need to keep a file with the Ministry of War
None
Although the file has been burned
But the person who made the tiger talisman
None
Tao Taifu is still alive
Prime Minister Wei will know as soon as he asks
None
Tao Taifu arrives
The old minister bows to your majesty
None
No gift for your love
Thank you, Your Majesty
None
Tao Taifu was one of the few people who experienced it
After all, we have to save the royal face
None
Please tell me, Aiqing,
Is this military symbol real or fake?
None
obedience to ministers
Your Majesty's Majesty
None
At that time, the veteran personally supervised the production of this military talisman
There are marks on it
None
This is the real thing
Mutually
None
What else can you say
You can be the queen soon
None
Wei Yan
You are so ambitious
None
Bullying the king and disregarding superiority
His crime deserves to be punished
None
Jinwuwei
exist
None
take it down
yes
None
Wei Yan you
Qi's children
None
See if you dare
Yigui, you can’t make the same mistake again and again.
None
newspaper
Your Majesty is not well
None
Rebellious thieves follow Yuanhuai
A large army has been sent to attack Dayin Gate.
None
What
How did you get in?
None
The day has finally arrived
He really knows how to choose the day
None
The grudge between you and my uncle and nephew
Must end
None
before that
Wait until I put down the rebellion first
None
Walk
everyone
None
kill me
Welcome back to the palace
None
Seventeen years
Gu finally found his own place
None
His Highness Shigetori Daiho
It is indeed God’s will.
None
destiny
shallow
None
how
The promise I gave you
None
I did it alone
you crazy
None
Do you think I really want to be your queen?
Just go ahead and dream
None
you will agree
Promoted brother
None
I've been sitting in this position for more than ten years
Very comfortable to sit on
None
Imperial brother
I've been waiting for you here for a long time
None
The jade seal is here
It's all yours
None
Please don’t kill me, brother emperor
Dayin has a idiot like you as its emperor
None
Are you worthy of the torture you have endured over the years?
Keep it
None
wait and see
yes
None
don't kill me
Is he really going to be the emperor?
None
Announcement that there is a movement in the direction of the gate
I'm afraid there are reinforcements coming outside the palace.
None
not good
Fell into a trap
None
Li Xing colluded with the rebels and planned to rebel against Yuan Huai
Such rebellious officials and traitors
None
When all are caught and brought to justice
Wei old man
None
Don't think
You only have this few people
None
can stop His Highness’s Fifth Army Camp
Isn't this enough?
None
Just this few people
Let’s talk about the sword of Marquis Wu An
None
I’m not sure who it’s for.
Since Marquis Wu'an has also come to join in the fun,
None
It’s better to cooperate together
I have detained the shameful emperor
None
It's better to be alone
After all, Gu is the bloodline of Prince Chengde
None
together
·You secretly colluded with Beijue
None
·Intention to take advantage of the opportunity to force Dayin
I really thought I didn't notice anything
None
Since Prince Yi Chengde
But forgot the former East Palace
None
The bravery of the Northern Jue who vowed not to surrender to the death
I thank you
None
How can I surrender to you?
What
None
How dare you collude with Beijue in private?
Handing over the rivers and mountains of Dayin to the barbarians
None
There is no turning back when the bow is drawn
Mr. Li, it's too late for you to regret it.
None
you
What Wei Xiang did was much more extreme than being alone.
None
The fall of Jinzhou
Citizens were massacred
None
The twelve counties of Liaodong were ceded to the barbarians.
It's all because of him Wei Yan
None
Desire to get involved in the Dayin River caused by mountain hands
Being alone is just the endgame that he has not finished yet
None
Just finished walking
you
None
Wei Xiang
seventeen years ago
None
You bloodbathed the palace
I thought no one knew
None
Are you messing with the palace affairs?
You bastard pretending to be a royal family
None
Still here talking nonsense and fabricating facts
Who is telling lies?
None
You, Wei Yan, know it better than anyone else, right?
take him down
None
All the rebellious officials and traitors present in the country today
Kill them all without mercy
None
Look, Prime Minister Wei
Your wife and children are here
None
I can't guarantee
If your people dare to step forward
None
Their heads fell to the ground
I didn’t expect Prime Minister Wei to be so cold-blooded
None
Then let Mrs. Wei
And Mr. Wei
None
Go to hell first
kill me
None
kill
Don't kill me
None
Can I make you a general?
ok
None
If you keep arguing, I'll kill you, you dog emperor.
It's time to make a break
None
Mutually
This is between our nephews and uncles
None
You all don't have to step back.
Your swordsmanship has improved a lot.
None
I want to use my father's sword skills
For me and Changyu’s parents
None
The former East Palace. There are also the soldiers who died tragically in Jinzhou.
seek justice
None
OK
bring it on
None
Just give up
things that don't belong to you
None
you'll never get it
You see, this country originally belonged to Gu.
None
I am lonely
How do you like it
None
Like it or not
No more
None
It's hard to be an emperor
I don’t want to be the emperor anymore
None
you are really crazy
Gu is not crazy
None
I chose to live because of you
for me
None
good
If I die you won't be crazy anymore
None
I won't allow you to die
Qi Yan
None
Let go of Sister Qian
Changyu
None
You don't have to worry about me
I can't escape
None
let me go
Otherwise I will kill you
None
Changyu
Just let it go
None
The matter between me and him shouldn't involve you.
I want imperial power
None
Want you too
But finally
None
But both hands are empty
Let go
None
you will kill her
He won't let go
None
He will never learn to let go in his life
you are selfish
None
brutal
moody
None
This is all your disguise
You're just hiding your fear
None
You are a poor person
Is lonely love so cheap?
None
I can only be ruined by you
that's not love
None
It's possessiveness and control
i don't want anything
None
I just want to leave you forever
for you
None
I am willing to learn once
Xuan'er
None
This arrow
It's to repay your kindness for saving my mother-in-law.
None
my dad
Not you bastard
None
Xuan'er
Jizhou Army Xie Jiajun has arrived
None
No worries in the forbidden palace
The soldiers who followed Qi and Wei in their rebellion
None
Listen to me all
Those who lay down their weapons and surrender
None
exempt from death penalty
Resistant person
None
All were punished for treason
Zhu Lian Jiu Clan
None
prime minister
So defeated
None
Do you still want to fight to the death?
Jiuheng
None
It really didn't disappoint me
Prime Minister
None
Retreat
We'll escort you out
None
No more
lost
None
Just lost
As early as seventeen years ago, I embarked on this road of no return.
None
Today's fruit
It's already doomed
None
Keep it
Let's go, Mr. Xiang
None
it's over
all this
None
It's over
it's over
None
We will live better in the future
If there really is an afterlife
None
I'll pick you up instead
Marquis
None
Mrs. Wei is here
lady
None
please
aunt
None
Zheng'er
aunt
None
What do you mean by this? Get up quickly.
Zheng'er
None
My aunt wants to ask for Zheng'er
Save the prime minister's life
None
Sit first
aunt
None
He doesn't even care about the lives of your mother and son.
Why do you need to plead for him?
None
What's more, the national law does not allow
The Prime Minister is not a heinous person
None
If there is no Prime Minister
Xuan'er and I
None
He's dead a long time ago
What does this mean?
None
Xuan'er's father
He's a subordinate of the Prime Minister
None
Xuan'er's father and I have a private life-long marriage
But his father died in battle
None
people at home
You want to take me back and soak me in a pig cage
None
It was Mr. Xiang who saved me
Prime Minister said
None
Xuan'er's father is his old subordinate
Anyway, he will never marry again in this life.
None
But the family is busy
It just so happened that the baby in my belly and I
None
Already cornered
He said it was the best of both worlds
None
The Prime Minister treats our mother and son
Kindness is as heavy as a mountain
None
Zheng'er
Please look at Xuan'er for you
None
Take a few servings to block an arrow
Save the Prime Minister’s life
None
aunt
He doesn't take a wife
None
But for the sake of Concubine Shu Qi
The Prime Minister is thinking deeply
None
I don't know
Zheng'er
None
If it is really unacceptable under the national law
I beg you, for the sake of your uncle and nephew.
None
The whole body of the Prime Minister
General Hairpin has arrived
None
Changyu
how are you
None
Is the injury okay?
I am fine
None
Come here
mother concubine
None
Empress Dowager
Wei Yan was captured
None
The emperor's brother is stupid
This day has changed
None
You keep hiding it
What's the point
None
The sky has indeed changed
from seventeen years ago
None
It has already changed
When Concubine Shu Qi first entered the palace,
None
He's just a person with a very weak personality
Never compete for favor in front of the Holy One
None
Until she was diagnosed with Hi Pulse
The imperial physician determines the month of pregnancy
None
It actually doesn’t match the Shangshu’s introspection records.
Concubine Shuzhen had an affair with Wei Yan
None
Qi Rongyin is three months pregnant
Push days forward
None
She must have been conceived around the Mid-Autumn Festival
At the Mid-Autumn Festival banquet that year
None
Wei Yan got drunk at the palace banquet
Immorality after drinking
None
He insulted a palace maid
Unfortunately, I called the late emperor who went to admire the moon.
None
Confronted with the courtiers
Just a palace maid
None
The late emperor had a bad attack on the spot
Then he gave the palace maid to Wei Yan
None
royal ruthless
After Concubine Shu was found to be pregnant
None
Tortured every night
Until the night of Laba
None
Qingyuan Palace suddenly went bankrupt
Wei adult
None
The Jinwu Guards who went on patrol
Rush to put out the fire
None
But found Wei Yan
There was no imperial edict to go to Beijing
None
Appeared in the forbidden palace
roll
None
Zhao Xun once confessed
It is said that the fire in the palace was started by the Crown Princess of Chengde
None
Is there a hidden secret in it?
Have you ever seen fire water thrown into a fire?
None
Does the tongue of fire lick higher?
I have seen it
None
The fire was filled with the smell of tung oil
Miyagi is under siege
None
The sound of fighting is loud
Just like the day before yesterday
None
Later, the doctor who treated me became self-conscious.
Leave a suicide note
None
Concubine Shu is not pregnant at all
so
None
The person who set the fire was the Crown Princess of Chengde
The one who burned Concubine Shu to death
None
It's the late emperor
Thank you, Empress Dowager
None
Tell me about this past incident
Jiuheng, are you here to see your uncle off?
None
It’s me who came to meet with Prime Minister Wei
Finish the unplayed chess game
None
The brat’s father, General Xie, died tragically in Jinzhou
This happened back then
None
He wants an answer no matter what
It was obviously a trap set up by the late emperor
None
Why do you Yigui have to bear the infamy in this life?
What are you planning?
None
This chess game
Wei Xiang couldn’t be more familiar, right?
None
Have you thought about it?
If you haven't thought about it
None
Please allow me to take a nap for a while
Third brother
None
You're cheating
I promised that I would only use the power of three successes to accompany me for entertainment.
None
You are obviously
Go all out to encircle, suppress and intercept
None
I did only use 30% of my strength.
Then just say it
None
I'm not good at chess
Not as good as third brother
None
No more rain
Okay, I'll take another step
None
let me think about it
How to lose beautifully with 30% of your strength
None
What’s so hard about losing chess?
Let me help my brother
None
Little sister, don't make trouble
Brother, you have a stupid head
None
Be careful if you win again, your sister-in-law will be angry and run away.
I said you guys are playing chess here
None
I'm here to join in the fun, too.
No gift, no gift
None
Hurry, sit, sit, sit
If this chess piece is left alone and helpless,
None
Need to work quickly to activate it
This chess game is like life
None
You should be willing to give up
Chess is like life
None
When willing
Tutor
None
this is what you said
So far
None
Don't play charades with me anymore
I never believed it
None
It was you who planned the Jinzhou Massacre
But why did you rush back to Beijing at that time?
None
What the hell is going on
Remember that New Year’s Eve eighteen years ago
None
Osmanthus banquet in the East Palace
Officail website =dramacool.club=
None
Tutor
You were also present
None
that night
I was young and frivolous
None
Sows the seeds of verbal misfortune
Today is New Year's Eve
None
You are specially invited to come
Try the sweet-scented osmanthus wine brewed by Donggong
None
Winter wine
Venison grilled
None
Isn't it wonderful?
Thank you
None
This osmanthus wine
Mellow and tangy
None
Really good wine
Come to His Majesty the Prince
None
Another toast to you
Thank you, General. Thank you, General.
None
Did you get permission today?
Just open it and drink it
None
I advise you to drink less.
Leave some for us guys to taste, right?
None
Zhonglang Jiang is absolutely right.
There are so many mountains and seas
None
You drink without restraint
We don't have anything to drink.
None
You
Tutor
None
Just osmanthus wine
As long as you like it
None
Enough
good
None
Drink, we have wine to drink
Come, come, come
None
This delicious food and wine
Loyal minister and wise king
None
Treat each other as close friends
This is the greatest pleasure in life
None
Qilin brother
This may be the last time for you and me
None
Go to Jinzhou
Brother He
None
Poverty in the northwest border
Jinzhou, Chongzhou and Jizhou are particularly poor.
None
You must take more care when you go this time.
A good man should make achievements
None
Better than being in Beijing
It's good to flatter the powerful and powerful by nodding and bowing.
None
What a pity
Can't wait until my eldest nephew is born
None
eldest niece
like girls
None
Brother He, you read more books than me
Please give your eldest niece a name.
None
Why don't you let your lord-in-law name him?
The official position of General Zhonglang is too high
None
I'm afraid my child won't be able to bear it
Great sacrificial wine
None
This Jiu Heng of my family is also very smart.
When can he come to your Imperial College?
None
Ask for a book and read it
Xie Zheng is still a child
None
you are uncle
I’m not in a hurry yet when I give birth to a father.
None
Who says I'm not in a hurry?
You don't know
None
This guy is disgusted with cats and dogs now
Be naughty all day long
None
Not gonna lie to you
I immediately want to send him to the Imperial College
None
Let you teach him well
Long jade.
None
right
Wei Changyu
None
Long-term wish to inherit the beauty day
Jade steps spring grass fragrance
None
how how
This name is good
None
Come back, I will take my eldest niece to kowtow to you.
Good wine
None
Next year the general will lead his troops to guard Jinzhou
If the general does not give up
None
Walking alone
Go to the national disaster together
None
His Royal Highness's safety
It is related to the stability of the DPRK and the country.
None
Don't be hasty
yes
None
The son of a rich man cannot sit down in the hall
Your Highness, please think twice.
None
You don’t know something
Floods in the South this summer
None
Go to disaster relief alone
But the Jia family obstructed everything
None
The victims are suffering unspeakably
Father is furious
None
but not chasing
The Mistake between the Sixteenth Prince and the Jia Family
None
blame alone
Ineffective disaster relief
None
over the years
My father was very harsh on Gu, especially
None
To the Jia family and the sixteenth prince
Tolerant
None
Lonely and confused
Maybe
None
Just stay away from the court
Contributions to the frontier
None
Only then can one be lonely
final way out
None
Trivial matters at home
Let you all
None
Funny
His Highness is both benevolent and virtuous
None
Wisdom and courage
He is the perfect candidate for succession
None
I don't understand
Why is the Holy One so biased?
None
This Your Majesty is immoral
Then let him take the Zen position