This Your Majesty is immoral
None
Then let him take the Zen position
Yigui
None
Be careful
What I said today
None
solitary
With all my dear friends
None
Unheard of
continue drinking
None
shared
This moment is beautiful
None
That Zen sentence back then
Only a few of us, God knows
None
Could it be
Someone else snitched
None
I'm not confused
The late emperor had too much power and power.
None
So that the people are in dire straits
He was afraid again
None
The prince's virtue spread far and wide
So I deliberately supported
None
The Jia family and the sixteenth prince
If it were that year
None
Thanks to the three families of Wei and Qi
Pushing the Prince of Chengde to the Dragon Throne
None
Is the political Qing harmonious?
Prince Chengde
None
too indecisive
Lost the opportunity
None
The prince and Linshan died in battle
Where are you, Taifu?
None
Depressed all day long and unable to reuse
you say
None
Would I report myself?
At that time, Prince Chengde said
None
Although Li Xing was born in a pure family,
But obsessed with power
None
Could it be
So
None
When the prince decided to go to Jinzhou
This is destined to be a dead end.
None
The prince is faint
Prefer to listen to words
None
You actually tried to take me and replace me
What do you think, Aiqing?
None
The Holy One has his own discretion
I'm far away in the northwest
None
I don’t know the middle and the end of the dynasty
Don't dare to lie
None
For the sake of Jiangshan Sheji
I
None
You can only do the unbearable things
My nephew is willing to lend a helping hand
None
You are the son of my royal sister
Has half the blood of my Qi family
None
His Majesty's intention is
I am willing to work with you all over the world
None
May we be married forever
The late emperor made a false promise to King Chang Xin
None
Let him refuse to send troops
To eliminate parents and children
None
Not hesitate to lure the wolf into the house
It's really unethical
None
late emperor
Write to me in fake Rongyin handwriting
None
Forced me to turn back to Beijing on the way to rescue
Third brother
None
Run while the fire is strong now.
No
None
Let's go together
Mr. Wei, you
None
If I don't stop trying to survive
They are the treacherous ministers and thieves who are causing trouble in the palace.
None
My Wei family
The nine tribes will inevitably be implicated
None
roll
Third brother
None
You go first
Yoon
None
Don't worry, I have everything here
Thank you, Qi, and the three generations of Wei for being loyal to Dayin
None
Fighting until the flesh and bones wither
Why is that dog emperor?
None
Play with us in the palm of your hand
What happened next
None
The master should probably know this.
I bloodbathed the palace
None
If there is no uterine change
How do you want me to deal with it?
None
After Rong Yin passed away
I can only pinch that dog emperor's neck
None
Forced him to write an edict to abdicate.
I am the only one in charge of the government
None
Only then can Dayin be kept from chaos
The country will not be destroyed
None
Wei Qilin’s infamy
That's why I had to install it
None
Just because of this late emperor
Calculated too carefully
None
Before returning to Beijing, I will bring the tiger talisman
Leave it to my most trusted subordinate Wei Qilin
None
Let him recruit troops for support on my behalf
The tiger charm is fake
None
Not on
Everything was planned by the late emperor
None
Later I was confused by Qi
Zheng'er reexamines an old case in Jinzhou seventeen years ago
None
Unexpectedly, I learned that Wei Qilin's family was still alive
Only silence
None
Only in this way can we preserve the friendship between our uncle and nephew.
who would have thought
None
Man’s calculation is not as good as God’s calculation
Zheng'er was actually saved by that girl Fan
None
God's will
Seriously
None
The emperor wields power and his loyal ministers die in vain
so
None
After all, I still lost.
Do you want to go in?
None
Let's go
fortunately
None
Xie Zheng this knife
Found his scabbard
None
Fan Changyu
Let me borrow a word from Chang Yu, too.
None
Be a good pig in this life
afterlife
None
Be a good person
people like me
None
I'm afraid I'll fall into hell
There will be no afterlife
None
Trojan horse
Run
None
The little boy is very ambitious
Sword-holding battle song therapy
None
Want to drive you all away
It's morning
None
Dear friends
What do you want to tell me about?
None
Mr. Wei, why are you kneeling down?
Am I so scary?
None
That’s all
If you have nothing to do today, just leave the court.
None
It seems that this country
In the end, you can only count on me
None
Count on me Count on me
Imperial younger brother
None
Let's see what delicious food I bring you.
All your favorite food
None
Plum preserves
And your favorite osmanthus cake
None
Come and have a bite
delicious delicious
None
Eat slowly and don't choke.
tasty
None
Imperial younger brother
You still recognize it clearly
None
who am i
Imperial younger brother
None
What did you say
I am wise to
None
What did you say
I thought you wouldn't come
None
I always give you the last ride
you will break your promise
None
I won't
It's hard for you
None
He even made a special trip to make a cup of soup for me.
Take the trouble
None
ordinary death row inmate
On the execution ground
None
You also need to eat a decapitation meal, right?
You feed me
None
Don't waste your time
What's wrong
None
Can't bear it
The heat is holding up well
None
Just let it cool down a bit
did you know
None
When did I
Really happy with you
None
Know
But if I could do it again
None
I will definitely not fish you out
You are the only-
None
After seeing my face
A person who is not afraid
None
Reward you
I'm still in you
None
Saw what I've longed for
comfortable
None
You originally had it too
right in front of you
None
But it's covered by your mask
Thank you
None
no sooner said than done
you hate me so much
None
But it still went as I wanted
Yu Qianqian
None
I really like you
therefore
None
If there is another life
I hope
None
we no longer meet
Is there any more?
None
Don't waste it
Finally
None
You once told Gu
you are dead
None
can go back
I want to know
None
who are you
Lonely ghost
None
Fairy in trouble
Tell me
None
You have to understand if you want to die alone
I am who I am
None
My name is Yu Qianqian
you
None
you liar
Are you okay?
None
Changyu
i have a secret
None
I come from a place far, far away
I may not be able to go back
None
If it's too far
We won't go back
None
Let’s go back to Lin’an
live a good life
None
Let's go
Yongping 18th year
None
Yu's Bao'er's name was officially included in the Royal Jade Collection
His mother, Queen Mother Yu, changed his name to Qi Yu
None
In the middle of spring of that year, the new emperor Jianzuo changed the Yuan Dynasty to Yongxing.
Honoring birth mother Yu as Empress Dowager Mingde
None
Granted the right to listen behind the curtain
Posthumously granted the title of Huaihua Lang General
None
Wei Qilin is the loyal and brave uncle
Therefore, General Meng Shuyuan was named Wu Suhou
None
Xie Zheng, Marquis of Wu'an, was specially appointed as regent.
cardinal general
None
Promote Fan Changyu to Huaihua General
Conferred the title of First-class Dame Protector of the Country
None
Assisting the government together
The new emperor Chong Ling ascended the throne
None
The Three Lords Stand in Dignity
Both the government and the public look forward to
None
Qingping within the country
Long live
None
Long live long live long live long live
Don't forget what you promised me
None
The Queen Mother is not here
Hurry up and eat more
None
Sister Changning, don’t worry
I will be in power in the future
None
Will not touch the regent and general Huaihua
Only an incompetent emperor is jealous of his ministers
None
Wait until you take power in the future
Can you give me a princess?
None
Do you want to be a princess?
Like the imperial doctor sister
None
So majestic
I will hire a consort from now on
None
He had to use all his family's wealth as a betrothal gift.
This world belongs to me
None
No one has more wealth than me
Do you want to be my queen?
None
You want to use the palace as a betrothal gift for me?
Not only the palace, but also the country
None
country
what is
None
that is
From where your sister fought
None
Come to this palace
to the boundary further south
None
It's all mine
You became my queen
None
These are all yours
Such a dog
None
It takes several days to fly to Jiji.
You can't regret it
None
Let's pull a hook
Hook hanging
None
No change allowed for a hundred years
Who is lying and who is a puppy
None
Qi Yu, how many times have you given snacks to others today?
Are you not afraid of getting cavities?
None
come out
come here
None
you really are now
You're becoming more and more disobedient, aren't you?
None
Fairy sister, don’t hit me
Changning, please be obedient.
None
Do you know that you are now
A few cavities have killed you
None
Dare to run
come here
None
come over you
You practice calligraphy and calligraphy while I am lazy
None
You dare to eat sweets?
Come here
None
Tap
Be careful when searching your home
None
Go and stand over there
grandfather
None
Battle of Dayin
The treasury was empty due to the Northern Jue
None
Our Li family donated all their belongings
It can also be regarded as meritorious service.
None
The Holy Emperor and the Regent will keep their word
Let bygones be bygones
None
Grandpa, feel at ease
Take care of yourself until old age
None
What do you mean by taking care of yourself?
But that's it
None
Confiscated and exiled
What the Li family committed was a heinous crime.
None
This is the best result
If they don't show mercy
None
Just afraid of the Li family
Nine tribes have been implicated
None
I'm a villain in vain
I was seventeen years ago
None
It’s useless to be a villain
Literary threshold
None
Do you take it seriously
Asking to be demoted to the frontier
None
Go to that bitter cold place to suffer
perhaps
None
This is the best arrangement of fate
Changyu is back
None
Changyu girl
Changyu is back
None
Fan Niangzi
Changyu girl
None
Changyu
Fan Niangzi
None
General Huaihua is polite.
please
None
General Huaihua
My daughter is back
None
back
Lady Fan is back
None
Sister
you are back
None
Huaihua General Fan Niangzi
Changyu girl
None
Sister Changyu
back
None
Fan Yatou is back
this moment
None
Been waiting for a long time
I hope the children will come back soon
None
Old lady, please be on your way soon
Changyu and the others have their own destiny
None
It'll be fine for sure
You men
None
How do you know how to be a mother?
The feeling of having your heart and liver ripped away
None
Our face is so big
Let's go and be parents to General Huaihua.
None
What are you thinking about?
uncle aunt
None
Old man, listen
we are back
None
Is it Ning Niang’s voice?
Do you think they want magic evidence?
None
uncle aunt
you listen
None
What should I listen to?
uncle aunt
None
real
they are really back
None
someone
uncle aunt
None
Changyu
Changyu is back
None
uncle
aunt
None
Dark
Lose weight, you kid
None
you suffered
It's good to come back
None
Godmother
godfather
None
I'm back with all my heart
I will be filial to my father and mother from now on
None
never separate again
I also want to honor you
None
Changyu
What do you call us two?
None
Changyu is on his way back
Been thinking about it
None
Want to change my mind
I hope the two elders can make it happen
None
good
How can we both have such blessings?
None
It’s fine if you don’t leave or don’t leave.
No matter how big an official we see outside,
None
What a world
How can there be a better home?
None
How can there be no better parents, my child?
Don't separate the children
None
We will never be separated again
Uncle Zhao Aunt Zhao
None
we are back
Uncle and auntie, we are all back
None
From now on, we will serve you two elders together.
gold ingot
None
mature
Get up quickly
None
Full warehouse
You are still so strong
None
Full house
aunt
None
The ground is full
Still missing one
None
Godmother
All over him
None
Can't come back
Why is one missing?
None
good boy
Just come back
None
kai kai kai yakuya
Come
None
Go home to Changning
daughter
None
His Majesty
You should call the Queen Mother Queen Mother
None
Mother, come here
What's wrong
None
Queen Mother, I want to announce a decree
Give sister Changning a queen
None
Then you have to ask
Sister Changning, are you willing?
None
Last time, sister Changning asked me if I wanted to be a princess.
I don't want to
None
I made her a queen
Sister Changning has already agreed
None
We even pulled the hook
That won't work either
None
Why
Because you are all still too young now
None
You can't get married until you grow up
Wait until after your crowning ceremony
None
You go ask Changning again
good
None
It's snowing
three quarters to noon
None
It was the time for Wei Yan's execution
Yigui
None
This is the wine Jiuheng personally prepared for you
lest you suffer
None
Lingchi type
It’s another year of heavy snow
None
But it made your uncle angry again
It’s hard for my uncle to teach
None
No patience
always scolds me
None
uncle
i won
None
you are finally here
It's getting late
None
It's time for you to go back
Be a good pig in this life
None
afterlife
Be a good person
None
people like me
I'm afraid I'll fall into hell
None
There will be no afterlife
do you know
None
Since we returned to Xigu Lane
This tree has become a marriage tree inexplicably
None
It is said to be the marriage between General Huaihua and the Regent.
It started from this tree
None
Why did it become like this?
You didn't pick me up from the snow ferry
None
Anyway, everyone says this tree is very efficacious.
Just throw your red ribbon up the tree
None
entangled
He will be the destined person
None
You are quite superstitious
real
None
After many people prayed
Everyone has met their destiny
None
We both need to be like thieves
Did you sneak out in the middle of the night?
None
Let people see that both of us are here to pray.
Don’t be laughed out of your wits
None
Come on
Afraid
None
I am the head of the family
I should give you a ride
None
good
bring it on
None
Must catch up
Doesn't count
None
what do you want to do
Start over
None
I have to take it off and throw it away again
I didn't get along with you
None
fine
Already caught up
None
Where did it catch up?
You don’t even know whose ride it is with you.
None
Believe me
this life
None
next life
life after life
None
All caught up
But I still have to take it down
None
Officail website =dramacool.club=
Let's go
None
Let me go
Don't let go
None
did you hear
Can't hear
None
I have to go back
How many years have I been to the military camp?
None
Memory is like a revolving lantern
yes
None
gather
hurry up
None
See Regent General Huaihua
Invasion of the Northern Jue
None
The Blood Riders are gathering
Madam, let me send someone to take you back to Lin'an.
None
What to say
I'm with you
None
Nonsense
How many years have I been on the battlefield?
None
Stop looking down on me
I am General Huaihua
None
But it was earned through many battles.
Someone coming
None
exist
Get my armor
None
yes
General Xie
None
If there is danger
hide behind me
None
Mother of two children
Be more mature
None
Then be careful
Return safely
None
drive
Zheng'er is really hard at practicing swordsmanship.
None
few days ago
Yefu
None
Sword skills are not practiced well
These few buses
None
Apart from eating, sleeping and studying
remaining time
None
Everyone is practicing swordplay here
It’s a child’s play
None
His temper is so stubborn
It's really not like me at all
None
Not like his father either
More like his uncle
None
Nephew Uncle Xiao
I don’t say this for nothing
None
I have this in my stomach
Quite tired and lazy
None
It’s all full term
There is also little movement
None
I'm thinking
She should be a girl who doesn't like to make noises
None
When her father teases her
The movement she made was very loud
None
She was so scared that her father couldn't sleep a wink all night
Tell me with a sad face
None
What if it’s a kid?
What's wrong
None
General Wei likes his daughter so much
Tell me sullenly
None
If it were a girl
It’s called Changyu
None
What if it's a boy?
He said he was a good boy
None
When you give birth, you should iron the egg first
Shouting wildly
None
Equally big
Then ask grandpa to give the child a name.
None
I heard
There is a folk law
None
Let young children identify the inside of a pregnant woman’s belly
Is it a boy or a girl
None
Do you want to try it?
OK
None
levy
Come here, mother
None
Mom is asking you
Do you think there is something inside Aunt Meng’s belly?
None
Is it brother or sister?
younger sister
None
If it were a sister
Just marry her home
None
Be your mother’s daughter-in-law
Why do you want to be your mother’s daughter-in-law?
None
Because my mother likes her
good
None
If it were a girl
It’s called Changyu
None
Met Mrs.
Auntie is busy
None
How did it happen?
Yes, mother and daughter are safe
None
An old slave was specially sent to announce the good news.
Auntie is busy
None
Come to the house and invite
Thank you very much, sister
None
I also prepared a small gift
express your feelings
None
Thanks
How is your sister doing?
None
Everything is fine
Could you please give me a message for my sister?
None
I'll go see her in a while
OK
None
Madam, please stay.
Grandma is busy
None
Was mother born by Aunt Meng?
how
None
Zheng'er is starting to miss your little wife now
these five years
None
My father finally brought the Beijue Army to the
Consume until the treasury is exhausted
None
This old thing in the court
Propose a truce at this time
None
Isn't that obviously given to the Northern Jue Army?
Provide rest and recuperation
None
Any chance of a comeback?
I am going to Beijing on behalf of my father this time
None
I also want to impress His Majesty
Continue to send troops
None
Go straight to the home base of the Beijue Army
Never give back favors
None
But do you really think
It was the veterans who proposed the truce.
None
The wars your father fought over the years
Just want to consume the North Hall
None
completely defeat them
But the Holy One doesn’t think so
None
But my father is very fond of His Majesty
That's true loyalty
None
His Majesty twenty years ago
Just like the current crown prince Qi Yan
None
Virtuous and loyal
But over the years
None
His attitude towards Dong Palace
I've always been worried that old things will happen again.
None
Even my own parents and children
All so wary
None
Not to mention those stationed in the northwest
A prince with a different surname who holds a hundred thousand soldiers and horses
None
How can we let him just let it go?
alright
None
Let’s put aside the counterattack against Beijue for now.
Waiting to see His Majesty
None
You raise it again
The Holy Spirit will still
None
Nowadays, things like floods in the south are happening
push back
None
Thanks for the tip, uncle
Come, come, come
None
Right
Auntie made some food
None
Let's eat something
Now
None
You can finally have a few sips with me
Now neither my father nor General Wei can drink from me.
None
Then today I will compete with my uncle
Your wings are stiff
None
Then we'll meet at the wine table.
please
None
Two of you, please
please
None
Be careful and don’t know why
I'm here Lin An
None
Feeling friendly
You are also a nobleman from the capital, right?
None
Please upstairs
Other nobles are already waiting for you two.
None
Shopkeeper
You look familiar
None
Have we met somewhere?
I don't know why
None
You said that
I feel this way too
None
Maybe in a previous life
We are really good sisters
None
good sister
I'll take you to try the craftsmanship in the building
None
Walk
You guys have worked hard all the way
None
Drink this cup
Come, come, come
None
Hard work hard hard work
Done
None
You guys have been waiting for a long time
This is our signature snow clam soup at Yixianglou
None
Dear guests, please have a taste
Snow clam soup smells okay to me
None
So fragrant
Dear guest, would you like to try it?
None
Your Majesty, what's wrong with you?
I'll go change first
None
Please feel free to
are you really okay
None
No problem
Shopkeeper, go ahead and do your work first.
None
The soup tastes so good you'll vomit
I'm so good-looking and you still vomit
None
baffling
Are you okay, Your Highness?
None
His Royal Highness is always the most courteous and courteous corporal
why today
None
Would you be so resistant to a restaurant owner?
Just now, Tomson also tried it.
None
Nothing unusual
I don’t even know the reason
None
Maybe they were enemies from a previous life.
met her
None
Clearly full of joy
But can't get close
None
I feel like vomiting when I'm close
This may be what people often say
None
Maybe by fate?