It's all her flesh.   It's
just you in every [song],
every time I close my eyes you will be in
my dream [song]
and human,
it's all right to you. You
will be like a dream,
just [song] in my hand. This has been so long. That
time I used to listen to you, my love.
K is
like cooking a meal.
We have to experiment until we get the right taste.   Once you've found something you
like, keep it delicious for as
long as possible. That's where
our love story began.
Mom asked you to write a positive review of Khun Ying's restaurant.
Ingchanok, why can't you do this for your mother?   I
knew my mother needed to find the money to repay her friend.
Just one positive review from you,
Mom. If I were lying, my credibility would be
ruined.
You're a famous food critic, you're blindly following orders.   Even if you
praised it a million more times, nobody would mind.
Maybe you should help your mother a little?   My
mother, the lady of the house, also helped to wash these.   It's
no good if I do it; I'm the one who'll be ruined.
Okay, if you can't find the money in time, then go visit your mother in prison.
Hello Mom?
Mom,
thank you for loving me.
[Song]
Thank you for loving Kim.
Thank you for loving me, thank you for every day you're by my side.
Thank you for caring, for comforting me
when
I cry,
because you understand everything.
She never meant it because of that [song].   It
is everything I buried.
[Song] Because it's only you.
She is an important person [in the song] because of her.
Keep sharing [the song] with me.
Thank you to those who love me. Do you love me now?
[Song]
Yeah.
Yeah, I've arrived at the shop you told me about. Yeah, almost there.   You can
wait inside the shop, just tell them my name is on the reservation. Okay, okay. I'll have the
golden bag dessert, the coconut milk dessert with lotus stems, and the mackerel. That's all for now.
Tang Tang is in trouble now, Tang.
What's wrong, P'Fuang Tang? Are you concentrating?   "
Guests are coming into the shop, that's
why? The
menu is normal, isn't it? So what? Well, the
guests who come to the shop are extraordinary people.
Who? Wait
a minute...
[Music]
[Music] So
intense, like the whole ocean is here.
[Music] Am
I even cooking for people to eat?"   I'll do my best,
look at the [song], what else do you want to criticize?
What are you all doing?   "
Fueng, why aren't you going out to greet the guests? Your mother is so busy."   I'm
reviewing the food that Phueng told me about.   The one with your
name in it.   He got
drunk at our shop and is now dead. Okay, then... (the rest of the text seems to be a jumbled mix of
Hurry up and take good care of him, and then go
get Dad.
Why would Mom want Dad? I'll handle it myself.   It's better to have your
dad watch this time, in case you get caught.   If you
criticize us harshly, our shop will be ruined, Mom.   That's right, I'll go and get her myself.
[Song] Mother   I'll go get
Grandma too; she probably wants to come down and supervise
herself.
Good words, okay?
[Song]
Don't worry, Nong Fueng, your shop is fine.   The business
needs to gain more customers and expand.   That
shop, En, has someone who is my close friend.   Getting a turn in the
queue isn't easy at all.
Thank you, but actually, Brother Khed should have told Feng.
First, let me clarify that my friend is you.   Do
n't worry, I think your restaurant, Nong Fuen, has
high standards.
Thank you. Okay then, please make yourself at home. I'll go
get the food. How's it going,
friend? Doesn't the restaurant look good? Don't make that face!   Oh, I see. I know you do
n't like it when I use it.
Connections may be important, but I'm confident in the taste of the food.
This is really for my nephew, but I wanted you to try it, you know. It's good.
By the way, you've had another fight with your mother, haven't you?
What's the matter this time, huh?
Hey, do you know that the recipes here are original?   Even the
royal court's utensils pale in comparison, my dear descendants.
This has to be made exactly as requested, no mistakes or deviations. How is it? Is it
delicious?
Mmm, it's delicious, smooth and creamy, and there's plenty to hold.   I feel
relieved now that you're talking like a bear.
Yeah, don't worry about it. It's fine. I
just ordered it.
[Song]
Damn, it's so delicious!   I
apologize, there may have been a misunderstanding.   I'm
sorry.
I found a foggy scene. Is something wrong?
[Song] Is
it still brutal?
[Song]
Go back into the mud right now!
Yeah, I think there might be some misunderstandings involved.   There's
no misunderstanding.
Hey, this is an apology. Let's just say, for this meal...
We won't be cutting corners on food costs.   Oh,
no problem. The food was delicious. I'm happy to...   I got to
eat here. [Song]
[Song]
I think your taste buds must not be up to standard.
Okay, Mr. Critic,
why do you always find something to do?
Dad wants to try something new.
Dad, taste it first, then you can scold me.
Dad, do you know
how long it takes to learn how to cook sticky rice?
Coming up with a cream formula isn't easy, Dad. So what? I'm putting in the same effort as
you put into your studies.   I
learned Thai recipes from my grandmother.
Dad, try some.
I told you Thai food is a heritage.
What our ancestors passed down to us, we must preserve.
[Song] You're still being stubborn and defying the norm, coming up with crazy formulas, I don't know what they are.
Calm down first, [Song].
Count the money and apologize to your father, son.
What did Tang do wrong? Tang didn't intend to destroy the inheritance.   This is
what my grandparents gave me, and I want to do something
new with it. The
world keeps spinning, Dad. [Song] We will...   Are we
really stuck in the same place?
This is my shop [Song].
If you're thinking of doing something unconventional, then go ahead.
Do it somewhere else, but as long as you're here, you have to.
Follow my rules [song],
but if not, go out into the cave like your brother. Go! Got the money?
Stop! Go!
Your
mother,
your
money...
You are the heir of Mr. Anan.
The will stated it that way.   Is that
your grandfather's restaurant?
Yes, there are restaurants, houses, and land around there.   It's
located on an island.
Can I sell it?
Hmm, okay, but
[song]
Hello,
I know everything already.   How
would I know?
Well, Feng told me everything already, you know.   Why don't
you come stay at my place tonight?   We'll talk about
other things later.   I'll let you know when I arrive.   See you soon, see you again and again.
I really want people to be with me during times like this, you know
?
[Song]
Thank you for loving me, [Song] Thank you for every day I
have you, [Song]
Thank you for always [Song] caring and comforting me.
When I look at [the song]
Because she understands everything about the song.
She never truly understood because of her [song].   It
is everything I buried.
Because it's only you [in the song] that makes it beautiful.
She's important because she, [the singer],
shares her life with me.
Thank you for loving me.