Did you stay up late last night?
Yeah.
Hey, don’t fall asleep yet. Tell me the route first.
Whose car did you take?
Well, you said there wasn’t a car to move your stuff, so I asked P’Johan.
He gave me the keys to this one.
Hope he's just renting it.
Turn right at the intersection.
Got it.
We’re here, we’re here.
Ter, Maew.
We’re here.
Ow, Daotok.
How’s they gonna wake up if you just call them like that?
You get out. I’ll handle it.
Ter, Maew.
Wake up.
Ouch.
We’re here.
North, why are you yelling?
You could’ve just called us nicely.
Come on, let’s move the stuff.
Yeah.
Which floor is it?
The 7th floor.
Shit.
Your new condo is so fancy. You’re rich, Daotok.
I’m not rich.
They gave me a discount.
Really? How much?
70%.
What?!
Why is it discounted that much?
With that kind of discount, is there some kind of promotion or what?
Like…
comes with a couple of ghosts or something?
- Hey!
- Watch your mouth, North.
Doesn’t it make you suspicious at all?
With that kind of discount, they might as well let you stay for free.
Right?
Hey! That scared me.
- Maybe it’s a power flicker.
- See? I told you it probably comes with something.
The light’s broken.
Let me introduce myself.
My name is P’Pae.
I’m the owner of this condo.
If you rent a room here, I’ll give you a 50% discount.
But if you rent room…
702,
I’ll give you 70% off.
Are pets allowed here?
Of course.
What kind of pet are you keeping?
Someone once kept a snake here.
You could even keep a buffalo if you want.
I mean it.
Okay.
Then I’ll take room 702.
You really want to rent room 702?
Yes.
- Is something wrong?
- No.
Nothing at all. Here’s the contract.
The rental contract. 70% discount.
Please read it.
70%.
I have a special ability.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Hey, let’s go eat shabu.
Feel… happy.
I can sense people’s feelings.
Your life is about to take a turn.
Wait, am I gonna win the lottery?
- Ouch.
- No, North.
Not a life-changing turn.
- Huh?
- But it might affect some parts of your life.
Now I’m stressed.
I’m not watching anymore then.
I can read people’s fortunes.
And…
I can communicate with spirits.
It was just a power flicker, right?
It’s nothing.
Really?
You’re bold for saying that.
This is the room.
Why did you bring so much stuff?
Thanks, Maew.
Hey, Dao.
Why does this floor feel so quiet?
Umm.
It’s just me and the room next door on this floor.
Why? Is the rent that expensive?
What’s wrong?
Oh, nothing. It just feels… strange.
- Ter.
- Hmm?
My hand is freezing.
Touch it.
Shit.
Look, I’ve got goosebumps.
I don’t think this is normal.
I’ve got a bad feeling about this room.
It feels weird.
So depressing.
It’s just that no one’s lived here for a long time.
That’s why it’s been closed up.
It’s nothing.
- Let’s move the stuff.
- Yeah, yeah.
Hurry up.
Thanks for helping me move.
Sorry for the trouble.
It’s fine, Dao.
This is the first time you’ve ever asked us for help.
We’re more than happy to.
Did anyone even ask me?
You’re happy to help too, right, North?
Yeah, yeah, I’m happy.
But can you treat us to some Moo Jum at least?
Sure.
Alright, we’ll head back first.
If you need anything, just tell us.
Mm.
Thanks.
See you.
Bye-bye.
Bye, Dao.
- Hey.
What?
Do you think Dao will be okay?
Okay how?
North.
Haven’t you heard the news?
What news?
That condo has a history of a lot of deaths.
Especially room 702.
Hey.
They say it’s a cursed room.
Shit.
Wait, I remember now.
Pull over for a sec.
Phoon.
Tell us.
Didn’t you read the news?
Five years ago,
a fourth-year medical student
killed herself.
They said she was stressed about school and her boyfriend.
So she…
jumped off the balcony.
Then two years later,
there was
a working woman
who was killed by her boyfriend in the bathroom.
Hey.
They said
her throat was slit in the bathtub.
Let’s talk this out.
I’m the one paying the rent for this room.
So that makes me the owner.
You can check the contract.
So anyone who has no right to be in this room
please leave if possible.
Hey.
That’s already two bodies.
And there’s a recent one too.
A male student from the Faculty of Political Science
was stabbed to death by his girlfriend while he was sleeping.
I think he probably died without even knowing.
Died.
Was it last month?
Oh right, I remember. It was on the university news.
His girlfriend got arrested too, right?
Guys, I think we should go back and get Daotok. This is dangerous.
Really dangerous.
Don’t panic yet.
I think
Dao already knows.
About moving in there. What can we do?
- You know him well, don’t you?
- Yeah, I do.
I know he doesn’t like being forced. And I also know he’s not afraid of ghosts.
- Because he can see ghosts.
- Yeah.
No wonder no one lives on that floor. Just the room next to his.
Damn.
- Hey.
- Ah!
Why are you grabbing me right now, Phoon?
I was just saying we should hurry back.
Oh. Right.
Let’s go.
Arthit.
Thit.
You’ve gotta help me.
The new guy who moved in isn’t scared of me at all.
Arthit.
You asshole, I told you to wake up.
Thit.
Shut up, asshole. I’m trying to sleep.
Shit.
Hmm.
Damn it.
Make it a bit smaller.
Even smaller.
If it’s any smaller, you won’t see it.
What should I do?
If I adjust it more, it won’t stand out anymore.
Try changing the position.
Hmm.
That’s a good idea.
- Michael
- What?
The new room looks pretty spacious.
But I don’t feel very good about it.
My friends said the same thing.
Are you still going to move, Michael?
No.
There have been three deaths in this room’s history.
Maybe it’s a ghost from somewhere else.
Try taking off your bracelet.
Maybe you’ll see it.
No.
I don’t want to see it.
Stop knocking.
Open up.
I’m not opening it.
And stop knocking.
Are you lonely?
Lonely my ass.
Open the door!
Why are you such a rude ghost?
What ghost? I’m a person.
I’m your neighbor next door.
Open up.
Hey!
I said open it.
Go tell Do to stop dragging the chair already.
Damn it, I can’t sleep.
P’Do didn’t do it.
I don’t care. I’m blaming Do for now.
Damn it.
Whoever it is, tell them to stop making weird noises already.
People are trying to sleep.
Do you even know what time it is?
Do you know about this?
I’ll tell him.
Yeah.
Hey, Thit.
When you wake up, come talk to me first.
Can you see me? Hello?
Can’t be helped.
Why would a spirit from another room come here?
What should we do?
I probably can’t stop a spirit from killing itself over and over.
But there should be a way to make the chair-dragging noise stop.
From now on, could you not drag the chair so loudly, P’Earng?
Will that even work?
She’s a spirit from somewhere else.
Not very powerful. Just wearing the bracelet makes her invisible.
A spirit like this isn’t complicated.
Thit.
Arthit.
Thit, Thit, Thit, Thit.
Thit.
Thit, Thit, Thit.
You’re late again.
You just got here too, asshole.
Hey.
You guys are late.
I tried.
Jo was late.
So, you’ve moved into the new room?
Yes, Papa.
When will you bring Mr. John over?
Um, I’m not free right now.
Can it be next week?
Sure.
And the new room—nothing strange, right?
I saw that it was cheap.
So I'm a bit worried.
Don’t overthink it, Papa.
Let me talk to Dad.
Sure, sure.
Hey, your son wants to talk with you.
Okay.
Hey son. When you're coming home?
I just got here.
Can you snap a photo of Mr. John for me?
Sure, I’ll send it to you.
How’s your room?
It’s so spacious and very convenient.
Sounds good.
See you soon.
See you.
Is that enough to fill you up?
I’m not very hungry.
You’re so stubborn, Michael. I’ll tell Ter next time.
Don’t.
What are you laughing at?
When it’s the three of them—Ter, North, and Phoon—Michael always gives in every time.
Mm.
They’re my friends.
That hurts.
I’ll get mad if you keep hurting me like that.
Give me your hand to hit.
It hurts. Don’t do that to me.
I can’t breathe.
- I won’t do it.
- It hurts.
Excuse me.
Is something wrong?
No.
Good thing the door’s closed.
What are you doing?
Not talking.
I'm going to sleep.
If you’ve got something to say, say it.
Your name’s Dao, right?
Yes.
I have something I want to ask for your help with.
Help with what?
I want Pad Kra Pao from Auntie Jum.
Please. I really want to eat it.
You yanked my leg—
—just because you wanted Pad Kra Pao from Auntie Jum?
No.
There’s something else.
What is it?
Help me find out
who killed me.
Wasn’t it your girlfriend?
The one who killed you?
I don’t believe my girlfriend did it.
Please. I’m begging you.
No.
I don’t want to get involved.
Why are you so heartless?
You look like such a nice person on the outside.
Can’t you help me?
Please, help me.
Please?
Otherwise, I’ll keep bothering you every night like this.
Do you know that where you’re sleeping—
—is right where I died?
I can do anything to you.
Are you threatening me?
So how do you want me to help?
I don’t know.
What?
Try asking the med student next door.
He knows my girlfriend.
Hey, are you done with class?
I don’t have class today.
Then what are you doing?
Sleeping.
Sleeping in the evening? A ghost might pin you down.
What is it?
I just finished class. I’ll come see you.
Why?
Okay, see you.
Can you really stay here?
Yeah, I can.
I heard this place has…
has…
a pretty bad history.
It might not be safe for you.
Everyone’s just worried about you.
Ter and Phoon are worried too.
What about North?
Me?
Why would I be worried about you?
You don’t need to worry about me.
Once the condo owner found out about what happened here,
they tightened up security a lot.
The rent’s cheap.
And besides,
there aren’t many people.
Just how I like it.
Mm. If you can live with it, then it’s up to you.
You haven’t run into anything weird, right?
There’s still over 20 minutes before P’Jo picks me up. Want to play a game?
Yeah, sure.
Honestly, Dao,
I saw you wanted to walk me to the front, so I let you.
Actually,
- I can go back by myself.
- Hey.
Oh, P’Thit.
What are you doing here?
Well,
my friend lives here, so I came to see him.
What about you? What are you doing here?
You live here?
Yeah.
Which room?
Next door?
Mm.
Shit, what a coincidence.
That makes me feel better. Leaving this guy alone is scary as hell.
Hey.
Or is having you next door even scarier?
Hey, P'Thit.
You can just drop me off here.
See you. P'Thit, let me see your room.
Why are you following me, North?
- Let me in.
- No need.
Unbelievable.
Why are you coming in?
Take your shoes off too.
Shit.
So damn nice.
Hey.
This is freaking beautiful, P'.
How much was this?
Two or three hundred thousand, I think. I don’t remember.
Does it bite?
- Wanna try?
- No thanks.
Don’t open it. No.
You said you used to live alone on this whole floor, right?
Really?
Yeah.
Now I’ve got your friend here.
Since my friend moved in, please take care of him.
Why’d he move here anyway?
I thought I’d get to live alone until graduation.
The owner gave that room a 70% discount.
Huh? 70%?
Yeah, so he moved in right away.
I only got 50%, damn it.
That’s more than me.
Well...
What’s with you?
Someone died in that room.
If you want a bigger discount, move in there instead.
Hell no.
Whatever.
What’s wrong with you?
It’s right next door.
Come on, can you head back now?
I’m exhausted. I’m going to sleep.
Why are you chasing me away?
Fine, I’ll go.
Shit.
Has P'Jo arrived yet?
He should’ve. He left with me.
Mm.
Let’s go.
- Walk me downstairs.
- Huh?
Shit, North. You’re grown as hell already.
You’re tall as a buffalo now. Go on, get out.
Please, P'.
Walk me down.
Please.
North looks cute in his engineer uniform today.
You say he's cute every day.
Is he close with the guy next door?
He’s North boyfriend’s friend.
North boyfriend’s handsome. They two suit each other.
Mm.
What’s wrong with you?
You’re late. Couldn’t keep up with me?
Shut up.
Alright, see you.
See you.
What’s up?
This is your dad.
Watch your tone.
Direk.
Am I your buddy or what?
Direk is my father.
Or if you want to be friend, just say so.
You little brat. If you weren’t my son—
So what is it? Why’d you call?
Hey, you haven’t gone to the racetrack lately?
I’ve been busy as hell, Direk.
Morning and evening shifts nonstop. I wanna quit, Direk.
Support me, will you?
What, I’m not supporting you already? Huh?
Seriously, where else would you find a great dad like me?
Oh please.
And stop blocking me on LINE.
I already unblocked you.
You keep making Johan talk to me instead.
Oh come on, Direk. You talk to Jo just fine.
But your actual son, you won’t talk to.
Johan’s cute.
He actually makes sense.
Oh?
So I don’t make sense or what?
You’re annoying.
What's your problem?
You only ever call to ask for money. You think I’m rich?
If you’re not rich, just say so. I’ll borrow from Jo instead.
So?
What is it?
Why’d you call?
I had a bad dream.
Shit, am I supposed to comfort you now?
It’s okay, Dad.
Your nightmare will turn into something good, okay?
Like that?
Your dad, my ass.
You’re cursing yourself again.
Oh? And what did you dream about?
I dreamed about your mom.
Emma?
Yeah.
What did she say?
She didn’t say anything.
Same as always.
You’re probably working too much, Direk.
Get some rest.
Yeah, I guess so.
Mm.
I’m gonna sleep like crazy tomorrow. It’s my day off.
Jo, wanna go out for drinks tonight?
Celebrate our one day off?
Nah. I’d rather go home and cuddle my wife.
For once, Jo said something nice.
Yeah, seriously.
Alright, let’s split up.
Hope I never see you again.
Yeah, get outta here.
Go cuddle your wife, asshole.
I’ll live the single life for you guys.
Bottoms up.
Another round.
Let me.
Finish your glass!
Hey, the music’s great. Let’s go!
Finish your drink first.
Shit.
Hey, open the door for me.
Let me crash here.
I lost my keycard.
Open up.
Can I crash on your couch?
Thanks.
Ugh, you asshole.
Hey, I can sleep on the couch!
So damn stingy.
Hey.
Open the door.
He said he lost his keycard. Just help him out.
If you leave him out there, the mosquitoes will carry him away.
Hey.
Let me stay over.
Hey, next door!
What the hell is this? Mosquito repellent?
Well, that works too.
So they won’t bite me.
Ugh, asshole.
North.
What did you tell your friend?
I told him not to leave you outside or the mosquitoes would carry you off.
So? Did you get in?
He gave me mosquito repellent instead.
Hey.
Can I use your bathroom?
You.
If you don’t let me in, I’m gonna puke in front of your door.
What did I do to deserve this?
Shut up.
I said shut up.
Won’t you bring him inside?
No.
Why?
It’s a hassle.
Why should I help him?
Don’t be so heartless.
You’re neighbors.
In the future, Michael might need his help too.
It’s so hard to fix that cold personality of yours.
Thit.
Hey, Thit.
Arthit.
Shit, I’m trying to sleep, asshole.
Come on, talk to me.
I’m serious.
It takes a shit ton of energy for me to appear in your dream.
This time, I’m serious.
I want Aunt Jum’s Pad Kra Phao.
Light some incense and bring it to me.
Aunt Jum ran off with a younger guy to Surat.
Then tell my mom I want Pad Kra Phao.
Tell her to stop bringing me stew.
I’m sick of stew.
Seriously.
I think the reason I haven’t been reborn yet
is because I have unfinished business.
I feel like
Meen didn’t kill me.
Time to wake up.
Is it morning already?
Did I sleep here last night?
Mm.
What’s this?
P’Pae left it for you this morning.
He said don’t lose it again.
Thanks for letting me crash here.
Wait.
What?
Your shirt.
Thanks.
Seriously.
I think the reason I haven’t been reborn yet is because I have unfinished business.
I feel like Meen didn’t kill me.
Hey, long time no see.
Yeah.
How’ve you been? You doing okay?
That outfit looks good on you.
Having fun, I guess. Asshole.
The hell kinda question is that? I’m in prison.
What the hell are you doing here?
- Visiting?
- Yeah.
Yeah, visiting you. I just talked to Do last night.
How many hits did you take?
Taking hits my ass.
That bastard Do keeps showing up in my dreams.
Ever since he died, he’s been coming over to my room all the damn time.
It’s fucking annoying as hell.
What’s his problem? Lonely or what?
Damn it.
Hey, Meen.
Your old room—
someone’s already moved in.
Seriously?
Yeah.
What kind of idiot would live in a room that haunted?
More crowded than mosquitoes.
Mm.
Someone who can talk to spirits.
Funny.
Yeah, fucking hilarious.
Who the hell can even talk to ghosts?
You can.
You’re still talking to Do.
And you’re mocking others.
You used to live in that room too.
Damn it.
The rent was cheap.
Besides,
I’m not afraid of ghosts.
You know, I was close with the ghosts in that room.
Only that idiot Do was scared shitless.
Hey.
Has he visited you?
A ghost that’s scared of ghosts, maybe.
Can you believe it? He told me he’s being bullied by a female ghost in the room.
It’s fucking pathetic, Meen.
Without me, no one can protect him.
Meen.
Hm?
Do said you didn’t kill him.
I’ll be honest with you, Mhor.
- I don’t know.
- What?
What do you mean you don’t know?
Back then, we were fighting like crazy.
How could you cheat on me?
I told you I didn’t. Look at this.
Don’t lie to me. You think I’m an idiot?
Hey, where are you going?
Sometimes I even thought about killing him.
And that night…
I was wasted. I don’t remember a damn thing.
When I woke up, he was lying in a pool of blood next to me.
And I was holding a knife.
If it wasn’t me, then who?
Huh?
Do.
So you just assumed you killed him.
If not me, then who?
With evidence like that.
But that idiot swears you didn’t kill him.
Problem is, he can’t remember that night either.
Then who the hell would want him dead?
As far as I know, he didn’t have any enemies.
Shit, Meen.
What if someone else did it
and you don’t know?
That night, the CCTV just happened to be broken.
Who do you think saw what happened besides…
Shit.
The ghost in the room.
Help me out.
Can you talk to the ghost in that room for me?
Please?
No.
Hey, wait.
North.
Your friend is such a pain in the ass.
You really don’t remember anything from that night?
Nothing. I didn’t even realize I was dead until days later.
Then why not ask the other ghost in the room?
P’Praw.
The night Donut was killed, did you see anything, P’Cream?
So you’re gonna help me, right?
Before it happened, a woman went into your room and argued with Do.