Aren’t you mad at him for not talking to you directly?
I’m actually glad it was Phoon.
Why is P'Fah so kind?
He even remembered that I’m afraid of the dark.
Here you go, cocoa for someone special.
Someone special?
Seriously, what are you guys doing?
Disguising.
I just wanted to know how I’d feel if I got to meet you.
And I found out that it feels really good.
Wait.
I really like how soft your lips are when I kiss you.
Yes, P'Fah.
Are you free to talk, Phoon?
Yes, I am.
Is there something you need, P'Fah?
I wanted to ask if you’re going home this break.
I probably won’t.
So you’ll be alone, Phoon?
I think so.
I was alone last break too.
Then how about spending the break with me?
My parents said they want to see you. It’s been a while.
At your place, P'Fah?
Yes. Or do you want to go somewhere else?
Can I let you know again later?
Sure.
Phoon.
Yes?
Was today a good day for you?
It was.
A very good day.
What about you, P'Fah?
Very good as well.
Hurry up, damn it.
Of all days to be late, you had to be late on exam day.
You complain so much.
Why are you so late?
I overslept.
Who’s gonna pass?
It’s like everything I studied got returned to the professor already.
I couldn’t do any of it.
Do you think anyone will pass?
Even with P'Hill tutoring me, I still couldn’t do it.
Are you complaining about the exam or showing off your boyfriend?
So how are you getting home? Want me to take you?
You go on ahead. I think I’ll stop by P'Gib’s cafe.
Wow, great. Just leave me behind.
I’ll be all alone and lonely like this.
You? Lonely?
I see you changing girls you talk to all the time.
That reminds me, I should go see my sweetheart too.
- See you!
- There he is.
Friends never even get to see your face.
See you.
So, how was it?
You went to see him?
How was it? Tell us, Maew.
Well, uh—
- I’ll tell you all at once later.
- Oh?
You sure?
Come on, this needs details.
So? Come on, Maew. Tell us.
Damn it, North. You’re quick about stuff like this.
If you told me like that. It means you tell to Daotok too.
I know it. You went and pushed him, didn’t you?
- North was the one who dragged me out.
- See?.
I knew it.
You never help me.
You’re such a nosy.
Whatever.
Let’s talk about this instead.
So, how was it? Your first time meeting—
Stop. Don’t say it.
P'Fah isn’t bad at all, you know.
Aha.
Ugh, stop making that face already.
What face?
The face like that.
- Your face is way less bad than mine?
- Of course.
Here. A mirror.
Damn it, Dao. When are you ever free?
- Hey, when are you going to have time to work? You never submit club work.
- What are you nagging about, Ter?
P'Fah.
Hi, P'Fah.
What a coincidence.
Yeah.
Such a coincidence.
We haven’t seen each other in a long time, P'Fah.
Didn’t we just see each other yesterday?
You’re here to get drinks at P'Gib’s cafe again?
Oh, uh… the peach tea at P'Gib’s cafe is really good.
Are you heading home already? Want me to take you?
That’d be great.
North’s going to see P'Jo anyway, and I was planning to see P'Hill.
Daotok, don’t you have work this evening?
- Yeah.
- Busy again.
Everyone’s busy.
Man, Phoon has to go home alone. I’m worried about him.
True, but if P'Fah takes him home, that’s a relief.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Exactly.
Then please, go ahead.
Yeah, if you go home with P'Fah, that’s reassuring.
Bye, P'Fah.
Bye. Please take care of him for us, P'Fah.
Of course.
So, have you decided whether you’ll come with me during the break?
Uh…
Is your place far, P'Fah?
Not far from the university.
Just a short drive.
But if you don’t want to go, that’s okay.
Don’t overthink it.
My parents would understand.
Uh…
That’s not it, really.
I’ll go.
I was just thinking about uncle and aunt anyway.
That’s great. My parents will be really happy.
Oh, by the way, how were the exams?
They were good.
Mm.
And how about transferring?
About I tutoring you like I said.
I really meant it.
That wouldn’t be a burden for you, right?
Of course not. Are you free tonight?
I’ll tutor you.
Huh?
Would that really be okay?
Of course.
I’ll call you later.
Oh, a call?
Why?
Or do you want me to tutor you in your room?
Ah— a call would be better.
Okay.
I’ve got a light exam tomorrow.
So I should be free tonight.
Alright.
Thanks for taking me home.
I’ll call you tonight.
Okay.
Hello.
Ready?
I’m ready.
Then let’s get started.
You still have your high school textbooks, right?
I do.
Okay.
Phoon.
Yes?
Today…
I went to see him.
Uh…
Who?
The person from the letters.
Oh.
Are you okay?
I’m fine.
And…
How was it?
I was really happy he agreed to meet me.
But…
He cried.
I really didn’t want him to cry.
If I asked him not to cry anymore… would that be okay?
I was really scared.
What were you scared of?
That he’d overthink things.
Because of everything that happened.
It was all intentional.
I don’t want him to think I wasn’t serious.
Oh.
Sorry, I got off topic.
Shall we continue studying?
Uh, sure.
Mm.
Done.
You did great.
Shall we stop here for today?
I’ll tutor you again later.
Okay. Sure.
Alright. Go get some rest.
Good night.
Holy shit, dude. P'Fah posted a photo of you.
Damn, look at his face.
Huh?
Didn’t expect that.
- Why is he like that?
- Yeah.
Seriously, I thought you’d be grinning ear to ear after seeing P'Fah’s IG story.
What’s with that sour face? Like a cat’s butt.
Cheer up, now!
Is something wrong?
Do you think…
If P'Fah finds out I’m the person from the letters,
Would he be disappointed?
Ugh.
Doesn’t P'Fah seem to like you though?
Mm.
P'Fah is kind to everyone.
Maybe he really likes the person in the letter.
But with me, he probably just sees me as a little brother.
Come on, what kind of little brother gets posted on IG Story like that?
"Study hard, alright, my good boy."
Wow, what kind of “little brother” is that?
Definitely not just bros.
I think so too—it’s not like bros.
I mean…
What if I’m just his option or something?
It’s hard to say, you know.
Maybe because we know Maew is the person in the letter.
So it doesn’t really feel that strange to us.
Why are you kids looking so stressed?
- Eat some snacks first.
- Oh, that’s too kind of you, P'Gib.
Wow, and that’s you being considerate?
You jerk.
Hey, what?
What if it’s poisoned?
Oh come on, this is to celebrate finishing exams.
Once it’s break, we won’t see each other for days.
Yeah.
So during the break,
how are you going to talk to Fah?
I honestly don’t know.
Huh.
Hmm.
Have you tried reading Fah’s letter yet?
Ugh, you’re so damn nosy.
Just like you.
You're worse than me.
If it’s not too much trouble,
may I see you again?
There’s something important I want to talk to you about.
After the last exam day.
I’ll be waiting at the park.
What should I do, guys?
Do about what?
- He said he’ll wait at the park, just go see him.
- Yeah.
What’s wrong, Phoon?
This is your chance—go for it.
If it’s break, how are you two supposed to keep talking through letters anyway?
Just go.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for coming.
You forgot this the other day.
You said you had something important to talk to me about.
Yes.
I haven’t felt at ease at all.
So I wanted to apologize
for overstepping my bounds.
It’s really okay.
Thank you.
Shall we take a walk?
It’s really beautiful here.
It’s even nicer in the evening.
Next time,
would you like to come here with me again?
You…
don’t want to come with me?
Will you come?
About what I said I wanted to talk to you about—
you might be wondering why I kissed you.
The answer is,
simply because I wanted to kiss you.
Not just yesterday.
Right now as well.
I want to cherish you,
not only in letters.
I want to hear you call my name,
and tell me you love me.
Not just cheering me on from afar.
I want to hold you,
and take the best care of you
as much as a man possibly can.
I love you.
For the rest of my life from now on.
Please be my boyfriend.
If you find out who I really am, you won’t be disappointed, right?
There’s no way.
Just being you is enough.
No one could be better than this.
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry for trying to pull you out of your safe zone.
But from now on, may I be your safe zone too?
This might be too fast.
So how about this?
I’ll count from one to ten.
The question I asked just now—
if you’re not ready,
you can just walk away.
And we’ll go back to where we were before,
the place where you feel comfortable.
No matter how long it takes, I’ll wait.
But if you say yes,
could you please turn back around?
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Yes.
Nice to finally meet you.
The person from the letters.
Likewise.
As the person from the letters.
It’s my first time hearing your voice.
Would you like to introduce yourself?
Typhoon.
And you?
Tonfah.
Nice to love you.
Nice to love you too.
Phoon.
P'Fah is cheating. I didn’t even have time to prepare.
Can I post it on Instagram and tag you?
Would that be okay?
Hey, we’re dating now. Can’t we post a couple photo?
Alright.
Oh.
You have my Instagram too, P'Fah?
Yeah. I check it pretty often.
Phoon.
Wait a sec. You’ll get lost.
I won’t get lost.
Really?
Then I’m not necessary anymore?
Uh—no. That’s not what I meant.
And this—
how did you get here?
Well—
I called a ride.
Then—
want to go back with me?
You mean you will take me back to my dorm?
Right?
Can’t you stay over at my place?
We’re dating now.
So what if we are?
Then we should spend time together.
What are you thinking, Phoon?
Hmm?
I’m not thinking about anything.
- Let’s go.
- Hey.
You’re really not coming?
- No.
- My bed’s really comfy.
Phoon, wait for me.
I thought I’d never come back here again.
You had to come back.
No matter where you go,
you have to come back to P'Fah.
By the way—
why did you turn back?
I thought—
you were going to walk away.
No.
I’ve always been right here.
I made a promise to myself
from the day I left this place.
that I wouldn’t go anywhere.
If you turned around,
I’d always be right here.
Come on, good boy.
Why did you say back then that I annoyed you?
Where are you going?
P'Fah, let go.
I won’t.
So I can know whether you lied to me or not.
I didn’t lie.
Really?
Bad kid need to be punished.
Uh—
I can’t tell you yet.
About—
why I had to do that.
So you have a reason but can’t say it?
I’m sorry.
Then it’s okay.
I think—
we should change your apology
into something else.
P'Fah is going to—
let—
change the apology into what?
What are you doing, P'Fah?
Let’s save it for later.
I know you’re not ready yet.
Don’t go yet.
If you’re a good boy, you should stay like this for now.
Okay.
You smell nice.
That tickles.
Phoon.
Don’t you have anything you want to ask me?
Aren’t you surprised, P'Fah, that the person from the letters was Phoon?
Honestly—
I already knew it was you, Phoon.
Huh?
How did you know? When?
On my birthday.
When you wrote that birthday message.
The handwriting on the card and in the letters—
it’s the same.
Oh.
So I messed up, huh?
Then when you let me read the letters, that means—
You wrote them yourself and read them yourself.
I even thought—
how cute it was.
P'Fah, why did you have to tease me like that?
Well, why are you so good at being cute?
I don’t know.
I.
I should go take a shower.
Do you always run away when you’re shy?
What are you doing?
I’m looking at these photos.
So many people sent you things.
But why did you choose to reply to this letter?
Because this letter—
it was thoughtful,
sincere, and caring.
And it didn’t expect anything in return.
It felt like you just wanted me to know you liked me.
Also—
there was someone in it who’s my type.
Someone who’s your type?
You really are my type, Phoon.
I really like you too, P'Fah.
I always have.
Where are you running off to?
I’m sleepy.
Stay and talk to me first.
I can’t believe this is real.
Tomorrow—
you won’t disappear, right?
No way.
You too.
You won’t disappear again, right?
I won’t go anywhere.
Then tonight we’ll have to hold each other tight.
So no kid sneaks away from me in my sleep again.
I told you—I’m not going anywhere.
Okay.
I believe you.
So, shall we sleep?
Phoon.
Can we turn off the lights?
Sure.
You’re not scared anymore?
With you here, I’m not scared.
Good job.
Good night.
Good morning, P'Fah.
I saw there was food in the kitchen, so I thought I’d—
I told you I wouldn’t disappear on you.
I’m sorry.
I woke up and couldn’t find you, so I panicked.
I just wanted to make breakfast for you.
This is—
the sandwich and milk you used to send all the time.
But it seems—
P'Arthit gets to eat them more often.
That’s true.
My hands are full.
Can you feed me?
Mmm, it’s really good.
Oh—
I already told my parents I’d bring you to visit.
Won’t Uncle and Aunt be suspicious?
About—
why I suddenly came to see them?
No.
Ever since I told them you study here,
they’ve wanted you to visit many times.
Actually,
I should’ve made time to visit more often.
Back then, Uncle and Aunt were kind to me—and Fun too…
I’ll go get more milk.
- Do you want anything else, P'Fah?
- No, I’m good.
You’re here already, dear?
Phoon, it’s been so long since I last saw you.
- Hello, Auntie.
- Hello.
How have you been? Are you doing well?
- I’m doing well. And you?
- I’m well too.
I heard you’re studying at the same place as Fah, right?
Yes.
Why don’t you come visit us more? We miss you so much.
I haven’t talked to Rit in ages either.
Uh—sorry.
I’m just teasing you.
I know you’ve been busy with your studies.
And you’re living far from home now, right?
Let’s go inside first, dear. Come on.
Uh, and how is uncle?
He’s in the hospital, dear. But he said he’d hurry back so we can have dinner together.
He’s still working just as hard as ever, isn’t he?
It can’t really be helped.
Ma’am, a client is calling. They’re waiting on the line now.
See? I didn’t even finish speaking.
Alright then, I’ll step out to take the call for a moment.
Fah, help watch him for me, okay?
Yes, Mom.
Your mom hasn’t changed at all, has she?
That’s true.
This is P'Fah’s room.
It’s even bigger than the old house.
Mm.
But without the neighborhood kids coming over to play…
it feels a bit lonely.
You still haven’t made up for letting go of P'Fah’s hand, you know.
This is your house.
- We can’t hold hands.
- Why not?
Well—
What if someone sees us?
Phoon, you don’t want others to know?
Hmm?
I’m worried uncle and aunt might see us and not be okay with it.
I’m sorry.
Phoon won’t let go of my hand.
I’ll tell Mom and Dad that we’re dating.
- But—
- We really are dating.
Okay?
Okay.
That’s a relief.
Typhoon, it’s been so long. How have you been?
I’m doing well.
And what about Rit? Is he doing well?
Dad is…
doing well.
Last time he said he’d come visit, but he never did.
- Phoon, dear.
- Yes?
Eat a lot, okay? We haven’t seen each other in ages.
How are you still this small? I really can’t accept that.
Yes.
Fah.
Yes?
I heard that Hill and Johan already have lovers. Is that true?
Yes, Mom.
And what about you, Fah?
Aren’t you going to find me a daughter-in-law?
Our son has been too busy studying.
Oh, Dad.
Shouldn’t he at least have someone to talk to?
Or should you finish your studies first?
What do you think, son?
Dad. Mom.
Phoon and I are dating.
Really?
Oh my, when I said I wanted a daughter-in-law,
I didn’t expect it to happen this fast.
Dad, are you okay with it?
Of course.
I’m not that old-fashioned.
It’s even better that it’s someone we already know.
That way, we don’t have to worry.
about Fah meeting the wrong person.
Thank you.
How long have you two been together?
Not very long.
This is such good news. We should celebrate.
We definitely should celebrate.
Yes.
Phoon.
- Do you want anything else to eat?
- I’m fine, thank you.
Here, eat up.
Should we order from this restaurant again?
Sure, Dad.
Eat plenty, okay?
What are you watching?
Easter and North.
They sent photos showing off their trip abroad.
Mm.
Phoon, do you want to go too?
Hmm?
If I want to go, can I just go like that?
If you want to go, P'Fah will take you.
Don’t spoil me too much.
Or I’ll become a spoiled kid.
Mm.
I always spoils my boyfriend anyway.
Let me think about it first.
But right now, I don’t really want to go anywhere.
What about P'Fah’s room?
Do you want to go?
Just kidding.
By the way—
Do you feel better now?
My parents didn’t seem upset at all.
They even looked happy.
They’re still just as kind as ever.
Was today a good day for Phoon?
Yes.
So, was today a good day for P'Fah?
With Phoon here and all.
Then of course it has to be a good day.
P'Fah.
I'm starting to lose my patience now.
But I will wait until Phoon is ready.
Is that okay?
Phoon.
Yes.
You’re not alone anymore, you know.
Those heavy things you’ve been carrying—
you can share them with me.
Do you understand?
Hmm?
Yes.
About what you asked me to look into, Khun Tonfah,
I have some updates to report.
Go on.
Thorfun passed away three to four years ago.
Oh, you’re up early, Phoon.
Come, sit here.
Is Fah still asleep?
Oh, he’s awake already. He’s taking a shower.
Yes.
- Go ahead, dear.
- Thank you.
And what about Fun? Is she doing well?
That’s right, it’s been a long time since we last saw her.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, dear.
- How are you?
- We’re doing fine.
We’ll probably head to Phuket.
Goodbye.
Come visit often, okay?
I will.
Drive safely.
Yes, Dad.
We’re heading off now.
- Goodbye, Mom and Dad.
- Take good care of each other.
That’s sweet.
Is there anywhere you want to stop by, Phoon?
The temple in the village.
Um…
Aren’t you going to ask why we came back to Phuket?
Is it strange that I didn’t ask?
It is.
At least you should ask.
P'Fah must be angry with me for sure.
Why would I be?
It’s okay if you’re angry at me.
I’ll apologize.
But…
Can we not break up?
Phoon.
We just started dating. Why are you talking about breaking up?
That’s not good at all.
Should I punish you for that?
I’m serious.
We’re not breaking up.
Yes. No way.
It took so long just to meet you.
P'Fah won’t let go that easily.
Let’s go.
P'Fah.
I’m sorry.
About everything—
I lied to you.
Phoon.
It’s okay.
I already knew.
I’ve known for a long time.
I was just waiting for you to be ready to tell me yourself.
You’re not angry with me?
I understand you.
Fun.
I’m sorry I never came to see you.
You don’t have to worry about Phoon anymore.
From now on,
I’ll take care of him myself.
Don’t cry.
Fun.
I probably don’t have anything to worry about anymore.
It’s really time for me to go now.
Can’t you stay?
Thank you for everything.
Mm.
I love you, Fun.
I love you too, Phoon.
Are you okay?
I can feel Fun.
Even though it hurts,
and I miss her,
every time I feel her,
it’s such a good feeling.
But this time,
she came to say goodbye.
Because she has nothing to worry about anymore, right?
I understand.
I want Fun to rest peacefully.
She doesn’t have to worry about me anymore.
But when I think about it again…
I thought we might never see each other again.
It’s just…
a bit heartbreaking.
Phoon, listen to me.
Fun hasn’t gone anywhere.
Because Fun
will always live on in the memories of both of us.
That’s true.
I never thought I’d get to watch the sunset with you like this.
Why not?
It just felt impossible.
Huh? Why’s that?
Back then,
whenever I looked at the sky,
I’d always ask myself
whether P'Fah was looking at the same sky.
But today, I got my answer.
That we’re looking at the same sky.
Then that means we’re looking at the sky together.
Phoon, would you like to move in with me?
- Please?
- Don’t overthink it.
P'Fah believes your parents will understand.
I heard there’s an investor in Chiang Mai
who’s interested in partnering with us.
They want to discuss the details first.
You ungrateful brat, a complete waste of everything I’ve given you.
I should never have let that woman give birth to you.
This is the result of your own actions—take some responsibility for it.
Don’t think you have to face everything alone anymore.
Phoon, you’ll always have me.