In today's civilized world,
there is still a kind of human
who is obsessed
with the triangular area of the body.
Perhaps because
it is a forbidden triangle,
reserved only for those who are permitted
to enter.
But humans, the more they're forbidden
from doing something,
the more they want to do it.
And every act of defiance
comes with consequences.
PINK KITTY
TONIGHT, PINK KITTY IS COMING STRAIGHT
TO YOUR BEDROOM. STAY TUNED.
Since they've been upskirting us,
how are we supposed to keep practicing?
You have to deal with them, Teacher.
And they even posted our faces
next to our underwear.
They even gave us ratings.
It's disgusting behavior.
This is not a marketplace.
Stop using vulgar language.
This is exactly why
every female student's skirt
must be one palm-length below the knee
and may only extend
to the permitted length.
And the reason we constantly teach you
how to sit, stand, and walk properly
is so you won't
embarrass yourselves like this.
When you change clothes,
don't you spread your legs too, Teacher?
Mookdamanee.
Who taught you to interrupt like that?
Today, I won't punish you
for your nails,
your bras, and those short skirts
that violate regulations.
But could you please improve yourselves?
And suspend club activities for now
for your own good.
I have a meeting. You may leave.
Oh…
Take the new student
to your classroom too, Mook.
I'm Nanno. I'm a new student here.
Who the hell are those Pink Kitty guys?
They've been secretly filming.
You'd better be careful too.
- So we're at fault?
- Did she treat you like you were right?
What are we going to do next?
It's embarrassing wherever we go.
Yours isn't bad, Da. You got an eight.
Look at mine. I wore something old.
I only got a 4.5.
It's fucking humiliating.
They should've told me first.
I'd have worn something nicer.
Does my face look like your mom's?
Bastard.
Okay.
Could you introduce yourself briefly?
I'm Nanno.
New student in grade 11, class 6,
and also the newest member
of the volleyball club.
Why did you want to study here?
I heard that
the guys here are cute.
And they're nice too.
THE GUYS HERE ARE CUTE,
AND THEY'RE NICE TOO
WE NEED THE NEW GIRL'S KITTY.
I THINK SHE'S A 10/10.
I WANT TO SEE NANNO'S KITTY.
NANNO, THE NEXT KITTY OF THE YEAR.
I'M MELTING. SHE'S MY TYPE.
HER FACE IS THIS NICE.
HER KITTY WOULD BE EVEN NICER.
Nanno.
Damn, she's hotter than Mook.
I bet she could go for a high price.
Then we raise the price.
3,000.
- Four.
- I'll say five.
5,000 BAHT. TRANSFER NOW.
RECEIVE IN 4 DAYS.
TRANSFER COMPLETE
Damn.
VIRTUOUS LADIES
No.
There isn't anything like that.
This is probably just a misunderstanding.
These days, photos are easy to edit.
Sometimes, they're even AI-generated.
Your team also hasn't even verified
the source of these images.
Let's not make this into a big issue.
Stop teaching.
- What is this?
- You're good at exposing things, right?
- What are you doing?
- Let go.
Mookdamanee. Passcode.
Passcode.
Mookdamanee, passcode.
Why should I tell you, Teacher?
My passcode is personal,
and it concerns my personal autonomy.
Shouldn't you ask for my consent first?
What you're doing
isn't any different from harassment.
Stop. Don't try to educate me.
Here, I educate you.
Aside from your academic duties,
as long as you wear this uniform,
you must remember
that everything you do
represents the school.
So when you broadcast something disgusting
that should remain under your skirt,
you are destroying your own reputation
as well as the school's.
Your body is your responsibility.
You must take care of it
and protect it yourself.
If you cannot protect
your own private parts,
no one can do it for you.
Do you understand?
You didn't do anything wrong.
If you were me,
what would you do?
Follow what the principal said.
We have to protect our own private parts.
It's not here.
This is getting fun.
Damn, they found it.
Just plant another one.
We'll put them everywhere Nanno goes.
Those perverts are rushing us every day.
We have to act fast.
Check another one.
Hey!
Damn it!
What do we do?
Damn it,
Nanno's kitty is haunted or something.
Haunted, my ass. Don't be stupid.
Or maybe Nanno has a signal jammer?
Hey, hey.
- I saw something.
- What?
Look.
What the fuck?
Nanno has a dick.
Damn. No way that's Nanno's.
That's disgusting.
It's tiny and even has a mole.
The mole even has hair. Shit.
Look, that mole looks like this.
Look at it. So damn small.
Is this yours? It's got a mole on it.
Doi.
I'm asking if it's yours.
The flash is on.
See you later,
Doi.
Nice. Test it.
Come on.
How's the footage, Doi?
Yeah, it's clear.
But will this plan work?
Just wait and see.
Markkaw.
Nanno.
Can I interview you?
There's a Mother's Day event coming up.
- I'd like you to help…
- Sure.
Okay.
All right. I'll start recording.
This Mother's Day,
I hope everyone will come watch.
There will be something unexpectedly good.
Let's do another take, just in case. Okay?
One more time.
Okay, let's start.
This Mother's Day,
I hope everyone will come watch.
There will be something unexpectedly good.
- Come watch.
- Whoa!
Hey! Shit! No!
Ugh! It hurts!
My balls, damn it!
Ugh! Damn it!
Let me go!
The patient is out of danger.
The wounds should heal
within two to three weeks.
EXAMINATION ROOM
However, we were only able
to save one testicle.
The other was severely damaged.
But don't worry.
He will still be able
to reproduce normally.
And if he has a son,
the baby will be born physically complete.
THANK YOU, DOG, FOR MAKING ME FINISH
NOT JUST MY BODY, BUT MY HEART TOO
MY LOVER IS A DOG
What the hell are you filming?
What are you looking at?
THIS IS TAKING TOO LONG
WHERE ARE YOU?
WHERE IS OUR KITTY?
- SO DAMN QUIET
- YOU STIFFING ME, BASTARD?
WHEN DO I GET NANNO'S KITTY?
I ALREADY PAID. WHEN DO I GET IT?
Ugh! It hurts!
Were you looking for this?
I didn't know where Markkaw was,
so I'm returning it to you instead.
You two are close, aren't you?
Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Then I'm heading out.
Hey, wait.
Since you're already here…
- Come inside first.
- Sure.
Wait here for a second.
I'll get you some drinks.
Drink it.
Do you have more?
That's all I have.
Do you want some water?
I don't like water.
Then I'm leaving.
Hey, wait.
You drank so much.
Don't you need to use the bathroom?
It's a long way home. You might need
to use the bathroom on the way.
No.
I'm going.
Thanks for the drinks.
Hey.
Don't stress.
They won't make fun of you for long.
MOOK: SEE YOU
IN THE AUDIO-VISUAL ROOM, NANNO.
Oops. That startled me.
I almost screamed.
You're not into secretly filming anymore?
Nanno, let go.
Let go!
Damn, I…
Film it.
- Shit, Nanno, that hurts!
- Take the shot.
- Nanno, let me go!
- Take it.
It might take a while.
The image resolution's a bit high.
Damn, why is it taking so long?
Damn!
Damn.
THIS IS HEAVEN
THIS IS THE HAPPIEST DAY OF MY LIFE
Damn, Nanno is insanely hot.
IT WAS WORTH THE WAIT
Nanno…
Peck.
Mom!
Why didn't you knock before entering?
Think you can come in whenever you want
just because you're my mom?
All those proper manners
you go around teaching people,
try using them yourself.
All right, I'm sorry.
- I just…
- Just what?
Get out!
I said get out. Don't you understand?
MOTHER'S DAY
"A MOTHER'S LOVE IS BEYOND ALL COMPARE"
Hello. Welcome to all the mothers,
students, and teachers
who have joined us today
for National Mother's Day 2025.
The school has organized a ceremony
to present love and happiness
to all mothers and children…
I've tried every position already.
Bastard.
You're right.
She freaking drained me last night.
- You too?
- Of course. How could I not do it?
Please welcome.
Next, may the students please come
sit in front of your mothers.
Students, please present your garlands
as a symbol of love
and gratitude to your mothers.
Today's atmosphere
is filled with smiles and warmth.
- Damn.
- Whoa!
Damn, right in my face.
Stop the projection right now!
I said stop it!
Who?
Who did this?
I'm asking. Who?!
I did.
Why? What do you want?
It's the slideshow for Mother's Day.
This is clearly obscene.
Aren't you ashamed?
How is it obscene?
Shouldn't the obscene ones
be the people
who secretly took these photos?
Shit.
Who took this? Damn it.
I don't know!
Mom!
Damn, we've been tricked.
He sent us the pictures
of his mom's panties.
Shit, I even did it to the picture!
What the hell are you filming?!
Doi, drag him away.
Hey, what the hell are you doing?
- You bastard.
- Damn you!
There, there.
No need to cry over this, Peck.
I was just playing a little joke.
You didn't even have to secretly film me.
If you just ask nicely,
I'd show you anyway.
Here.
I'll show you up close.
Da, what the hell?
- Jew. Jew.
- What, Da? I'm sorry.
- Jew! Jew, no!
- Da.
- Jew, I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
No, please, Jew. Don't do this to me.
We meet again, Nanno.
The follower count has reached 200,000.
By the way,
Hongtae, what do you think about Jamie?
PANGHAM: YOU LOOK LIKE
A TOTAL IDIOT PLAYING WITH A DOG
Everyone, start the war.
Push the hashtag to number one.
Ban Jamie!
What you did
made everyone
turn their attention to Jamie.
Because humans love violence.
Right?
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon