Hm.
Our bodies belong to us.
That's how the saying goes.
My body, my choice. My body, my choice.
My body, my choice.
We are free to decide what we do
with our body.
THE ROOM LOOKS VERY INVITING TOO
YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL IN ANY OUTFIT
YOU KNOW THAT?
DID YOU JUST FINISH SHOWERING?
YOU MUST SMELL SO NICE.
Huh.
THE PAJAMAS LOOK SO TOUCHABLE.
You want to see my bra? Huh?
THE PAJAMAS ARE SO CUTE
WHAT COLOR IS THE BRA, DEAR?
My body, my choice.
Tell me.
Who wears a bra under their pajamas?
BLOSSOM BLOSSOM BLOSSOM
So, I'm not wearing one right now.
Prove it?
XXARM: I DON’T BUY IT. TAKE IT OFF FIRST.
Here she is.
My body, my choice.
Hey, Blossom,
does having this body,
Can I take a photo, please?
Mean I have a choice?
Thank you.
Oh, my God, hi! Blossom, you are so
beautiful!
Do you realize the kind of message you're
spreading to other students?
And your actions are totally
inappropriate for a young lady like you.
It reflects poorly on the reputation
of this fine school
and will, indeed, affect your future
prospects.
Could you explain what I've done wrong?
Can you defend this?
They're all over the school.
Really… Ha…
I'm sharing the truth sir, nothing more
than we already know.
Young women find my words to be
inspiring.
They strive to be their best selves
and to do what's best for them.
You are ignoring how this impacts
the university's prestige.
I don't believe the school's name
was ever said.
You shouldn't be worried I damaged
my reputation.
I doubt my actions have had a
negative effect.
Students look up to me.
Now may I say something?
It's my body.
I'll do whatever I like, show
what I want, to whomever I choose.
That's the slogan, huh?
By the way,
you're too uptight.
Why don't you consider loosening up
a little?
Or unlocking your hotness potential?
Oh. Starting with that, um, top button on
your collar?
Hi Blossom.
I'm Nanno. I'm new here.
You sure are.
I like meeting cool girls.
Everyone's hyped up about you and not
even the dean can stop you.
I'm all about the truth.
My channel is meant to empower women
to do what feels right for them.
You can always subscribe to my channel.
Maybe you'll find what you need there.
I subscribed a while ago. You have
such great content.
You inspire me in so many ways.
Oh, wow! Love that.
Would you mind sharing what about me
that has inspired you?
Hm.
I was…
shy to wear something short…
and I'm not shy at all now.
That's great.
Also…
I was shy to start a channel like yours,
and now I have one.
Hm?
See? This is mine.
You helped me gain more confidence.
This channel wouldn't have started
without you.
Hello everyone. Nanno here.
HELLO, BEAUTIFUL.
WOW, GIRLS WITH GLASSES ARE MY TYPE.
Hi THERE. GREETINGS
YOU’RE SO BEAUTIFUL
GIRL WITH GLASSES, SO EROTIC
Weather got so hot today.
YOU CAN TAKE IT OFF.
HOW HOT IS THAT?
How should I stay cool?
PLEASE UNBUTTON YOUR SHIRT.
And how many buttons shall I undo?
SUPERSTAR: CAN YOU UNBUTTON THREE??
PHUPHUISSINGLE: TWO IS FINE. I’M WAITING
Oh my,
KODRUAY: JUST TAKE IT OFF.
Start with one?
Or two?
Or…
dare me three?
COOL118: YOU CAN UNBUTTON THREE.
IMPACC: THREE. GO FOR IT.
LITTLE: YOU CAN TAKE IT ALL OFF.
XJIGJAWX: YES. THAT’S THE WAY, NANNO
KOKO: TOO HUGE FOR MY SCREEN
ONLYYOU: IF YOU TAKE IT OFF, I’LL PAY
PUPPYLOVESCUDDLE: REAL “MY BODY MY CHOICE”
TIGER: EVEN HOTTER THAN BLOSSOM.
I'm much cooler now.
Ow, watch it, come on!
Move, you're in my way.
Hey.
- She's so cute, fuck.
- I mean, damn.
- Damn
- So hot!
I mean, come on!
- Of course, I did! She's so brave.
- And then, oh, fuck!
Hella cute
- I'll go if you go!
- Yeah dude, let's go.
Look at them go. Seriously, look.
Excuse me, do you mind if I take a photo
with you?
Love to.
- Here, snap some pics.
- You guys. Come on.
I want to look good.
Okay, playboy, it's my turn.
Just one more. Two-two more!
- Thank you Nanno.
- Come on.
Dude, she smiled at me!
She is something else.
Hey Blossom.
During my live last night, I was
channeling you
and I got a lot of fans just by doing
what you do.
Do you mean subscribers?
Mm.
Fans, wanna see?
Tah dah!
You know what I think?
That your slogan
that says our bodies do
You're late, and I'm mad, deal with it.
Belong to us makes us all inspiring.
Well,
I should be going.
Bye.
What's all this?
Is this all for me?
Well done, Blossom.
I doubted you would ever show remorse,
but I'm relieved
that there's still some sense in you yet.
Now I understand
what I should do and shouldn't do.
Mm-hm.
Hm.
Goodbye, sir.
You've just started at this school.
And already you're displaying such a
deplorable attitude.
I've never seen anything like this.
This reflects badly on our university
and on your character.
You find this acceptable?
Don't you want a future? A family
someday?
What would your parents say if they
knew about this?
Hello everyone.
Really, I must apologize to all of you.
I can't do my livestream now.
I was told to end my channel, that
the school's reputation's at stake.
I know you do.
DAMN IT. WHO THE HELL DID THIS?
LEAVE NANNO’S BODY ALONE
MAXNUM: YOUR BODY MUST BELONG TO YOU.
IT BELONGS TO YOU, NANNO.
TIGER: I’LL GIVE YOUR BODY BACK TO YOU.
SAVE NANNO
YES. DON’T LET THEM TAKE NANNO
NO ONE CAN TAKE NANNO AWAY.
THERE THERE.
I LOVE NANNO’S BODY.
SAVE NANNO
What's all this? Don't drop your junk
here.
But this is a delivery for the
university's dean.
Put this shit back. We weren't
informed of a delivery. Now move it.
What's going on here?
Just doing my job.
You okay?
He said he's got a package for you or
something.
Oh, yeah?
Oh!
Yeah, it's from a Mister Suea OnlyNanno.
This one's for you, sir.
And the other boxes are for the school.
Hello Mister Suea? I have the dean in
front of me.
- Yes, hello?
- Hello dean.
These are gifts that I wish to donate to
the university.
As thanks for your future support
of Nanno. Her body belongs to her.
All these boxes?
You should start by opening this
box, sir.
I will admit that my thinking and values
tend to lean more conservatively, and…
yes, I agree that a person's body
- belongs to them, so.
- Oh!
You're amazing Blossom, you are.
Your philosophy is inspiring.
Even the dean is open to it.
Hey, can I have this pen?
Come on!
SO HOT.
HEY HEY. NANNO IS BACK
NANNO IS HERE
Only Nanno fans are so awesome
I was told to stop and close my channel.
Now I don't have to, so, thanks
You all deserve a gift, right?
Time to unwrap your present.
HUGE COME BACK.
SO GOOD.
I’M OUT OF JUICE
SO AWESOME
NICE BREASTS
NANNO’S VERY BEAUTIFUL
PIAK: TAKE OFF THAT INSIDE ONE
JUL.JU: TOP-NOTCH
TUNGTUNGTUNGPO: BEAUTIFUL BREASTS.
SSAWADEEKABB: DRINK MILK AND KEEP GROWING
Uh.
TAKE IT OFF
NAKED = WIN
SHE DID IT TOO
SO MUCH GOOD STUFF. WHO WILL I WATCH?
FINALLY, BLOSSOM’S BREASTS
THE BATTLE OF HOTNESS
You want to see my boobs? They're
natural and mine.
You should see them bounce as I dance,
dance, dance.
I LOVE BOUNCING
ONE AND ONLY BLOSSOM
Woo-hoo.
TOMORROW: YOU CAN’T BEAT BLOSSOM
PEANUTBUTTER: SO MUCH TO SEE HERE.
That's what you call dancing?
DAMN, PANTIES GONE.
KEEP GOING ALL THE WAY
THE SKIRTS TOO.
WOW. THAT’S TOO HOT.
NANNO’S UNPREDICTABLE
I LOVE THIS. THIS IS THE REAL DEAL
It's so hot.
Whoops
LET’S SHAKE IT
HARDER. KEEP GOING
NANNO DID IT, NOW’S YOUR TURN
AWW. BLACK IS HOTTER.
I LOVE THIS STRIPPING GAME.
THE BRA GOES OFF.
SMOOTH AND GLOWING. 10/10
NAKED = WIN
WOW YOUR HOTNESS MAKES ME SWEATY
THE QUEEN IS HERE.
LITTLEPEPO: CAME FROM NANNO’S. SO HOT
POOPOO: THE REAL DEAL WILL BANG IT
Stripping's not daring enough.
PATT: I CAME
NICKY: VERY BOLD. I’M HORNY
PPUT: VERY FXCKABLE
ANONYMOUS: BLOSSOM CAN’T EVEN COMPETE.
Thank you all so much!
I'm humbled by you. You've made me so
happy.
Now, I think you deserve another gift.
Here it is.
I'll spend exclusive time at the movies
with one of you.
Good luck.
And to my top donors. You'll earn
more chances to win.
'Cause I'll be drawing often.
1.SUEA - 2. WITTAWAT
3. SIMP - 4. LEO - 5. ARMARM
Wow!
So generous Mr. Suea.
I can't wait to thank you.
Time to spin the wheel.
And my date is…
Come on.
Is it safe?
Of course, you're safe with me.
Shall we take a photo?
What are you up to?
I never watched your channel.
I'm not up to anything.
Just wanted to see you.
Can you tell what's real and what isn't?
With you, I can.
Actually,
no one has ever found me,
You're the first that has.
Only because you let me, Nanno.
Am I right?
Sky? Who the fuck is that!
I don't see his name on the fandom page.
WHO THE FUCK IS SKY?
I’VE NEVER SEEN HIM IN OUR FANDOM.
WHAT DO WE DO?
SHALL WE GET HIM?
BUT NANNO WON’T STRIP FOR US AGAIN.
WHAT WILL WE MASTURBATE TO THEN?
BLOSSOM ISN’T ENOUGH ANYMORE.
WE MUST PROTEST.
PROTEST. PROTEST. PROTEST.
WE CAN’T LET THIS GO.
Hello, guys, did you happen to follow me
on my date today?
Don't worry if you missed me.
Took a pic for you.
I'll post it on X later.
THE WINNER…
REALLY GOT TO GO ON A DATE WITH ME
Oh. What a mighty shame.
I thought you'd like that sweet picture.
FRAUD DATING AWARD
YOU CHEATED.
CHEATING.
What?
Cheating? When? How would I possibly do
that?
If you're not happy with this,
I'll spin the wheel again.
As my apology to you,
I'll offer more than a date.
Then how about a one-night stand with
me, boys?
This time the winner will be whoever
donates the most to the university fund.
I promise I'll be worth it.
I'll tell you who the winner is in
three days.
Good luck everyone.
ACCOUNT BALANCE 0.75
Expel her now.
She's gone too far this time.
So, it's no longer, "My body, my choice?"
Mm.
It is. This is blatantly inappropriate,
right? Prostitution's illegal
Not under these circumstances, This isn't
prostitution when two parties consent.
Nanno's initiative is raising money for
the school.
And you accused me of being uptight.
THE HIGHEST DONATION TO THE FUND
FOR A ONE-NIGHT STAND WITH NANNO
THE RESULTS TO BE ANNOUNCED
IN THREE DAYS.
She's on! Guys? Guys! Over here.
- What's up?
- Did you make a donation yet?
OnlyNanno. She's live streaming now!
Check it!
- The winner is up in three days?
- Yeah!
Suea, why are you in my room?
Stop snooping around.
THE RESULT TO BE ANNOUNCED
IN TWO DAYS
THE RESULT TO BE ANNOUNCED TOMORROW
My body, my choice!
My choice!
Choice!
Her choice, your choice!
Suea, why aren't you at school?
On my way, Ma.
ANNOUNCE IT ALREADY
THIS IS TOO EXCITING
GO AWAY, TEACHER
I DON’T WANT TO WAIT ANY LONGER
I'd like to hand over the mic and to
invite Nanno
in the spirit of freedom and the autonomy
of our bodies
Thank you, for your support everyone.
This couldn't have happened without you.
I am humbled and in awe that my body
could inspire so much good for you and
for the university.
I would like to especially thank this
person who's an inspiration to me.
Thank you, Blossom.
Ooh!
Mm-hm.
If Blossom hadn't had the courage
to speak the truth,
when she taught us all that slogan that,
"my body is my choice."
We'd never know the freedom we have now.
I respect you Blossom.
Yeah, Blossom!
Thank you!
Okay then,
it's now time to reveal who has made
the biggest donation and is the winner
of a one-night stand with me.
I donated too.
- A girl could win
- I'll keep the name private for now,
but I'll share their ID number.
It's time!
And now the winning number…
is…
one…
We're still in the game!
The anticipation is electrifying!
Zero…
nine…
Bullshit! Fuck!
Congratulations One-Zero-Nine You've won
a night with me at the Royal Resort
Park.
In room…
Two-Zero-Five
at eight o' clock tonight.
See you later.
- Hey! Is it you?
- I'll be waiting for you.
WHO IS 109?
NOT ME.
NOT ME EITHER.
Man. Bro, did she con us?
TRANSFER COMPLETED 274,600 BAHT
REDSALTYYOLK: AS IF I COULD WIN.
GIANTSAUSAGE: WHO THE FUCK IS SO LOADED?
MS.FLOWER: IT’S NOT FAIR THAT ONLY
109 GETS TO GO. WE MUST GET SOMETHING.
HI_SHUTUP: TRUE. WE DONATED A LOT.
KODJARB: HOW CAN ONLY ONE PERSON GO?
I’M IN.
LET’S GO FUCK SOME SHIT UP AT THE PLACE.
Hey! Wait!
What are you doing? Only guests
may enter. No, stop, please!
Whoa! Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, stop!
- You guys! You cannot enter!
- You are not guests here, we can't
- accommodate you!
- We are now!
- Room two-zero-five.
- Give us a key.
- We're in two-zero-five.
- You can't stop us all, man.
- We don't have rooms for all of you
- You do! Outta my way!
Stop! Please, no, no!
Yeah, this way.
Fuck you, one-zero-nine.
You bastard, you shouldn't have won.
Who the fuck are you, show yourself!
- Hey! What?
- No!
This time, the winner will be whoever
donates the most to the university fund.
I'll offer more than a date. How about a
one-night stand with me, boys?
INFORMATION-CHECKING
AMOUNT: 274,600 BAHT
TRANSFER COMPLETED
274,600 BAHT
Congratulations One-Zero-Nine.
You stole our money for a night with her?
- Get up, Perv!
- Yeah, get him!
Let's take him outside for a real lesson.
Grab his feet
Fucking pervert! Fucking thief!
Is this necessary?
Could you calm down?
This bitch is telling us to calm down?
Mm.
The fuck you mean telling me
to calm down?
We all spent a shit ton of money on you
with squat to show for it!
Yet everything went according to
the rule?
Rule? What fucking rule?
Hm?
Me,
and us loyal fans here.
Spent all our money for you.
And the old pervert lying in a heap stole
the right to sleep with you.
Well, that's not fair.
Hm? Your body,
your skin and everything is ours
by right.
Oh.
I thought you all supported it.
My body, my choice.
Isn't it my choice?
Yeah, it is your body.
But not when I paid for it.
Mm.
So, how do I pay you back?
Must I Break it up into pieces
for each of you?
I'm ready to pay my debt.
My body, my choice. Right, Blossom?
It's me, Blossom, welcome back.
Today, I feel empowered.
Because our bodies…
belong to us.
Powerful saying.
We can't let them open the 100-year
building. No matter what.
You guys wanna expose the corruption
around here, right?
Whose side are you really on here, Nanno?
I'd appreciate if you didn't disappoint
Dobby and myself.
This was all a setup.
If Atsajayree releases this clip…
ANOTHER CORRUPTION?
ATSAJAYREE GROUP IS AWESOME
Boy, will there be hell to pay.
The people doing this are still
out there.
Twisting the narrative
Shit!
Redirecting attention. That's the art of
those who control the game.
Checkmate
Like, actually dead.