Everyone carries something called
an invisible ruler in their hand.
And we use it to judge,
to measure other people's worth.
But then…
who will be the one
who gets struck the hardest?
HONG IS HERE
One, two, go!
Come on, Hong. Come here.
Good girl. Go to the camera.
WHY ARE YOU SO CUTE?
JAMIE, DON'T SMILE. I'M GONNA FAINT
Guys, screenshot this.
Hong's doing a half heart pose.
I love Hong the most in the world.
Do you all love Hong?
Good girl.
PANGSTOP:
YOU LOOK SO STUPID PLAYING WITH THE DOG
PAPA MEOW:
WHAT A WASTE OF MY INTERNET USAGE
PAPA MEOW
LET ME EDUCATE YOU
LET ME EDUCATE YOU:
SERIOUSLY, WHAT'S THE POINT OF THIS?
PANGSTOP:
YOU LOOK SO STUPID PLAYING WITH THE DOG
PAPA MEOW:
WHAT A WASTE OF MY INTERNET USAGE
GOD OF WAR: LIKE WATCHING
AN IDIOT PLAY WITH A DOG
RRDAJI
GUESS THOSE 3,000 WATCHING
ARE NO DIFFERENT
IDIOTS LIKE WATCHING IDIOTS
Whoa.
Yesterday, I watched
from the very start of the live stream.
Honestly, I could watch them all day.
I agree. Jamie's cute,
and Hong's cute too.
- Oh, Jamie.
- Jamie.
We were just talking about you.
Hong was so adorable yesterday.
And when Hong walked over to you
and her tail kept wagging,
that was so cute.
I've always wondered
how you take care of her so well.
I can't believe Hong used to be a stray.
JAMIE ME HONG:
ADOPT, DON'T SHOP. DO IT LIKE US
HANDSOME AND KIND-HEARTED
I don't do much.
I just give her attention.
Wow.
Well, they say if you love dogs,
they'll be happy too, right?
I thought everyone
would get bored of my channel.
Bored? Never.
Can you do it every day?
- Really?
- I love watching it.
- So cute…
- Ah!
Jamie, right?
Are you Jamie from Jamie Me Hong?
Uh… yeah.
I'm a fan of your channel.
- I really like you and Hong.
- Really?
- Anyway, you are…
- Oh.
I'm Nanno.
I'm new here.
Nice to meet you, Nanno.
You know, I really like
how natural you are.
Even though your videos seem ordinary,
they're special.
Not like other people
who try so hard to create content,
trying to be somebody.
But it's a mess.
Thank you.
Can we take a selfie?
I want to be friends with a famous person.
- Sure.
- Really?
Thank you.
Well, I won't bother you anymore.
Feel free.
- Hello…
- Your name's Nanno.
I heard that.
I'm Hongtae.
Don't pretend you want to get to know me.
I don't even want to know myself.
Oh…
A loner?
That's nice.
I like solitude too.
For this question,
who knows the value of X?
Zero.
Correct, Jamie.
PANGSTOP: WHAT? I RAISED MY HAND FIRST.
WHY DIDN'T THEY CLAP FOR ME?
FINE. I'LL DIE ALONE
I DIDN'T REALIZE I HIT 200K FOLLOWERS
PANGSTOP: WHY DO SHALLOW PEOPLE
GET SO MANY FOLLOWERS?
WHATEVER. BRAIN ROT FOR EVERYONE
Hongtae.
Dinner's ready. Come downstairs.
I'll be right there.
Did something happen today?
Why do you look stressed?
It's nothing.
Actually, there is something.
I answered correctly in class today,
- but I don't understand why the teacher…
- Oh!
Jamie's about to go live
to celebrate 200,000 followers.
One second.
I must be follower number 200,000.
HONGTAE? HE CAN'T EVEN COMPETE WITH HONG
Hello, everyone.
Can you hear me?
Let's get started.
Thank you all again
for being with us
until we reached 200,000 followers.
Hong, you're happy too, right?
Say thank you. Thank you.
Hong says thank you.
Look, Hong. So many people have joined.
IS IT HARD TO TAKE CARE OF A FEMALE DOG?
Don't be shy.
FEMALE
Thank you.
Say thank you, Hong. Thank you.
HOW CAN YOU GRAB A FEMALE DOG'S BREASTS?
THAT'S SEXUAL HARASSMENT OF AN ANIMAL
What?
Someone posted
that I sexually harassed Hong?
What?
That's ridiculous.
Hong's adorable.
SOMEONE QUOTED YOUR POST
Everyone carries something called
an invisible ruler in their hand.
NAMELESS GODDESS:
THE DOG'S GOING TO GROW UP TRAUMATIZED
But then…
who will be the one struck the hardest?
YOU'RE NORMALI…
Hey!
Are you trying to normalize
sexually harassing animals?
I won't accept that!
ARE YOU TRYING TO NORMALIZE
SEXUALLY HARASSING ANIMALS?
Ban Jamie!
PANGSTOP: #BANJAMIE
Okay, let's get back to playing…
GOD OF WAR: I SAW THAT
GOD OF WAR: DID YOU HARASS AN ANIMAL?
You think just doing that
can stop me?
GOD OF WAR
LET ME EDUCATE YOU
PSYCHO. GRABBING A DOG'S BREASTS
HOW DO YOU THINK THE DOG FEELS?
DISGUSTING
RRDAJI
YOU'RE TRYING TO COVER IT UP
You're trying to cover it up
because you really did
sexually harass your dog, right?
RRDAJI: CAUGHT RED-HANDED
That's right.
Hong might grow up traumatized.
That's right. Ban him.
Ban Jamie.
Save Hong from that piece of shit.
HE NEEDS TO BE EXPOSED
DISGUSTING
TRASH
HE JUST ENDED THE LIVE
HIS FACE WENT PALE
NAMELESS GODDESS
AND 78 OTHERS FOLLOWED YOU
Damn.
Serves you right.
Who are you chatting with?
A friend, Mom.
Mom, you know,
I have tons of friends now.
PANGSTOP
EXPOSE HIM. THE EVIDENCE IS CLEAR.
THANK YOU FOR SAYING
WHAT NO ONE ELSE DARED TO.
UNBELIEVABLE. IT'S HIS OWN DOG.
EVEN IF IT'S A DOG,
IT DESERVES RESPECT.
What is it?
We came to comfort you
after last night's ridiculous backlash.
Seriously, it was so ridiculous.
Here.
Wow.
And to protect you
from those crazy people,
I have a gift for you.
What is it?
An outfit for Hong.
This way, no one will say
you touched a naked dog again.
Thank you.
For those of you who have pets,
don't forget to get them
vaccinated for rabies.
This is very important.
HONG'S OUTFIT IS SO CUTE
AREN'T YOU GOING TO ADDRESS THE ISSUE?
PAPA MEOW
All you're good at is running away.
You'll just go back
to harassing your dog again.
- Where are you going?
- Hey.
- Follow him.
- Hey!
- There.
- Hurry up.
- Follow him.
Confess it.
You didn't take her in out of kindness.
You're just perverted.
Perverted with animals.
Using a dog to satisfy your own desires.
Ban Jamie!
We've had enough!
This has gone too far!
I'm going to expose all of you.
I'LL EXPOSE ALL OF YOU #SAVEJAMIE
I AGREE #SAVEJAMIE
NANNO:
I'LL HELP TOO #SAVEJAMIE
Let's go!
DON'T GET COCKY
What do you mean "save Jamie"?
You should be saving Hong.
She's the one being harassed.
If dog owners can't even touch their dogs,
what are they supposed to touch, squid?
You're insane.
Don't be afraid.
We have more people than… Ouch!
Jamie's a good person.
Jamie is Hong's dad!
HONG FANCLUB: JAMIE'S A GOOD PERSON.
JAMIE IS HONG'S DAD #SAVEJAMIE
Think you're the only one
with a burner account?
Jamie's a good person!
Jamie is Hong's dad!
Jamie is Hong's dad.
Fall back for now.
We'll start another war tomorrow.
Fall back!
HATERS ARE GONE #SAVEJAMIE
WE WON THIS ROUND #SAVEJAMIE
LOSERS #SAVEJAMIE
DON'T JUST DISAPPEAR.
I'M CONCERNED #SAVEJAMIE
The adrenal gland is an organ
that produces
many important hormones for the body.
The chemical formula of the hormone…
Ban Jamie!
Save Jamie!
Let's go!
Everyone,
even if the save-Jamie side
has more people, don't worry.
We're smarter than they are.
Because we're more educated.
Let's educate these fans
so they stop being so stupid.
Make this bigger than before.
Go! Go!
Call the Animal Welfare Department.
I WOULD LIKE TO REPORT AN INFLUENCER
WHO SEXUALLY ABUSED HIS OWN PET
PLEASE ANSWER
What's this? Another surprise cake?
We just wanted to cheer you up
after all that backlash.
But don't worry. We'll protect you.
Like they say,
when you're famous,
you face more obstacles.
If you have fans, you'll have anti-fans.
That's normal.
Having anti-fans just means you're famous.
And those anti-fans
are already running out of ideas.
They just repeat the same insults.
If it stays like this,
the issue will die down on its own.
You don't have to do anything.
Don't worry.
I'm totally fine.
But thank you.
Come on, let's eat it together.
JAMIE ME HONG
JAMIE AND HONG
EP36: LATE-NIGHT CHAT
I first saw her
at the Bang Wa BTS station.
She was wandering around,
so I started to feed her every day.
But the more I fed her,
the more attached I became to her,
so I asked my mom if I could keep her.
When I first took her in,
she was very hyperactive.
But now?
At first, Hong was super…
active.
She's still super active now.
DOG FOR SALE 22/05/23
PET D
DOG FOR SALE
SOLD
22/05/23
Hong.
I'm going to class.
PANGSTOP: OOPS
FAKE BACKSTORY
FAMOUS INFLUENCER CLAIMS HE ADOPTED
A DOG BUT WAS SPOTTED AT A DOG FARM
AND THE DOG BEING SOLD THERE
HAS THE EXACT SAME MARKINGS
HONESTLY, I'M DISAPPOINTED
FAKE ADOPTION
Guys, I checked.
Jamie's absent today.
He said he's not feeling well.
Ugh. It must be about
that latest dog-buying issue.
Do you think it's true?
It's obviously fake news.
I agree.
But I don't understand
why everyone believes it.
Why is that?
Honestly, is there anything else
we can do to help Jamie?
Just to find the one who started it.
Yeah, I'm actually curious now.
Who is that jealous anti
who stirred everything up?
Oh.
I remember
that the account was named…
"Pangstop."
I wonder who that is too.
Maybe it's someone closer than we think.
PANGSTOP
#BANJAMIE
WHAT? I RAISED MY HAND FIRST
WHY DIDN'T THEY CLAP FOR ME?
DID HE REALLY ADOPT HER,
OR IS HE JUST LYING?
PANGSTOP
FAKE BACKSTORY
DELETE ACCOUNT
SO SURPRISED: HELLO, HONGTAE.
WHY DID YOU DELETE THAT POST?
PANGSTOP
Oh, Hongtae.
Aren't you going to chemistry class?
Everyone's already left.
And what are you going to do
with that ruler?
Nothing.
By the way,
what do you think about Jamie?
Why do you ask?
Jamie's been in the news lately.
So I was just wondering,
what do you think about Jamie?
He's nice.
Everyone likes him.
So that means…
you like Jamie too?
Really?
It's a shame.
I might as well confess.
I'm actually pretty indifferent
about Jamie.
But I pretend to like him
because I'm afraid of having no friends.
Jamie seems kind of fake.
No wonder the ban movement keeps growing.
I think…
if they push it hard enough,
#BanJamie could definitely trend
to number one.
Jamie should suffer a real impact.
Oops.
What did I just say?
But you wouldn't get involved
in something like that anyway, right?
Let's just forget about it.
Everyone, start the war.
Push the hashtag to number one.
Let the whole country know.
Ban Jamie!
HOPE YOUR MOM GETS GROPED LIKE THIS TOO
GOOD-LOOKING BUT FILTHY
Save Jamie! Go!
IT'S HIS DOG. WHY DOES IT BOTHER YOU?
NO ONE IS BETTER THAN YOUR MOM
Don't be afraid of them, dear! Fight them!
Fight them!
You jealous pieces of shit.
You've got issues? Broken family?
Do I need to spell it out?
Don't even.
You're just pretending to be nice
because you want Jamie
to be your boyfriend. It's obvious.
Guys, the dog farm just posted something.
WE'D LIKE TO CONFIRM THIS IS TRUE
MR. JAMIE PURCHASED A DOG
FROM OUR FARM ON MAY 22, 2023
PLOT TWIST #BANJAMIE
I've known for a while
but didn't dare speak up.
I'VE KNOWN FOR A WHILE
BUT DIDN'T DARE SPEAK UP
I'M READY TO BEAT HIM UP
Hey, everyone. I think
I found something strange.
It looks like the accounts named
Rrdaji,
Papa Meow,
God of War,
Let me educate you,
and Pangstop…
…might all belong to the same person.
Impressive, right?
I posted the original source in the group.
You can go say hi.
- Hey!
- Follow him!
- Where are you going?
Hey!
IDIOT
HELLO
I found you.
- Damn you.
- Come here!
What?!
Let go!
So here is where you are.
Reveal yourself.
Popcorn's ready.
- No!
- You're not getting away today.
No!
Don't!
Shit!
Let go!
NANNO:
OOPS. A PHOTO JUST DROPPED
Hey!
I'LL GO TO KOSHIEN IN 5 YEARS
Shit.
GUYS
I NEED TO SHARE THIS
LET ME GET ON MY X
OH, TURNS OUT IT WAS SOMEONE CLOSE
THE ONE NOBODY WANTS TO BE FRIENDS WITH
THE ONE WHO MAKES TRASH CONTENT
ATTENTION SEEKER
Damn it.
YOU WANNA BE FAMOUS?
I'LL HELP
JAKRAPAT HONGTRAKUL
CLASS 6/4, BOWORN SCHOOL
HE'S SO CRINGE
Leave me alone!
WHAT KIND OF FAMILY DID YOU GROW UP IN?
YOU'RE A TERRIBLE PARENT
PATHETIC
CAN IT GET ANY WORSE THAN THIS?
EXPOSE HIM
Stop!
Leave me alone!
IT'S GOING VIRAL
Damn you!
Stop!
Why?
Even though
Jamie
lied to everyone
and didn't even adopt that dog,
why are you still helping him?
Helping?
Helping Jamie?
No. I wasn't helping Jamie.
I've been helping you all along.
Helping me?
Yes.
IS IT HARD TO TAKE CARE OF A FEMALE DOG?
YOU HAVE TO BE CAREFUL, RIGHT?
You're trying to cover it up
because you really did
sexually harass your dog, right?
Yeah. He should be banned.
But what a surprise.
You went this far.
No one in class
can compete with you.
Hongtae,
you must really love Jamie.
What are you talking about?
Oh?
You still don't realize
what the outcome of this war is?
Did you really think
the account of a random boy
playing with a dog every day
with nothing new or interesting
could reach 500,000 followers on its own?
What you did
made everyone focus on Jamie
because humans love conflict.
They love violence.
Right?
I won't accept that!
Without your hatred,
Jamie wouldn't have gotten
this much attention.
It was fun.
Very fun.
Fight them!
I finally found you.
A stalker?
But you could only find me online, Sky.
Maybe not.
Go!
Anyway,
in the end,
this war ends with you being sacrificed.
But…
don't worry.
You've got plenty of fellow martyrs.
Everyone,
I'm sorry for disappearing recently.
I was seriously sick.
But I'm getting better now,
thanks to all of your support.
There's another thing
I want to tell everyone.
Lately,
a group of people
has been trying to defame me.
So I've decided
to sue both the ringleader,
whom I now know the identity of,
and all the followers involved.
At first, I hesitated,
not sure if I should sue.
But everyone told me
I should set an example,
so I have to do this.
Thank you all so much,
including the people
who sent me information.
Hong says thank you too, right?
Thank the fans.
PANGSTOP
You know that your support
is the best energy for me and Hong, right?
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
Zero.
Hongtae.
You're the cutest anti-fan ever.
Did you know that?
Jamie! Jamie!
It's my body.
I can do whatever I want with it.
I can show whatever I want.
It's my business.
My body, my choice.
The whole idea
that our bodies belong to us
is amazing.
If you hadn't inspired me,
we probably wouldn't be having
this much fun right now.
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon