They say
those who suffer pain
will pass that pain on to others.
So, do you want me to beat you,
or are you going to beat him?
-Hurry up.
-I'm sorry.
Harder.
-That's still too soft.
-I'm sorry.
That's because
hurting others
is the only way
they can ease the pain in their hearts.
Get up.
Humans are so fragile,
so weak,
so pitiful.
Will there ever be someone
who can stop this cycle?
I WAS SO STUPID TO BELIEVE NANNO EXISTS
DOES NANNO… EXIST?
IS NANNO A GOOD PERSON?
LEAKED PHOTOS OF MYSTERIOUS GIRL
RUMORED SHE IS "NANNO"
Hello.
THE NEW STUDENT
WHO KEEPS TRANSFERRING
FROM SCHOOL TO SCHOOL?
I'm Nanno.
I'm a new student here.
NANNO'S WAY OF REVENGE
THEY SAY SHE LIKES TO TAKE
BRUTAL REVENGE ON BAD PEOPLE
WHAT GOES AROUND COMES AROUND
BITCH
HOW CAN I FIND NANNO?
IF SHE WANTS TO SEE YOU,
SHE'LL COME TO YOU HERSELF
Nanno.
Have you been waiting long?
Let's go.
YOU WANT TO MEET ME?
HAHAHAHA
Mr. Sky.
During the exam the other day,
you didn't give me a single answer.
Didn't a word I said get through to you?
I'm giving you one last chance.
My report has to score higher than yours.
Sky, just do what Jom says.
I'm scared you'll end up dead.
You're not Nanno,
who can take revenge on everyone.
That's the way, buddy.
Come on, I'll treat you to a meal.
I'll submit the report first.
See you at the cafeteria.
See you, buddy.
YOU FUCKING BITCH TEACHER
WRITTEN BY JOMPOL TEWARATTANAKUN
I really don't understand.
Why would you do this to Teacher On-usa?
This is too much.
This time,
I'll have to report this to your father,
as well as your exam results.
Hello.
Yes.
About Jompol, I'll handle it myself.
Thank you, Teacher.
Well, about--
Don't talk about unpleasant things here.
This is so damn embarrassing, you clown.
Ja, how did the scholarship exam go?
I received a full scholarship
which pays through my doctorate.
Especially now that you're campaigning,
I want to help you however I can, Dad.
You know,
I've never expected anything from you,
so you don't need to apologize.
Everyone should be able
to make their own choices,
even trash like you.
Left hand or right hand?
Stop embarrassing me already,
you clown.
Look over there.
Where are you?
Where are you, buddy?
There you are, you bastard.
Okay.
I only found this.
You piece of shit.
But trash like you
deserves a choice too.
Are you going to hit it,
or should I beat you up instead?
Choose.
Well?
Hey. Damn.
You fucking idiot.
This isn't over yet.
What are you going to do?
Take off his underwear.
Don't, you asshole. Don't!
-Damn you.
-Don't!
No, no, no!
What are you doing?
Burn his hair.
Hey!
Hey, buddy.
Don't!
There's still some left.
Audi told me you like to search
about how to get revenge, right?
This right here.
This is what you call revenge.
Where's your Nanno? Go get her.
The next time you dare to mess with me,
you'll be famous.
And you'll go through this every day.
Every day.
Every single day.
But I'll always give
trash like you a choice.
Either you obey me,
or if you can't take it anymore…
just go die.
Look at your damn face.
DAD, MOM
If Nanno really doesn't exist,
maybe my death
will be the only way…
DAD, MOM, I'M SORRY
SKY
…to haunt him for the rest of his life.
I was so stupid
to believe Nanno exists.
Hello.
I'm Nanno.
I'm a new student here.
It's my first day.
But I guess I came a little too early.
Oh.
Then I won't disturb you.
Do you want me to help?
Nanno?
You're really Nanno?
Of course not.
Do you know how long
I've been searching for you?
I know.
I've already chatted with you.
The other day,
I even sent you a clue about me.
But you blocked me.
GIRL FROM NOWHERE:
YOU WANT TO MEET ME?
Oh.
So in the end,
are you stupid for believing I exist?
If I didn't exist,
that wouldn't be fun.
Hello.
That's great.
Hey.
What the hell is this?
Who did this?
Do you know what Jom fears the most?
I asked who did this!
It's the moment
when no one is afraid of him anymore.
It was you, right?
What's all this noise? Go sit down.
Just sit down for now, Jompol.
I'll handle this.
All right, everyone.
I have an announcement.
Today, we have a new student joining us.
Come in.
Hello. I'm Nanno.
I'm a new student here.
Nice to meet you all.
Go ahead and take any empty seat.
Yes.
All right, I'll hand out the test now.
Please focus.
What are you doing, Jompol?
What's that in your hand?
Unfold it.
I said unfold it.
It's actually poop!
-That's funny.
-Whose ass did he wipe with that?
All right, quiet down. Continue your test.
You said Nanno was behind all of this.
What do you mean?
Sky told me before that Nanno
likes to take revenge on bad people.
NANNO
I don't see any info
on what you're talking about.
But… but Sky told me.
Forget it.
If all of this came from her,
then let's just say she started it.
Hey!
No need to hide, Sky.
Or should I call it
hiding behind a skirt?
No one can help you.
Not even that fucking Nanno bitch.
Come out!
What the hell are you joking about, Sky?!
Why do you think it's me?
Everyone in this school hates you,
those two included.
Where are you?
I asked where you are!
Hey, Jom.
The hell is wrong with your hand?
I re-dressed the wound.
It should be fine now.
But if it hurts, lie down first.
What the hell is this?
COME MEET ME IN THE STORAGE ROOM
Hey.
What happened to your arm?
Is that some new type of bandage?
Pretty funny.
What's so damn funny, asshole?
Sorry.
Mjolnir?
Hey, are you making fun of my friend?
The hell are you laughing at?
Shut up!
Get off me!
Hey, where did the clown go?
Isn't he right next to you guys?
Ta-da!
That doll isn't
as funny as you are anymore, Jom.
Do you want to replace it?
You…
Your hand is so soft.
It feels like
I'm getting a massage.
Aren't you going to film it?
I think if this clip gets out,
lots of your friends will laugh at it.
Shut up!
You're really hurt now, aren't you, bitch?
Film it.
So anyone who dares mess with me
can see what they'll end up like.
Are you done talking?
I'm sleepy.
Damn it!
Shut up!
What the hell is wrong with you?!
I'm so happy that we've started filming.
From now on,
it's going to be even more entertaining.
Let me tell you something.
This will be a viral clip.
Because it's the funniest, Jom.
The hell are you laughing at?!
Shut up!
What?
From now on,
you won't be just your father's clown.
You'll be the entire school's clown.
Enough…
That's enough…
Go on, post it.
I know you've all hated Jom
for a long time.
How many times
has he made you his victims?
Humans aren't that hard to predict.
Those who suffer violence
pass violence on to others.
And those others
will continue passing it on.
How is this enough
to repay what you've done?
You bastard!
You idiot!
That's enough.
I didn't expect Jom to cry like that.
Really?
I thought you knew everything.
I just expected
a different kind of crying.
Did I make the right decision?
I just didn't want to become
the person I hate.
What made you interested in me?
Well…
everything that you are.
For example,
you made me realize
there are things we shouldn't give in on.
And…
you made me understand hope.
Like, every problem
should be handled properly.
Otherwise, you wouldn't come help me
and make things turn out like this.
Right?
But I don't think I helped anyone.
But you helped me a lot.
Actually, I gained a lot from you too.
Do you want anything else from me?
That's it?
Would it be okay
if I asked to stay by your side forever?
You won't be able to find me, Sky.
They've been upskirting us.
You have to deal with them, Teacher.
I'm Nanno. I'm a new student here.
Why did you want to study here?
The guys here are cute.
And they're nice too.
Nanno.
I bet she could go for a high price.
You don't have to secretly film me.
If you just ask nicely,
I'd show you anyway.
Take it.
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon