Van's right.
None
It's my fault.
I was being selfish.
None
I didn't think about
how you would feel.
None
I'm really sorry, guys.
Wait
None
was Dave with you?
He hasn't come back
from his classes.
None
Let's look for him!
Dave, where have you been?
None
I needed fresh air after class.
On the verge of Bloody Night?
None
Do I need to be a demon like them?
Do I need to be more
savage than them?
None
I am the Supreme Student Secretary.
I have the right to object
None
to your decisions.
Let us talk about the big event
None
that's going to happen in this school.
And we will call it.
None
Bloody Week.
Where killing is legal in
a span of a week.
None
At any time.
We know that you know HU's secrets.
None
I will do everything in my power so
all of you can leave this hellhole.
None
What happened to you?
I was one of their test subjects for
the serum that they're making.
None
This is an order from the SSG President
if I say something
None
you answer quickly.
Got it?
None
You know
you just might be my Achilles' heel.
None
Ms. Shion.
Just tell me where the
laboratory is hidden.
None
Come with me.
I'll show you.
None
Where's the laboratory?
Just tell me where
the laboratory is.
None
The laboratory you're
looking for is...
None
It's hidden at...
Just tell me where it is please.
None
It's hidden at...
What are you doing?
None
What the fuck!
She’s going to die anyway.
None
I saved her from her suffering.
Why are you doing this
you crazy bitch?
None
I'm just saving you.
Us.
None
Stay away from Alvarez.
Chill
None
hurting me won't do you any good.
I'm just saving you.
None
Us.
Stay away from Alvarez.
None
Listen, Zein.
If you accept Ace's offer
None
you'll be able to find out
where the hidden laboratory is.
None
Secret lab.
Being the SSG secretary
has its benefits.
None
You'll know everything.
Learn things no one else can.
None
Once you take this position
you'll have control
None
and people will fear you for it.
They're heartless!
None
Monsters!
You're just like them.
None
You're a monster too.
We thought you're
the next Samantha
None
but just like her,
you can't change anything.
None
Why was she able to do something?
I thought...
None
you're like Samantha.
But you're not.
None
You're a coward.
Who is this Samantha
they keep mentioning?
None
Why are they calling
me her name?
None
Who is she?
Her name is Samantha.
None
We all thought it would last forever.
But nothing is for sure here in Hell U
None
except for bloodshed and death.
What's worse is...
None
the demons became more brutal.
Are you going to help us or not?
None
Us? There are others?
Wait!
None
Where are you going?
I still have a lot of questions left.
None
Where is the lab?
Just tell me where it is please!
None
It's better to be careful, Zein.
Because our lives are in your hands.
None
Don't ever cross the line with them.
I've been explaining this multiple times
None
and you still can't understand?
My throat is hurting
from all these lectures!
None
How are you this stupid?
Get a grip!
None
What do you want to happen?
Are you going to be
this stupid forever?
None
I'm sorry, ma'am.
That's just a piece of cake, idiot!
None
You never listen to any of it
that's why it doesn't
seep into your brain!
None
Airhead!
Enough. I told you
to stop it, didn't I?
None
How dare you!
You stupid girl!
None
You brain doesn't absorb
anything doesn't it?
None
I said stop it!
I'm so tired of this!
None
You're always picking on me.
Embarrassing me.
None
I have no face to show
because of you.
None
If I'm stupid
and you're smart?
None
Prove it to me and answer this question.
When do you think
you're going to die?
None
I'm aware a lot will
happen this Bloody Week.
None
But I didn't expect it would be this bad.
The week has barely started
None
but this is already unbearable to me.
How worse can it get in the incoming days?
None
What are the horrors in store for us?
Zein!
None
I'm going to kill you!
There are moments
where I start to lose hope.
None
that we'll make it out
of Hell University alive.
None
My friends are my only source of strength
to continue fighting.
None
Hey...
you're spacing out again.
None
We're going to get through this.
Where are they?
None
You know what, Zein
with everything going on.
None
My fear and nervousness
lessens when we're together.
None
Just like yesterday
you made us worry
None
but we trust you.
Didn't we make a promise
None
that we'll stick together?
I need to go.
None
I thought we'll stick together?
We are sticking together
None
we'll see each other again.
But I need to do something.
None
You know as a sexytary.
I like that. Sexytary.
None
And Van's there.
You won't be alone.
None
So don't worry too much, okay?
Go on.
None
Do a good job, Ms. Sexytary.
Come join us, Zein!
None
Catch this, Zein!
- Bye, Zein.
- Bye.
None
- She's so busy.
- Hurry!
None
Here, Dave.
Nice one.
None
I'm still supposed to be angry at him
after he didn't do anything
to stop Bloody Week.
None
But I don't know.
I'm still impressed by his
bravery and composure
None
amidst the chaos.
He's built different.
None
I still can't believe he
protected me from Madam Violet.
None
At least he's still fair.
Does he think of me as a friend?
None
Alex Mendoza, Supremo.
X on it, Ms. Shion.
None
Do it!
But why?
None
He's still alive.
You're wasting our time here, Ms. Shion.
None
If you were in my shoes
what would you do?
None
I would save him.
Okay.
None
Let's say we help him
and he lives.
None
What do you think will happen next?
That'll be all?
None
Will his enemies let him stay alive?
But...
None
Why waste my time with someone
who’s supposed to be dead?
None
We can't save everyone, Ms. Shion.
You and Matt said the same thing.
None
I'm going to kill you!
Zein!
None
Killing is legal now.
You might get hurt from
stepping in their fight!
None
We can't save everybody Zein!
Matt said the same thing.
None
Sir Alvarez
you're ten minutes late
for your next subject.
None
I needed to do something, Supremo.
I'm rushing over there.
None
Excuse me.
What's your relationship with him?
None
Nothing.
Supremo.
None
I've secured the files.
Um... Supremo
None
is there anything else
you need me to do?
None
None.
You're good.
None
Angelica, show me through it.
Okay.
None
I can review.
You can leave.
None
But my duty is not done.
Excuse me?
None
Angelica and I can handle it.
We can take it from here.
None
Really? Angelica?
Supremo called her by her first name
None
while he calls me by my surname?
What am I even talking aboout?
None
Matthew might be looking for you.
Obviously.
None
They're so annoying!
Who does he think he is?
None
You have a lot of nerve, Supremo.
This one, solve this.
None
Try me.
Don't you dare!
None
Let me go!
Be quiet!
None
Shut up, stay away.
Get me out of this hell!
None
Let go off me!
If you don't
None
I'll kill this girl!
Supremo...
None
Let's leave, Supremo.
I'm not kidding!
None
How could I forget?
Other people's lives have no value to them.
None
Zein!
Even my life.
None
Why would he help me?
Let her go!
None
I'm just his secretary.
Let me go!
None
Who are you going to kill again?
Zein!
None
Who'll die now?
What's happening to you, Zein?
None
Almost...
he's still alive.
None
Zein.
You're bleeding.
None
This won't kill me.
Let me out of this hellhole!
None
The wound is shallow.
What happened to
you earlier, Zein?
None
I don't know.
It's like I was possessed.
None
Even your eyes were
different earlier.
None
It's like the eyes of a killer.
That's too much.
None
She didn't kill anyone,
Jerome. Stop it.
None
I know that
but...
None
she became different.
I even hesitated if
I should help Matt
None
but I was afraid that
you might stab me.
None
Zein won't do that.
But you were a different
person earlier, Zein.
None
I felt your rage.
It's like you turned
into a monster.
None
Me?
A monster?
None
You're wasting your
time, nurse Cha.
None
That's just a flesh wound.
Who was that?
None
That's Dr. Razon.
There's a doctor here?
None
He doesn't seem to care
about us students.
None
What happened?
Where have you been?
None
I got stuck outside.
I was hiding until
the chaos stopped.
None
Where are they?
Don't tell me...
None
This can't be.
I shouldn't think this way.
None
But if they're not in their rooms
that only means one thing.
None
This has been going
on for a while.
None
Van?
They leave every night.
None
What?
We need to find them!
None
Zein
not tonight, please.
None
Van
what is happening?
None
Have you known they were
sneaking out all this time?
None
I'm scared, Zein.
Of what?
None
I've been waking up at night
recurringly with the boys gone.
None
Sometimes Matt
then Dave
None
and Jerome.
I don't know where
they're sneaking off to.
None
But they keep leaving
during Bloody Night.
None
I'll figure out where they keep going to.
Zein, please.
None
Van...
We're the only ones here.
None
Let's stick together.
Just this night.
None
Please.
Please, Zein.
None
Didn't we already talk about this, Van?
This is only for emergencies.
None
We need to survive Bloody Week
if we want to leave this place.
None
Our lives are in danger, Zein.
If we don't help ourselves
None
who will help us?
Help!
None
Help me!
Jerome?
None
Help me!
Please!
None
Jerome!
Help me!
None
♪ Happy birthday to you! ♪
♪ Happy birthday. ♪
None
♪ Happy birthday to you! ♪
Oh my god, Jerome.
None
You guys scared me there!
Happy birthday, Ms. Secretary!
None
Happy birthday!
Thank you so much guys!
None
I forgot my own birhtday.
It's because you have too
much on your mind!
None
Good thing we thought about you.
Did we do a good job?
None
Super!
Thank you so much guys.
None
But you didn't have to.
Of course, Zein.
None
Go on, Matt. Aren't you
going to greet Zein?
None
He's right, your saliva
will dry up.
None
I'm doing it, guys.
That's our boy.
None
Happy birthday, Zein.
That's our boy!
None
Thank you, Matt.
She's turning red!
None
I think she's more than okay.
Let's go, Zein. Blow the candle?
None
Here she comes.
Make a wish.
None
Yey!
Happy birthday!
None
Let's eat!
Let's go!
None
And because it's your
birthday, sit in the middle.
None
Our princess.
Thank you, guys.
None
Who cooked this?
Of course, there's no one but Mia!
None
Wow, Mia!
Okay?
None
Yeah.
It says in the student records
None
that the percentage of absentees are high.
List it down. Okay?
None
Prepare it.
I'll take care of it.
None
Check it properly since you volunteered.
Make sure you won't make any mistakes
None
or Supremo will reprimand you again.
Fine.
None
Since you guys can’t expect anything
from your good for nothing secretary.
None
Hey
why are you so damn happy?
None
That's none of your business.
Watch your words.
None
Onel!
What's the occassion?
None
I think it's better if you
ask Ms. Secretary, Supremo.
None
What? I don't know anything.
Okay, can somebody just tell me
None
what we're supposed
to be celebrating?
None
Nevermind.
Just leave!
None
All of you.
Why are you so happy?
None
Why are you smiling?
Am I not allowed to?
None
You know
instead of wasting your time
None
thinking about why I'm smiling
you should focus on Bloody Week.
None
Cause what's happening around us
should be taken seriously.
None
Fine.
Just leave me alone.
None
Gladly.
I said leave.
None
Okay, I'm leaving.
So impatient.
None
I'm leaving.
Bye!
None
Why does he care if I'm smiling?
He should mind his own business.
None
Just like yesterday
when someone tried to kill
me and he didn't do anything.
None
He was right.
You're weird.
None
Um... Zein right?
You amaze me.
None
You're really one of a kind.
I saw how you defended yourself yesterday.
None
I can only tell you one thing
he believes in you.
None
Even if he wanted to help you
he restrained himself from doing it.
None
I had my doubts but.
I was wrong.
None
I'm sorry
I've been blabbering.
None
Okay,
I'll go ahead.
None
What is she talking about?
Do I have the wrong impression about Ace?
None
Why are people acting so weird today?
It could've been perfect.
None
If only someone added sugar in the cake.
True.
None
It was already tastleless,
but it collapsed too!
None
What a waste.
I know, it's my fault.
None
I got tensed and distracted by the smoke
that's why I forgot to add in sugar.
None
I'm sorry, Zein. I'm sorry.
At least we decorated it well.
None
It looked like an actual birthday cake.
He's right.
None
Right, Matt?
And it's the thought that counts.
None
You liked it, didn't you, Zein?
Of course.
None
I enjoyed it.
Thank you, guys.
None
I couldn't ask for more.
You guys look like you're having fun.
None
Here he is again.
But I need my secretary.
None
Can't you function without your secretary?
So I'm still his secretary, huh?
None
I thought I was already replaced.
Sorry guys,
None
duty calls.
You can go ahead.
None
Let's see each other at the dorm later.
Okay?
None
Um, okay.
What do you need?
None
You really won't tell me about it?
Did I really have to look into it?
None
Do you enjoy giving me a hard time?
I knew there was
something about your smile.
None
You made my head hurt from thinking.
Huh?
None
Happy birthday...
Zein.
None
I always thought Ace ignored my existance.
That he didn't care.
None
But with three words,
he made me feel seen.
None
And for whatever reason, I appreciate it.
Good morning, students.
None
What is this again?
Do you find Bloody Week a little boring?
None
Then let's play a game.
To make Bloody Week more exciting!
None
Look inside your lockers.
On the paper are names you have to kill
None
before the time runs out.
If you didn't get a name.
None
You are chosen to die.
Did you know about this?
None
No.
Where are we going?
None
Check your locker.
Supremo's here. Let's go!
None
Open it.
Do I have to?
None
Do I have to do this?
Is this really happening?
None
You can check it.
I'll be here with you, okay?
None
I'll stay with you.
Hey...
None
Hey.
Calm down.
None
Calm down, breathe.
Calm down, okay?
None
What if I pick one of my friends?
Or your name?
None
Don't look too far, okay?
Let's check it first
None
then we'll see from there.
Okay?
None
For you.
What is it?
None
A gift.
For Bloody Night.
None
There's nothing written here.
Nothing.
None
It will last one whole week!
And we will call it Bloody Week.
None
Where killing is legal for one whole week.
I'm tired of you!
None
I'm always you're target!
I'm done with you embarassing me.
None
- Be quiet. Don't come near us.
- Help me!
None
Let me out of this hellhole!
If you get targeted by the gangs
None
you will never find peace again.
No!
None
I tried to ignore the
recurring disappearance
None
of my friends during Bloody Night.
But I can't turn a blind eye anymore.
None
I need to know what's
happening with my friends.
None
Hoy!
Did you hear that?
None
Something moved back there.
That's just the cat.
None
Is he upstairs?
Can we really trust him?
None
He's instantly the co-leader?
That doesn't make sense.
None
What else can we do?
Boss likes him.
None
And let's give him a chance.
Boss sees something in him.
None
I hope he's right...
This gang war has been tiring
None
we always have to be one
step ahead of the DGW.
None
Let's go.
Let’s go.
None
Let's hurry before Boss gets mad.
I want you to see everything.
None
Who is Van talking to?
That's Liam.
None
Who was written in your paper?
Anonymous.
None
There are things we should keep hidden.
You're drunk.
None
So what if I'm drunk?
Even if I'm drunk.
None
I know
that you're still beautiful.
None
You promised that when you find the
man you'll love for the rest of your life
None
you'll love him forever.
The wound is deep!
None
Doc!
Please hurry!
None
Open the door!
We're sorry but the clinic is closed today.
None
Ms. Shion!