Not disappointed.
None
Surprised
It seems Supremo has a heart for you.
None
I don't need him or want his help.
Do you have a family?
None
Are you Shion?
Why are you suddenly so into small talk?
None
My oldest sister, Allison.
The eldest daughter's textbook
None
she is good at everything, she is beautiful
and brave.
None
I am done.
A little slower than I thought.
None
But
You can go now.
None
Who is more handsome?
me or Supremo?
None
Of course, you!
Do you have time for your friends?
None
but when I call you
It's not right to keep me waiting.
None
Okay.
If that's all, goodbye...
None
Almighty.
You remind me of someone.
None
Madam?
You will regret this.
None
Raze will know about this.
Is it true?
None
Are you the one who started the fight with Roxane?
Aren't you afraid?
None
You are endangering yourself.
What do you think the boss will do to him?
None
Death.
I'm sure he'll kill him.
None
You are not Raze Silvenia.
Shut your mouth!
None
Your secret is my secret too.
Hey!
None
Where do you think you're going?
Let go!
None
Thank goodness, you're safe!
Do you always want to make us worry about you?
None
I thought we were all in this together?
Why do you always do all this alone?
None
What matters is that he is here now.
He's right, Wan.
None
No.
Van is right. This is my fault.
None
I am being selfish.
I don't even think about how you'll feel.
None
I'm really sorry, friends.
Thank you to all of you.
None
I'm grateful that you're here.
Even though this place is like a hellhole.
None
We are friends.
we will stay together
None
no matter what hell we will face.
Wait
None
Is Dave with you?
What?
None
He didn't.
Hah?
None
Then where is he?
He hasn't come home from class yet.
None
Let's find him!
Hah?
None
The Bloody Night has begun.
How can we find it?
None
Zein, your carelessness has rubbed off on him.
Are you really blaming me for this?
None
I'm kidding, you're too serious.
But where is he?
None
He knows best that the people in this place
turning to the wild at this time.
None
Friends, please help. Let's find him!
No one will be left behind, right?
None
Mia is right.
Dave can't live alone outside.
None
It's too dangerous.
This will be dangerous
None
but I got in.
Matt and I will look for him.
None
Wait, wait!
Isn't it you who said
None
that it's dangerous outside
When is Bloody Night?
None
Now, do you want to go out?
If anything happens to you two
None
it will be harder for everyone.
Zein is right.
None
It would be even worse if you both disappeared too.
We'll just wait for him here.
None
He will return to us.
Okay?
None
Let's guard these doors.
So we can open the door immediately
None
as soon as he returns.
Okay?
None
Me.
Where did Dave go?
None
Is the right decision waiting for him?
Is he still alive?
None
What if he runs into the Black Blood Gang?
Now I know how my friends feel.
None
when I left without telling them.
In this place
None
The night is longer than the day.
If you want to live
None
You have to endure all the screaming until morning.
Dave...
None
Dave, where did you go?
Ouch.
None
It hurts.
What happened?
None
Where are you going?
I hid outside until the noises stopped.
None
Dave? Dave!
Hey!
None
Dave!
We are very worried about you.
None
Water... I'll get some water for him.
Here, drink some water.
None
What's out there?
What happened to you, sister?
None
Why are you back so late?
Didn't you notice at that time?
None
I need some fresh air after class.
On the brink of Bloody Night?
None
Do you need to catch your breath?
Why?
None
I'm sorry, guys. I don't want you to worry.
I should take a nap.
None
Dave!
But seriously, does he need to come up for air?
None
He should have known better.
Exactly right.
None
You should know better too, Zein.
Now you know how it feels
None
when one of your friends leaves during Bloody Night.
He's not funny, is he?
None
Excuse me.
Man, man...
None
you know
You need to rest.
None
Calm down.
We just sleep.
None
You're right, let's just sleep.
Dave!
None
Oh my God! Oh my God!
We're going to be late!
None
Is Sir Alvarez's class your first class?
Exactly. What are we going to do?
None
We're past it.
Stop overreacting.
None
We can skip class.
because it will be ready in thirty minutes.
None
Don't you know today is our regular exam, Zein?
Is it really?
None
Oh God
I was not informed.
None
You shouldn't be complacent, Zein.
What if we fail the class?
None
Good morning!
You know since we're late.
None
Let's eat a little.
FT, bro.
None
Feet!
Hey
None
no one cares
that periodic tests are 16% of our grade.
None
We will definitely fail.
What about our dream of getting into the top ten?
None
I almost forgot.
That's why they're so disappointed.
None
they will not be able to join the top ten.
They will not be able to leave this place.
None
It's out. It's out.
Top ten or not, we're getting out of this place.
None
Do you know, friends?
That's hunger talking.
None
Let's just eat.
so we can calm down.
None
It smells delicious!
Hey, is that porridge?
None
Of course so.
Zain's favorite.
None
And everyone's favorite.
Okay, let's just eat.
None
Let's go.
- You're very thoughtful. - I'll help you, Mia.
None
I will set the table.
I'll help you with that.
None
I'll put this here.
Okay.
None
This is my station.
Periodic examinations?
None
Has anyone passed such an exam at Hell U?
Isn't surviving the Bloody Night more important?
None
from any type of exam?
Check your face.
None
Sometimes, Jerome is right.
Good, bro.
None
Whatever
if you fail
None
Don't come crying to us, okay?
Me?
None
Yes, you!
I cry?
None
Exactly right.
That's for the weak.
None
Like you.
Hey, Zein. Are you okay?
None
Doesn't that feel bad?
It's delicious.
None
You are a great cook.
Hey
None
They pretended like we weren't in this room anymore.
I smelled something fishy.
None
Jerome, you know what?
That's hunger talking.
None
Come on, I'll stuff this bone into your mouth.
Are you done with your assignment?
None
Why?
The subject discussion is wrong.
None
Oh, fu-
What's that?
None
It looks real.
I don't know.
None
Should we be worried?
What do you think?
None
It was Dave's fault.
Yes, it's Dave's fault once again.
None
Why me always?
Good morning, sir.
None
Shion's daughter.
Men
None
I will continue.
I need to take care of something.
None
I will follow you.
No need, Matt.
None
You know, the job of the SSG Secretary.
Trust me, I can do this.
None
Goodbye.
Let's go.
None
Ms. Shion, why weren't you here earlier?
Sir, can we retake this exam?
None
You do not need to retake your exam.
I will make sure your grades are high even without him.
None
Are you really going to do that?
My friends will be happy to hear about this.
None
I appreciate this, sir.
Don't say thank you again.
None
How is your secretary's job?
Hell.
None
It's very difficult to connect with people.
who are not on the same wavelength.
None
But why is that a concern, sir?
Don't worry about your grades.
None
I will take care of that.
But remember what you need to do for me.
None
Thank you, sir.
but I don't have any ideas yet
None
about where the hidden lab is located.
Even SSG members
None
hasn't mentioned anything about it.
Are you sure there is one?
None
Naturally
they won't mention it to you.
None
Trust me.
just do your secretarial duties
None
monitor all their movements.
What if they catch me, sir?
None
I'm not ready to die yet, Sir Alvarez.
I still need to escape
None
with my friends
from this hell hole.
None
Be careful, Zein.
because everyone's safety is now in your hands.
None
There is a storm coming.
Be a devil.
None
Get along well with SSG and admin.
But don't ever empathize with them.
None
Can you do that?
Do I have to be a devil like them?
None
so I can fight fairly?
Should I be more violent than them?
None
I don't want to die yet.
Please.
None
We can't do anything.
They have no heart.
None
You are a monster!
You are just like them.
None
You are a monster!
We thought you were going to be the next Samantha.
None
but just like him, you can't fix anything.
Samantha?
None
Number nine?
Number nine!
None
You are a monster!
Monsters! All of you!
None
Good morning.
Mrs. Violet.
None
Mr. Francisco.
Good morning.
None
Isn't Teacher Shion going to welcome us?
Good morning, Mr. Francisco.
None
Mrs. Violet.
Samantha.
None
Madam
Let's get started.
None
Good morning, our beloved students.
We are gathered here today.
None
to honor our late principal
Dominic Valdez.
None
I am happy.
that we are free from his foolish leadership after all these years.
None
After all these years.
Isn't it funny?
None
No!
He didn't commit suicide!
None
You killed Principal Valdez!
They killed him?
None
Who said he was dead?
You are right.
None
we have killed him.
And you will be next.
None
Just follow us.
Let me go!
None
Where are you taking me?
Stop fighting.
None
This doesn't make sense!
By!
None
You killed the late principal.
Why was he punished?
None
Should you both be punished?
Oh? You can all laugh now!
None
However you try to hide it
the student body knows
None
that you killed the headmaster!
Get rid of him!
None
No!
Stop!
None
Let go!
You can't do that.
None
Vans are protected under council regulations.
You really tested me, Ms. Shion.
None
Get rid of him!
Touch her one more time or you will regret it.
None
Stop this deception, Saman-
Which Shion?
None
Why do I need to?
Am I right?
None
First of all
you have no right to carry out the sentence
None
because only Supremo can do that.
Second
None
the way you stand here
seems disrespectful.
None
How do you expect
to gain our respect?
None
And finally,
I am the Supreme Student Secretary.
None
I have the right to object.
your decision.
None
Is there anything else I forgot, Mrs. Violet?
Great
None
control your secretary.
He is right.
None
Great
You should punish your rude secretary.
None
Why?
He actually deserves an award.
None
instead of punishment
because of all the secretaries I've ever worked with
None
he is the only one who knows
that I am the only one who can carry out the punishment here.
None
Now, based on the student council rules
That looks amazing.
None
Isn't that right, Madam?
Ace Craige.
None
Did I forget something?
Mr. Francisco?
None
No but
Let's not forget why we are here.
None
Let's go back to what I said a moment ago.
Let's talk about that big event.
None
that will happen at this school.
It will last for a whole week!
None
And we will call him.
Bloody Week.
None
Where killing is legal within a week.
At any time.
None
Good luck everyone.
Apparently half of the population of Hell University
None
want it.
Seriously?
None
Do you have a problem with that?
Are you Shion?
None
If it's already been determined
forgive me
None
I will prepare for Bloody Week.
It seems we all should.
None
So, how are you feeling now, Vanessa?
Fear
None
but great.
They deserve it.
None
That's not even half of my anger.
You know, you're reckless too.
None
Why did you do that?
Do you want to end up like me?
None
Flagged by admin?
At least
None
there are two of us.
It will be difficult to track.
None
You are very brave.
You're overreacting.
None
I am serious
that's why.
None
I'm falling more and more in love with you.
Excuse me.
None
You almost got hit.
But wait, friends.
None
I almost died there.
Good thing.
None
Madam Secretary has come to the rescue.
Mrs. Violet couldn't do anything about it.
None
Nothing?
But Zein, what you're doing is making me worried.
None
How did you find out about those rules?
Is that true or
None
Did you make it up at the last minute?
Zein wouldn't lie about that.
None
He will be in more danger.
Those rules are true.
None
I read it in the SSG bylaws.
Supremo is the only one
None
who has the power to carry out the death penalty as punishment
to anyone who breaks the law
None
or anyone who rebels against the University of Hell.
Supremo overcomes HU professor.
None
Wise...
At least we know that the student council is pro-student.
None
I almost forgot.
Our grades are taken care of.
None
Sir Alvarez supports us.
Greetings?
None
Did you hear what I said earlier?
I said
None
We didn't fail history class.
Shouldn't we celebrate it?
None
You know
Our questions will not be answered by themselves.
None
Why are you keeping that a secret from us, Zein?
What do you mean?
None
I don't want to go anymore.
What?
None
We know you know the secret of HU.
And we know you can't leave this place again.
None
Wait, what?
How did you know that?
None
Do you think we are noobs?
Of course we notice when you keep something a secret from us.
None
You are our friend.
You are very stubborn.
None
You always help us but you don't think about yourself.
I need to protect you all.
None
I will do everything I can so that you can all leave this hellhole.
You mean us.
None
We will all leave this hellhole.
You think we're going to let you get stuck here?
None
I'll put you all first, Matt.
I had to.
None
We will escape together, Zein.
No one will be left behind, remember?
None
Okay, we'll stay together.
And don't worry.
None
we already know.
What do you mean?
None
We know about Dr. Quizon
and the secret formula for bringing the dead back to life
None
and the oath was very great.
And to be honest
None
I thought it was a joke.
If we don't get out of here
None
We will rot together in this hell hole.
You are not alone, Zein.
None
We will never leave you alone.
We will die here together.
None
No. I can't let us die here.
You're heartless!
None
You can do something about this.
But you're scared.
None
That's where you're wrong.
I can't do anything.
None
I'm just a secretary.
Why is he able to do something?
None
I think
You're like Samantha.
None
But I was wrong.
You are a coward.
None
Who is this Samantha you mean?
Why does everyone call me that?
None
Who is he?
He was once a new person
None
like you.
But the difference between you two
None
is that
he has helped us.
None
Is he the former Secretary of SSG?
I need your help!
None
I don't know how long I'll last
from all the serums they injected me with.
None
What happened to you?
They used me as a human test subject.
None
They experimented on me.
I was one of their test subjects for a serum they created.
None
Serum?
Wait
None
Did they take you to the lab?
Do you know where it is hidden?
None
Don't block their way.
if you don't want to be like me.
None
How can I help you?
If you can't tell me where they took you?
None
You don't know what you're facing.
Just help me.
None
But how can I help you?
If you don't show me where the secret lab is?
None
Can you help me or not?
We?
None
Is there anything else?
Wait, where are you going?
None
I still need an answer!
Where is the laboratory?
None
Didn't I warn you?
Stay away from Alvarez.
None
Why do you care?
Very stupid.
None
It's really slow, right?
You know
None
You did a great job at the party.
Don't ever offend the admin again.
None
Or me.
Hey
None
What's bothering you?
Hey...
None
What's your problem?
I have no problem.
None
Look.
I'm just tired.
None
Can you please leave me alone?
So I can finish this.
None
and relax.
Let me help you.
None
Let me understand that.
You don't have to.
None
I can handle this.
This is my punishment, right?
None
I can do it myself.
I'll get you some dirty cloth.
None
Could today get any weirder?
What is he planning?
None
Why is he helping me when he's the one who gave me this punishment?
Have you found any rags?
None
Yes.
Don't touch anything
None
or they will say I don't respect you.
Do you really trust or care about the opinions of others?
None
I don't want to get into trouble.
You won't get in trouble.
None
Don't be reckless anymore.
Shion's daughter.
None
Are you serious?
Does it look like I'm kidding?
None
This is an instruction from the President of SSG
if i say something
None
You answer quickly.
Understand?
None
Hey
I answered.
None
Yes.
You know
None
You may be my weakness.
Shion's daughter.
None
Here...
for you.
None
What's that?
Prize.
None
You're quiet again.
I have received your gift.
None
What else do you want me to say?
Won't you thank me?
None
Thank You.
I'm going out.
None
You should go back to SSG too.
before the Bloody Night.
None
Does that mean you care about me?
No, it is not.
None
You want.
Just so you know.
None
For your information
I wouldn't care anyway
None
if you are stuck outside during Bloody Night.
Or even if you die.
None
You don't need to worry.
I can take care of myself.
None
Shion's daughter.
Be careful.
None
Alright. Goodbye, Supremo.
Sleep well.
None
There's still a lot I need to do for you...
Which one?
None
Huh? He called me by my first name.
I am very hungry.
None
Look who's here.
Hai, Zein.
None
How are you?
Luckily you were here before the alarm went off.
None
Thank you, brother.
Let's eat first.
None
before the official start
Bloody Week.
None
What's this?
Our last meal on earth?
None
Hey, don't be like that.
Can't we just eat something delicious in peace?
None
before the riots outside started?
Let's enjoy the food.
None
Matt cooked it.
Wow, are you cooking again?
None
This should be delicious!
To lure you back to the dorm early.
None
By the way
What is your punishment?
None
Looks like you finished early today.
This is because someone helped me.
None
WHO?
Almighty.
None
Wah, Zein.
You are built differently now.
None
even the student government president helps you clean up.
Hey
None
I didn't ask him to help me.
He did it willingly.
None
Why are you being defensive?
Maybe you're into Supremo?
None
Watch your words, Wan.
We're not even friends, how can we be lovers?
None
Whatever.
Matt's dish looks delicious!
None
Adobo!
Let's eat, friends.
None
Yes, while the rice is still lukewarm.
Stay away from Ace.
None
Hah?
Why?
None
I will get some water.
Did I say something wrong?
None
He's just jealous.
You know he's in love with you.
None
You should take it easy.
He's right, Zain.
None
Don't be the kind of person who feels sorry for Matt.
He's just worried about you.
None
Griefer? Apa?
Just search.
None
Come on, let's eat.
Go ahead.
None
Are you okay?
Water, do you want some?
None
I have weapons ready for us.
What weapon?
None
What is this for?
We need to be prepared.
None
For Bloody Night?
Sunday, Zein.
None
Bloody Week.
I'm not sure if I'm ready for this.
None
Didn't we talk about this, Van?
And this is for emergency purposes only.
None
Let's just hide them in our bags.
for protection.
None
Is that right, Matt?
This is a bad idea, friends.
None
This is necessary.
Starting tonight until the end of the week
None
We will walk on the side of death.
So if you don't want to go with him
None
we need to defend ourselves.
No!
None
I don't want this, Dave!
We are not murderers.
None
We're just defending ourselves, okay?
We have to get through Bloody Week.
None
if we want to leave this place.
I...
None
Our lives are in danger, Zein.
If we will not help ourselves
None
who will help us?
Nobody!
None
I'll hide them both, Zein.
If you change your mind.
None
Matt...
Catch him!
None
Why are you doing this?
Why? You took her away from me!
None
What!
We can't do anything to save them.
None
You might get hurt!
Matt, if I can't do anything about this...
None
they will kill each other.
What is the use of Bloody Sunday
None
if no one dies?
Zein, kita tak boleh buat apa-apa pasal ni.
None
What?
Fuck all this! Someone stop them!
None
We can't save everyone, Zein.
We have bigger problems than this.
None
He's right, Zain.
Be strong, please!
None
Listen to him, Zein!
This is not even the beginning.
None
This is just a pre-match.
I can't stand to see people kill each other.
None
without doing anything!
Which one...
None
What do you think you can do about this, Zein?
Huh? Tell us.
None
Which one?
Don't approach them.
None
Die already!
Just tell me where the lab is hidden.
None
I'll show you.
We can't save everyone...
None
Shion's daughter.
Matt also said the same thing.
None
You know what, Zein.
Of all that has happened
None
It calms my heart and mind knowing we are all together.
Happy birthday, Zain.
None
That's our boy!
Hey
None
Why are you so happy?
It's none of your business.
None
Why are you so happy?
Almighty.
None
I have secured the files.
You can go now.
None
Matthew might be looking for you.
It's obvious.