We need information
so we can fight back
and escape.
Celine.
She knows something.
Zein,
that's Hell U's secret.
Now you know the secret of Hell U.
You will never get to leave.
You will die here.
You'll get involved.
You'll get involved, Zein.
Stop complaining.
You've been kicked out of your position
Miss...
- Fritzy.
- I don't care about your name.
Kill me now.
Not yet, Ms. Shion.
You need to heal before you
face your punishment, okay?
we will behaving another
acquaintance party!
- Dave! Oh my god!
- Dave!
- Shit, bro. Are you okay?
Dave!
Shit!
Zein and Dave drank
the same thing!
Everyone that's not involved
please continue to party.
Don't let one incident
ruin the night.
What a bitch.
Blood has started to shed.
Shut up, bitch!
So annoying.
Dave...
wake up!
The dosage they took is too high.
That's why it affected
them this way.
Dave is stable for now.
He'll wake up any time soon.
But Zein...
her body's reacting to
the drug differently.
The toxin is behaving differently.
How did this happen?
Zein only drank two glasses.
And to be honest...
Dave drank more than her.
So I'm wondering
why is the effect
worse for Zein?
I can't really explain
that’s why we need to
observe her further.
Whoever is responsible for this
I swear I will never
forgive them.
Isn't there medicine
to counter the poison?
Why aren't you doing anything?
They could die.
Where is the doctor?
He's busy right now,
you'll have to wait.
These bastards...
Is this really a clinic?
Aren't you going
to do first aid?
Jerome...
That fucking nurse.
Bro, calm down.
This isn't the nurse's fault.
I'm calm
but Zein can't wait
any longer.
She needs to be
treated right away
but no one seems to care
in this goddamned place.
They don't care even if we die.
Matt, stop it!
I can't take this anymore!
I want to leave this place!
Mia...
put yourself together, huh?
What's that?
Matt...
Where did that come from?
What's that?
Does it say anything?
It says we should
let them drink this.
Huh?
We can’t do that.
We don’t know where
that came from.
They might get worse
if they drink that.
Do we really have a choice?
They're going to die
if we don't do anything.
It's better to try this
than nothing.
Matt's right.
Maybe it's a healing potion.
What do you think, Mia?
We can't trust anyone
here in Hell University.
What if it worsens
their condition?
Come on, let's try it.
Zein?
Leaving soon, Supremo?
This party's pointless.
Aren't you happy-
that blood didn't shed tonight?
What do you call
what happened earlier?
Just a minor commotion
for all you know
it's food poisoning or...
they got too drunk.
Nothing major.
Plus you are the SSG President
your presence is
much needed here.
It's better that you're
visible to the student body
too boost their moral.
Moral?
Does this school
still have morals?
Watch your language, Ace.
You may be the Supremo
but I am the headmistress
of this school.
I too have authority
on these grounds.
Like what I said, Madam Violet.
Everything you're saying is-
pointless.
Everything will make sense soon.
You'll see.
Whatever.
Why isn't anything happening?
Did we make a mistake?
They'll wake up.
Zein will wake up.
She'll bitch on us soon.
Dave!
Zein...
Why...
Why isn't it working for her?
Why isn't she waking up?
Zein...
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
I'm not your enemy,
I'm here to help.
- Oh my god!
- Stop!
Oh my god!
What are you doing?
What are you doing to her?
Hey!
- Zein!
- Fuck!
Now, try to feed her
the medicine again.
Oh my god.
Matt..
What are you going to do?
That's the antidote.
A drug that cleanses
her bloodstream.
It didn't work the first time
because she was asleep.
So I cut her chest so
she could wake up.
Zein!
Zein?
Get her some water!
Zein!
Yes!
Here you go.
Drink slowly.
Slowly.
Hold on, let me help you.
I told you she was
going to wake up.
Where's the girl?
Who was that?
Let's talk about that later, Van.
They're safe now.
That's what's important.
So are you guys both
seriously okay?
Like, aren't you nauseous?
Or something?
You see these guns?
I'm well equipped for
the Bloody Night.
I don't see anything.
Bloody Night? As if!
You almost died, remember?
I was blindsided back then
but if the enemy was
in front of me
they're no match for me!
If you say so!
You're all talk.
But seriously guys
who was the girl
who saved us?
Any ideas?
Maybe she's...
A witch?
Or a healer?
Gaming characters?
Really, Jerome?
You're at it again.
But from all the things
that are happening to us daily
honestly, I don't know what
to figure out first.
I just want to get through
this day in one piece.
Amen to that.
Amen!
Good morning, class!
Hey, we're going to be late.
We'll go ahead to
gym class, Zein.
- Bye bye.
- Be careful!
Bye, Zein.
- Matt's going to miss you.
- Stop it.
- Bye.
Why are you guys
so down today?
Anyway,
before we start I'd like
to inform you all
that your classmate,
Nicky Colt
has decided to drop
out of my class.
I don't know.
I can't say why but I do wonder
am I boring you guys?
Only a bit, sir.
Is that so, Mr. Almario?
Then let's start with my
boring discussion of the day.
Shall we?
Okay, Spanish Colonial Period
from 1565
to 1898.
Look around you, Zein.
Who do you think
the real enemy is?
Okay...
I'm boring, huh?
Let's see, Mr. Almario.
What are you talking about?
You're too innocent
and numb.
Do you think everything
is as it seems?
Think again.
Your friends aren't your allies.
In the end...
When everything goes to shit
they'll save themselves first.
Okay.
Now.
For every innocent smile
there's a secret kept hidden.
Don’t hug anyone too tightly
You never know who’s holding the knife.
Before you realize it--
you’re already bleeding.
I get it. Trust no one.
You can’t!
But, you can play smart.
You already know
the ranking system here.
I'm not planning on it.
Are you sure about that?
You know being part of
the top ten can give you
benefits not all
students can have.
Benefits that can save your life.
Now tell me, Zein.
If you're presented
the oppurtunity
will you abandon your
friends to save yourself?
Ms. Shion...
May I go out, sir?
Alright.
Miss!
Are you okay?
Is someone chasing you?
What happened to you?
Miss?
Please...
What?
Miss!
Miss, hold on! Wait for me!
Isn't that Zein?
Let's go after her.
Come on, let's go.
Hello?
Where are you?
I'm here to help.
Who are you?
Do you want to say something to me?
Don't worry
we can talk.
Miss!
Help! Help us!
- Zein!
- Help!
Zein?
Zein! We're going in!
It's not 7pm yet!
Zein? Are you okay?
Zein, are you okay?
That's enough!
Everyone step back
and go back to your classes!
I said get out!
Come on, let's go.
Ms. Zein Shion
May I invite you to the office?
Hold on, Principal.
Zein didn’t do anything.
The girl was already dead
when we found her.
There's nothing to
worry about, Jerome.
We only want to talk to her.
We aren't going
to pin this on her.
We'll go with you.
There's no need, Matt.
I can do this alone.
I'll meet you at the dorm.
But Zein...
You heard her.
Now...
Go back to your class
just like everyone else!
Ms. Shion, let's go!
Principal Carmie
what took you so long?
Why did you make me
wait this long?
Sorry for keeping you waiting, Ace.
Why is the principal afraid of him?
Sit down!
You can leave.
I'll take it from here.
If this is about the dead girl
sorry but I'm not
involved in that.
How rude, Ms. Shion
Aren't you forgetting that
you're in front of the SSG President?
Show some respect.
Anyways,
this meeting is about you...
Miss Shion.
As the new SSG Secretary.
How many times
do I have to tell you
that I'm not interested
in that position?
Well...
this isn't really a negotiation.
You don't really have
much of a choice.
I handpicked you for this job so
I'm simply keeping you
in the loop.
I don't want it.
Miss Shion,
I don't think you realize
what an advantage
being a SSG Secretary is
here in Hell University.
Being the SSG Secretary
has its benefits.
You'll know everything,
learn things no one else can.
Once you take this position,
you'll have control.
And people will fear you for it.
Not so bad, Ms. Shion?
I'll think about it.
Fine.
How are you?
I heard what happened last night.
What are you talking about?
A lot has has happened.
Are we done here?
If we are, I'll take my leave.
I still have class.
I know who did that do you.
Can you not make me guess?
Who are you talking about?
Don't be a fool.
Trust your instincts.
You know who did it.
The president's so annoying.
I can't catch a break!
He's always out to get me.
He just to make my life harder
As if it's not already hard
trying to survive in this school.
Ms. Shion
Sir Alvarez, what do you need?
Can we talk?
Sir, I need to go to my friends.
They might be worried.
This is important, Zein.
This will only take a few minutes.
Okay, sir.
Okay.
I didn't know it was Italian Day today.
Zitti, that's my favorite.
That's delicious.
Thank you.
I need your help.
With what, sir?
I'm not just a teacher
I'm a detective.
I was sent to uncover
what's really happening
in Hell University.
And to rescue all the students.
And you'll help me.
What do you mean?
Listen, Zein.
I'm a detective
at the same time,
secret agent.
We've been monitoring this place
for a long time now
But we can't get any information.
We don't have jurisdiction
over this university
because it's not
under the government.
That's why we forced a way in
but I've been here for a month
and I still don't know
how to save everyone.
I’m at my limit
that’s why I need your help.
Sir...
I can't help you.
I'm just an ordinary student in HU.
I don't know
anything about this.
I can't give you
any information.
Zein...
you can be a big asset
if you accept Ace’s offer.
Of being an SSG secretary?
If you accept that position,
you'll have access to more information.
You can find out the
location of the laboratory.
Secret lab?
Yes.
This school has a
secret laboratory.
That's where the research
of the formula is being done
after they stole it from
Dr. Quizon's death bed.
Dr. Quizon didn't die
a natural death
They murdered him
to attain the formula
That's why they have
a copy of the formula
but it's incomplete
Dr. Quizon chose a student
to hide the final ingredient
and until now,
it's location is still unknown.
They're still looking for that
student and the ingredient.
They're finding other means
to attain the formula.
Something to replace the formula.
That's what they're doing
in that hidden laboratory.
We need to find that laboratory.
before it's too late.
We need to stop them, Zein.
Zein, I really need your help.
And for you to be able to help me
you need to accept the position
being offered to you.
Zein, please.
You need to help me.
You're the key in helping
all of us escape this hell.
Please.
I'm not sure
if I could trust you.
I hope you understand.
What happened afterwards?
Principal Carmie went
to all the classrooms
to let all the professors
know that all students
should be punished.
They made us leave class
to run laps.
It was so tiring.
I'm so annoyed.
Anyway, what happened to you?
Where have you been?
We've been worried about you.
Did they torture you
to get information?
Did you spill anything?
Did you, Zein?
Van, stop it.
Nothing happened.
They didn't torture me.
Good for you.
But they're forcing me
to accept the position
of being the SSG Secretary.
So did you accept it?
Zein...
Hey.
Not yet.
But you're planning to?
Hey!
You're planning on it, aren't you?
Zein!
What is it?
Zein
what are you planning?
Not even one mention
of any laboratory.
These are just full of history.
Dates, founders, and how this
university was "built on excellence".
Yeah right.
Excellence, my ass.
But if there really is a secret lab,
it's obvious they wouldn't put
any information on it here.
It's a secret, isn't it?
Don't be dumb, Zein Shion.
What's keeping you so busy?
Let me see that.
I'm trying to find us a way out.
Way out?
It's pointless to find
a way out of here.
How are you so sure?
If there really is a way out,
we would have found it by now.
You're right
but are we just
going to give up?
Of course not.
I didn't say we should give up.
We made a promise
to leave this place together.
So, no one's giving up.
Matt, thank you.
Thank you for always
being there for us...
for me.
Of course.
Always remember
if you have any problems
or whatever your plans are
anything.
I'll always be here for you.
I will never leave you.
I promise.
Zein, it's you.
Don't forget, okay?
Was that an earthquake?
I'm not sure.
Secretary position...
undercover mission...
it's all too much.
What am I supposed to do?
If I say "Yes" to Ace
I'll have power...
control.
But what's the catch?
I don't think you realize
what an advantage being an SSG
Secretary is here in Hell University.
Being SSG Secretary
has its benefits.
You'll know everything,
learn things no one else can.
Once you take this position
you'll have control
and people will fear you for it.
Trusting him?
Following his rules?
And there's Sir Alvarez...
the detective.
He wants me to help him
save all the students here in Hell U.
Listen, Zein.
I'm a detective...
at the same time, secret agent.
We've been monitoring
this place for a long time.
But we can't find any information
Zein...
you can be a big asset
if you accept Ace's offer.
Of being an SSG Secretary?
Yes.
If you accept the position,
you'll have access
to valuable information
and you can find the location
of the hidden laboratory.
Secret lab?
Yes
this school has a secret laboratory.
But am I able to do that?
I can't even save myself.
What if both of them are lying?
What if I'm just a pawn
in their game?
My mind is reeling!
I can't even decide who to believe
in this godforsaken hell!
What's the right move, Zein?
Power or purpose?
My safety or everyone's safety?
What's the right thing to do?
Whatever.
I need to choose and
stand by that choice.
It smells rotten here.
Damn!
what happened here last night?
This is so bad.
It smells.
There's so much blood.
I'll catch up with you, guys.
I need to do something.
Don't be late, okay?
You might get another warning.
Ew!
Oh my god,
is this really normal here?
This is so gross.
Be careful,
they already cleaned that.
It smells so bad.
Here.
these are your new clothes.
Wear it and I'll show you our office.
Do I need to change
into that now?
Yes.
Is there a problem?
And where do you
think you're going?
The restroom...
to change.
No.
Change here.
In front of you?
Why?
Do you want to?
In your dreams.
I'll guard the doors
so better hurry up.
Wow, he really thinks he's being cute
guarding the door like that?
He's still an asshole.
But he's being a gentleman today.
Is this one of the perks of
being an SSG Secretary?
So do you think Zein will accept
the offer of being the SSG Secretary?
I'm not sure
but knowing Zein
I think she'll take it.
More so if she feels like
she has something to prove.
I also feel like
she'll accept the offer.
I think so too, Matt.
So what's the plan
if she accepts it?
is that good?
Or is it too dangerous?
It depends.
If she accepts it,
she gains a position
in the student council.
That's an advantage to us
here in Hell University.
She can gather
information on the inside.
Actually, Dave's right.
And if she decides to accept it,
she can protect us even more.
But what if she gets into Ace's world
and can't get out anymore?
Mia has a point.
Power is a dangerous thing.
People change when they gain
a powerful position.
They can change from allies
to enemies real quick.
Zein isn't like that!
How sure are you?
Dave, you know that
Zein accepting the position of
being the SSG Secretary
is the right move.
She can be our biggest asset.
Don't you think so?
Right?
She can be
but it's a double-edged sword.
You both have valuable points
but we don't know
what's waiting for Zein
after she accepts the
SSG Secretary position.
You know, Matt's right.
Let's wait for Zein's decision
and let's plan from there.
Nice.
It suits you.
What's next?
Matt...
why are you so restless?
It's okay for Zein
to be a part of the SSG
but I don't trust the people there
especially Ace!
Huh?
Supremo?
I feel something
wrong about him.
I can't explain it but
Zein needs to be wary of him.
- Maybe you're just jealous?
- No, I'm not.
He's just being jealous.
You're just jealous, bro.
Why is she wearing that badge?
Is she the new secretary?
How?
Isn't she a newbie?
Maybe she put him
under a love spell.
Hey, stop that!
She's the new number 9.
Didn't you see the list?
Move
Number 9? Really?
It's really her?
I'm sorry, miss.
We didn't know it was you
I said move and
get out of my sight.
Come on, move.
Let's go.
Zein.
You're catching on pretty quick.
I like that.
Let's go.
Why are they together?
That bastard.
President Ace
Fritzy is still the SSG Secretary
Get out of my sight
Ms. Fritzy Saldivar
From now on
Ms. Zein Shion is
Hell University's new secretary.
Don't let it get to you
you're still one of
Hell University's top dogs.
I'm sorry, Supremo.
SSG!
The Dark Hell Jail
is waiting for you.
This is our job, Ms. Shion.
We need to punish
the rule breakers.