HUMINT
INTELLIGENCE GATHERING
THROUGH HUMAN SOURCES
MAHADOR, SOUTHEAST ASIA
Soo Rin, it's me.
Put your clothes on.
Her vitals are stable.
Thanks for your hard work.
What's this?
It's nothing special.
Wow, it's the first time
I've received a gift at work.
Anyway…
Thank you.
Can I…
really get out today?
Two hours after I leave,
a backup team will come and escort you.
Before you leave,
we need to go over your testimony
one last time.
You can do that, right?
Originally…
I was sent to Russia
as a foreign currency earner.
Foreign currency earners…
must leave their families behind
in the fatherland.
So I left my child and husband
to work in Vladivostok
and receive training.
Then one day,
while I was working at a restaurant,
State Security raided the place
and I was suddenly ordered back home.
They said
they were taking me to a ship
headed for Rajin Port.
But then…
some Russians
took me away.
Those Russian animals
treated me like their plaything,
and they even recorded it on video.
And…
they even injected me
with something like bingdu.
"Bingdu" mentioned, sir.
Have her confirm it was narcotics.
We need to confirm that
for her escape op to be approved.
What exactly is bingdu?
In our country,
we call the ice drug bingdu.
And so…
I barely stayed alive, dealing with men
whose faces I can't even remember.
And before I knew it…
I had been taken all the way to China.
Hey, we need more info
on the drug situation.
When was her first dose,
and who gave it to her?
But we're getting info
on the human trafficking route.
That's not what's important here.
Get her to talk about the drugs.
Sir! I'll do whatever you tell me!
- Please get me out of here!
- What the hell? Stop her!
Please just get me… No!
Can you send backup first?
You get out first.
We've got all the info we need.
What do you mean?
We're getting her out today.
This is an unauthorized op,
so the budget hasn't been approved.
Once we get funding
with this intel, we can get her…
Just get out of there first!
Is this seriously…
the best we can do?
Listen carefully.
There's a hiccup
in our communication right now,
- but I'll fix it right away, so--
- Please!
Please don't leave me!
I have to get back to my family!
Okay.
You'll expose the whole team.
Just pull out now!
I'll pay extra.
Do not engage.
Get out.
You son of a bitch!
Hey, you South Korean bastards!
You got what you wanted
and now you're leaving me?
Keep your promise!
Please don't abandon me!
Please!
Please don't leave me…
Please… Please!
Please!
Stop it!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry. Please don't!
I said do not engage! Get out of there!
Soo Rin, stay with me.
Manager Zo.
You didn't take your gun, did you?
If you open fire, there's no turning back.
NATIONAL INTELLIGENCE SERVICE
SAFE HOUSE, MAHADOR
Checking her pupils.
No pupillary response.
Soo Rin.
Soo Rin, wake up.
Hooking her up to the monitor.
Oxygen saturation is low.
Give her oxygen.
What's wrong? Can't find a vein?
Her veins are blown.
Let me check her feet.
What is it? What's happening to her?
She's in V-Fib. Get the defibrillator.
Start CPR.
Charge to 150.
Shocking now. Stand clear!
Clear.
Charge to 200.
Shocking now. Stand clear!
Clear.
One more time. Out of the way!
There's no pulse.
What are you talking about? No, wait.
What else could we do?
The higher-ups wouldn't sign off.
She wouldn't have lasted long,
even if we had pulled her out.
If we'd just done what we promised,
Kim Soo Rin would not have died.
She trusted us.
There's no such thing in this business.
Everyone's just using each other
to survive.
It's part of the job.
Get used to it.
Is people dying
something we can just get used to?
No one starts out being used to it.
You get used to it as you go.
NATIONAL INTELLIGENCE SERVICE
REPUBLIC OF KOREA
Manager Zo, is this your first time
losing an informant?
Yes, it's his first,
but he's handling it fine.
Well, it must be a bit of a shock.
But thanks to Ms. Kim Soo Rin's efforts,
we have a clear picture now.
We can directly tie this case
to the drug distribution network
in the Daechi-dong academy district.
"North Korea has been distributing drugs
to our teenagers,
trying to ruin the future generations
of the Republic of Korea."
We've secured multiple testimonies
related to drugs
from North Korean female defectors.
And traces of drugs were found
in Kim Soo Rin's body--
This HUMINT operation has made it clearer
that international human trafficking
crimes are targeting North Korean women.
Hey, Manager Zo.
No, no. Go on.
They were drugged and trafficked
through Russia and China to Europe,
Southeast Asia, and even South Africa.
Many of the trafficked women's
point of departure was Vladivostok.
Many testimonies suggest the North Korean
State Security's involvement,
so we suspect
the consulate's involvement too.
This is the latest intel
from the Russia team
on the Vladivostok mafia.
VLADIVOSTOK MAFIA ORGANIZATION CHART
Wow.
This is a good case.
With North Korean-Russian relations
growing closer these days,
even the US and China are on edge.
Imagine we get control of a situation
where international crime
is happening within their borders.
Chief Jung, you work on the report.
Manager Zo,
you head to Vladivostok immediately.
VLADIVOSTOK, RUSSIA
ARIRANG RESTAURANT
Welcome.
Let me take your coat.
Is this your first time here?
Welcome.
Over here!
Hello.
You're here early.
No, I just got here.
Aren't you tired?
I'm fine.
They look quite wealthy,
so take good care of them.
Welcome.
It's our first time here.
What's good here?
Are you from the South?
You don't refuse to serve South Koreans
or anything, do you?
It's sad enough our country is divided.
Must we draw a line
when serving a meal too?
Come here.
My friend here runs
a large pharmaceutical business.
If I treat him well tonight,
I could make quite a bit of money.
CHAE SEON HWA
Ms. Chae Seon Hwa?
All right, then.
Today, I'll put my trust in you
and go with whatever you recommend.
I'll ensure the warmest hospitality
so your business can succeed.
FIVE MONTHS LATER
TUMEN RIVER FANGCHUAN REGION,
NORTH KOREA-CHINA-RUSSIA BORDER AREA
If you don't stay on your toes,
you'll end up like that too.
But isn't this Russian territory,
not China?
China's Public Security Police are
cracking down hard these days.
It's safer for someone from Russia
to cross you over to China.
Don't make any trouble, and stay strong!
Boss! Bingdu.
New one. The best.
First, sample.
If you like it, our consul general
will supply this one next time.
Get rid of the defective product.
Nice and clean.
PURITY 99%
It's grade A.
Test it on them first.
Stay the night.
Damn it.
Do you have any goddamn idea
who you're messing with?
I'm Park Geon
of the Ministry of State Security.
For illegally smuggling citizens
and human trafficking…
I've come to arrest you.
I heard you were coming, Comrade Captain,
but I didn't think
you'd take such immediate action.
I'm just here to do my job.
NORTH KOREAN CONSULATE GENERAL,
VLADIVOSTOK
Unlock it.
Wow, my dear Comrade Park.
You just got here,
and you're already getting results.
I was going to report to you
after completing the investigation--
You came all the way from Pyongyang
and went straight to work.
How could I just stand by, doing nothing?
Don't you think you've gone too far
on one of our compatriots?
I will give you a chance
for self-criticism now.
Write down everything you've ever done
since the day you were born.
Including every crime,
even the ones you got away with.
You should answer if you understand.
For the sake of your family
back in the fatherland.
I understand.
You're going to catch a cold.
Put some clothes on him.
Let's go eat.
ARIRANG RESTAURANT
Our Republic's art troupe is very popular.
Lumberjacks can work themselves
to death here earning foreign currency,
but they can't compete
with those female comrades.
Let's sit down.
Comrade Park.
Since you're in Vladivostok,
you should try some vodka.
I'm good.
My dear Comrade Park…
You must have gone through
many party loyalty tests.
To be honest,
I'm just nervous.
The legendary Comrade Park Geon,
who is said to track down even the dead,
has come to keep an eye on me.
My mission is to investigate
the disappearances of our people
in the border area
caused by the Russian mafias.
Do you remember
the Hero of the Republic, Pyo Jong Seong,
who worked
at the Berlin branch ten years ago?
He was in State Security.
When Comrade Chairman Kim Jong Il
passed away,
and the Berlin branch
was rampant with betrayal,
he attempted to seek asylum.
During all that, his pregnant wife
got shot and killed.
It was his attempt to defect
that went sideways,
but he became obsessed with the idea
that the Party had set him up.
He pushed in from Berlin
to turn Pyongyang upside down.
He broke through everyone
who tried to stop him.
He was a tough one.
In the end, he managed to come
all the way here to Vladivostok.
And he met you, Comrade Consul General.
Even a Hero of the Republic
can vanish without a trace
beneath the frozen sea
here in Vladivostok.
But a part of your story
is different from what I know.
The Party confirmed the facts.
What more do you need?
Listen carefully.
When traitors who flee the fatherland
realize they have no way to survive,
they end up selling themselves.
And when they're caught,
they all say they were tricked
by South Korean operatives
or got caught up
after being lured by some foreigners.
Well, a broker like the one you arrested
might show up every now and then.
But organized crimes
like human trafficking is a myth.
You, Comrade Park,
are here to watch me.
That's the only explanation.
Have you done something
to warrant being watched?
Must one do something
Excuse me.
Welcome.
Do you two know each other?
That's all of your food. Please enjoy.
Comrade Seon Hwa is
the most popular female worker here.
It's impossible to catch her eye.
You two must have quite a story.
Somehow you'll come to mind
Even if you are a cold-hearted person
Memories of loving you so much
I won't be able to forget
At times, I'll miss you
When I look up at the round moon
Thinking of the vow we made that night
I'll regret the days gone by
Although we parted far, far away
Over the mountains
Although our two hearts
Parted across the seas
Sometimes you'll come to mind
Even if you are a cold-hearted person
Memories of loving you so much
I won't be able to forget
Park Geon speaking.
What?
What a coward.
He admitted his wrongdoings already.
Why kill himself
after begging us to spare his family?
Guess he really wanted to save them.
He left a full statement before going.
About the money he got
for handing people over at the border,
the amount, who he smuggled out…
It's all written there.
There's nothing about what happened
after he got them across the border.
These guys just get them
across the border,
take the money, and run.
What more would there be?
What about video records?
We weren't ordered to record him
writing his statement,
so we only observed him.
Don't let yourself get sentimental.
Take swift measures so his family
in Pyongyang can be investigated.
Since it ended up like this,
I guess you'll return
to Pyongyang sooner than expected.
You went to
all that trouble to record him,
but that reactionary caused a ruckus,
and it ended up like this.
Still, it's been a while
since you came out here.
Why don't you go sightseeing
while we wrap things up here?
ARIRANG RESTAURANT
Don't take too long like last time.
Call me if anything happens.
It's cold, isn't it?
How have you been?
Signal normal.
You may proceed.
Your mother's medication
must be running out.
You just need to make up your mind,
but we've been authorized to proceed
with her cancer surgery in Seoul.
Bringing her over won't be easy,
but treason and whatnot doesn't matter
when it comes to saving a person's life.
Chapter 1, Article 3 of the Constitution
of the Republic of Korea.
"The territory of the Republic of Korea
shall consist of the Korean peninsula
and its adjacent islands."
According to our Constitution,
you and your family are all our citizens.
If I decide today…
how many days at most
would it take to get me and my mother out?
REPORT ON CONSUL GENERAL HWANG CHI SUNG
ARIRANG RESTAURANT
Chae Seon Hwa's heart rate
is getting unstable.
By any chance, have you ever
mentioned our meetings to anyone?
Maybe your family?
I would never.
Last time we spoke,
you weren't thinking of leaving.
Someone who knows me…
Someone who knows me deeply
came to the restaurant where I work
with the consul general today.
Who is it? Did he come to see you?
I don't know for sure, but…
Never mind.
I'm still sorting out my thoughts.
First, let's talk about what we agreed on.
PURITY 99%
This is the mafia boss
who is running the largest drug operation
in the Vladivostok area.
Have you ever seen him?
The North Korean consul general
is colluding with the Russian mafia
on something here.
We wouldn't even be able to look
at someone this powerful.
Then where do you get the bingdu?
The manager gives it to us
whenever we go out.
To prevent us from using it,
she controls the dosage strictly.
How do you give it to the customers?
When waitresses serve customers outside,
we slip it into their drinks.
And then…
we sleep with them.
Then, when customers start asking for it,
we start selling it to them for money.
It's that easy?
It's never failed. Not once.
But…
if I don't know what's going on higher up,
will that ruin everything?
No.
Just telling me what you know truthfully,
like you have so far, is enough.
Now, shall we continue
from where we left off last time?
Some of the comrades at the restaurant
got into trouble
and were taken by State Security.
Apparently, they've been
repatriated to the fatherland.
But even their families couldn't find out
whether they had returned or not.
And you know some of them?
There was a lady who came here before me.
But we lost contact
after she was taken by State Security
for trying to defect to South Korea.
Could you tell me her name?
It's Kim…
Soo Rin.
By any chance…
Does her name ring a bell?
Do the State Security officers
in charge of repatriating people
work under cover identities?
They're comrades from the consulate.
The person who came
looking for you earlier…
Are they also from the consulate?
It's your birthday soon.
She mentioned a new person she met today,
but she didn't care to elaborate.
She could be making someone up
just to raise her value.
We still don't know anything
about Chae Seon Hwa, do we?
We don't really know much
about each other either, do we?
Do you remember
the first thing you told me
when I was assigned here, sir?
That you neither start
a family of your own
nor keep close ties
with the one you already have,
because you know your work
could put them in danger.
What about it?
But you're so kind to Chae Seon Hwa.
Then should I torture her instead?
Her heart rate today
was much more unstable than usual.
At that level, it should've registered
as a deceptive response.
The strange part is
she stayed right under the threshold.
Are you saying she's been trained
to control her physiological responses?
It's a relief you can get
your mom's meds, even if it's like this.
You're lucky to have met
the Russian pharmaceutical businessman.
It's all thanks to you looking out
for me, Comrade Manager.
I only made the introduction.
You did the rest.
It's a great gift you got here.
Don't send this to Pyongyang.
Just keep it for yourself.
Won't you be too tired for the night show?
It's my performance.
It doesn't matter
whether I'm tired or not.
Can I have a word with Comrade Seon Hwa?
Her night show's on soon.
Don't be late.
Have you been well?
And your mother's illness?
You know how it is.
Is there anything
I can do to help?
I have to go perform now.
I looked for you for a long time.
Did you know I was here?
You know what kind of work I do.
Did you think I wouldn't find you
if you covered your tracks?
Why did you have to disappear like that?
You've seen what kind of work I do now.
Did you come all the way here for money?
You should go now.
It's cold out here.
GEUM TAE HYUK
Hey, how did those two meet?
Captain Park Geon was
waiting for Chae Seon Hwa.
Out of all the men she's entertained,
there should be at least one
we can frame as reactionary.
Find out all of her movements.
How do we explain to Captain Park
about getting rid of the broker's body?
Tell the truth.
Pyongyang refused to take the body back.
Declaring the death of the likes of him
would only increase
the crime rate in our Republic.
Park Geon may be here to keep tabs on us,
but he wouldn't dare
disregard the Party's dignity.
The police contacted you
for cooperation, right?
I need to confirm something
for diplomatic purposes.
Which room did the North Korean
who came today stay in?
The man at the hotel was
from the North Korean consulate, right?
The North Korean consulate
regularly tracks dispatched workers,
so it might be no big deal.
Earlier, Chae Seon Hwa said someone
who knows her well came to see her.
So let's start by analyzing
the North Korean restaurant data.
Okay. I'll get it ready, sir.
- Agent Im, hold on.
- What is it?
Is this guy in our database?
I've never seen him before. Let me check.
Send it over to me.
Look.
The North Korean consul general
drove him there himself,
but looks like they barely had time
to eat and left in a hurry.
Then, they went straight back
to the consulate.
Our database, the US, Japan…
There's no data on him anywhere.
But doesn't he seem like the person
Chae Seon Hwa was talking about?
I'll check her movements.
See if there are traces of this new guy
around the North Korean consulate
or staff's apartments.
Sir, I think you should see this first.
And here.
Early this morning,
a car entered the consulate,
but not quite at the usual time.
And more importantly…
something was illegally taken out
of the consulate.
Does this look connected to the guy
who came to see Chae Seon Hwa?
Well,
at first glance,
they seem to be romantic partners.
If they were, he would've waited inside,
not out in the cold.
An ex.
This guy is trained.
He's on perimeter alert
when he moves with the consul general
and he's minimizing exposure
when meeting with Chae Seon Hwa.
I'm worried about her.
Here, look at the footage
from the camera across the street.
That's the consulate employee
we saw at the hotel, isn't it?
Double surveillance.
This man who was on perimeter alert
is losing control here.
He's losing his composure.
She might've already been exposed.
4 MONTHS EARLIER
Seon Hwa, don't be startled.
We don't mean any harm.
Please have a seat first.
You know me.
If you're really uneasy,
you can just leave.
But before that,
I brought some medicine for your mother.
Are you…
from the National Intelligence Service?
If you're worried about your safety,
we guarantee you that we'll keep you safe.
The Party already knows I'm here.
So how can you guarantee my safety?
If you're in danger, we're in danger too.
I promise.
I'm here to help you.
Let's get her out
before it gets more dangerous.
If we push through,
it could get dangerous for all of us.
We haven't verified her testimony,
and we don't have approval.
Then should we abandon her?
We're not out here volunteering
at a refugee camp.
What if she's just telling us
what we want to hear?
There's no guarantee she's not conning us.
You've watched her with me
for over four months.
Sir.
Is this because of Kim Soo Rin?
She's my informant.
I make the call.
You don't even smoke.
And you can't fall asleep.
Is something troubling you?
It's nothing.
Don't keep it all bottled up.
If there's something
you want to do, do it.
From what I've seen these past few months,
that Russian businessman
seems very fond of you.
A friend of mine who was a manager
in Cambodia had an employee
fall for a customer and run off with him.
Even if that happens…
there are ways for cadres like us
to move on without getting hurt too badly.
So don't worry about me or anyone else.
Do what you need to survive.
Don't miss your chance
and regret it like I did.
VOICE RECORDINGS
This is Chae Seon Hwa singing
to Park Geon as a birthday present.
This is really it?
Just don't delete it like last time.
That wasn't on purpose--
Please shut up.
Oh, come on.
One, two, three, four.
Somehow you'll come to mind
Even if you are a cold-hearted person
Memories of loving you so much
I won't be able to forget
At times, I'll miss you
When I look up at the round moon
Thinking of the vow we made that night
I'll regret the days gone by
REPORT ON CONSUL GENERAL HWANG CHI SUNG
Although we…
You're going to get hurt, Comrade Captain.
It's us.
Calm down.
Now why did you drink so much by yourself?
Comrade Consul General
is looking for you urgently.
I mean, look.
Why didn't you tell me
the two of you had been engaged?
I almost got the wrong idea.
I thought you came
all the way here because of me,
but it was actually
to find Comrade Seon Hwa.
Let me apologize.
No need for an apology.
Did I get the wrong idea again?
No matter how long and hard I thought,
I just couldn't figure out
what I'd done to have you on my back.
When I realized this was why you came,
it all just clicked.
Anyway, let's take a look.
For the past month, this Russian merchant
has been calling Comrade Chae
to the same room at least once a week.
And each time, those two also used
the room right next door.
Why do you think she's bowing
to an empty room?
Well, I suppose we can let that pass.
But watch carefully now.
What's interesting about this is
that those two rooms are connected.
Now, a different hotel
from two months ago.
The guests of both rooms
came and went at different times,
but they used connecting rooms
on the same day.
This was three months ago.
Each time, it's a different hotel,
but it's always the same situation.
Why are you showing me this?
Come on.
Isn't this why you're here?
Whether you knew about it or not,
it's not looking good for you either way.
Chae Seon Hwa has been
recruited by the South.
Yes, sir.
A vehicle left
the North Korean consulate just now.
It looks like they're raiding
the restaurant staff quarters.
Why would they do that at this hour?
Where are you, sir?
I'm heading to the site.
Keep an eye on things for me.
This isn't our job.
Our job is to collect intel,
conduct surveillance, report--
What on earth did you do?
You tell me.
What did I do?
Who are they?
You can hide things from the others,
but I can only help
if you don't hide anything from me.
You know what happens if you get framed
as a reactionary in contact with spies--
Is this why you came to find me?
State Security has figured it all out.
Have you been in contact
with the South Koreans?
Once the investigation starts,
you won't be able to hold out.
Admit that you were approached by them.
Say you were gathering intel for me.
Over here.
I found a stash of dollars
in Comrade Seon Hwa's room.
Search thoroughly. Don't miss a thing!
- Say the dollars are--
- You haven't changed a bit.
You've worked so diligently all your life,
Comrade Seon Hwa.
Twenty-eight years…
Brief in some respects, long in others.
Thank you for such a truthful confession.
Comrade Seon Hwa must be
deeply disappointed with you,
Comrade Park.
Your father was caught
smuggling from China,
trying to cover
your mother's cancer treatment.
Because of this, you even had to drop out
of Pyongyang University of Music.
You came all the way here
to earn foreign currency
and went through so much trouble.
It's only natural
that you would've expected
Comrade Park to help take care of this.
But instead of covering up the mistakes
of those who would have been his in-laws,
he personally took charge
of the investigation.
That's the problem
with people who put work first.
I would have lost all affection too.
Everything here is true, isn't it?
Yes, it's all true.
Since you only wrote down the truth…
you can write it out again
exactly the same, right?
Word for word.
Your memories from
when you were three are correct.
The ones from 13 years ago
are correct too.
And from three years ago as well.
So how can you possibly be wrong
about your memories from three days ago?
Pardon?
The number of customers who came
to the restaurant where you work
doesn't add up.
The number of times
you went to the toilet is also off.
Comrade Consul General.
Could I have some water, please?
Why are your lips so parched,
like someone who's lying?
Water can wait.
Write it out again truthfully.
Water…
Water, please…
I guess it can't be helped.
Serve her some water.
Take a deep breath
and hold it.
To be handled by
the top expert of our Republic…
What an honor for our Comrade Seon Hwa.
So sweet, the two of you.
You got an expensive gift, huh?
They might even fit me.
You left out the story
of the South Korean operative
who gave you these.
Start the engine.
As I said,
the money she received from
the South Koreans as recruitment funds
was going to be sent to Pyongyang
as loyalty funds through me.
It simply wasn't reported
because it was a secret operation.
This doesn't warrant
her immediate repatriation.
A secret operation the consul general
was never made aware of?
Why, I've never heard of such a thing.
Is this because of my mission?
Isn't your mission to investigate
the disappearance of our people?
Rules are rules. What can we do?
Let me escort you myself.
Port inspection won't go smoothly
if an unfamiliar face shows up.
Even if they take you to Pyongyang,
say you gave false testimony.
Just say what's written here.
I'll do whatever it takes to find
the South Korean operative and save you.
I will not let you down again.
There's no need for us to die together.
Those who can live should live.
Hey!
Bring me everything you have
on the South Korean operatives.
What, are you going to catch
some South Korean spies
and hand them over
to overturn her treason charge?
Of all suspected South Korean
undercover operations offices,
this one's the shadiest.
About four months ago, the owner changed.
The new one looks like
the guest who stayed in the room
next door to Chae Seon Hwa's--
Why didn't you report that?
Didn't you come
knowing all of this already?
You seemed to know things even we weren't
aware of, like the broker case, so…
Let's move.
There was no direct order
from the consul general.
We can't move without it.
What if we leave our posts
and something happens at the consulate?
That's right.
We should stick to our own jobs.
Clear!
When we get to Rajin Port,
will I stand trial first?
The Party will proceed according to
whatever the standard proceeding is.
VLADIVOSTOK PORT
She's our top foreign currency earner.
I'm returning the favor
for handling the broker's body.
Did you have to kill the broker?
What's going on?
Pyongyang sent me a nuisance
to keep tabs on me.
But don't worry.
I'll kill him and send him back soon.
Live fiercely!
MANAGER ZO
KOREA TRADING COMPANY
CONSUL GENERAL HWANG CHI SUNG'S
TRANSACTIONS WITH RUSSIAN MAFIA…
PHOTOGRAPHIC EVIDENCE
It's bulletproof.
This item is going all the way to Moscow.
You really think
I wouldn't have planned for that?
I've come to meet your superior.
AGENT IM: CALL ME
If you want to save her,
get over here immediately.
At least tell me who I'm talking to.
An innocent person has been repatriated
because of you people.
You don't need to know who I am.
Just know that I'll break one bone
every minute until you get here.
You're Chae Seon Hwa's lover, aren't you?
I'm currently at the place
where Seon Hwa is being held.
Don't try to fuck with me.
I have evidence that your consul general
handed Seon Hwa over to the Russians.
The person you're with right now
will confirm it for you.
It's one bone per minute.
MANAGER ZO
This is the final location
where Chae Seon Hwa was taken.
Try not to make a mess.
It's not as if an employee you managed
fell in love with a customer and ran off.
She colluded with a reactionary spy.
Your son.
He's starting
at Kim Il Sung University soon, no?
Captain Park Geon
told Chae Seon Hwa
he could make it look like
they'd been working together.
I heard it with my own ears.
Why didn't you report it sooner?
Park Geon caught on
and threatened me.
He told me to keep my mouth shut
since it was State Security business.
What about the South Korean spy?
Pardon?
"Pardon"?
Chae Seon Hwa has been
secretly meeting and colluding with
a South Korean spy, and…
Loyalty funds.
I was able to confirm that
Park Geon was using this
to siphon off money received
from South Korea,
claiming it was "loyalty funds".
Park Geon and Chae Seon Hwa
are traitors to the Republic!
All right, applause.
Now that we've secured the testimony,
let's go catch Park Geon, that traitor.
Keep that up,
and you'll actually end up dead.
If I die, I'll die by my own hand!
Anyone who touches me
dies with me.
Park Geon is headed to the auction site.
Hey, you…
You should've stopped him!
What's going on?
What?
The guy from Pyongyang
who's been keeping tabs on me
is headed there looking for
the woman I handed over.
Just him?
Looks like he's already here.
Kill him, sell his organs. I don't care.
Do whatever you want with him.
I'll be there as soon as possible.
How did that bastard get there already?
I'm looking for
the North Korean woman who just got here.
Stop!
Stay calm!
It's no big deal!
What's your goal here?
Why are you going to such lengths
to find Seon Hwa?
Because she's my HUMINT.
If it weren't for you bastards,
she wouldn't be going through this hell.
You're the ones
who sold her to the Russians.
I'm the one trying to rescue her.
Then shoot me and go find her.
Are you Korean?
North Korean?
Let's stay sharp and get out of here.
Everybody, hide!
Hide!
Quick, behind the cars!
Park Geon!
You fucking son of a bitch!
Do you have any idea what damage
you've just done to our Republic?
You bastard!
So you've really teamed up
with the Southern puppet regime!
Now that the North and South
have met like this,
we should hang
the Korean Unification flag!
Park Geon, you damn traitor!
Come out now so we can end this!
I need to at least take your head
to the Moscow mafia bastards
to keep the rest alive!
Those who can live should live!
Get down!
Take cover!
No!
Let go of me!
Please. Please…
Save him, please!
Save him!
Please…
Help him!
No, don't…
No!
Damn it.
Everyone's starving to death anyway.
What the hell are we doing?
They're all dying
because of assholes like you,
goddamn communist bastards!
No, it can't be…
This Russian organization
traded victims like this for profit.
They carried out
secondary human trafficking,
supplied pornography
through legalized websites,
and forced women
into prostitution and drug distribution.
Using these female victims,
they earned more than
a million dollars each month.
So you were unable to identify
the domestic distribution route
of North Korean narcotics,
which is what we actually wanted.
Manager Zo, records indicate
that you blamed yourself
for the death of your informant
during the Mahador operation
and showed signs of depression.
Did your personal feelings
affect any of your decisions?
That doesn't seem like a question
he can answer himself.
You were his partner.
How did he seem, Agent Im?
His personal feelings
never got in the way of our operations.
What about Chae Seon Hwa?
I'm sorry?
What I want to know is
why Chae Seon Hwa made such a decision
when we went as far as to save her life.
What other choice did she have?
We got Chae Seon Hwa to Japan.
While we questioned her at our embassy,
we hired a broker
to get her mother out of North Korea.
DEATH CERTIFICATE
But she died of cardiac arrest en route.
Even though Chae Seon Hwa lost everything,
she never asked us for any compensation.
She simply said…
I'd like to start over…
where no one knows me.
Sir.
Park Geon said something to you
right before he died.
Did he ask you to get Chae Seon Hwa out?
No.
He asked if there was
any way he could live.
He said he wanted to live.