IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
CHARACTERS, EVENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND PLACES IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
I'm not someone
who will leave in three months,
nor someone who might never come back.
Ms. Song, I want to stay
with you.
No, Haran. So I'll tell you everything.
But to tell you everything precisely,
I need some time.
It won't take long.
I'll tell you everything honestly soon.
So when I do,
please listen to everything.
What if you're not okay?
What if something else happens?
I've been okay, I'm okay now,
and I'll keep being okay.
So…
let's go see
the cherry blossoms in spring.
We'll have shaved ice in summer,
see the autumn leaves in fall,
and in winter…
it would be fun to go snowboarding.
EPISODE 10
I think you dropped your bracelet.
This is yours, right?
Oh. Hey, crybaby Song Haran.
- Let's go.
- Let me return her bracelet.
Oh, no. I'm sorry. Oh…
Get your stuff. I'll do this.
I came to ask you for help.
I really want to protect something,
but to do that, I need my memories.
It's okay. It breaks sometimes.
I've been wearing it for a long time.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'll get it repaired for you.
It's really fine, Haran.
Excuse me?
Ah. Your name was written on the pen.
That's a pretty name.
- Let's go.
- He seems to be in quite a hurry.
You can go. It's fine.
I'm really sorry…
Why are you so on edge?
No, wait. I'm sorry.
You should hurry home and get some rest.
Did the doctor say you're okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
So let's go.
If you feel dizzy or uncomfortable,
tell me straightaway.
Sir.
I'm sorry, but can you pull over nearby?
Shouldn't you get some rest?
I'm totally fine.
Oh? There's a look of doubt on your face.
Then I'll do 100 push-ups!
All right, fine. I believe you.
I feel like we'll just feel down
and regret it if we go home now.
So…
let's begin Seonu Chan's
birthday gift ceremony.
That's my present, right?
This…
Oh… Let me guess.
Mmm… It's clothes.
A cardigan you designed yourself.
How did you know?
I prepared this in secret.
It was obvious.
It was?
Oh. I see…
Hang on. Just give me five minutes.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Seonu Chan ♪
Wait.
You should still make a wish
even if it's just a humble
convenience store cake.
Then make a wish with me.
Wow!
What did you wish for?
It's a secret.
If I share it, it won't come true.
Right.
Then…
I'll give you your birthday present now.
- Happy birthday.
- Oh. Can I open it right now?
Huh?
I didn't know about this.
At least
I kept one thing a secret.
I'm glad I was born.
Song Haran wished me happy birthday.
Everybody!
Song Haran wished me happy birthday!
Are you crazy?
I'll wear this every day,
in spring, summer, fall, and winter.
I'll wear this to bed, too.
Ah. And even when I'm showering.
I wanted to do more for you
since it's our first birthday together.
Since you seem upset,
how about a date tomorrow?
We can watch a movie,
have a nice meal, hold hands,
and take a walk while we chat.
We'll do what other couples do.
You should just rest. I'm worried.
You leave me
no choice, then. I should do push-ups…
All right. Let's go on a date.
But can you sing that part again?
The…
"dear Seonu Chan" part.
I'll make your birthday
even more special next year.
I'm going to use that trial
for the rest of my life.
So…
stay healthy, okay?
I will.
Besides,
my mind's filled with you, Haran,
so a tiny fragment in my brain…
won't affect me.
Sir?
Just a moment.
What?
Why are we…
We were in Chuncheon earlier…
Manjae.
We're here. Let's get off.
How long has it been?
Where were you planning
to disappear off to alone?
Manjae.
What do I do?
What do I do about the kids?
I want
to stay with them longer.
I want to stay with you longer, too.
But what if I forget everything?
If I end up
forgetting you and the kids…
and everything else…
I'm scared.
I'm terrified.
It's all right.
Everything will be okay.
You can let it all out with me.
Don't worry.
I will never
let you be alone.
Never.
There's one missing.
Huh?
I took one of her charms.
How do I get this back to her?
The shrapnel's still lodged deep
in the temporal bone.
It's really fine,
Haran.
What did you wish for?
I won't wish for anything else
for the rest of my life.
Please just let me stay with this person
who let me live again,
through every tear and every smile.
I'm going to use that trial
for the rest of my life.
Just allow me this one thing.
Let me keep staying by her side.
My birthday, the day I decided
to explain everything,
despite the gaps.
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
PETROUS PART OF THE TEMPORAL BONE
Your sister's coming in.
What?
Are you applying for medical school, too?
I was just looking up something.
Is Grandma still sleeping?
Yeah, it's the first time.
She never slept in, even on the weekends.
Is she tired
after her trip to Chuncheon?
But what are those books for?
I just thought I'd work
to get my mind off things.
Do you have the pigment book?
It wasn't in Grandma's study.
It's probably in the attic. Hmm…
Why are your eyes puffy? Did you cry?
Huh?
Of course not.
I just slept well.
Just go and find that book for me.
Thank you.
You can overcome it.
You'll be able to escape on your own.
I wanted to show you, too.
What are you doing?
Why did you pull up your sleeves?
I want to clear out some stuff.
Like a spring deep clean.
Get your head together.
It's the middle of winter.
No, it's spring.
I don't think I'll wear this.
And this…
- I'm heading out.
- Wait.
-  You've got mail.
- Oh?
He must have sent a letter
since it's so hard to reach you.
That poor Kang Hyeokchan.
- See you later.
- Huh?
You're right. Oh…
Yes?
I'll be there right away.
Haran, you must still be busy.
It's already been a month
since I came to Boston.
Everything still feels unfamiliar to me.
I miss you, but it's hard to hear
your voice because of the time difference.
I've been thinking
about a way to communicate.
Can you use a messenger at work?
Tell me if you can.
Ah. Let me tell you something cool.
My dorm roommate is Korean,
and his name's Chan, too.
Isn't that funny?
But I think it'll be hard
to get close to him.
He seems a bit closed off.
I miss you so much, Haran.
I'll come see you during summer break.
Take care. I love you.
I booked the movie tickets.
I'll see you at 5:00 p.m.
Oh. I should get ready.
Mr. Park.
I might come home pretty late tonight.
All right.
Talk it out with Haran.
If you're sincere,
I'm sure she'll understand.
- All right. I will.
- Okay.
They must be in the corner.
This is broken.
It won't charge.
Do you have time
after the movie?
There's something I have to tell you.
I'll tell you everything honestly soon.
All right.
Oh? I forgot the other popcorn.
I'll go get it.
- Just wait here.
- I'll wait inside, then.
-  Sorry about that.
- It's okay.
Thank you.
- Is it a false alarm?
- What do we do?
Please follow the instructions
and evacuate immediately.
Please don't push.
Song Haran.
Please go downstairs.
Don't push!
Evacuate immediately.
You shouldn't go inside.
Sorry!
- Sir!
- Song Haran!
Song Haran!
Stop it!
Seonu Chan!
I'll tell you everything.
I'll tell you about the scars on my body.
I don't do well in noisy places.
Seonu Chan! Where are you?
Where were you?
I couldn't see you outside,
- so I thought you'd gone inside…
- I'm okay.
I'm so relieved nothing happened.
It's okay.
Let's go to the hospital
and get you checked.
I'll get a checkup soon.
Don't worry.
I'll be completely fine.
MEDICAL CHECKUP
Grandma.
What is it, Haran? Is something wrong?
What do I do, Grandma?
He's not well.
He keeps collapsing,
and there's something lodged in his head.
He says he's okay,
but he doesn't seem okay at all.
What do I do
if something happens to him?
I may not be
as good for her as you believe.
He's not keeping it from you.
He probably can't
because he's scared.
He probably doesn't want
to burden you with his pain
because it would hurt you.
He cares more
about protecting you than his own pain.
But I want to protect him.
I don't want him to go through it alone.
But there's nothing I can do for him.
Just stay by his side.
People can stay strong
even with just one person by their side.
Trust me, I know.
So don't worry too much.
I'm sure you'll find a way.
Waste container…
Kang Hyeokchan…
Lab…
Cha Sujin…
Stop it!
And me…
Was that day…
"Volatile reagent container fractured…"
"Self-reactive event
triggered by careless handling
of reagents."
"The cause has not been
conclusively determined."
No, there's nothing.
I said I don't know!
What is she trying to hide?
Don't do anything tomorrow
and get plenty of rest.
I'll always be by your side.
MY BIRTHDAY, THE DAY I DECIDED
TO EXPLAIN EVERYTHING, DESPITE THE GAPS
KANG HYEOKCHAN
CHA SUJIN
12-WEEK REHABILITATION PLAN
Ah. It's tomorrow.
But, Mr. Park, when should we tell
Hadam and her sisters?
Yougyum!
Hey, Dad!
Really? Okay.
Is it your dad?
- Let me say hi.
- Okay, Dad.
I said I wanted to say hi.
Oh, I didn't hear you.
- Sorry.
- Gosh.
Ta-da. It's pumpkin porridge.
It's rich in beta-carotene and vitamin A,
so it'll help with the inflammation.
Make sure to eat everything.
- Hadam.
- Yes?
You know I like you so, so much, right?
You helped me stay strong
when I was in pain.
If you ever have a hard time someday,
I'll do the same for you
so that you stay strong.
Sure.
But that's not going to happen.
Once you're better,
I'll have nothing but happy days ahead.
Hi.
- Did you have a good weekend?
- Yes.
I'm on my way to meet Mr. Chae.
He sent me files on the material,
but they kept getting corrupted,
so he's bringing them in person.
He must have something to cover nearby.
That's quite a coincidence.
Ah. I was checking the sample dye
from the color team.
I guess it wasn't dry yet.
I'll get going, then.
I felt so awkward
I ended up rambling.
Um… These are the colors
that Ms. Kim directed.
Then this would be the most similar,
but it might look muted on the fabric.
I think so, too.
We should try mixing the colors again.
Then let's apply the feedback
and submit a report for now.
Okay.
Coffee?
All right, everyone.
Fresh coffee.
- Mr. Park.
- Hello.
What brings you here?
I got a new batch of beans.
Gosh.
So I thought I'd deliver some
to my regular customers.
Thank you.
-  No problem.
- I'm taking this one.
It's totally my style.
Oh, I'm sorry.
This is reserved for someone else.
- Take this.
- Okay.
Too bad. Ribbons are my signature.
You brought coffee for everyone
since it'll be too obvious, right?
Oh…
- Could you tell?
- Yes.
How was your trip to Chuncheon?
Grandma was so excited to go.
Uh… Of course.
We had a great time.
By the way, is Mr. Seonu okay?
I didn't call
since I didn't want to bother him.
What? Did something happen?
He clearly doesn't seem well,
but he won't tell me.
Some people have a hard time
sharing things when they care
about someone deeply.
I can guarantee you
that when Chan
really has to tell you something,
he'll tell you honestly
without hiding it.
So just trust him
and wait patiently for that moment.
All right.
Mmm.
I startled you in Chuncheon, didn't I?
I was startled too and acted like a child.
I'm sorry.
But you don't have to worry.
I already planned everything.
What plan? To disappear on your own?
Your checkup's tomorrow, right?
You have to take me with you.
How did you know the date?
I met Yougyum.
He told me about the necklace
and how he's the only one who knows.
I see.
But I'm not a child, you know.
- I can go by myself--
- Nabong.
You don't have to act tough
in front of me.
I told you,
I won't let you be alone.
I guess this is why
we met after 50 years.
You have no one to rely on,
and have so many things to protect.
I'll protect you,
so you can rely on me.
I'll stay by your side.
Hmm?
What is all this?
You have to handle
everything on the desk in my place.
Finish them by today.
Hello? Ms. Kim--
Among the 12 SS candidate outfits,
the six I picked are fixed.
Pick the other six.
Submit a report on which to pick
and the reasons by today.
What? But--
You saw the pigment samples
yesterday, right?
Organize the differences in color
and decide which one to go with.
And the differences by fabric.
Send it by today.
Wait, Ms. Kim. I--
I received two drafts
of the press kit for Paris.
Choose the one that suits our image
and give it to Mr. Yeon.
I have work outside the office,
so I won't be there today.
Finish everything by today
and send it to me by email.
- All of that by today?
- Are you saying you can't?
Did you forget?
I told you to take my workload.
But still, this is…
Mr. Park!
Hmm?
He didn't mention anything.
Genius.
Do you know where Mr. Park went?
Hmm?
Where did he go?
Ms. Kim, can you confirm the materials…
Ah…
Right, she's at a meeting.
Okay.
I can't believe this.
Hayeong, you klutz.
Goodness.
What is this?
DON'T CAUSE TROUBLE FOR MY GRANDDAUGHTERS
I'M STILL OKAY
KEEP GLASSES IN FRONT OF THE MONITOR
DON'T TAKE OFF YOUGYUM'S NECKLACE!
"Noble Life Center"?
NOBLE LIFE CENTER
COUNSELING CENTER
Secure retirement.
This is the Noble Life Center,
Korea's premium senior care center.
Hello, this is Noble Life Center.
I…
I mean,
I wanted
to check my reservation.
What is your name?
I'm Kim Nabong's guardian.
Right, Kim Nabong.
She's still set to move in
at the end of June, right?
You wanted a single room
and signed up for the specialized
dementia care, right?
CLOSET KEY, JEWELRY BOX
"Closet key, jewelry box…"
I really don't need lunch.
When do I finish all of this?
Hayeong.
What is it?
What's wrong? Huh?
What do we do?
What do we do about Grandma?
What about Grandma? What's going on?
What is this?
NOBLE LIFE CENTER
CALL TO CONFIRM RESERVATION ON THE 17TH!
What do you mean?
Why would she go to a care center?
I know you're just playing a joke
since my CSAT is over.
- Hadam.
- That doesn't make any sense.
Why would Grandma…
Why would she go there?
I think she was trying
to leave quietly.
She must have been planning it
for quite a long time.
This was in here.
To my beloved granddaughters.
Bonjour, my beautiful granddaughters
who took after me.
By the time you've opened this,
I'll probably be having champagne
on a plane to southern France.
Don't move, ma'am.
Don't be too upset.
I want to reward myself
for working hard all these years.
So I'm really happy.
-  Please curl your back.
-  Oh.
And don't try to visit me.
I had such a hard time in my 20s
attending fashion school
with a baby on my back.
And I didn't get to try so many things
because I had no money or time.
I'm going to be extremely busy
doing everything I couldn't do back then.
So please…
-  Ms. Kim Nabong.
- Yes.
-  Let me enjoy my life here.
- Head to the next room.
Ah. And as for those
wedding gowns…
Your grandma's the famous Kim Nana,
so letting you wear wedding gowns
made by someone else?
Oh, no.
I can never let that happen.
I thought I'd be too busy
having fun in France
to make any clothes,
so I made them in advance.
I just made them easily in my spare time.
Let's meet again someday
after shining in each of our places.
I'll be rooting for your glorious lives
from far away.
Haran,
Hayeong,
Hadam.
My life was a brilliant shade of rose
because you three were my granddaughters.
Take care.
Au revoir.
Ah.
I hate saying cheesy things,
but I'm the type to say things I need to.
I love you,
my dear granddaughters.
Why…
She has three granddaughters.
Why would she…
It's weird that she's at a meeting.
Where is she right now?
She hasn't left already, has she?
SECRET WITH YOUGYUM
DON'T TAKE OFF YOUGYUM'S NECKLACE!
Why don't you spend some time
with your grandma--
Why are you suddenly
bringing up my grandma?
What?
Oh…
Why was your tumbler
in my grandma's study?
I ran into her a while ago in the park.
You know she wouldn't do such a thing.
Cha Yougyum.
You knew about Grandma, didn't you?
Where is she right now?
I already know everything!
Just tell me!
She's getting a checkup today.
Over there.
NEUROLOGY CENTER
-  Oh.
- Hey, Manjae.
- That took a while, didn't it?
-  Goodness.
You did great.
- Are you okay?
-  Yes.
How can you…
Of all people, how can you do this to me?
Why are you--
You should take some of my workload.
Let me get some rest, too.
He's not keeping it from you.
He probably can't.
He probably doesn't want
to burden you with his pain.
He cares more about protecting you
than his own pain.
A meeting?
And what's this…
I'll do it.
What was that, Grandma?
You didn't even look at him
and didn't say a word.
He left because
you made him uncomfortable.
Did Grandma summon you
and threaten you or something?
DON'T CAUSE TROUBLE FOR MY GRANDDAUGHTERS
Grandma.
I'm okay.
It's all right.
Ms. Kim Nabong.
Please go to the next room.
Okay.
I'll be back.
Let's go.
You've a lot of granddaughters.
All right.
See you in a bit.
Make sure to keep it dry,
and tell me if it's too tight.
Okay. Thank you.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You need some vitamins.
I'll peel these for you.
- It's fine, I'll do it.
- Mmm-mmm.
- Ah…
-  Cha Yougyum!
Bye.
Hadam…
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
about your grandma.
She said…
Thank you, Yougyum.
Thank you so much.
Yougyum has been taking care of her.
Without the necklace he gave her,
I would've lost her in Chuncheon.
It must have been tough
keeping that secret on his own.
She would've had a hard time on her own.
Thank you
for taking care of her.
Sorry, I didn't tell you.
You must've been shocked.
Thank you.
Thank you so, so much, Yougyum.
Let's go see her.
I didn't know.
I should've known,
but I didn't.
Why?
How could you not know?
It was you of all people.
You said she was your savior,
and you promised to take care of her.
You were always by her side.
How could you not know?
When I asked if anything happened
in Seongsu-dong,
why did you hide it from me?
No, if you weren't going to tell me,
shouldn't you have
looked into it more, at least?
If you'd found out then…
I'm sorry.
No.
Pretend you didn't hear that.
What I just said
is actually what I want to say to myself.
I know it's not your fault,
but I feel so pathetic and stupid.
So I don't know what to do.
I should've known.
I'm sorry…
I yelled at you.
Sorry.
He's not picking up.
Mr. Park, where are you?
Customers are coming in,
asking why you're closed today.
The hospital?
Then what about…
What about Ms. Song?
The MRI shows
normal intracranial pressure,
but the ventricles
are significantly enlarged.
We also ran a cerebrospinal fluid test
to double-check,
and the results show…
that it's not dementia.
Really?
That's such a relief.
But we suspect
normal pressure hydrocephalus.
Hydrocephalus?
It occurs when cerebrospinal fluid
isn't properly absorbed,
leading to symptoms like memory loss
and problems with walking.
The symptoms are similar,
so some mistake it for dementia.
I see.
Have you had any problems
with walking recently?
- I don't think I've seen…
- I'm not sure…
-  Oh!
-  Oh gosh.
She did. Last time,
you had bruises on your legs.
Huh? Did you hit your leg somewhere?
It's fine. I just fell.
My legs suddenly wouldn't listen.
Patients usually show a response
within 24 hours,
even within 10 hours
after draining the cerebrospinal fluid.
We'll be able to confirm this
after the gait test.
So let's see
how much improvement there is.
You can see how you sometimes
had narrower strides
and dragged your feet
in the morning, right?
But it improved significantly
after draining the fluid.
The tap test confirms
normal pressure hydrocephalus.
She can get better
with treatment, right?
With successful surgery,
she should improve.
All right.
We'll create a small opening in the skull
and insert a thin tube called a shunt
into the ventricle
to drain excess cerebrospinal fluid
into the abdomen.
Ah…
Given your age, I suggest
getting hospitalized a few days in advance
to run some basic tests first.
Proceed with the admission,
and we'll set the surgery date
based on your condition.
The admission's done already?
Yes, a tall man in a suit
came and finished the process.
He even paid the fees.
Mr. Yeon.
Cha Yougyum.
Yes, Ms. Kim.
You're an athlete.
Go take care of your own condition.
You need to recover.
- Song Hadam.
- Yes?
You said you'd help him.
Stay right by his side.
And…
Song Haran, Song Hayeong.
No, Lead Designer Song,
Designer Song Hayeong.
If anything at my company
goes wrong while I'm away,
I'm kicking all of you out.
So focus on work from now on.
Don't even think about coming here.
But…
Okay.
I'll be taking care of her
from now on,
so you youngsters
go and focus on your own stuff.
We'll take turns coming here.
You have your coffee shop.
Mmm-mmm.
SHIM is temporarily closed
until she gets surgery
and recovers well.
I'll think of this as winter vacation
and enjoy my time here with my old friend.
All right. Everyone, stop bothering us.
But where did Mr. Yeon go?
- I thought I saw him in the hallway.
-  Oh.
He'll probably be busy
taking care of things
in Grandma's place.
Oh?
I'm sorry, I took so long.
How did you know?
I heard from Mr. Park just a while ago.
I'm sure her surgery will go well.
I wish the people I love won't feel pain,
physically or mentally.
I'm sure she'll overcome this.
So don't get too scared.
Everything will be all right.
Sorry, but can we stay like this
for 10 more seconds?
We can stay like this for 10 minutes
or even 10 hours.
Sorry,
I didn't contact you sooner.
Things were so hectic.
Oh?
I'll be upset if you feel sorry over this.
You must've missed lunch.
Wait here, I'll get you something.
Then can I just get some coffee?
I don't think I can eat anything.
All right. Hang on.
Why are you dressed so lightly?
This cardigan is really valuable to me,
so I don't usually lend it to anyone.
But I'll let you wear it just this once.
Don't ruin it.
We meet again.
Oh. Hello.
My grandma's getting hospitalized here
for a few days.
Ah. Really?
Oh, um… I accidentally took
one of your bracelet charms.
I'll give it back to you
when I visit tomorrow.
Really? I was wondering
where that charm went.
That's great. But…
the man who was with you last time…
Is he your boyfriend?
Yes. Why do you ask?
You looked good together.
He reminded me of someone I used to know.
Ah.
Oh… You're a neurology doctor.
My grandmother's getting surgery
for hydrocephalus.
Please take good care of her.
I'm only visiting, so I'm not authorized
to treat patients directly.
I came from Boston.
Oh.
I see.
The neurosurgeons
will take good care of her.
The neurology department
will see the results, so I'll check.
And my bracelet…
I was worried
about the gap in my bracelet.
I'm glad you'll give it back to me.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- All right.
Bye.
You're back.
Yes, Mr. Park.
Oh, I met Mr. Seonu in the lobby.
Really?
Okay.
Grandma said
she wants to talk to you alone.
Is that okay?
- If you feel uncomfortable…
-  No, it's fine.
I should have put more thought
into what you said that day.
I'm sorry, Ms. Kim.
"That day"?
Thanks to you,
I'll be able to leave in peace.
Are you going somewhere?
I'm planning to stay in France
after I retire.
I hid this on purpose.
How could you have known?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
But…
I'd like to ask you the same thing.
I heard about your head.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm fine.
No,
I'm going to make sure I'm fine
so I can stay by Ms. Song's side.
My head, and everything else…
I'm going to make it all okay.
Haran cares…
for you a lot.
It actually surprised me
how sincere she is about you.
And she seems to be
thinking of a future with you.
I know, and I feel the same way.
I want to see you two
getting along well for as long as I can.
At least for Haran's sake and your sake,
make sure you're okay.
I will.
Thanks for coming.
Oh. When's your checkup again?
Next week.
It'll be fine, so don't worry about me.
Take good care of Ms. Kim.
I'll get going now.
- Right, your cardigan.
- Ah…
Keep it on. You'll catch a cold.
Don't worry.
Grandma was right.
Having just one person to lean on
will help you stay strong.
I do have a pretty broad back.
When did you notice?
Should I leave my back here
for you to lean on?
- Go.
- Okay. I'll go now.
Bye.
Head back inside.
Let me talk to you.
What do you think you're doing?
Stop messing with her.
The thing you wanted to protect…
was her?
Are you worried you'll lose her
if I say something?
Does she know
that you went to the same school
as Hyeokchan and were his roommate?
Does she know who you are?
Hyeokchan's dead, but you're alive,
and the person you want to protect
is his old girlfriend?
That's funny.
Since when?
Did you have feelings for her then?
You must've jumped at the chance
when he died.
Don't say it like that.
That's not the case.
She's going through a hard time right now.
Don't say things that…
will only dig up old wounds.
Please.
Why should I do that for you?
I remembered something.
The day that the waste container fell,
you were in the lab as well.
And you were shouting at him to stop.
I don't have the time
to answer all your questions.
Why was the waste container
next to Hyeokchan?
The day Hyeokchan's lip was busted…
Was that day
the day of the accident?
I didn't have any memories
of that day until now,
but it feels like it's from that day.
Tell me what happened in the lab that day.
You know what happened.
You can't tell Haran the truth.
No, you're not telling her.
So why are you so obsessed
with finding out what happened?
If everyone involved
has the right to know,
shouldn't Haran also know
that you're fake?
I'm going to tell her.
- But right now--
- If you go and tell her first,
then I might think about telling you, too.
Please.
Stop asking me strange questions.
If you provoke me,
even I don't know
what I'll end up telling her.
Hey, Kang Hyeokchan.
I have to tell you something.
I've been chatting with your girlfriend.
She thinks she's been talking to you.
You were pretending to be me?
Do you have any idea what you've done?
- I'm sorry.
-  Did you have feelings for her?
You must've jumped at the chance.
Shouldn't Haran also know
that you're fake?
I told him…
I told Hyeokchan everything.
But…
what happened after that?
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
It's all my fault.
"Fault…"
-  Nineteen.
- Nineteen.
-  Thirty-one point five.
- Thirty-one point five.
Everyone, let's keep our spirits up.
When Ms. Kim comes back,
we should show her how much we did
to put her mind at ease.
So how about a quick cheer?
No, forget it.
One, two, three.
Let's do this!
Whatever it is.
- Hey.
- It's Chan.
What's the occasion?
There's no meeting today.
We got the additional script,
so I dropped by.
And since SHIM is closed,
I made these myself.
I can't guarantee the taste.
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
But Ms. Song isn't here right now.
Really?
- Where did she go?
- She took the afternoon off.
Even if Ms. Kim told her not to come,
I guess she's pretty worried.
Did she go to the hospital?
No, she said she had to drop by somewhere.
She had to return something to someone.
Oh…
And my bracelet…
I'm glad you'll give it back to me.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Sunyul National
University Hospital is 1.5 km ahead.
Does she know who you are?
If you provoke me,
even I don't know
what I'll end up telling her.
Ah. The last patient's tone
seemed worse than the tremor.
- Let's reduce the dose.
-  Okay, I'll check.
- Oh. Haran.
-  You're here.
Mr. Seonu's upstairs, right?
I have to give him something.
He just left when I came here.
He said he had to go somewhere.
Oh…
Then can I just leave this in his room?
Sure, that's fine.
I'm heading back to the hospital.
I just came to get my stuff.
Then I'll give you a ride.
I'm heading there, too.
No, it's fine. I called a cab.
I made a lot of coffee
to share with the doctors.
I'll leave one for you.
Take your time drinking this
and meet Chan first.
- Okay.
-  He'll be back soon.
Mr. Park.
Yes?
Thank you for taking care of my grandma.
Gosh.
There's no need to thank me.
TEMPORARILY CLOSED
SORRY FOR THE INCONVENIENCE
Pardon me.
SEONU CHAN
Hey, roomie.
Yes, she's here.
She brought something for you,
so she went upstairs.
Hang on.
No, it's okay.
I'll be there in a few minutes.
Really?
Huh? My cab's here.
I'm going to the hospital,
so take care of Genius for me.
Is there a Post-it? Oh?
Is she upstairs?
Are you here?
Huh?
Hmm?
THANKS FOR THE
KANG HYEOKCHAN, GLASS TUBE, BLOOD
THAT SOUND AGAIN
KANG HYEOKCHAN HOSPITALIZED, WOMAN
THAT SOUND WAS HER BRACELET
I'll tell her everything
and apologize to her.
I want to tell her everything
and love her as my true self…
from now on.
Before it's too late.
Chan.
Why did you come back?
Well…
Did Ms. Song come here?
Hey, what's gotten into you?
- We told you she's going to the hospital.
- Ah…
All right.
Mr. Park, is Ms. Song
at the hospital right now?
No, she's not here.
Did you not see her?
Oh…
It's nothing. Never mind.
RAN
Are you home?
If you're home, come out.
Let's meet. Let's meet up and talk.
I'll explain everything.
- Hey…
-  Don't come any closer.
Boston Institute of Technology.
Kang Hyeokchan's roommate.
Have you really known me
for seven years?
- Song Haran.
- Don't say my name.
Did you have fun
pretending to be Kang Hyeokchan?
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
She found out about everything.
I didn't have the chance to explain.
If those two facts don't change,
I won't change, either.
Don't ever show up in front of me again.
You don't have to look at me
or listen to me. So please,
just look at this.
Haran, you're burning up.
You did a great job so far
working by my side.
Haran's gone.
You're the only one I could ask
where she could be.
I have to go find her.
It has to be me.
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Translated by Juyoung Park