IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
CHARACTERS, EVENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND PLACES IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
But why would you say liking me
is being greedy?
Because you'll go back soon?
It doesn't matter if I'm being greedy now.
I can't stop my feelings anyway.
So I'll just keep going,
because I don't want
to waste our time together.
Then don't say
you're being greedy anymore.
If you say that again,
I won't let it slide.
I should be careful, then.
EPISODE 8
Stop staring at it.
It won't even be visible tomorrow.
Oh. And make sure to call your grandma.
She'll be worried sick
after you left like that.
I will.
I used to be just like that watch.
I was frozen in time,
but someone made time move again for me.
Like this.
So how about letting time with your dad
start moving again?
The past is the past.
What's important
is the time that will flow from now on.
Her boyfriend died back then.
He went to study in Boston,
but he suddenly died.
Hey, roomie.
The fact that I lived
while he died from that accident…
It's a good thing you took it out.
I want someone to have joy in their life.
She was a grateful disruption
that made me live again.
Mr. Park, we…
Of course. I know.
Take her home safely.
Let's go, Genius.
Go on in.
Bye.
Look forward.
It'll be dangerous
if you fall down the hill.
I'm relieved.
You're warm.
It's just that…
this feels like a dream.
I can't believe it.
Should I make this feel more real?
No, thanks.
I'll go now. Head inside.
Get back safely.
What a relief.
Now, now.
You didn't take your meds again?
I told you to take them on time.
Let's go to the hospital this week.
Keep your cardiac enzyme
test results in your wallet
so someone can see it if you ever collapse
when you're not with me.
We have to go, okay?
Just think of me as a nagging son,
and come with me.
All right.
And you
should think of me
as a father who listens to you,
so tell me anything
that you have a hard time
telling anyone else.
You can tell me
anything that troubles you.
I'll be your safe space.
I wasn't trying to hide
my relationship with Ms. Song…
You really like her, right?
- Yes.
- All right.
Let her feel joy again.
You don't need a reason
to want someone to be happy.
As long as you're sincere, it's okay.
Ms. Song,
there's an international delivery.
Wow.
I finally got the sketch sample
for my design.
Make some noise!
It's all thanks to this pen.
But how did you come up
with the idea of sending me a pen?
I kept thinking about how you said
you felt like you were trapped.
I used to feel that way, too.
Back then, I kept thinking the same thing.
If…
there was just a small crack
to breathe through, I could live.
But…
that "if" never came true for me.
I guess I wanted
that pen to be that "if" for you.
Chan understands me so well…
Sorry, I was rambling.
I should go now.
-  Great work today.
-  You too.
- I'm going back to Korea first.
- Okay, sure.
Maybe it's because I lost
the pen I used for seven years,
but I couldn't sketch anything
during the two days here.
Yes, seven years ago. Early July.
And the engraving is Haran.
One second.
Uh, yeah. We have the model name
and the engraving design on file.
The past is the past.
What's important…
is the time
that will flow from now on.
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Grandma.
Where have you been?
I was at a meeting.
Our dinner ended late.
A meeting dressed like this?
And what's this…
I'll do it.
I'm tired. I'm going to bed.
Grandma, did you go to Seongsu…
I'm sorry, but just let this go for now.
Please.
What?
I just…
thought we haven't been
talking much lately.
Are you sure nothing's wrong?
What's wrong is you asking questions
when I'm so sleepy.
Go to bed.
All right. Good night.
Why are her shoes like that?
It couldn't have been a meeting.
Where in the world was she?
EXAMINATION
The door is closing.
Let me get on!
Thank you.
What's that?
He's the definition of neatness,
and he's got bedhead?
Okay,
I'll check and email you.
He's late and has bedhead? Mr. Yeon?
What's going on?
That doesn't suit him at all.
Look. Isn't it crazy?
- This is insane.
- Is this for real?
Sorry! What are you up to?
Hayeong! Seunggyu took a rare photo.
What photo?
I was organizing the photos
I took during my trend research…
and I was shocked.
That stiff, uptight Mr. Yeon is dating?
This is crazy!
But they look so good together.
They do.
How shameless.
Why is she being so loud when she's late?
Hey, look.
She's the head of La Mode Eclat,
and that's the co-head and her husband.
Oh, geez.
Seunggyu! They were just having
a business meeting.
So they were the heads
of La Mode Eclat.
Sorry about that.
Oh, dear. Why is she suddenly whistling?
There's no in-between with her.
He's right.
Why am I relieved?
But I wonder if Mr. Yeon
would still have that default expression
when he's dating.
No way. I'm sure he'll be different.
He might be
really sweet to the woman he likes.
Sweet?
Your hand.
You might slip
since you're wearing heels.
This happened to my friend,
uh…
but this guy
brushed off dry leaves in the dirt
with his bare hands so she wouldn't slip.
What does that mean?
With his bare hands?
That's love.
Love?
Then if the woman cried,
and he looked at her with pity
and wiped her tears with his hand,
what does that mean?
Love.
He loves me?
And the fact that
you're overanalyzing his every move
means you like him too.
No, that wasn't about me.
That was my friend.
It's obvious it was about you.
My friend told me during a school reunion.
You liar.
Ms. Song Hayeong.
- The new material you mentioned…
-  Ah.
Uh… Mmm…
Hello?
Yes, hello.
I just got an urgent call.
Are you busy right now?
I'm busy too.
What should I say when I give this to her?
Hmm?
Hey, you said
you're coming in the evening.
I'm meeting someone here.
Goodness.
You mean with me?
She's meeting me!
- Hmm?
- What? This is so sudden.
Something came up,
so she's returning to Mungyeong today.
Wow. You were going to meet without me?
- You're always leaving me out.
-  Right.
He's sulking.
This place looks nice.
Wow.
It's shattered and cracked.
And there seem to be
some pieces missing. Hmm?
Will it be too hard?
I can make it work.
It may take some time,
but as long as we don't give up,
it can be fixed somehow.
It would be different from the original,
but let's think of it
as making it stronger.
Thank you so much.
Here's your coffee.
My grandson must be troubling you a lot.
If he does anything to irritate you,
you can just smack him on the back
and kick him out.
Really?
He's been nagging me so much lately
that I've been thinking about it.
I will keep that in mind.
Stop it.
You must be curious about the house.
You can take a look after you're done.
No, it's your private space. I shouldn't…
It's fine. It's also Chan's house.
Give her a tour later.
Seeing you stay with someone so nice
makes me feel at ease.
Be good to him, all right?
I will.
Wow.
So how about letting time with your dad
start moving again?
Chan.
It's nothing. Never mind.
It was nothing.
When will you visit again?
That little brat isn't even seeing me off.
I should give him a smack.
Grandma.
Can you drop me off on the way?
Where?
Daejeon.
I don't know what I'll do there,
but I think
I should at least give this back to him.
Mm.
I saw Yougyum this weekend.
He was going to karaoke with his friends.
Are you having
a lot of fun these days?
Did you have fun at karaoke?
What? I…
Yeah, I had fun.
You seemed to be having fun, too.
You gave Seokhyeon
a drink with a heart on it.
What?
So you saw it.
Yeah, I'm happy these days.
I'm really glad to hear that.
Yeah, so let's both live happy lives.
CHEMICAL AND BIOLOGICAL ENGINEERING
PROFESSOR SUNWOO SEOK
May I help you?
Oh. I'm here to see Professor Sunwoo.
Ah.
He's gone to the president's office.
May I ask what you're here for?
We're family.
- If he's not here--
- He'll probably be back soon.
Why don't you wait inside?
Ah…
He's taking a while.
Should I try calling him?
No, I'll just go.
Would it be okay
to leave this here?
Sure, go ahead.
KOREA SCIENCE UNIVERSITY
Let me keep this, Dad.
How long are you going to keep doing this?
What more do I have to do
to make you stop?
Excuse me, you said you're family.
Are you his son who's working
as an animator in the US?
You are, right?
I heard a lot about you
from Professor Sunwoo.
He always rushes to see
any movies that get released.
He even buys tickets for his students.
Can I ask you something, sir?
I heard there's a famous bakery nearby.
Do you know where it is?
Excuse me?
I came here to buy bread.
I heard there's
a really famous bakery here.
You're such a bad liar.
Were you worried
something would've happened again?
Well…
I also came to check
Daejeon's fashion trends.
Wow.
Everyone's so fashionable here.
And I thought that if anything happened,
I could give you a hug.
Look at you.
When going to Gyeongju,
at the airport, and now Daejeon…
You keep surprising me like this.
You'll make me get my hopes up.
I'll keep thinking you'll appear anywhere.
Fine.
I'll appear anywhere you are,
so you can get your hopes up.
Seonu Chan!
I'm so glad you've recovered.
Professor Sunwoo gave up on his research
just before presenting it
to go take care of you in America
when you were badly injured.
We've done everything we can.
Now we just have to hope
that he'll pull through.
The truth is, you should be aware
it's not very likely that he'll wake up.
Thanks…
for the watch.
Maybe you should return your degree.
A famous engineering professor
can't even fix a broken watch?
It's working well now.
Thank you…
for fixing it.
If you're grateful,
you can pay me back later.
Grandma called.
She thanked me and said I did well.
Really?
That's great.
I'm so glad you gave it back to him.
That watch must be
dozens of times more precious now.
It could have ended
with him being sad about losing it,
but now, it's the watch that his son
fixed and returned to him.
Can I see you for a moment again?
Huh?
How did you…
Remember when we went to that restaurant?
When I was in bad shape because of my ear.
It's noisy in there.
I'll go bring our stuff.
It must have gotten mixed up
in my stuff back then.
I found it
when I unpacked my luggage here.
Ah…
I don't need it anymore, though.
I'm already using a different one.
Plus, I have dozens of pens now.
Someone gave me a whole bunch
as a gift.
That's why I'm giving it back now.
I…
was worried that I'd remind you
of the memories back then.
But I thought you wouldn't be wavered now.
Just think of it as a pen
that's the most effective and use it.
I know how important it is
to have a tool that fits you just right
since I'm an animator.
I can just get used to this pen.
Let me borrow this for a second.
Just consider this pen
a pen that I found for you,
not a pen that you got as a gift
or a pen that made you sad
when you lost it.
And… here's a lucky charm.
You know you'll get lucky
once you see an iridescent cloud.
You can see one every day now,
so you'll be lucky every day.
Just use it.
I sincerely want you to use it again.
All right.
I will.
It's the pen you found for me now.
Hello?
Really?
All right.
Thank you. Okay.
No way.
- This is crazy.
- What is it?
Something good really happened.
I'm receiving an award.
The Best Designer Award
at the Fashion Awards.
See? I told you that you'd be lucky.
Congratulations.
Genius.
Are you here?
Huh?
Hey, Genius.
Is there something there?
What…
Nabong!
What are you doing here at this hour?
Hey, Manjae.
I wanted to get a cup of coffee
after I finished work,
but I didn't realize it was so late.
The snow was beautiful,
so I was watching it for a bit.
It's so late…
And you're dressed so lightly.
It's cold.
Come on, let's go inside.
Get yourself warmed up.
What on earth is going on?
I was so absorbed in work,
I didn't notice the time.
You know how focused I can get.
Are you sure nothing's wrong?
Is everything really okay?
Is this some trending challenge?
Why is everyone asking me that?
Did I neglect my skincare
because I was too busy?
Have some warm tea.
What on earth
is going on with you?
LAUNDRY DETERGENT
LAVENDER
Aren't you my Hadam?
It's me.
Mom.
Mom?
Oh, my goodness!
I finally got to meet you.
I wanted to see you so much.
It's me, Yougyum's mom.
What? Ah…
Ah!
Hello.
Goodness, it's so nice to meet you.
I recognized you right away.
Our house is plastered with photos of you.
I feel like I'm meeting a celebrity.
If it's all right, could I give you a hug?
My dear Hadam.
It's so nice to see you.
What's wrong? What is it?
♪ Sleep well, dear Hadam ♪
♪ Sleep in Mommy's arms ♪
♪ Sleep tight ♪
I found…
Mom's smell.
Come on. I'll make you a meal.
Let's go.
Excuse me.
Where is the grocery store?
-  Honey.
- Come on in.
Hello.
Look who it is!
Isn't she our superstar?
- Our dear Hadam.
- Ah…
We told Yougyum to bring you,
but he said
we shouldn't bother your studies
and kept you hidden all along.
I ran into her by chance
at the supermarket.
Welcome.
Did you eat?
Join us for a meal.
Gosh. I told you to bring me
when you're buying heavy stuff.
I'll bring these upstairs.
Gosh!
My goodness.
I can't believe him.
LET'S BE SOMEONE HADAM WILL BE PROUD OF!
I wondered why
he only got perfect scores in English.
I heard you told him in your first year.
The Major League?
If that's your goal,
shouldn't you at least
study English in advance?
I want to be better
than I was yesterday.
"Challenge."
Challenge.
Since then,
his father has been studying English, too.
He said he wants to help Yougyum.
This is how much influence
you have over our family.
He's unbelievable.
Honey, should I braise the fish?
Hang on.
- Sorry. Take a look around.
- Okay.
But how did you end up dating Yougyum?
He said he had a crush on you
since elementary school.
Thinking back,
he was the only one who understood me.
Why aren't your parents
here for the field day?
Hey, she's the poor kid
whose parents both died.
Really? That's so pitiful.
Hey, having your parents
pass away isn't pitiful.
It's just sad.
I solved this when I stayed up
studying last night.
Hadam.
In baseball, throwing pull power
every time will strain your body.
You need a breather to grow stronger.
A breather?
That's why…
you need a breather now.
All right. Pitcher Cha Yougyum
is ready to throw.
I hit it!
Run, Hadam!
Go!
Right.
Yougyum always understood me.
Nabong, guess what I found?
Manjae, where did you get that photo?
Oh.
I was organizing my vinyl collection,
and it just fell out.
I can't believe it.
That was such a long time ago.
I wonder if that tree is still there.
Remember the tteokbokki place
we used to go to in the market?
What was it called?
- Ah! Fat Tteokbokki.
- Fat Tteokbokki.
Right?
Ah… I'm craving
that super sweet tteokbokki.
Do you want to go
have tteokbokki this evening?
No…
You shouldn't ditch work, right?
Come on.
Nabong, have you forgotten
that I'm the owner?
I can totally ditch work.
Well, well.
I caught you. Are you ditching work?
No, I'm receiving an award.
Oh, right. The Fashion Awards is today.
Congratulations.
See you.
Love.
That means you like him too.
No way.
Was he right?
Why does he look so cool
when he's just walking?
Why am I blushing?
And why am I sweating?
Are you free this evening?
This evening?
Not morning or afternoon?
Is he asking me out?
On a date?
I got a reply that the factory
couldn't get any of the bio silk
you talked about.
I did more research
and got in touch with an industry
tech reporter who wrote about it.
We're meeting this evening.
We may find a way to do it.
Mr. Yeon's cheeks
seem a little red, too.
Huh? And he's sweating.
Was Raemee really right?
Then we really like each other?
Great job with the meeting.
How about some wine?
Just you and me,
alone.
Sure. I'd like that.
Pardon? Uh…
Are you saying you'll come?
Ah.
Yes, I'm free.
I'll drive, then.
I'll see you at the parking lot
at 7:00 p.m.
Why are we meeting at 7:00 p.m.?
Right.
The new material.
The meeting.
GYUM'S LAUNDRY
I'm home.
Mom.
Mom, I must have lost my mind.
I miss Hadam so much,
I must be hallucinating.
But…
it's still so nice to see her.
You idiot.
It's really me.
Wow.
She's even talking now.
I must have gone crazy
from missing her so much.
You idiot.
It really is me.
Is it really you?
You're really Hadam?
I didn't give Seokhyeon my number.
Someone left a drink at my seat
with a heart post-it,
and I rushed out thinking it was from you.
When I heard it was from Seokhyeon,
I gave it back to him.
Really?
I'm sorry I misunderstood.
I wasn't having fun at karaoke either.
My friends took me there to comfort me,
but I just kept crying
at the thought of you.
I'm sorry I misunderstood you, too.
But why are you wearing glasses?
Has your eyesight gotten bad?
No,
I don't need them now.
And you? Why were you
at the nurse's office? Were you sick?
I just got a small cut on my hand,
but I'm all better now.
I'm sorry, Hadam.
I'm more sorry.
I missed you so much.
I missed you even more.
The Best Designer Award.
Nana Atelier, Song Haran.
There are two winners this year.
Onne Apparel, Kang Eunchan.
Haran.
I have to go to the factory.
There's a fabric issue.
I booked a table at Haeon,
the restaurant nearby.
Take this and go there.
I said I'd buy dinner for my brother,
but I can't let him eat alone.
Sorry, but just have dinner
with him, okay?
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday… ♪
I'm sorry. I haven't slept
for the past three days.
Sorry. Right.
♪ Happy birthday, dear… ♪
Kang Hyeokchan.
♪ Kang Hyeokchan ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
A Mr. Kang from our house
asked me to give it to you.
- What?
- Good luck.
VITAMINS FOR ENERGY
A CUSHION FOR A NAP
CHOCOLATE AFTER LUNCH
CHAMOMILE AFTER WORK
WITH THESE, YOU CAN SLEEP BETTER
- I love you.
- Hmm?
That's so sudden.
It's work.
Good luck with the embassy interview.
Hello?
I can't believe I have to work
when you're leaving.
I'm so sorry, Chan.
It's fine.
I told you I won't get upset
about you being busy.
I'll be back during vacation. I love you.
I'm so sorry.
Leave me a message when you arrive.
I can't go back to Korea
because of my lab schedule.
And my phone's broken,
so I won't be able to text for a while.
Leave me a message
if there's anything urgent.
I knew it.
Are you sure he just doesn't want to come?
- What?
- Well, I haven't seen it myself,
but he was so nice to you
when he was in Seoul.
But you were always busy
and didn't keep in touch often.
You didn't even show much affection.
You'll get dumped at this rate.
You're right.
I guess I deserve it.
That's too bad.
What's that reaction?
Do you even like Hyeokchan?
Of course I do. He's my boyfriend.
No, not like that.
Do you love him?
Mmm?
Did Chan send that?
He sent a drawing pen
for his designer girlfriend?
Wow. And even with your name
engraved on it?
But how did you come up
with the idea of sending me a pen?
I KEPT THINKING ABOUT HOW YOU SAID
YOU FELT LIKE YOU WERE TRAPPED
I GUESS I WANTED THAT PEN
TO BE THAT "IF" FOR YOU
Chan understands me so well…
SORRY, I WAS RAMBLING
I miss you, Hyeokchan.
Ta-da! I'm at the airport!
I wanted to tell you something in person.
Chan. I love you.
I love you, Chan.
Haran, what do I do?
Chan…
Hyeokchan is dead.
I moved to Onne Apparel.
It's awkward giving you my business card.
Have you been well?
It's already been…
seven years.
I always wondered how you were doing,
but I felt too guilty to contact you.
Why would you feel guilty?
- What is it?
- Oh…
Were you getting checkups here?
Huh?
Ahh.
I was at a different ER
when I collapsed last time.
I got a referral, so I come here.
It's closer.
- What is it?
- Ah…
I got treated here before.
I'll go ask where we can get the results.
We have to go to the annex.
Really?
But why are you dressed up today?
Hmm?
I have to be dressed up
to go somewhere later.
Mmm…
Where are you going?
The door is closing.
Huh? Hey, roomie!
Mr. Park.
Sorry, I'll head over there.
Okay.
Visiting neurology resident
from Boston General Hospital,
Cha Sujin.
I'm Cha Sujin.
I'll do my best
to learn as much as I can here.
Nice to meet you all.
Dr. Cha.
You shouldn't wear accessories here.
Sorry. I forgot to take it off.
MEDICAL STAFF SEARCH
LEE SUJIN
I'm sure she was in a gown.
All right.
I got the results.
But why did you suddenly get off earlier?
Oh. It was nothing.
There's a convenience store nearby.
I'll go buy some drinks for the nurses.
Mmm.
Hmm? They didn't say it was going to rain.
Is it a shower?
I have a hood, so it's fine.
I'll be back soon.
Okay.
Who's that? Your friend?
No, just my roommate.
Dr. Cha, we're starting rounds.
Okay.
Hospitalized?
- Hyeokchan?
-  Don't you remember?
He hurt his hand badly in the lab.
He even got surgery.
A surgery?
I never heard anything about that.
Manjae, what do you think?
It looks like
Genius' paw print. It's cute.
- Right?
- Should I buy it for you?
- Sure.
- Okay. How much is it?
- Manjae!
- What? What is it?
Tteokbokki! Tteokbokki!
It's good.
Having tteokbokki after ditching
is the best.
Right?
That only applies
to the Chuncheon fashionista Nabong.
I never ditched school.
Ah. Right, of course.
You were the bookworm Park Manjae.
That's right.
Excuse me.
Are you Kim Nana, by any chance?
It seems like it, right?
We're fashion design majors,
and we're huge fans.
Could I have an autograph?
Mmm… Oh, dear. My face is my autograph.
You can take a selfie with me.
One, two, three.
Thank you.
By the way, your husband is freaking…
I mean, he's really cool.
- No, I'm…
- He's freaking cool, isn't he?
I care about looks.
Why do I feel so nervous
being alone with him?
Oh… I feel so hot.
Should I turn off the heater?
Would it show that I'm nervous?
It's hot.
Should I close the window?
No, it's fine. You can do as you like.
Then would it be possible to get samples?
Yes, but it's over five times
the price of silk,
and the durability tests
aren't stable yet.
That's why I want to try this.
I want to make clothes
not just for display
but to prove the future.
I really want to achieve that
for our brand.
You seem very determined.
How should we get the samples?
There's a research facility
I came in touch with.
It's a bio startup company.
I'll give you their number.
- Really?
-  Yes.
And I'll ask them again
for their cooperation.
Thank you…
I was just so grateful.
- Are you all right?
-  Yes.
- You really mean it?
- Of course.
- Ms. Song, here's my business card.
- Ah.
Contact me if you have any questions.
Thank you.
It was nice seeing you again, Taeseok.
What? Do you two know each other?
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm actually his junior from college.
He asked me
to keep it a secret
in case you felt uneasy.
I tried to get close to him,
but he never let me back then.
And now--
Thank you for today, Mr. Chae.
I'll see you next time.
You haven't changed a bit.
I'd like to get to know you better.
How about a glass of wine together?
Just the two of us.
Just the two of us?
That's okay, right?
I don't think it's my place
to say yes or no.
Then excuse me.
What was that?
Did he just set me up on a date?
Didn't he have feelings for me?
Mr. Yeon.
Is it really okay for me
to have a drink with him, alone?
Why are you asking me that?
I think it's your business.
Ah. Fine.
Mr. Chae, let's go have some wine.
I'm really craving a drink today.
Hadam, enjoy these dishes.
You even packed side dishes for me?
Thank you.
Make sure to visit after the CSAT.
I promise I will.
But could you give me
one more hug?
Of course, I can. Come here.
I'll see you again later. Hmm?
Okay.
- Me too. I want a hug, too.
- My goodness!
Then I should join as well.
A surgery?
I never heard anything about that.
You didn't know?
I guess Chan didn't tell you
in case you got worried.
Excuse me.
You're Designer Song Haran
who won the Best Designer Award, right?
Oh? How are you here?
I have a habit of congratulating people
who receive awards.
Here.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
But why do you look so down
when you just won an award?
No, I'm really happy.
No, your expression looks…
like this.
Let's go.
Go where?
Photos? That's so random.
I told you, what you took doesn't count.
Oh. This one's good.
All right. Come here.
Our Best Designer.
Okay. One, two, three.
You should smile.
This time with the flowers.
Here. Smile.
All right. One, two, three.
I'll do an ugly face for you
to make you look prettier.
One, two, three.
Pretty pose.
Look at your expressions.
- Let's go to our next course.
- What?
Where? Where are we going?
Come on, let's go.
This way.
Wow. You came to such
a nice place alone? Tsk.
You're the one
who disappeared without telling me.
Excuse me, could you take a picture of us?
Sure, of course.
Two, three.
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
Would you like a photo, too?
Sure.
Okay. Smile.
It'll look nice
if you smile at each other.
- Can you look at each other?
- Like this?
What should I do?
I'll do an ugly face for you.
- We'll take one for you, too.
- Oh, I'm okay.
Thank you.
I'll take it now.
One, two, three.
There's a blanket I've been using
since I was a baby,
and it had this distinctive scent.
It felt warm and comforting
and made me feel like I'm going to cry.
But that scent disappeared.
It smelled just like my mom used to.
But when your mom hugged me earlier,
I smelled the same scent.
So I ended up crying.
I thought it was the smell of detergent,
but I guess that was the scent of a mom.
Oh? Then wouldn't I smell similar?
Try smelling me.
You have a different scent.
I'm going to marry you, no matter what.
What?
Whenever I see you,
I wonder how you could be so wonderful.
But I understood when I saw your parents.
If they become my family,
I'll be so happy.
Still, I'll love you the most.
What do I do?
I'm so happy,
I feel like I'm going to faint.
There's nothing left
but happiness for us.
Mm.
Let's go. I want to study.
Okay.
The minimum CSAT requirement?
It's going to be a piece of cake.
Why aren't you coming?
Did you really faint?
Come on. Stop fooling around.
Hadam, what do I do?
I can't get up.
My foot…
What?
Huh?
Yougyum…
Thank you for the umbrella.
See you.
-  Yes!
-  Bye.
Sure. Bye.
- Bye.
- Get home safely.
Okay.
Tsk. He made me
get my hopes up for nothing.
I should thank him.
I'm so grateful that he introduced us.
Why isn't he picking up?
Mr. Yeon, I had so much fun
with Mr. Chae today…
What are you spying on?
Gosh, you scared me.
Did Mr. Yeon not come back here
after the meeting?
He just dropped by for a bit and left.
Ah.
You'd better buy me lunch…
for the information.
He always gets off work late, though.
Mr. Yeon Taeseok?
There's a delivery for you.
I'll take that.
Thank you.
YEON TAESEOK
Mr. Yeon.
What? He's not home, either?
Mr. Yeon, I…
Oh?
What…
What's going on?
This keychain is so cute.
Manjae, let's go have sujebi next time.
And let's visit Chuncheon as well
before it gets colder.
- Let's…
- Kim Nabong.
What?
Why aren't you coming?
You.
Where are you going this time?
I said let's go to Chuncheon.
You're behaving just like back then.
When you suddenly left for France
when you were 20,
you acted just like this.
You called me out of the blue
and said, "Let's do this. Let's go here."
Then you suddenly disappeared
without saying anything.
That was a long time ago. Don't be silly.
Tell me.
What is it this time?
What on earth is going on with you?
Hello?
Yes. May I ask who's calling?
Oh…
All right.
I'll go and check.
Ah.
I miss you already.
- Hmm?
-  Can you come out for a bit?
That was fast, wasn't it?
Aren't you tired?
I mean, I told you to go home and rest,
but…
I was actually really sad
that you left.
What is it?
Is something wrong?
I just got a call from the restaurant.
What restaurant?
I think you owe me an explanation.
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
It sounds like
they're not meant to be together.
Can you tell me what you know
about what happened seven years ago?
I'll tell her everything
and apologize to her.
The chance
of Ms. Song and I dating is zero.
Am I really just mistaken
about all those situations?
It's rare to find
someone who makes you smile.
What if you're not okay?
What if something else happens?
I want to stay by her side,
but I don't know what to do.
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Translated by Juyoung Park