IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
CHARACTERS, EVENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND PLACES IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
Then is it okay if I like you?
Uh…
I think we should turn this off.
I didn't mean that…
I didn't mean that, either.
My grandmother kept talking
about us dating,
so I was just…
trying to stop that in advance
since you might feel uneasy.
That's all.
That's really it?
Should there be something else?
I'll start driving, then.
EPISODE 5
GYEONGJU
The cold is expected
to arrive earlier this year than usual.
The first snow may fall sooner
than average as well.
The continental high-pressure system--
It would be a shame to just leave.
Can you pull over?
Wow. It would've been a huge shame
if we'd just left.
I hate snow.
Especially the first snow.
The first snow?
Remember what I told you about my parents?
The accident happened
on the first snowfall.
So it became an unlucky day for me.
Mmm.
I know it's a lame jinx, though.
Then I'll start hating
the first snow, too.
Oh, um…
I have a habit of copying other people.
I'm not sure if it's okay to ask this,
but when I talked about my mom's voice…
you said there's someone you miss.
That was your mother, right?
Your grandmother told me.
I was surprised when you spoke
like you experienced the same thing.
Uh…
Croissant.
Croissant?
The pastry?
The crescent moon.
It's "croissant" in French.
Don't you crave croissants
when you see the crescent moon?
Anyway, your grandmother said--
What about the half-moon?
Omurice!
And the full moon?
It's pizza. Huh?
Was it just me, then?
I'm craving pizza.
Ben, we're here.
Are they not here yet?
Surprise!
- How have you been?
- I'm good, I'm good.
- It's great to see you here in Korea.
- Me too.
Let me quickly introduce her.
Guys, this is designer Haran Song.
Uh… Nice to meet you.
I'm Peter. Uh…
-  It's so great to meet you.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- This is my team.
- Nice to meet you. Hi.
Nice to meet you.
We're going to spend the morning
taking in the scenery,
visiting some historic sites,
and then we will head over
to Yangdong Village.
So on page 3, there's more information
about Yangdong Village.
So as you can see, there's a big tree.
This tree is more than 500 years old.
It's really famous.
So his father sent him to America,
and he suffered there.
"Something terrible"?
What happened in the US?
Why won't he tell me about himself?
That's a great idea.
Let's use that tree.
It's famous in Yangdong.
Ms. Song,
about the materials you sent over…
Yes.
It's pretty decorative, right?
We'll turn it into a pattern.
Why am I someone you shouldn't like?
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Oh?
What are you doing?
Oh. Playing a game to pick the driver.
You saw our team, right?
They're all mischievous.
Did you lose?
- Then I'll drive--
- I'm the king of games.
I won, of course.
We're here!
Hey, Sol!
Why are you alone?
Raemee is here!
Gosh, I just realized on the way here
how beautiful Gyeongju is.
It's totally my style.
It seems like
you're moving here.
I need this much luggage
at least to dress for the occasion.
Don't play dumb!
- We're here, too.
- Me too.
Okay, everybody's here.
We'll leave in 10 minutes. Okay, guys?
Let's lie down!
This is so nice.
HWANGNIDAN STREET
GYEONGJU BREAD
Yes, Ms. Kim.
Seeing it in person,
I think we should emphasize
the Korean elements a bit more.
Then I'll come up with another sketch
with that in mind.
All right.
This is pretty tough.
Aren't you tired?
It's a tough schedule, isn't it?
It's okay.
Everyone seems excited, though.
You seem like friends
rather than colleagues.
We weren't this close,
but after Too Much joined us…
You didn't join at the same time?
Too Much is several years my junior.
At school and at work.
He joined this field pretty late.
Oh. Then he studied something else
before animation?
I don't know, either.
He never tells me
what he did before entering CalArts.
It's like he erased it.
Erasing his time…
Are you two badmouthing me?
You caught us!
I'm fleeing!
You badmouthed me, didn't you?
- No, we didn't.
- I think you did.
Did you sketch something?
- Oh… Yes. Do you want to see?
- Sure.
Wow.
Your grandmother said
you didn't draw for a while.
How did you end up drawing again?
I'm curious.
Was there a special reason?
Oh. Hmm…
I'd like a ticket
for the earliest departure anywhere
except the US.
Hi, where are you from?
Well, anyway… Enjoy Florence.
THE PAST
THINGS TO DO FROM NOW ON
THINGS I WANT TO DO FROM NOW ON
DRAW
I just…
didn't want to live like a corpse.
A corpse?
Doesn't it feel like we time-traveled?
This tree is over 500 years old.
Mmm.
If you can time travel,
when do you want to return to?
Mmm… I don't want to go back.
I don't have a past I want to return to.
Doesn't everyone have
a certain moment, though?
You never know when you'll die.
You should enjoy your life
instead of regretting the past,
so you won't feel upset later.
Mmm.
Maybe it's that free trial.
I do feel kind of excited these days.
We went to the Hangang River,
made pottery,
and came here.
You're doing great.
Keep enjoying your life
like this every day,
even when…
I'm not here later.
Oh? You changed your outfit.
You weren't wearing that earlier.
Why did you change?
Oh… I just bought it
while doing some trend research.
That's strange.
It really isn't your style.
It looks like
you picked it out in a hurry.
Did I miss some kind of new trend?
- Or--
- Shut up.
You're so talkative.
I'm just curious about you.
This is my way
of expressing love and affection.
I'll just go meet Cha Min.
What's this awkward silence?
Say something, Hayeong.
You're usually talkative.
It'll seem like he's making you nervous.
Just tease him or something,
like you usually do.
- Is there something wrong?
- What?
You seem quieter than usual.
Do you think
I'm always…
just chatting loudly?
That's not what I meant.
Sorry.
But aren't you getting off?
Right. I am.
Be careful.
Hey, Manjae.
Did you move or something?
You said you'd drop by sometime,
but you never came.
Sorry, I've been pretty busy.
Why don't I drop by after work today?
Sure. Come and see Genius, too.
Okay. I'll see you later.
Hey, it's Yougyum.
What?
He just came out of a jewelry shop.
I bet he bought matching rings.
You're so lucky, Hadam.
Matching rings?
Thank you for the food!
Try this one, try this one.
Yummy. This is amazing.
I'll eat those for you.
The snot and neon aliens.
Thanks.
Don't you guys think that
Yangdong Village was just so gorgeous?
It was really unique, don't you think?
I totally agree.
It kind of felt like it was timeless.
Actually, I think it feels
even better than the photo. Right?
Yeah, it's so beautiful.
But do you know the scene
where Won first goes back to the past?
Uh… Maybe we can make that moment
a little bit deeper. Do you guys agree?
Maybe that's exactly
what we should do, yeah.
Awesome.
- Okay, then… Mmm.
-  Let's do it.
Thank you so much. Let's just eat first.
All together. One, two, three!
The ocean!
Wait!
No, wait! Hey, Raemee!
I can't even decide on a concept.
You there, who's mulling over pens.
Do you want to go see the sea cave
to clear your head?
Nice timing.
I needed
a reason to take a break.
Oh, right.
I never told you that, though.
I told you I don't eat oysters,
but I never told you
eggplants seemed like neon aliens.
I'll eat those for you.
The snot and neon aliens.
It's neon-colored. Yuck!
The taste of a neon alien.
Uh…
No, how else would you know?
I guess I told you.
Sorry, I must've forgotten.
Is it this way?
What are you doing?
Don't you want to ride a plane
when you see a vapor trail?
I actually rode one after seeing one.
I went to meet the person
who gave me that fountain pen I lost.
I used to work at a different company,
and he was the brother of my team leader
who really cared for me.
But soon after we started dating,
he went to Boston to study.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kang Hyeokchan.
I'm glad you're Korean, too.
I hope we get along.
Are you okay?
Are you all right? You've gone pale.
If I'm not okay, will you carry me?
Are you seriously joking right now?
Are you sure you're okay?
I'll be okay.
It's all going to be okay.
- Yougyum!
- Hey, Hadam.
My academy ends at 9:00 p.m.
Should we meet after?
What?
Did we plan to meet today?
Mmm…
No, but I think you have a reason
to meet me later.
I don't.
Why don't you spend some time
with your grandma--
Why are you suddenly
bringing up my grandma?
What?
Oh… Well…
Hey, Changmo!
I have something urgent
to discuss with Changmo, so I have to go.
Hey, Changmo!
What? Changmo isn't even there.
He should hurry up
and give me the ring.
Unfortunately, it seems like
he gave the ring to Han Sora.
She didn't have that a few days ago.
But she was wearing this
in her recent feed.
Don't be ridiculous.
If a girl group trainee with her looks
hits on him,
he could easily fall for her.
That's nonsense.
GUARDIAN
I wanted to give you this.
It finally found its owner
after over 50 years.
What? "La Vie en rose"?
This is my favorite song.
But what did you mean
by this finding its owner?
You were humming that song all the time
when we lived in Chuncheon.
I played it with the harmonica, too.
Right.
I remember.
After I went to college in Seoul
and heard you got accepted
to a medical school the next year,
I went to Chuncheon to give you this.
I waited by the tree
where we always hung out,
but you never showed.
You waited for me?
It snowed like crazy that day.
I almost became a snowman
waiting for you there.
I only heard the news later on.
The news that I ran off with my tuition
and hopped on a flight to Paris?
Yes!
I didn't get to give you this record,
so I just listened to it.
It was so nice.
That's how I got obsessed
and started collecting vinyls.
And this is the result.
It's all your fault, Kim Nabong.
Is that so?
We were dazzling back then.
It's nice seeing you again.
I'd been so busy pushing forward
that I'd forgotten about our old hometown.
I agree.
Instead of just reminiscing,
why don't we visit Chuncheon sometime?
Chuncheon?
Aren't you curious
whether that tree is still there
and how much our neighborhood has changed?
Right.
All right, let's go there sometime.
Okay. Let's do that.
Lab, glass tube, blood…
Whose blood?
Yes, Ms. Kim.
Je Raemee sent his design?
Oh. Sorry, I haven't
sketched anything yet.
If you don't want to suffer again
because of your past,
it would be best
to keep a distance from her.
Did something else happen
besides the explosion?
Hurry up. Why are you so slow?
Sorry.
All right, everybody.
Let's head back and get some rest.
Yeah, let's go.
We'll see you later.
Oh? Where's Ms. Song?
- Huh?
- What? Weren't you with her?
You were hanging out the whole time.
She said she forgot her scarf.
She went to get it.
Goodness. She's a klutz sometimes.
Oh, uh…
I'll go and get her. You go ahead.
Ms. Song!
Song Haran!
Oh?
Why were you--
Why are you so fast?
I…
I thought I'd left this here,
but I found it in my pocket
and headed down.
But then I heard you went to find me.
I kept calling, but you wouldn't answer.
I'm sorry.
I guess I didn't hear it over the rain.
I should've been more careful.
You're always apologizing.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Let's get out of the rain.
Over there.
Sit down.
Oh. Thanks.
Are you hurt?
No, it's nothing.
You shouldn't climb
with your shoelaces so loose.
Your feet must have hurt a lot.
Hey, it's dirty.
Tell me if it keeps hurting.
I'll carry you if I have to.
I can't hear on this side.
So his father sent him to America,
and he suffered there.
To be honest, I'm curious.
About what?
About what I heard from your grandmother.
I want to know what happened in America,
what you meant by being trapped in winter,
and who freed you from it.
I'm getting more comfortable around you,
and I've been telling you
things about myself,
but…
you don't seem to be telling me
much about yourself.
I started studying animation
six years ago.
I worked my butt off and graduated early
then entered my current company
as a character designer.
I became a supervisor by luck
since Won was a Korean character.
I commute by bike
since the office
is a 10-minute ride from home.
You met my teammates, right?
Everyone's really close.
- And--
- Wait.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm sorry,
but I'll use it now.
You said it's okay
to keep some secrets to yourself.
You tell me a secret too next time.
We can keep big secrets to ourselves.
Just a small one.
I'll tell you everything
about the present…
but I'll use that card…
for my past.
Sorry.
Ah…
Oh, no.
I guess I was being really rude.
Right, we agreed
to do a three-month trial,
but I was prying too much.
I was being selfish.
I'm so sorry.
This looks so delicious.
-  Thank you.
- Yeah, no problem.
The staff prepared this since
the costume team is leaving tomorrow.
- Thank you.
- That's so nice.
I'm so touched.
Do we seriously have to leave this behind
and return to Seoul?
I can't leave!
Since this is our last night,
let us all have a drink.
Everyone…  Cheers!
Cheers!
♪ Altogether
Game start ♪
- Numbers game! One!
- Two!
Three!
Drink!
♪ Drink up ♪
It's my first time seeing her drink.
Wait, stop. I have to film this.
Can you drink like a beer model?
No…
Why are you so pretty?
♪ Altogether
Game start ♪
♪ Three, six, nine ♪
Why are you suddenly so serious?
It doesn't suit you.
Ben.
Hiding something
and not telling the truth
is the same as lying, right?
That's so random.
Hide what, though?
You mean like how Aladdin
hid the fact that he was a petty thief?
I guess it's similar.
It's just…
The other person is being honest with me,
but if I keep…
hiding things
and never being honest,
what will happen in the end?
Ah.
Do you remember?
What the genie says
to Aladdin when he says
he wants to keep pretending
to be a prince?
Mmm.
The more you gain
with deception,
the less you can truly gain.
That's right.
It may seem like
you're gaining something now,
but you'll probably end up
paying the price for it.
Paying the price…
What are you doing here alone?
I'm trying to sober up
so I can drink more.
It's been a while since I drank.
You're a heavy drinker.
How's your foot?
You hurt yourself
because of Grandma's scarf.
I'm okay.
Look, aren't they pretty?
Maybe it's because I lost
the pen I used for seven years,
but I couldn't sketch anything
during the two days here.
Maybe it's because
I couldn't stop thinking about it.
I've been so distracted lately.
Until now, I thought that pen was special
because of the person who gifted it to me.
But I'm not so sure now.
Maybe I just feel strange
because I lost something
my hand had gotten used to
after all those years.
The person who gave me that pen died.
I guess that's why
I was so attached to it.
Not long ago,
I would have done anything I could
to avoid coming here.
But this time,
I had quite a lot of fun.
Like I was on a spring picnic.
I guess we have grown quite close,
seeing how I'm telling you
things I'm not okay with.
You know we're not real friends
if we're always pretending to be okay.
Thank you for asking to be friends
and for knocking on my door.
You made me stop hiding,
and you made me
able to tell you sad things, too.
Stop thanking me. I didn't do anything.
Thank you.
I just feel like
pouring my heart out today.
I really am grateful.
Can I borrow that for a moment?
- This?
- Yes.
Odd or even?
That's so random.
Is there a prize if I guess right?
If you guess right,
I'll tell you everything.
I feel like
telling you everything today, too.
- Tell me what?
- I think I should stop
hiding things about myself.
Oh…
If it's because of what I said,
you don't have to--
Odd or even?
Odd.
Who keeps messaging?
It's me.
I'm uploading our photos
to our group chat.
Oh…
-  Mmm.
- Hi, Hayeong. Did you see…
What?
I'm not sure…
if I have the right to tell you
about myself.
To be honest…
I'm scared.
You asked me what happened in America.
I…
was actually…
in Boston, attending…
Haran's a total lightweight.
She can't drink a single drop.
Don't let her drink anything.
-  Stop!
-  She can't drink at all!
- Wait!
- Ms. Song!
Hey. Sorry, Haran.
That song?
Okay, I'll listen to it.
Can you message her back?
Sorry. Do me a solid.
Anything that a woman
in her twenties can use.
I have to go to the hospital
because of my hand.
Sorry.
-  Thanks, Chan.
- Who's that? Your friend?
No, just my roommate.
Sorry, Ran. My professor's calling.
I'll call you back later.
Sujin. You're here?
I'll head out now.
I'll be away for a few weeks.
I'm traveling around the East Coast
during vacation.
If our professor asks for me,
say I'm taking a break because of my hand.
Getting close to someone
is really difficult…
No, it's scary for me.
It's all thanks to this pen.
It's really valuable to me,
so I have to find it.
Chan, I saw a vapor trail earlier.
But that made me want
to get on a plane to go see you.
Whether you're a guy or not,
I don't want to get close.
It's morning?
Hey. You spoke as if you were
a heavy drinker,
but you passed out right away.
I don't usually pass out
after drinking like that,
but the alcohol tasted really good.
Maybe it was because the weather
was so nice.
Hey, Sujin.
It's okay to be a lightweight.
Why are you looking at me with pity?
No, I'm not looking at you that way.
You are. You just looked at me
like I was a lost puppy.
Hmm.
It's pitiful that
you're waiting for your old owner.
I should be good to you
so you won't remember them.
Is that how I looked at you?
No need to say it like that…
Let's go. Oh.
- Bring your jacket.
- Where are we going?
A hangover cure walk?
If walking cured hangovers,
hangover soup places would close down.
But when exactly did I pass out?
Don't you remember?
This.
Right. Odd or even.
I should have said odd.
Why did I guess even?
- You didn't…
- Let's just say I did.
There's no need to know everything.
Still…
You used your card
so you wouldn't have to tell me.
It must have been something bad.
I don't want to force you
to talk about it.
There's no need to dig into your scars
to learn more about you.
And even if I don't know about it,
we're already quite close, right?
Oh, right.
Here.
Honey water.
Hangover medicine, hangover drink,
roasted eggs, and…
They must have been really kind to you.
Who?
The person who showed you
a way to keep going.
The one who kept reaching out.
I just wondered
if you're so sweet to other people
because you learned it from them.
How should I say it…
I'm no match.
This is nothing
compared to what I received.
I received something so incredible
that I could never repay her.
Was it your girlfriend?
No, of course not. I wouldn't dare.
It wasn't like that. Mmm…
She was just…
someone who broadened my world.
Broadened your world?
Yes.
She let me experience things
that I couldn't see or feel before.
My world used to be
black and white, but she…
filled it with vibrant colors.
Right. High five!
I have a habit of doing high fives
when I'm grateful.
You're grateful? All of a sudden?
I found the answer.
My choice was filled with question marks,
but you just changed them
to exclamation marks.
Your choice?
I chose never to do anything
that might get in the way
of her happiness.
Thanks to you, I just realized
that not digging up old wounds
is also a way…
of protecting their happiness.
That's why I'm asking
for a high five.
Well, I have no idea
what you're talking about,
but since you say I helped…
Two green onions…
Three green onions…
Isn't that for your hangover?
Why are you making art
instead of eating it?
I may be friendly with everyone,
but not green onions…
What? Hang on.
Mmm.
He picked out the green onions for me.
How did he know I don't eat green onions?
Green onions… What does that mean?
Did he flirt with green onions?
I'm heading out now.
Right, the tonics.
I should take a tonic
that Mr. Yeon gave me.
- Huh?
-  Oh.
I should take the vitamins
that Mr. Yeon got me.
- What?
- He seemed a bit reserved,
but he takes care of our whole family.
He's so thoughtful.
- I'll get going now.
- See you.
Okay.
Grandma.
Did Mr. Yeon always
take care of everyone like this?
What's the point of having you three?
Mr. Yeon's the only one
who takes care of me.
Geez.
I was overreacting for no reason.
Gosh, that's hot.
- Great work.
- Great work, everyone.
- Thank you.
-  Great work.
Thank you for everything.
I'll see you in Seoul.
Okay. I'll see you in 10 days.
Oh. That's a day for pizza.
How about pizza that day?
- Is it a full moon?
- Mmm.
Sure, pizza sounds good.
And here.
For the hangover stuff you gave me.
HANG IN THERE!
I also have…
this.
Hmm?
Homework.
A film camera?
What kind of homework?
Well…
Ms. Song, hurry.
Come on.
Hurry!
It would be a huge waste not to see that.
Wow, it's beautiful.
It's called an iridescent cloud.
An iridescent cloud?
We also call them
mother-of-pearl clouds.
Because of the diffraction of sunlight,
the cloud particles…
Forget it.
It's a good omen.
They say you have good luck
if you see an iridescent cloud.
That's childish.
Do people say it's lucky?
Wait, it's blurry.
You should look for iridescent clouds
in the sky, too,
instead of just vapor trails.
Vapor trails are just traces
of something that already passed by.
But iridescent clouds
make you excited for the future.
The past…
may not be as beautiful as you remember.
They get blurred,
overwritten, and distorted.
Or they may have been romanticized
because some things…
were hidden.
Why are you suddenly saying that?
I was just…
worried that you'd miss
an iridescent cloud
while staring at a vapor trail.
I have a habit of feeling upset
if I miss something exciting
while thinking about the past.
All right, everybody. Come here!
- Ending a trip…
- With a group photo…
...is a must!
Let's go.
All right. Here goes.
Hurry.
Okay, everyone. What's one plus one?
-  Two!
But what sort of homework is this?
Take one photo each day
and show them to me
when I return to Seoul.
Isn't it crazy, though?
How did they know I'm leaving in 10 days
and sell a 10-shot camera?
What should I take photos of?
Something fun, delicious, or pretty.
Just anything
that made you feel good that day.
Hang in there!
- I'd like some coffee.
- It's on me, so help yourselves!
-  This is so good!
- I got us some coffee.
What's with the coffee?
I heard Je Raemee was bringing
Gyeongju bread today.
I thought it would go well with coffee.
Can I have one?
Wasn't Gyeongju amazing?
There were so many things to see and eat,
and the beach was so beautiful…
What is it?
We've never seen you talk for so long
about something other than work.
It's the first time since I joined.
Let's start working, then.
She's suddenly
acting so friendly.
Well, she's not tinting her windows
or brooding like before.
I guess she's a tiny bit… better
than before.
Hello.
Wow. You and sweet and sour candy?
That really doesn't suit you.
Ah. I guess you're giving it to someone.
Pardon?
Would you like one?
Sure.
I'll try one, then.
Thank you.
Hello.
I'm Yeon Taeseok
from Seoul Commercial High School.
Mr. Yeon Taeseok.
Even your name sounds proper.
But you said hello to the wrong person.
Oh… Sorry.
No need to apologize.
Wow. You're sweating a lot.
Ah.
Would you like one?
The sour taste will snap you awake,
and the sweet taste will help you relax.
Eat that to relax your nerves.
Thank you.
And…
There's a piece of tissue here.
Then good luck.
- You can do it.
- Right.
I tried to get some pocket money
from Grandma but got a noogie.
Mr. Yeon Taeseok,
Ms. Kim will see you now.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'll be right back.
Hadam!
Are you going to your math academy?
What is it?
You look worried about something.
Tell your boyfriend everything.
Yougyum.
Did you go to a jewelry shop
a few days ago…
Hey, Yougyum!
Enough with the PDA and get back here.
We have to practice.
Go on. We'll talk later.
I'll call you later.
If anything is bothering you, tell me.
I'll take care of everything…
I mean, everything besides studying.
All right.
Hang in there!
Park Yeseul…
Why did she have to bring up
Han Sora?
CHA YOUGYUM
SORA
Yes, Ms. Kim.
The revised sketch?
No. I'll hand it in by today.
Okay.
I really need an idea. Please…
I'm sending you a photo
since you said yours was blurry.
Ms. Song, the material check…
What happened to your hair?
Whoa. What's that? The colors are amazing.
I saw it for the first time in Gyeongju.
It's called an iridescent cloud.
It's a cloud?
Wow. It looks like a rainbow.
They call it a rainbow cloud, too.
It's also called a mother-of-pearl cloud…
because of the color…
- Oh. Can you get my rolling cart?
- What?
Right.
Here's the revised outfit design.
Sorry, I'm late.
It wasn't just a simple revision.
The color was important,
so I made a colored illustration.
That's a color palette
I haven't seen before.
I applied mother-of-pearl colors
on the basic silhouette.
Mother-of-pearl…
- As in shiny seashells?
- Yes.
I thought it could be a great material
to highlight a Korean aesthetic.
For now, I just expressed
the general vibe with gloss pens,
but if we can capture
the texture of mother-of-pearl
so it has a mysterious glow
whenever she moves,
I think that would add some fun
to the animation as well.
Well…
Not bad.
Mother-of-pearl is normally used
for decorations.
How did you come up with the idea
of using its colors?
Oh…
This is an iridescent cloud
I saw in Gyeongju.
This photo became a great inspiration.
I heard it's also called
a mother-of-pearl cloud
because of its colors.
Mmm.
It will go well with Raemee's idea
of emphasizing the collar and front panel.
So that trip wasn't for nothing.
You can go.
Okay.
She won't need me anymore.
Hmm?
My sketch finally got accepted.
Huh? Wait.
Was this inspired
by that iridescent cloud?
That's right. You said it's also
called a mother-of-pearl cloud.
It's all thanks to you.
I'll treat you to 10 pizzas.
Let's see…
Mmm…
They say you have good luck
if you see an iridescent cloud.
He was right.
It worked out
thanks to him.
The cloud you saw in Gyeongju?
Why do I feel like
I know who you saw it with?
What?
The Haran before wasn't my style,
so she was about 0.5 points,
but the new Song Haran
after our Gyeongju trip… Tsk.
Right, I'll give you three points.
Fine. I'll give you 3.5.
- Excuse me?
- Don't get too excited.
My points…
are out of 10.
All right.
Didn't I tell you to stop coming?
It's grated yam.
I did some research,
and they said it helps.
I'm already taking good care of myself.
Just focus on baseball.
I'm practicing really hard too, you know.
But what about
that examination you mentioned last time?
It's next week.
Are you getting along well with Hadam?
Why aren't you talking
about marriage anymore?
I decided to support her quietly
until the CSAT so I wouldn't distract her.
Have you been wearing
that necklace I gave you?
If it's not the right length, I can…
GUARDIAN
You're just a student.
Where did you get the money?
I'm a future Major Leaguer, you know.
Gosh. I should get
an autograph in advance.
Huh? Did you hit your leg somewhere?
It's fine. I just fell.
My legs suddenly wouldn't listen.
You have to make sure
Hadam doesn't find out until the CSAT.
Okay. I'll take good care of her.
- Hello?
- Are you free next next Friday at 7 p.m.?
Next next Friday?
- Well, yes…
- Okay.
Then let's have dinner at Samcheong-dong.
Samcheong-dong?
It's a one-table restaurant
I booked before coming to Korea.
Maybe it's thanks to that cloud.
There was a long waitlist,
but I just got a call
that someone canceled for that day.
- Mmm.
-  I'll send you the link.
I haven't seen this place before.
I confirmed the reservation.
Ah. Mark that on your schedule.
You'd better not forget or show up late.
I got distracted.
Good morning. Did you sleep well?
Our team did a sunrise shoot,
so everyone's knocked out now.
Hey, a flower bloomed.
But why aren't you sleeping?
Aren't you tired?
I have to enjoy every moment.
Ah. There's a beautiful half-moon.
Can you see it clearly in Seoul?
Yes, I can.
So today's dinner is omurice.
Donggu?
- Hello.
- Hi.
What did you draw that character
on Donggu's uniform with?
A fabric marker?
That's right.
Right. Mr. Park's checkup is on Wednesday.
Can you check up on him?
Mr. Park.
Hey, you're here.
Genius.
You didn't forget your checkup, right?
There's someone
calling me every day to remind me,
so I remember it
more clearly than my own birthday.
But have you started a new hobby?
You've been taking a lot of photos.
Ah. Someone gave me homework,
telling me to take photos
of what makes me happy.
Mmm. So what did you take photos of?
Nothing special.
Just people around me,
the moon, delicious food,
that flower… Things like that.
Oh.
I'm so curious how they'll look.
They say happiness is always there,
but you just miss it,
so it belongs to the person
who discovers it.
I guess it's true.
I went on a walk with Genius earlier,
and the sky was so beautiful.
But no one even looked up.
They were all walking around,
staring at their phones.
I have a feeling
that the person who gave you that camera…
...is someone who knows
how to look up at the sky
on days like this.
I guess that's why
they gave you that homework.
So you can discover nice things every day,
no matter how trivial they are.
They probably wanted you
to smile at least once while doing so.
Isn't that right?
Mr. Park, I think I get it now.
What?
I was surprised at how different I was
these days, but I didn't know why.
I guess that's because
it's been such a long time since I saw it.
Saw what?
Myself.
My past self.
I used to be able to find happiness
in the smallest things.
It's been a while since I saw
that side of me.
I was able to see it again
thanks to someone.
I guess that's why I was surprised.
Mmm.
Oh, my.
The moon is beautiful.
I hope I can see a full moon soon.
Where can I find a photo studio?
Remember, we're stopping
at the rest area halfway, okay?
- Okay.
- See you later, bro!
- Okay. See you guys.
- Drive safely. See you.
Sorry, Ben.
Take a different car.
I'm going straight to Seoul.
But it's at least four hours.
- Bye.
- Hey, don't strain yourself.
I'll drive.
Huh? I said I'll drive.
It's fine. I'll see you in Seoul.
- Hey!
- I'm fine, Ben.
Seonu Chan! Drive slowly, okay?
He really
shouldn't be driving.
I'll arrive around 6:30 p.m.
Find a nice pizza place for us.
See you later.
ETA
1 HOUR
One hour.
Oh? Has he arrived early?
- Yes, Ms. Kim.
-  Come to my office.
18:04
MS. KIM
Right now?
Me?
Yes, you. Who else?
Why would you make me handle the business?
I'm retiring later than planned,
and you held on longer than I thought.
It's time you took over.
I didn't get to go at 60 as I planned,
but I'm going to retire soon
and go to France.
So start preparing.
No, I can't do this.
I'm already overwhelmed with doing design,
and I'm not qualified…
You'll develop your abilities.
And that was an order, not an offer.
I'm not making excuses, I--
You don't have a choice.
If you really can't do it, then quit.
I raise people for their abilities,
not with sentiment.
I'll give you…
a week for that report.
This is so sudden…
MISSED CALL
ANIMATOR SEONU CHAN
The number you have dialed
is unavailable. Please leave--
Why is it off?
Call me when you get my message.
I couldn't react properly…
Was he driving here?
- Mr. Park, did you hear from Mr. Seonu?
- Oh?
I guess you haven't heard yet.
I got a call.
What call?
He suddenly had to return to America.
He had to head straight to the airport,
so he asked me to send
his passport through express delivery.
I don't know what's going on, either.
He said he'd call me again soon,
but he hasn't called.
What…
- I…
-  He would have left already.
He said he'd take
the earliest flight to the US.
He must be gone already.
MISSED CALL
ANIMATOR SEONU CHAN
YOUR PHOTOS ARE READY FOR PICKUP
HOBAK PHOTO STUDIO
What? He said there were 10 shots.
He was lying.
Keep enjoying your life
even when… I'm not here later.
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
They are all gone?
What kind of trial ends like this?
-  Ms. Kim!
-  Why did you go to the hospital?
Are you sick?
I just want to walk for a bit.
Chan was such a nice guy.
When we first met,
he said I looked like
someone trapped in winter.
You're not worried about Haran?
Do you regret it?
Do you regret getting close to Seonu Chan?
Yes, I do.
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Translated by Juyoung Park