[♪ Theme song]
[♪ dark music]
[A clanging sound rings out]
[Haran] What’s wrong?
[A clanging sound rings out] [Haran] Are you okay?
yes
Oh, because of the light
yes, it's okay
[Haran] It’s not, but it doesn’t look okay?
I won't do anything bad, ever
Especially during the 3-month trial period.
[♪ Calm music]
[Chan] It was the first time I heard it.
Small metals collide
It sounds like ice mixing
Ah, the door [creaking sound]
It sounded like it was coming from outside the lab door.
[Grunting sound]
But I don't know what you're talking about
Why did that explosion come to mind?
From what I've heard so far
It seems likely that this is the second trigger.
Second trigger?
[Haran] Nice to meet you.
My name is Chief Designer Song Haran.
[Doctor] I think meeting him again recently was the trigger.
I touched something again
I couldn't think of it
I think I remembered a piece of my past.
Wait a minute, no, no, that…
Well, that doesn't make sense.
I remembered it all from 7 years ago
When I first saw him at Jamsu Bridge
Everything that happened in Boston
What is the basis for your confidence that it is everything?
[Chan] That’s what I experienced briefly due to the shock of the accident.
It was because of temporary aftereffects.
[Doctor] Are you saying that all your memories came back to you from that time?
Yes, after that, there are sounds and scenes that I don't know.
It never occurred to me, not even once
[Doctor] What if
like this
A blank space in my memory that I wasn't even aware of.
What if it still exists?
A blank space in your memory?
[Doctor] Seon Woo-chan seems like a completely different person than he was back then.
Enough to imagine how hard he must have tried to change over the past seven years.
The stronger the will to let go of the past,
Defense mechanisms to protect yourself are also activated.
No more suffering from the past
There is a high possibility that the unconscious has covered up uncomfortable memories.
Inside Seon Woo-chan
There's an inch that hasn't been opened yet.
[Chan] That sound
If it is part of a closed inch
Is this a signal from the past?
Signs that it is connected to the explosion 7 years ago
[Doctor] I don’t know anything right now, but
One thing is clear
That he is the key that opens that closed inch
You're not very happy?
I mustered up the courage to come here to commemorate the start of using the trial version.
Oh, it's cold!
If I'm happy to see you
I have a habit of doing a welcome water show.
[Manjae] No, who is this?
uh? Genius, how are you?
[wow]
- [Haran] How have you been? - Uh, how long has it been since this?
No, but how did you get here so early?
Grandpa, I want to drink coffee quickly.
I got sick after not drinking for a few days.
[Manjae] Oh, really?
Then I have to get it down quickly.
Come on, come in
- Come in - [Haran] Genius, let's go, let's go
[Doctor] Now that I don't have to suffer again because of my past,
It would be better not to have him around.
In order to protect the current Mr. Seon Woo-chan,
Because a lock is safer than a key.
lock…
[♪ Calm music]
[Clicking Moonsori]
- Uh, the roommate is also seated - [Chan] Ah, yes.
[Manjae] Now, let’s go to VVIP coffee.
[Chan] Yes
uh?
[Manjae] Oh, I guess that guy fortunately got over his troubles.
Ah, I guess it was a good idea to take it out, right?
- That's right - [Manjae] Yes
[Manjae’s laughter]
I think it was a good idea to take it out.
[Chan] Even if I break again, I will be by his side
Even now, when I live like myself, that person gave it to me.
If it wasn't for him, I would have died a long time ago.
[Haran] Why do you look at me like that?
It's my heart?
Come on, Cheers.
[Chan] Whatever is hidden in that blank space
I'll handle it
If only that person becomes happy
I don't care, whatever happens
So that my presence doesn’t hurt that person.
Be careful
I'll do everything I can and leave.
Have you seen the data?
[Ben] Yes
Still, the background team field trip material was a bit disappointing.
When did you find it and organize it?
Because there is a lot of modernized data
I found it again in a traditional hanok
The Eiffel Tower is French
Was Hanok something Koreans should find?
[Ben's laughter]
[English] Then, share the data with the background team.
We'll schedule a departure for Gyeongju on Tuesday morning.
[Korean] Oh, I'm joining a day late
Teacher Nana gave me a draft of the Dancheong design on Tuesday.
[Ben] Um, okay
But if you come separately, what should you take?
rent
Are you okay?
[Chan] It’s very good
[Ben] Hey, you really shouldn’t use that.
Hey, okay
Hey, really
[Chan] Please calculate here
[Chan] Designer Song!
[♪ Lively music]
Why are you coming like that?
You're off work, right?
Do you have any plans?
nice
Okay then, let's get on.
yes? Oh, suddenly somewhere...
[Chan] Ah, car, car, car, car
[Nana] Because I have a special lecture tomorrow
Meet with the buyer and organize the final contract.
[Taeseok] Yes
[Chan] Hurry up and get on, now.
[♪ Lively music]
Head, head, head [car horn]
Uh, sorry.
Oh, yeah
Did you ever say, ‘Oh, yeah’?
Those two
Please keep an eye on me
effort
It wasn't a sister fraud group.
Oh, let’s eat some chicken, so here we go…
Essential missions you must do in Korea
Han River, mat, chicken 3-piece set
I am a traveler from a foreign country.
right! and!
The Han River is really nice
[♪Soft music]
Oh, I have something for you, sit down.
0.3, 0.4, 5, 6
And meteor, mercury
Nib type, ballpoint pen type
Oh, wait a minute.
Are you really going to do n-jobs?
Ah, what kind of pen…
I have a habit of buying new pens for people who have lost them.
In human terms, I should have a pen like this.
Ah, but this isn't a full-fledged trial version yet.
What can I say
Light preview?
What do you preview?
I won't be in Seoul since Wednesday.
About two weeks?
I have to go on a field trip
I decided to become friends
If I don't do something, I'm afraid I'll end up in the same place.
I don't want to do that.
In that sense
Can you take care of him too?
No, why are you doing this to me?
Set your priorities
Let’s do it together when we come to Seoul.
[text notification sound]
uh? They said chicken is here
I'll get it right away
Put it away here.
Ah, this way.
I need to eat chicken here, so put it away quickly!
‘That person’?
[Click] [Woman] Wow, the night view is so pretty
[Man] Right?
Oh, would you like to go to Jamsu Bridge over there for Christmas?
They say it’s a famous fireworks spot there.
- [Woman] I love it - Jamsu Bridge?
[Couple’s laughter]
- [Man] Ta-ta - [Woman] Ta-ta
[♪ Dreamy music]
[Article] Oh my, it’s jammed.
Hey, I heard there are fireworks starting at 7 o’clock.
It's not moving.
[sigh]
How long will it take? I have an important meeting.
[Article] If you are in a hurry, it would be faster to cross on foot.
[Haran] Yes, Photo Yoon.
Eve is very blocked.
Oh, is that so?
Yes, then please come slowly.
yes
[Call end sound]
[♪ Bach Goldberg Variations - Aria]
[People cheering]
[Haran] Hey, Kang Hyuk-chan
Why can’t I contact you?
[Hyukchan] Oh, I’m sorry I didn’t receive it because I fell asleep.
Do you have insomnia?
These days, my sleep pattern is messed up and my sleeping times are all mixed up.
[Haran] They say this song is effective for insomnia
Listen to it when you can't sleep, okay?
[Chan] Come on, withdraw!
- Suddenly? - [Chan] Yes
[Man 1] Hey, should we order pride?
[Man 2] Isn’t the seasoning better?
[Chan] Wait a minute
[Man 1] Chicken is fried
[Chan] Okay, ta-da!
- [Man 3] What is this? - You have won a free chicken
[Man 4] Can we eat it?
[Chan] Oh, sure, sure
It's still warm, so enjoy it.
[Men] Thank you
[Chan] Quick, this is something precious, so take care of it.
Ah, the 3-piece set was too obvious, wasn't it?
Let's go creative with charcoal grilling.
- Ben told me about it... - [Haran] Ah, boy…
I understand it’s a charcoal grill and all that.
Why is this…
[Chan] Ah!
We're going to take this and cross the Jamsu Bridge over there.
That's the shortest distance
Oh, hey, I'm sorry.
I wish I could just go today
no way
Oh, no way
Can’t you ride a bike?
Oh, no, that's not it... [♪ Pleasant music]
Hey, it's okay.
What's the shame of not being able to ride a bike?
- I'll just return it - [Haran] Oh, no, that...
I know how to ride, but…
Yeah, let's ride, yeah
[Chan] Okay
ruler
But I'm bored just leaving, so would you like to make a bet?
Will the person who arrives late buy food or call?
No, what a bet.
- just… - [Chan] Start!
[♪ Soft music] Oh, what a bully…
[Chan] Huh?
uh? Ah, everything…
Oh, wait
Ah, all, all, legs, legs
Wait, wait, wait, wait ah, ah, ah, ah
why? What's wrong with your legs?
[Chan] You have long legs
yes?
Oh boy, really
wow
Hey!
[Haran] Wow
Hey
Wow, it's really pretty
Right?
Wow, the Han River is nice.
Did you copy me by any chance?
But that's not how you do it
right! and!
The Han River is really nice
What's different? It's the same?
It's not
I won, buy me food.
[Chan] It hasn’t arrived yet?
[Hayoung] Good morning
[Hayoung’s laughter]
- Uh, Dam, hi - [Hadam] Good morning
Everyone knows Yugyeom is coming today, right?
7 o'clock later, don't be late even one second
of course
I waited desperately for today
Just sit in the first row and watch these scrawny kids
I will take a close look at every detail...
what?
Sister, where are you going?
It was a bit long
[Hayoung] Sister
You're not saying that our maknaeng is really going to get married, are you?
well
See you later
[Student 1] Awesome, Sora Han
[Student 2] Sora Han, did you come to school today?
[Student 3] Wow, awesome
[Yugyeom] What? Who are you?
Why do you need to know my number?
Why would you do this?
That's because I'm interested in you, Cha Yu-gyeom.
[Students’ elasticity]
I'm not interested in you at all
And I have a girlfriend
[Hadam] Yugyeom
uh? Put it in
[Yugyeom’s laughter]
what's the matter?
It's nothing
[Sora] Oh, is this your girlfriend?
See you next time
who? Do you know him?
at all
I saw this kid for the first time today and I will never see him again.
Hey, hey, hey, that's him
- Wive girl group trainee Han So-ra - [Yugyeom] Hadam!
[♪ Humorous music] Fighting today too
- See you later - [Hadam] Yes
[Player 1] I guess you filmed it, really.
[Yugyeom] Are you really not quiet?
[Player 2] Why!
- [Player 3] It's really pretty, but - [Player 1] I mean,
[Yugyeom] Aren’t you really quiet?
[Player 1] Hey, you’ve got a dot on it. Meet it. It’s pretty.
[Yugyeom] Be quiet, be quiet, be quiet
[Player 2] Good-looking things are really…
Sora Han?
[Haran] Huh? oh
[telephone rings]
Yes, Nana Atelier Design Team 1…
[Nana] Why isn’t everyone answering their phones?
[Haran] Teacher, why are you on this phone…
It’s an emergency, listen carefully now [♪ Meaningful music]
It's a special lecture on women's clothing, but I only took materials on men's clothing.
It's my mistake, it's my responsibility
- Taxi, taxi, taxi! - [Nana] Right now, settling things comes first.
30 minutes to the special lecture, move right away
[Haran] Ha… Oh, what should I do?
[car horn]
Uh, I'm a friend from the neighborhood.
Do you have about 20 minutes?
Oh, sure, 2 hours.
Just rent a car and take a walk around the neighborhood...
[Haran] Ah, he lived, ah, that…
Then over here...
I have an urgent meeting, but I can't find a taxi.
I'll be there in 15 minutes, so let me do you a favor.
[Chan] Uh, no, I, that…
No, but...
[car horn]
yes
[Haran] Hey, do you know that we’re going to 20 right now?
It's okay up to 60 here.
I'm sorry, but can you go a little faster?
I have less than 20 minutes left
yes
[♪ heavy music] [loud car horn]
[Haran] Oh, a motorcycle!
[shaking breathing]
[Driver] Mr.
Get down, get down [loud car horn]
Look down, man, look down
I almost got into an accident because of you.
What if you suddenly intervene like that, Mr.
[Chan] Oh, sorry
If there is any damage, I will take full responsibility.
ah…
[Driver] Yes, yes, I will pick you up right now.
[Chan] I’m really sorry
Designer, look at me.
I'm sorry for making this happen.
But everything got better
The situation has been resolved and nothing has happened.
Are you hurt anywhere?
It's okay, really?
I…
I, I asked for a ride for no reason.
[Chan] Nothing happened, no one got hurt, everything is okay.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Haran] Ugh
[Chan] I’m sorry, but I don’t think I can take you there now.
Oh, there's a taxi over there.
This goes first now, so hurry up
I'll make everything okay here
Don't worry
[♪ Calm music]
[Haran] Getting close to someone is difficult for me...
It’s such a scary thing [Chan sighs]
If no one becomes special
At least nothing will happen
[sigh]
[Haran, Chan] Just now…
[Chan] I’m really sorry about what happened earlier.
I'm sorry
I wasn't riding that recklessly.
Because of your ears?
I think so
[loud car horn]
[tire rubbing sound]
[Chan] A few years ago
Ben got hurt a little because of me.
A horn sounded from the left.
Because I defended myself wrongly
Just like before
From that day
I'll never let anyone ride in the car I'm driving
I did it
Because today is the first time
I guess I was very nervous.
sorry
something happens
I'm a scared person
For making me go through something like that
Well, that ridiculous trial version was really effective.
It was the same at the Han River yesterday.
Same thing in the car earlier.
I found it quite effective
[♪Soft music]
personally
Jamsu Bridge is not a very good memory.
I can smile even in a place where I thought I would only have sad memories for the rest of my life.
Maybe even sad memories can be overwritten little by little.
I first found out about it yesterday
I was really scared in the car earlier.
Thanks to you, I got better quickly
If it were me a few days ago, I would definitely have tried to run away again.
But not anymore
At least until the trial ends
I will never go into a cave again.
So don't blame yourself
Okay?
Ah, thank goodness
I'm honest
I was a little scared.
I barely got up the courage
I'm afraid I'll take a step back again
I said let's have fun
from the beginning
I'm afraid I messed up
[Haran] Teach me a lot again
I will really try hard to learn
[Haran] I’ll go, see you later.
[Chan] Yes, let’s go
[Haran] Ah
But I don't like that
Just have good things and have fun
That's fake friendship.
If it's not okay, you can say it's not okay.
Aren’t we really close friends?
So let's talk about this in advance.
So that we don’t have to feel sorry for each other like we did today
I will
But don't do that anymore. If you really want to become friends.
Why don't you do that?
You don’t have to worry too much about not being able to hear on one side.
Me? Me?
[♪ Bright music]
Not at all, not at all?
[Chan] Wow, it’s all clear.
No, I know this
It's always on my right side
Because usually there is no problem
It really doesn't matter
okay?
no…
It's been a long time since I got close to someone.
What should I do, where should I start, and how should I do it?
Sometimes I don’t feel it well, and…
Even if it looks adult
I don’t eat eggplant like a child.
Grandpa Manjae likes coffee.
The bicycle
very good ride
Even if you pretend to be indifferent, it’s still warm
yes?
Is this how we become friends?
Slowly, without effort
As I learn about things I didn't know, one by one
Actually, I don’t even eat oysters.
It feels so runny
yes? Runny nose, runny nose?
I'm just talking about something you didn't know.
Ah, isn't this how you do it?
[Chan] That’s right, that’s how you do it
Give me your hand and I'll stamp it for you.
Well done.
Since I told you one, let me tell you a secret next time, to be fair.
Ah, well, should we each keep the strong ones and keep the weak ones?
I'll go
[Chan] Let’s go
secret…
[Hadam] Yes, head okay
The clothes are pretty
Well, your face is prettier
1,000 points out of 100
[Yugyeom] Ah… I'm so nervous
I don’t think I was this nervous even during the Comets signing interview.
If you're trembling, it's okay to tremble
Just be yourself
oh my god
When you say that, I suddenly don't feel nervous at all.
Then please hold my hand
[Crying]
Actually, I feel like I'm going to die from shaking.
[Yugyeom] Just trust me
let's do well, let's
[Hadam] Yes
[Nana] You’re finally here
Let’s take a look at what kind of guy he is.
[Yugyeom] Hello, this is Cha Yugyeom.
[♪ Meaningful music]
[Walk signal] [Yugyeom] Uh, green light
[car horn]
[Loud car horn] Uh, uh, uhh!
[loud car horn]
[Hadam] But why were you late earlier?
Who did you help?
[Yugyeom] Some kind of grandmother
The light was red, but you were standing in the middle of the crosswalk.
dangerously
Grandma, are you okay?
Where are you going?
[Yugyeom] I thought you had dementia.
[Yugyeom] Uh…
Hey, nice to meet you
Hadam doesn’t know.
Make it like you saw me for the first time today
[Hadam] Isn’t our Yugyeom pretty?
[Hadam’s laughter]
what?
Cha Yugyeom, are you crying?
uh? [♪ Lively music]
Oh, that…
Hal, I’m so happy to see grandma.
I'm in tears
[Call connection tone] [Hadam sighs]
Oh, why don't you take both?
[Call end sound]
Not all sisters accept it.
Let’s just go first…
Hey, why are you sweating like that?
Is it hot?
[Yugyeom] Ah…
I'm not feeling well
I'll come back when you guys are here.
- what? - [Nana] Do you want to?
See you next time
See you at school
[Hadam] Yugyeom!
[Sound of door slamming]
Grandma, what's wrong?
Yugyeom didn't look at me properly and didn't say a word.
Because I make him uncomfortable, he just goes.
Uh, Hadam.
Well, I'm also in a bit of a bad mood today...
[Hadam] The sisters don’t come
How could you do this to a child who is so important to me?
why? Do you think I'm joking about getting married? Is it funny?
- Ha, Hadam - [Hadam] Everyone is doing too much, really!
- Yugyeom! - [Nana] Ha, Hadam!
[Sigh] [Sound of door slamming]
How could that student...
Oh, Hayoung!
- [Hayoung] Sister, why are you here now? - [Haran] No, I’m a little…
-There's chalk on your face... - [Hadam] Yugyeom!
[Hayoung] Sister, I…
[Haran] Hadam!
Yugyeom went?
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm a little distracted.
I don't even know how much time has passed
[Hayoung] I’m truly sorry too.
No, I'm having a model fitting tomorrow, and the sample shoulder line...
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
Everyone had their own circumstances.
are you okay
Wow, how big your heart is.
The Gobi Desert is separate
I thought it wasn’t there [♪ Lively music]
Are you not okay?
Are you angry?
Yeah, a lot
I'm holding on with reason
So don't tell me
It seems like I'm ahead of you, so are you jealous?
[Hadam's exasperated breathing]
I'm really annoyed
[Hayoung] What should I do…
[Clicking Moonsori]
[Hayoung] Grandmother
Why did Yugyeom go so quickly?
Yeah, I guess I'm not in a good mood.
I need to wash up, everyone go up.
[Hayoung] What is it?
Doesn’t grandma’s condition actually look worse?
Was the special lecture work very difficult?
[♪ Heavy music]
[loud car horn]
Grandma, are you okay?
Where are you going?
I don't know
I can't think of anything
[Yugyeom] It’s okay
When the signal changes, cross with me.
[sigh]
Hadam, I’m sorry, Hadam.
Let's reschedule the date, okay? Yugyeom tells me to come back
[♪ Calm music]
“Hadam”
[Haran’s sigh]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Yes, Mr. Charmin.
Oh, lunch?
Ah, good
I'll go there right away.
yes
Designer Hayoung
The teacher is looking for you
Me?
for a moment
I went there like that last time and he got off work, right?
[♪ Humorous music] Why doesn’t it fit the character?
Are you kidding me?
I misunderstood when I told you to come today.
I think you should go right now.
Really?
Well, okay.
Ah, Mr. Charmin.
I don't think we can have lunch together today.
sorry
Oh, keep singing!
yes
[knock knock sound]
[Nana] Yes
wait for a sec
Come in
[Hayoung] Teacher
You said you were looking for me
[Nana] Did you dream?
I didn't find it
Get out, don't disturb work.
yes?
Oh, Director Yeon, what is it really?
Why do you keep lying?
I recommend going out and talking to yourself.
yes
Take care
[Sound of door slamming]
Did I find him?
It's not
[sigh]
[♪ Meaningful music]
[Hayoung] Sol, your shoulders are 17, right?
- [Sol] Ah! Yes, just a moment - [Hayoung] Yes
what? This unfamiliar feeling
It definitely feels different than usual.
[Sol] What is it, what is it? What's different from usual?
[Rammy] Huh?
Ouch! [♪ Pleasant music]
That one, that one
You didn't do it once today, don't do it.
[Sol] Oh! Is that so?
- [Sol] Wow… - [Seunggyu] Ah!
[Sol] Uh, sorry
[Rammy] Oh, it’s already 4 o’clock
It's already this time
What really happened?
[Haran] Yes? Gyeongju?
Our costume team too?
[Chan] Yes, it’s our director’s idea.
If you have a high level of background understanding
He said it would look much better on clothes.
[Nana] Of course
I can't figure out the temperature in detail just by looking at the script.
Then we too...
ah…
I have a tight schedule
You can go there on your own without interfering with other work.
Rammy is ready for sortie
Living in a pit of fabric dust all the time
I'll take a good breath of air
Going on a picnic?
Only when you're on vacation do you have a snoring breath.
Rammy, I'm going to go and work really hard.
picnic, pooh
Business trip, beep beep beep beep beep
[Rammy’s laughter]
I think it would be enough for the design team to stay for about two nights.
How is your schedule?
Uh, then our costume team will be leaving on Thursday.
yes
Hey, Yang Changmo!
Uh, Hadam
What about Yugyeom?
I jumped out first because I had somewhere to go.
Uh, didn’t you have an appointment with Song Ha-dam?
[Hadam] Huh?
[Athlete] How are you holding on today?
[Yugyeom] Well, I do it every day.
[Hadam] Oh, Yugyeom!
[Yugyeom] Oh
go first
sorry for yesterday
Let's talk after this
[Yugyeom] Hey, I’m sorry
I was rude because I couldn't manage my condition.
But what should I do?
I'll see Changmo later.
Oh, kid, do you want to consult about something?
[Yugyeom’s laughter]
[Hadam] Uh, Yugyeom, what are you doing?
Oh, I heard you met Changmo.
Have you met?
[Yugyeom] Huh? Uh, why?
Is there anything urgent?
[Hadam] Huh? [♪ Meaningful music]
Oh no, I just did it.
Uh, I'll hang up.
[Call end sound]
[Hadam] Huh?
Yu, Yugyeom…
Yugyeom!
[♪ Soaring music]
[Sora] See you next time
I also wanted to meet you sooner [Kwang Moon So-ri]
So is it good? Are you happy to meet you?
Hadam!
Cha Yugyeom, how did you meet Han Sora…
[Haran] Hadam
-Why is my eldest sister here? - [Hayoung] I have one too.
[Hadam] What? You just waited in front of the school?
Even though you don’t know Yugyeom’s face?
[Hayoung] Hey, how do you not know about this famous person who is also in the news?
[Hadam] The sisters threatened you, right?
So you lied about going to see Changmo, right?
I told you not to tell me
I wanted to meet quietly and apologize
[Yugyeom] Oh, what about apples?
I went early because I wasn't feeling well.
[Hayoung] Hey, but who is Han Sora?
You just said something like Han Sora.
well?
I don't really know what you're talking about
Well, eat.
Mmm, delicious
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Yes, put it in
[Hadam] Oh, I heard you’re meeting Changmo.
- uh? - [Hadam] Have you met?
Uh, why?
Is there anything urgent?
[Hadam] Huh?
Oh no, I just did it.
uh
[Call end sound]
Are there guests coming?
who…
[Yugyeom] Are you feeling very unwell?
[Nana] Sometimes my mind goes blank
Sometimes I buy the same book two or three times.
There are still a lot of fine days.
Even when it’s not supposed to be, it comes suddenly
Like the day I first met you
Have you been to the hospital?
I received a suspicious finding at a center that conducted a simple examination.
I made an appointment for a detailed evaluation and will be tested in a few weeks.
But if you live around my age
I know most things by feel.
[♪ Calm music] Probably right
I don't know what to do
You have to tell your family...
no
Now I just have to do what I can
I don't know if I can stay sane for a month or a day.
I have to organize things in there.
You will also receive treatment
I'm sorry that I feel like I'm putting a burden on you when you're young.
Still, I'd like to ask you a favor.
[Hayoung] They say the french fries here are delicious
[Haran] Hadam, you like eating this, right?
[Nana] Hadam’s eldest sister
I've already let go of so many precious people.
I don't want to add myself too
[Hayoung] This sweet potato is delicious too
[Nana] Hadam’s younger sister is the one who laughs so loudly
If I knew that my grandmother had become like this, I wouldn't be able to smile much.
Hadam is a senior in high school.
I don't want you to break down because of me at the most important time.
So let me ask you a favor.
Just for the time being
Just pretend not to notice for a while
Time is shorter than I thought
Hey, how much did you scratch?
what
Did you call me to say there was an accident?
[♪ Meaningful music]
[Taeseok] It’s true that I called.
There was no contact accident.
Oh my, what is that...
Why did I have an unexpected accident?
wait for a sec
Right, you?
- It was just planned - [Tae-seok] Mr. Cha-min?
[Chamin] I’ll shoot the full course
Huh?
uh! fish oil, fish oil
What is that?
Why is it like that?
The hotel parking lot a few days ago
Reverse bread!
Ah, why did it appear again...
You don't need to know what I am
The women whom Cha Min placed on octopus feet
Let's organize it
[Chamin] Ha, what are you saying?
Ah, why does it keep popping up and causing a fight?
[Taeseok] So that no one gets hurt
It would be okay if you were assigned overseas.
If you don't clean up that non-recyclable trash,
Let's meet again
[Car remote control operating sound]
[Charmin] Hey!
If you do this, it's trash.
How, destroy the rest too?
Whether you smash it or not, you just have to clean it up.
I think it would be a good idea to send a DM right now.
[Chamin] Well, I don’t like it, I don’t like it
I'm not going to clean it up.
What can I do if I’m popular?
What to do, what to do, what to do
[♪ Upbeat music] Huh?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
uh! my phone, mr.
uh…
hey!
If you don't organize it
What I won't be able to use next time
It won't be a cell phone.
[Call connection tone] [Charmin] Oh, wait a minute.
- Hey, wait a minute - [Tae-seok] Yes.
I'm contacting you to request on-site car repairs.
Because the phone went in
- [Military worker] What are you doing? - [Chamin] Mr...
[Chan] I’ll be back!
[Car remote control operating sound]
- uh? - [Haran] I will drive.
[Chan] Why, why here…
I have to go to Gyeongju
Uh, I have to go, I
But the costume team is tomorrow…
I'm leaving today
Oh, please put that bag on me.
[Chan] Uh…
[♪Soft music]
yes
[Chan’s elasticity]
[Chan] Hey, I feel really good
The designer took care of all my worries.
[Haran] Are you worried?
Me? Me?
You came because you were worried about driving.
Because I almost got into an accident last time.
My, I...
that's right
No, it won't be my first time driving on the highway in Korea.
thank you
[Haran clears his throat]
But do animations also go on field trips like this?
Oh, sure
You know the Kingdom of Arendelle, right? [♪ Mysterious music]
It was inspired by a lake town called Hallstatt.
Oh, and the ice castle
That's in Quebec
It is based on the motif of an ice hotel made entirely of ice.
Oh, and Won is Korean.
That's why I'm looking for a background in Korea.
I have to decide exactly where and how I grew up.
Because I can completely incorporate it into my work.
[Haran] I always felt like a semi-unemployed person in the neighborhood.
For the first time, I feel like a pro.
[Chan] Half, half unemployed…
Ha, really
I wasn't going to say this out loud
I'll just do it with my mouth.
Hey, I'm doing well.
I'm getting scouting offers from all over the place.
It looks good.
I said that because you seemed so excited when talking about work.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Wait a minute
Uh, Ben
Oh, here it is...
I didn't make it half way.
[Chan] Yeah, they said they didn’t make it to halfway.
Ah, I'm going with designer Song.
That's how it happened
Uh, see you later.
[Call end sound]
Ah, the smell of rain
[♪ Calm music]
Is it a shower?
[Haran] But this doesn’t smell like rain
What organic smell is spreading?
Well, that's the deal.
What was it?
- Petrico - [Haran] Oh! Petrico
But I know that very well.
Last time, at the police station, they said something about hypochlorite, blah, blah, blah.
I thought you went to engineering school, not art school.
[Haran] Huh?
I stopped, why are you doing this?
- uh! - [Chan] Huh? Can't you?
Uh, wasn't this inspected when I rented it?
Uh, I got it checked.
But not much has arrived yet.
[Rumbling thunder]
- [Haran] Huh? Suddenly, wait a minute - [Chan] Uh, uh
[Haran] Oh, are there too many people?
[Chan] First, let’s stop on the shoulder of the road.
[Haran] The shoulder? uh…
Uh, what should I do?
[Chan] Huh? ‘No shoulder’?
What if I don't have it?
Oh, so we can't build a road.
first… [♪ Pleasant music]
Quickly see if the car is coming, now.
[Chan] Just wait for now
- I'll solve it - [Haran] I can't see it too much.
I can't see anything, what should I do?
Wait a minute, wait a minute
- [Chan] Wait a minute - [Haran] I can't see it so much, what should I do?
I can't see it so much, what should I do?
[Chan] Wow
- [Haran] What are you doing? - [Chan] It wasn’t this.
[Haran] Let’s see if the car is coming or not.
I can't see it too much
[Chan] Uh, it’s a rest area, a rest area.
[Haran] Rest area?
I can't see the road, I can't see the road, I can't see it
[Chan] Well, I’m watching, so you just have to keep going.
[Haran] I can’t see the road.
[Chan] Now, I’ll count three, three.
- Count to three and go to the right. - [Haran] Yes.
[Chan] Now
one, two
three
[♪ Calm music]
- [Chan] Ah… - [Haran] Ah…
[Chan’s sigh]
[Chan] Ah!
I'm taking a breather
I'll contact the rental car company and come back.
[Haran] Uh, uh…
[sigh]
[Chan] Yes? Four or five hours?
The motor is completely gone.
On-site repairs are difficult
I'll repair it at a nearby repair shop and bring it to you.
If you want a replacement vehicle
We will send a rental car to your location tomorrow.
sorry
[Chan] Uh, I think it will arrive at night
Okay, Ben.
I'll contact you again when I leave.
huh
[Call end sound]
eww…
- Wipe it down. - Oh, it's okay.
I really don't listen
[♪Soft music]
[Haran] Ugh
How can I wait for so many hours
Ah, in the Mungyeong Saejae direction.
There is a place to request SOS
Seonwoochan!
[♪ Bright music] [Chan] Huh? You flew all the way, right?
[Woman] You’re this damn kid, huh? [Chan’s sound of pain]
If you came to Korea, you should have come a long time ago.
Are you finally contacting me?
- uh? Ugh, Ugh - [Chan] I'm sorry
oh my
Oh, but did you eat wild ginseng?
uh
You've become so much more awesome.
Yeah, ugh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Hey
[Chan] Ah, designer Song Haran who works with me.
Hello
You are my maternal grandmother.
Maternal grandmother…
Ah, hello
[Jomo Chan’s laughter]
This looked rough at first glance.
- Nice to meet you - [Haran] Hello
- [Chan's grandmother] Let's go - [Chan] Ah!
- uh? Why is it such a shame... - [Jomo Chan] Is it a waste?
How many times do I have to empty it like this?
As impurities fall out
The harsh taste disappears and becomes softer.
It's the same as people
People should also live by emptying themselves well.
Miscellaneous thoughts disappear
Because my heart becomes softer too
Ah, the color came out pretty.
Drink it.
thank you
[Chan] Oh! hot, hot
Drink it later
Oh, it's okay, it's not hot.
[Chan] Ah...
uh? That's right, it's not hot.
Or would you like me to make you some coffee?
I brought coffee beans from Manjae’s grandfather.
I will soon...
[Haran] Ah, I like the car much better now.
It's so delicious
It's delicious, right?
[Haran] Wow
No, both the teapot and the cup.
The dishes are all so pretty
[Chan] All of this
Made by my grandmother
You're a potter.
[Jomo Chan] The separate building is my studio.
Would you like to take a look after you finish your tea?
Oh, that…
uh…
Wow
Yes, I…
Yes, I, I want to take a look, take a look, ugh.
[Hayoung] Uh, Chaewonseu
What are you sorry about?
[snorting sound]
What are you doing?
Savoring the only food of the day to restore jaw line
[Hayoung] Oh!
Uh, mom, I'm surprised.
[Sol] Samples have arrived
Ah, my sweet potatoes.
[Hayoung] Wow!
This really feels like I ate a sock.
Why, why?
[♪ Interesting music] Are you having a bad day?
There's a guy I've been seeing lately
He cheated, that bastard.
[Seunggyu] Oh, that ranunculus?
[Rammy] Such a bitch…
Correct and kind words, with whom?
I had an affair with me
I dug up a lot of SNS sub-accounts.
This woman and that woman are trash talking around.
He's even handing out wedding invitations saying he's getting married next month.
[Rammy] To kill someone like that... This is sure to make you cry!
Ah, that's enough
Just think you stepped on shit and pretend it never happened.
Why are you putting that shit on my feet?
I'm going to paint it off
[Hayoung] ♪ Congratulations on your wedding ♪
♪ Congratulations on your wedding ♪
♪ The Charmin I loved ♪
♪ Congratulations on your wedding… ♪
Mr. Hayoung
Did it come out well? Charmin’s wedding invitation?
If you knew, there would be nothing to see, right?
Ah, hey, is that you?
Lately, some guy the size of a door has jumped out and I was wondering if they were starting a fight.
Oh, was it your boyfriend?
What bullshit
How do you view a boyfriend who doesn't even exist?
[Charmin] Bread!
Threatening people with a car and putting their cell phones in a rag bucket
Wow, I should have blown both rear view mirrors.
Tell that bastard to be careful at night.
Don't talk nonsense
Be careful both at night and during the day.
Ah, it would be better to sleep with your eyes open when you sleep.
'Cause I don't know when it's gonna hit me
Hey, it's done
good
I'm not done yet
[Chamin] Ugh! [♪ Upbeat music]
Uh, my nose, Mr.
Oh, how much is this, Mr.
- hey! - [Hayoung] Why!
Try to catch my eye one more time
Next time, I dump it somewhere else.
[Hayoung sighs]
Where have you been?
Yes, I have a quick meeting.
ah…
But what's going on?
You don't look good
yes? It's not
baby, it's okay
No, why did you all take a taxi?
You always drove around like you were one with the car.
Oh, I had to take it to the repair shop for repairs.
Oh, I see.
Well, go in first.
I'm going to buy some coffee and go.
[Cha Min] These days, a guy the size of a door comes out and I wonder if there's a fight going on.
[♪ Interesting music] I should have blown both rear view mirrors
[Hayoung] Chamin, Chamin
Even the name has a feeling
What do you think, Director Yeon?
I'm not sure
[Hayoung] Ah, but Mr. Chamin
Teacher, please come to the representative office.
if
Did you have your car repaired because of your rearview mirror?
yes
But why...
Was it Director Yeon? Did you visit Charmin?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Oh, you have no idea?
Okay, then I
I guess I should go see Char Min.
Chamin’s number is…
What, ‘Teacher is looking for you’?
[♪ Humorous music] [Taeseok] Yes, teacher
Oh, I'll go up right now.
I didn’t get a call, Director Yeon.
Teacher, you just got off work.
[Taeseok] Yes, yes, I’m on my way.
You held the phone upside down!
What, really, why is it like that?
Surely not?
[♪ Lively music]
Probably not?
[Haran] Wow
wow
[Haran’s Elasticity]
Wow, look at the color, it’s so pretty.
Bring a few things you like.
- [Chan] Ah! -Why are you being generous, huh?
[Haran] Huh? What is this picture?
This is also my grandmother’s work…
[Music fades] [Chan] Ah, ah… ceramic
While you're here, do you want to try making pottery?
That apron...
[♪ Relaxing music]
[Chan] The end
Already?
- Uh, uh, wait a minute - [Chan] Uh huh
[Haran] Uh, uh…
thank god
[cell phone vibrating sound]
- I'll make a call and come back - [Haran] Yes.
[Chan in English] Hello
[Jomo Chan’s exclamation]
[Korean] Wow, you made it pretty too, huh?
How come you don’t want to come here and become my disciple?
Oh, really [laughter]
Give me your address and contact information.
I’ll bake it nicely and send it to you.
thank you
The animator must have taken after my grandmother’s dexterity.
[Jomo Chan] That picture from earlier
That's my mom's drawing.
My daughter used to draw too.
Ah, you look like your mother.
If we had a piece of gum paper this size, we could both draw anything.
Wait a minute
[Jomo Chan] When that guy was this size
These are the things I drew every time I came here.
[Haran] Wow
Why do you get so excited when you talk about work?
I really liked it, painting.
Even if my dad didn't hate the picture
I would have had more fun a long time ago
ah…
That guy's dad
Chan hated drawing so much.
I heard that my mother also drew, so why...
[♪ Calm music] Chan’s mom went abroad
My wish was to study painting more.
Chan’s father opposed it and told him to think about it when the child grows up.
[Young Chan] Look at this
[Seok] Why do we have to fight over this issue?
Don't you understand what I'm saying?
Why now?
Why do you have to study abroad?
You know it was my dream even before I got married.
I want to go and study properly before it’s too late.
Yes, do it
Let's do it here first
Let’s talk again when Chan grows up.
You don’t come home often anyway!
I work hard in the lab.
I went to England with Chan...
If I have to go that way
Leave Chan alone and go alone.
[Jomo Chan] But even so, I feel so distressed that I have so much regret.
I pushed my back
I do whatever I want without any reason
Spread it all out and live
If Chan wants to bring him, he needs to settle down quickly.
I was overexerting myself and not taking care of my body.
I got sick
Not long after entering the UK
at last…
Chan!
[Crying] Ouch
How did this happen?
Even if Chan dies, I won’t let him draw.
They kicked me out to the U.S. without any time to stop me.
That guy has never been able to do what he wants to do.
Go and experience hardships for no reason.
Chan’s dad
Just watching him draw must have been painful.
His mom left because of the painting.
Because I thought he died because of the painting.
[English] Yes, I understand
[Jomo Chan in Korean] At that time, I only thought about my daughter.
Every time I see Chan
My heart still hurts
[Click]
If only I had a mother
I thought it wouldn't have hurt my mind or body
[Chan] I’ve been long enough
Because I've been standing alone in the middle of winter
[Clicking Moonsori]
[Chan] Huh?
What about you, designer?
- [Chan's grandmother] Yes, to wash my hands - [Chan] Ah...
Are you still in love with yourself?
What?
Hey, grandma too
It's not like that.
What's not, huh?
I can see everything in my eyes
Right? What do you like about designer Song?
[Chan] It’s not really
He's someone I shouldn't like.
Who shouldn't be liked...
hey! You couldn't possibly date a married woman, huh?
Oh, I'm not a married woman.
No, then why on earth shouldn’t I like it, huh?
[Haran] Grandma, I’d like a towel, please.
Uh, uh, yeah
[sigh]
how can i do that
It's greed.
[♪ Bright music] [Jomo Chan] Come play again, huh?
You can leave that noisy guy out.
Yes, I will come alone without that noisy person.
[Haran laughs] [Chan] Huh?
Can you two stop becoming friends while swearing at me?
[Jomo Chan] It was so nice to meet you.
- I'm doing well - [Haran] Stay healthy.
Uh, wait a minute.
- [Jomo Chan] What is this? - Excuse me for a moment.
[Jomo Chan] Wow
[Haran] This is very moist.
[Jomo Chan] It’s a bit rough, right?
My hands touch the dirt every day
- Leave this on and apply it - [Jomo Chan] Oh my, oh my.
Wow, thanks to this, I’m going to be a Seomseom Oksu, huh?
Now, let's just stay still.
You know what?
No matter how warmly you dress
If your throat is stiff, you catch a cold.
- Oh, I'm fine. - Oh, oh, oh, come back to work.
Okay, let's see.
Just take it. You threw away your scarf because of me.
[Jomo Chan] Huh? Did you do that?
Wow, look at this
People just buy scarves because a pretty person wears them.
Oh, good, good, good
Thank you, I will do well.
Come on, grandma
Ah, [Jomo Chan’s laughter]
I will definitely come again before I return to the US.
- Ugh - [Chan] Ah!
[Jomo Chan] You don’t keep your promises, huh?
Chan, please, okay?
Take care and eat well, okay?
[Chan] Oh, of course, you eat well.
Grandma, make sure to eat a lot of delicious food too
- [Chan's grandmother] Don't worry - [Chan] Yes
[Chan] Go in carefully!
Take care!
[Chan] Oh, wait a minute.
Let’s check the wipers one more time.
- Again? - [Chan] Yes
-Okay? - [Chan] Oh, wait a minute.
Okay, OK, OK.
Let's go
why? What else is strange here?
[Haran] Yes
There's something strange
What is it? What's strange?
Why am I someone you shouldn’t like?
yes?
Why shouldn't I like it?
[♪ Calm music]
[Jomo Chan] Right? What do you like about designer Song?
[Chan] It’s not really
He's someone I shouldn't like.
[Jomo Chan] Is there anyone you shouldn't like...
hey! You couldn't possibly date a married woman, huh?
[Chan] Oh, I’m not a married woman.
[Jomo Chan] No, then why are you saying I shouldn’t like it, huh?
Grandma, can I get that towel please?
[Jomo Chan] Uh, uh, yes.
Sorry, I heard it by chance.
But I can't understand it
It’s not that the person I like is ‘not’.
If you like someone, you are 'not okay'.
Because the words are a bit strange
I'm not even a married woman
If I were to ask, well, there is nothing to worry about.
What does that mean?
Oh, I don't mean to argue.
I'm really just curious
Then can I like it?
[Music fades]
[♪ Emotional music]
[Haran] The person who gave me that pen is dead.
[Chan] What else happened besides the explosion?
[Haran] I’m honestly curious.
I feel like I'm only telling half the story.
[Chan] Things of the past
It may not be as beautiful as you remember
[Chan] If you get it right, I’ll explain everything.
Today is the day I want to talk about everything.
[Haran] Hall
[Chan] Hall
[♪ Theme song]