IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
CHARACTERS, EVENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND PLACES IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
ETA
1 HOUR
One hour.
BEN
Hey, Ben. I'm driving.
-  Do you have your passport?
- My passport? Uh…
It's in my room, in the third drawer. Why?
Get your passport
and come to the airport.
We have to go to the States right now.
What? What are you saying?
Why do we have to go?
Come to my office.
ANIMATOR SEONU CHAN
EPISODE 6
Hello?
Express delivery?
I'll head there right away.
Ben, I just got here.
I'm going to receive my passport.
Hurry. There aren't many seats left
for the 7:30 flight.
- Hey.
-  Hurry up! We don't have time.
I'm heading inside now.
Okay.
HANG IN THERE!
Hello. This way, please.
DESIGNER SONG HARAN
ANIMATOR SEONU CHAN
Dear passengers,
this is Korea Air, Flight 202
headed for Los Angeles
International Airport.
Please wear your seatbelts
and switch all electronic devices
to airplane mode.
MISSED CALL
ANIMATOR SEONU CHAN
Mr. Park, did you hear from Mr. Seonu?
Oh?
He said he'd take
the earliest flight to the US.
He must be gone already.
YOUR PHOTOS ARE READY FOR PICKUP.
HOBAK PHOTO STUDIO
The project's suspended?
Producer Ben said
there were major executive changes
at the US headquarters.
And the new decision-maker said
they'll halt all ongoing projects.
The project's up in the air right now.
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
They really left?
The entire staff?
The production team left in a hurry
after hearing the news.
I'll share any updates if I receive any.
This is just so sudden.
All animation work
will be on hold for now.
We'll start meetings
for the next season tomorrow,
so get ready.
Team 1 meeting's over.
- Call Team 2.
- All right.
-  Thank you.
- Thank you.
Wow. Weren't we pretty close?
He could've at least sent a message.
His phone's off, too.
He was using
a temporary phone here, right?
Pureum, he's not using
this number in the States?
- Chan isn't coming here anymore, then?
-  Hmm…
I feel like he'll come back soon, though.
Why? Did he tell you something?
No,
but I feel like he'll solve everything
and come back soon.
Chan doesn't seem like the type
to just end things like this.
Right. It hasn't been confirmed
that it's canceled yet.
Chan might already be pretty close
to the new person in charge.
You're right. He'll solve it straight away
and return with a surprise.
What kind of surprise?
For example…
What's this huge box? Fabric samples?
The Chan you ordered is here!
Ta-da!
He could appear like a magic trick.
That's possible.
That does suit him.
Seonu Chan really is something.
He's making us laugh even when he's away.
Geez.
I really miss him.
Hmm…
A reinterpretation
of Nana Atelier's early outfits.
Oh, my. This is going to work.
The new Haran's killing it lately.
You have digital files
of videos from the '70s, right?
I'll share them with you now.
Ah.
Okay. Then let's build on that
and do some more research…
Tsk.
I'm sure Chan will come back
in a few days, saying "Surprise!"
So…  Don't worry.
But if he contacts you
before then, tell us right away.
- What?
- Wouldn't he contact you first?
You haven't been screening your windows.
I know it's because of Chan.
I'm very perceptive, you know.
Hello?
New Haran?
It's mine.
Yes, Ms. Kim.
I was going to visit on the weekend.
My phone doesn't seem to be ringing…
ANIMATOR SEONU CHAN
LOS ANGELES TIME DIFFERENCE
SEOUL IS 17 HOURS AHEAD OF LOS ANGELES
It would be morning there.
HAVE YOU ARRIVED YET?
Darn it.
Did I fall asleep here?
What time is it?
I must be crazy.
Innovative materials?
You mean using new materials?
Yes. The same beauty,
but more eco-friendly.
We'll recreate
one of our archive's 1979 silk pleated set
with fermented protein fabric.
It'll be eco-friendly
and maintain its elegant mood.
Nice. Maison has been using
new materials these days, too.
We could target eco-conscious consumers
who don't buy clothes.
That's what I mean.
We can't.
Nana Atelier built its name
on silk and cashmere craftsmanship.
Using unstable, unverified materials
may jeopardize our launch schedule
as well as brand trust.
The show is meant to showcase
the brand's vision.
Young consumers care about
both style and sustainability.
We should adapt to the times.
It's all about
value-based consumption now.
If we don't, we'll get discarded.
Customer trust comes first for our brand.
Moving away from our premium materials
will risk losing the loyalty
of our longtime customers.
I know trust is important,
but the world has changed.
A brand that doesn't change
is even more risky.
Taking a risk is more dangerous.
We already have a packed schedule.
It won't be wise to make a risky move
that may disrupt our timeline.
- I--
-  Stop.
I welcome
discussions like this anytime.
Let's put some more thought into this
and discuss it again next time.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Okay.
I prepared everything.
There's something else.
I received good news this morning.
What? Do you want to perform or something?
Oh…
No, I just needed to adjust my outfit.
The pre-order stock
for the Lafayette coats
have already sold out.
We received additional orders.
That's amazing!
That's great news.
Good. Make sure everything stays on track
until they're shipped.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey. Was I wrong?
Using materials
that didn't exist back then
is what we call reinterpretation.
You're right.
The fermented protein fabric idea
was good.
Then why was Mr. Yeon like that?
"No. Customer trust comes first."
"We can't risk customer loyalty."
What?
Here's the list of outfits
for tomorrow's VIP fitting.
Please get everything ready.
It's my job to bridge the gap
between the artist's vision and reality.
He cares so much about our family,
but why is he so strict with me?
I'm not bothered at all.
She seems incredibly bothered, right?
Totally.
But aren't disagreements like that
common during meetings?
That's what I mean.
Why is she suddenly so upset?
I don't understand the reason.
The reason…
Hmm.
I'm sure Chan will come back
in a few days, saying "Surprise!"
When did you get here?
You should've called.
Did everything go okay?
Excuse me?
Oh… Sorry, I mistook you for someone else.
Am I sleep deprived?
WAITING FOR GODOT
Hello.
Hey, you're here.
Is Genius still not eating?
He doesn't seem to have
an appetite either.
- Sit. I'll make you coffee.
- Okay.
Huh?
You're not sitting
in your seat of seven years?
I want to sit here today.
It feels like there's a hole.
My heart feels so empty.
It's like wind is blowing through it.
I feel like he'll burst in any second,
shouting "Mr. Park!"
and going on and on about something.
Mr. Park!
Did you have fun? Huh?
Genius. Hey.
You forgot your meds again, didn't you?
I really need to scold you.
I feel like I'll start hearing him
nag me again.
- When will he come back?
- Oh?
What? Is he here?
Donggu.
Hello.
Is Chan still not back from Gyeongju?
I can't reach him.
He went to the US.
What?
Hadam!
Don't you usually go
to the study lounge on this day?
Yes.
It's so nice to ride a swing
after such a long time.
How did you get any free time?
I have something to ask you.
CHA YOUGYUM
It's grated yam.
I did some research,
and they said it helps.
Why was your tumbler
in my grandma's study?
Huh?
Oh… Well…
I ran into her a while ago in the park.
I left my tumbler behind,
and I guess she kept it for me.
Grandma lied and said it was hers.
You keep bringing up my grandma
for no reason,
and you've been behaving strangely
these days.
What was first?
My grandma?
Or Han Sora?
What?
Why are you suddenly mentioning Han Sora?
Park Yeseul…
Why did she have to bring up Han Sora?
Should I give him a snack?
SORA
Hey, Yougyum. It's me, Han Sora.
What are you doing after practice?
What about you?
Her number was saved on your phone
with a heart.
She just saved it without asking.
I only found out the day she saved it.
So you did meet her.
Well…
I did, but I actually…
Hadam, it wasn't like that.
She kept following me when I told her--
"You're too young to marry."
"Quit the nonsense."
Did Grandma summon you
and threaten you or something?
Why would you say that?
You know she wouldn't do such a thing.
You and Grandma both deceived me.
What are you hiding from me?
Did she throw water at you,
telling you not to disrupt my studies?
Did you get annoyed
and decide to meet Han Sora?
Don't say that!
Don't you know your own grandma?
- Don't you know me?
- I don't!
I met her to try to win
some brownie points,
and I met Han Sora
to tell her I'm marrying you
and that I'll report her as a stalker.
I told her to get lost.
That's all I said.
I only spoke to her for one minute.
It's nothing like what you think--
No.
I don't believe you.
I just can't believe
that you hid something from me.
You feel like a stranger to me.
What are you talking about?
Fine.
I couldn't tell you,
but that was only because of one thing.
I was afraid you'd get hurt.
But how…
Why are you crying?
I'm the one who should be crying.
Did I not mean anything to you?
It's you and me, Hadam.
- This is just something trivial--
- Trivial?
Is this trivial to you?
No, Hadam. I didn't mean--
If you were me…
If people were gossiping
about me seeing another guy,
then you see his name
saved with a heart on my phone,
and I keep hiding things from you…
- Then wouldn't you--
- No.
No matter what people say about you,
I only trust what I've seen
and the Hadam I know.
That's the difference…
between you and me.
I'm sorry,
but I can't walk you home today.
Ms. Song!
Oh…
It's you, Mr. Yeon.
Pardon?
It's nothing.
I just reported this to Ms. Kim,
but I got an email a moment ago
from Producer Ben.
All the other projects
have been canceled,
and it's not looking good
for Ben's team either.
Seeing how he asked
to halt the collaboration,
it'll be difficult to resume the project.
ANIMATOR SEONU CHAN
The number you have dialed is unavailable.
Please leave your message--
You can use me as a friend
when you're bored
or a misunderstanding for Ms. Kim.
Just try me out as a free trial.
As soon as the three months is over,
I'll disappear without a trace.
What kind of trial
ends so suddenly like this?
What was that look Mr. Yeon gave me?
He's so warm and friendly
to everyone else.
Why is he so cold to me?
Everything's a mess already,
and now our house, too?
Song Hayeong.
I almost slipped on this.
What? You didn't fall.
-  Just clean this up.
- I'll clean it later.
Just go do your thing.
When is "later"?
It's always when someone
cleans up after you.
Always? Why would you say that?
Do you think
I never clean up after myself?
Stop being childish
and clean up your own mess.
Yes, ma'am.
Song Hayeong.
I'm taking a short nap,
so please be quiet.
I'm coming back in five minutes,
so clean this.
I said I'll clean it later.
You didn't even fall down.
What did you just say?
Yougyum, let's talk…
Say that again.
It's okay if I didn't fall down?
Why are you taking
your anger out on me?
Go take it out
on the person who upset you.
Why are you picking a fight?
You're the one who caused it.
You clearly caused this,
and I'm the victim here.
If you're so logical,
you should've been a lawyer.
- Why did you become a designer?
- Hey!
You two are so childish.
Haven't you two aged at all?
Can't you be quiet for 30 minutes?
If you want to fight, go downstairs.
You sleep downstairs.
Being a high school senior
isn't everything.
When did you ever show
any consideration for me?
You never did anything
to help me with my studies!
Forget it.
What would I expect
from such immature people?
There's no point talking to you.
Song Hadam!
You shouldn't be so mean
just because you're angry.
Then why were you so mean to me?
You…
Forget it. Just clean this up.
Did you just…
- throw that at me?
-  Ah.
Sorry.
I was trying to clean it up,
but my hand slipped.
If you're so upset, throw it back.
I threw it like you said.
You're not the only one
who can be stubborn, you know.
That's not being stubborn.
It's being crazy.
- Hey!
- What?
You…
What am I even doing?
You cleaned it up.
Yes.
Are you… going somewhere?
Yes, I'm going there.
What's with the car key?
I was about to go there, too.
Should we go together?
Fine.
But just us?
E raised to the power of 3in
equals negative c plus one.
So for both sides to be equal,
c should be 0, and d should be 1.
Then hx to the power of x is negative 2…
We're going to go there.
If you want to join…
Applying this formula
would give you x squared minus 2x plus 1.
Did you get that?
And…
There are people passing by.
It's so pretty.
The ocean's beautiful.
- I ended things with Yougyum.
- Huh?
- What?
- Why?
Should we try talking to him?
We never argued before,
but we cried and shouted at each other.
So I can't even focus on studying.
At this rate,
I'll mess up on the CSAT as well.
My life is ruined.
Did you just laugh? This is serious.
I'm facing the biggest crisis
of my life right now.
My gosh. Arguing with your boyfriend twice
might destroy the entire planet.
You were acting like a grown-up,
- but I guess you're still a baby.
- Hey.
What did you two argue about?
There was
a small misunderstanding…
It's obvious
that it was your fault.
He did something wrong, too.
You should've seen his face.
How could he look at me like that?
And, Hayeong,
what were you so pissed about?
I don't know.
It wasn't even anything serious.
Why did I get so upset?
It's a mystery.
What?
I know. It's weird.
Anyway, I'm fine now.
So it's a pass.
What about you, then?
What made you
throw snacks at me like that?
What? She threw snacks at you?
I missed a fun event.
"Everything's a mess already."
Weren't you talking about yourself?
I guess I just felt a bit upset.
What's going on? Huh?
What is it?
It's just…
My spring picnic ended too early.
Geez. What are you saying?
I hate it when people talk in riddles.
Just be straightforward…
It's cold.
I should stick close to you for a bit.
Let's go if you're cold.
No, I want to stay a bit longer.
Why is it so cold?
Are you sure you're all right?
Me?
I'm fine.
I'm always fine.
I should be asking you that. Are you okay?
Yes.
I'll be fine.
And I want to be fine.
So I'm going to be okay.
All right. I hope you will.
Oh. I actually liked it
when we fought, though.
It reminded me of old times.
Chan's a really good guy.
Huh?
You'd normally never drink
on a business trip.
So I asked Raemee
about what happened in Gyeongju.
I'm sure Chan will get in touch soon.
So let's just wait.
It's called an iridescent cloud.
They say you have good luck
if you see an iridescent cloud.
You should look for iridescent clouds
in the sky, too,
instead of just vapor trails.
I guess that was fake, too.
ADD NEW WALLPAPER
It's okay.
Good morning.
It's not a good morning.
Our animation collaboration--
I heard. It's too bad.
Je Raemee, can we do the concept meeting?
Huh?
Sure.
Then let's begin in 10 minutes.
"It's too bad"?
That's it?
We even went on a trip
to Gyeongju together.
Doesn't she feel upset?
ARCHIVES
You must have cleaned out the archives.
When did you find all this?
I came pretty early today.
I was looking through the material, and…
You can take it.
Sorry.
Hmm? It's not mine.
Oh.
It's just spam.
Anyway,
although this is a reinterpretation,
I'd like a fresh twist…
One, you're really okay.
Two, you're pretending to be okay.
Which is it?
You're not even checking your phone.
You two were close--
Why wouldn't I be okay?
We haven't known each other long.
You're as cold as dry ice.
You're so cold.
I take back the 3.5 points.
You're zero points.
Anyway, if you look at these photos,
they seem pretty fresh even though
they're from 40 to 50 years ago.
So instead of struggling
to create something new…
Hi.
Hey. Come and sit.
- Do you want some coffee?
- Yes.
You're not sitting by the window?
This is my usual seat.
Wait, was I acting like I own this place?
By the way, it seems like the project
we were doing will be canceled.
Then Chan won't come back?
Probably not.
I thought I should tell you
since you've been waiting.
Then he could've told me…
CALCULUS
Wow. I've never seen Yougyum
wearing glasses before.
He looks so good.
-  Right?
-  He's so handsome.
I only trust what I've seen
and the Hadam I know.
That's the difference between you and me.
He's so handsome.
I can't believe it.
I wish I could date him.
Gosh, I'm so into him.
Has his eyesight gotten bad?
It'll be uncomfortable
playing with glasses on.
What does it matter? We broke up anyway.
Here's the operations report
you asked for last time.
You're done already?
Ah.
It's too bad
the animation project got canceled.
I'm actually glad
I can focus more on our next season.
Call me if there's anything else you need.
Should we bring the curve down
another 0.3 mm?
And I think we should lower the neckline
by 0.5 mm as well.
Then along the V-neck…
What is this?
It's so funny.
The number you have dialed
is unavailable. Please leave--
It's still turned off.
She didn't even come to work.
Where is she?
Isn't she in the storage room?
She's been going there before work.
Her bag's not in her office.
I don't think she even came here.
Oh? She sent an email.
"I'm sorry. I have to take a day off,
so I'm sharing what I was planning
to cover in our meeting."
What? Has she ever taken a day off before?
Why didn't she keep her phone on?
It's like she was determined to go AWOL.
Go AWOL…
Ms. Kim, Haran…
Knock!
Ms. Kim, why did Haran
suddenly take a day off?
She has the right to take a day off.
Is there a problem?
No,
but I think there's something wrong…
I'm not sure, but it was strange
how she threw those snacks.
And she said something
about her picnic ending
and everything being a mess.
You're the one who seems like a mess.
What I mean is…
Aren't you worried about her, Grandma?
No.
She's not a kid. She'll be fine.
Go. Don't bother me.
Where the heck is she?
Your daughter's growing up, isn't she?
LEAVE REQUEST FORM
SONG HARAN
Hello.
I'll be there on time.
Yes,
we're scheduled to ship today.
If the Lafayette customers respond well…
You've been
to the dementia care center,
- so we'll start with a screening test.
- Okay.
Don't you have
a guardian with you?
No.
We'll call you when it's your turn.
All right.
What? If this isn't urgent--
Didn't you confirm the Brulee Coat
as a one-button?
Yes, a one-button. Why?
The QC report for the factory
was stamped as a pass,
but there's no button in the sample.
We have less than four hours left
before shipment.
Contact the Seongsu-dong factory.
I'll be there soon.
How did I make such a mistake?
SUNYUL NATIONAL UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
Ms. Kim Nabong!
Wait, Na…
Ms. Kim Nabong?
Nabong!
What…
What was she doing here?
How much time do we have?
Two hours.
This won't work.
We should negotiate postponing--
No, I'm not negotiating anything.
If I can't keep our promises,
then I'm not fit to make clothes.
I mistook it for a no-button coat,
so I'll fix this.
We're adding buttons to all 70 coats.
Bring them when they're done.
I'll be checking each piece myself.
-  Pass.
Again.
Pass. Pass.
We have
an hour and 10 minutes until shipment.
Thank you.
The shipment to Paris
has just been loaded.
- What a relief.
- We did it.
I'm so glad.
I'm sorry.
I made you work twice
because of my mistake.
If it weren't for you,
we wouldn't have made them on time.
Great job, everyone.
I'm sorry. It was my mistake.
I should have checked it
before the final sample.
That's enough. It was clearly my mistake.
And don't tell the design team about this.
There's no need to alarm them.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll drive you home.
It's fine.
Treat the factory workers to a meal…
I booked a restaurant
and gave them expenses.
I'd like
to take you home today.
I just want to walk for a bit.
You can go.
Whatever it is, I don't want you
to bear everything on your own.
You can tell me anything, Ms. Kim.
Hey, Hadam. Is Haran home?
She didn't call either?
I'm on my way home,
but there's a lot of traffic…
Huh?
Hang on.
Was I mistaken?
Huh? Why are they sleeping here?
Shh.
They passed out
while waiting for you.
So I was the culprit.
It's late. Go and get some sleep.
Good night.
But why aren't you asking
why I took the day off
or what I did all day?
You're here, so it's fine.
But next time,
write a proper form when taking a leave.
It's not an art class, you know.
Don't scribble on the request form.
It wasn't a joke…
A butterfly knot.
You needed time to get some closure…
on Seonu Chan.
Normally, you'd never
go on a business trip a day early.
And the expressions on your face
in the videos…
I guess… you grew more attached to him
than I thought,
seeing how you needed time for closure.
I just…
wanted to be okay.
When we first met, he told me
that it seemed like
I was trapped in winter.
Thank you.
-  Thank you for these.
-  Enjoy.
Thank you.
Don't you crave croissants
when you see the crescent moon?
I didn't want to get trapped
in winter again, so I wanted to be okay,
but it didn't go well.
I forgot to buy this.
It's my favorite.
Take this.
Whatever I do, whatever I see,
I keep getting reminded of him.
There are 0.3, 0.4, 5, 6,
oil-based, water-based,
nib tip, and ballpoint pens.
SEONU CHAN
I couldn't figure out
a way to be okay,
but then I found this.
SEOUL DESTINATIONS LIST
Choose where to go first
so we can go together later.
So I thought I'd have some closure
if I checked off the whole list.
This could be the final knot.
-  What about this?
-  This?
-  Can I try this?
-  It looks good on you.
How should I choose?
Sorry, but could you take a photo of us?
- We'll take one for you, too.
- Thank you.
Oh, I'm okay.
Thank you.
So I went sightseeing
here and there
and tried a lot of things…
But I kept feeling bored, for some reason.
Everything I did with him
was just so fun and exciting,
so I thought it would be fun
to do whatever was on the list.
Haran.
People, relationships, and even memories
could disappear tomorrow
if you let them slip through your hands.
Go to the US and see him.
Whether you become okay or not,
get it sorted.
You can easily meet him if you want to.
No, we were never that close
to begin with.
That would be silly.
There's nothing as sad and stupid
as regretting things
after time has passed.
Life is too short
to spend it on regretting things.
He was going to go back anyway.
He just left earlier than planned.
This is why I didn't want
to get close to anyone.
So do you regret it?
Do you regret getting to know Mr. Seonu?
I do…
have regrets.
If I knew he'd leave so quickly,
I would have been…
kinder to him.
I was a bit mean to him at first.
But I don't regret
getting to know him.
A three-month trial!
There's nothing to lose.
You can overcome it.
Once you know how,
you'll be able to escape on your own.
I learned it through that person,
so I wanted to show you, too.
Thanks to that weird trial,
I learned how to escape on my own.
So I know I met a great person.
I feel grateful.
Then that's enough.
Traditional knots
each have a specific meaning.
A new life, change…
Sometimes, you have to free something
instead of clutching it tightly
to open up a new beginning.
That's what… this butterfly knot means.
Is she not coming today either?
Sorry, I'm late.
It took some time picking up bribes.
- She's here.
- Ms. Song.
I was late helping her carry this.
This is an apology
for taking a leave without notice.
-  Thanks.
-  Thank you.
Didn't you bring mine?
Of course, we did.
Someone go visit Mr. Yoon's exhibit later.
I have plans today.
I'll go.
All right. Go and visit him.
- Thanks for the coffee.
- Sure.
-  Thank you.
Drop by when you're free.
There's another thing
waiting for its owner.
Yes?
I'll go with you.
I thought you'd return
to your cold, distant self.
I'm proud of you.
Here.
What is it this time?
Did you find a flower ring
you were going to give me?
I saw you when I was getting my checkup.
Why were you at the hospital?
Are you sick or anything?
I was just visiting a friend there.
Then what made you rush out like that?
You even dropped your hat.
Something urgent came up at work,
so, of course, I wasn't skipping happily.
Oh, right.
Seonu Chan
didn't contact you either, did he?
What?
No, he didn't.
I'm actually worried about Haran, though.
There seemed to be something
going on between them.
I'm worried she'll end up in pain
like seven years ago.
It won't happen again.
She seems to have grown stronger
after spending time with him.
Right. My roommate
was quite an incredible guy.
I feel really grateful.
It's such a shame.
I loved the exhibit.
Gosh, look at all these people.
Being out here on a bustling street
makes me so excited!
7:00 P.M. SAMCHEONG-DONG
TODAY 7:00 P.M.
Ah. Mark that on your schedule.
You'd better not forget or show up late.
I totally forgot about this.
Can't I cancel it?
Oh, God!
Isn't this restaurant
so, so, so famous
that you have to wait for months
to book a table?
Take me instead of canceling.
There isn't much time left…
It's just right over there.
We can get there if we run.
Come on!
This is amazing.
It's so nice and peaceful here.
Yes, Ms. Kim.
Yes, I saw him.
I took a pamphlet, too.
All right.
Hello?
Really? Okay.
I'm really sorry.
My partner's a soldier,
and he just got an unexpected leave.
- So, I'm sorry, but I have to go.
- What?
Enjoy your meal. Bye.
I'm very sorry!
What…
Wait, your scarf…
Je Raemee!
Wait!
Je Raemee, here!
Your scarf…
Give it to me next time.
Sorry!
-  I'm sorry.
- It's okay, I'll do it.
- Sorry.
- No problem.
Why did I even come here?
It's even snowing?
Ms. Song!
Hearing things again?
How have you been?
I told you not to be late, but I'm late.
Oh? Why do you look so frail?
Did you not eat well?
Has work been tough?
Um… Well…
Aren't you happy to see me?
I'm so happy that I almost hugged…
I mean…
I almost did a backflip.
Here. How about a high five instead?
I usually do high fives
when I'm happy to see someone.
I have a habit…
of hugging people I'm happy to see.
I promised that I'd be here by today,
no matter what.
You messaged me? When?
Didn't you come here
because of my message?
Please wear your seatbelts
and switch all electronic devices
to airplane mode.
I'll be back soon.
Even if the project gets canceled,
We said we'd have dinner together.
I promise to be there by that day.
Don't worry even if you can't reach me.
Tell Mr. Park and everyone not to worry.
Sir, we'll be taking off soon.
- Please switch to airplane mode.
- Okay.
It's on.
Oh.
Look, I sent it…
Oh? What's this exclamation mark?
It means it failed to send.
Oh! If you didn't receive
my message, then you must have…
You're here, so it's fine. Eat up.
Have more of this.
Here.
Eat all of that, okay?
This is why you're so thin.
Are there no mirrors in the States?
You're the one who looks so gaunt.
I should've dressed up a bit.
It's been a while since we met.
What about headquarters?
Mr. Yeon said it's not looking so good.
Oh, um…
I'm not sure
how to tell you this,
- but…
- It got canceled, right?
Then do you have to go back soon?
This is really important, so…
I resolved everything really well.
It's me, Seonu Chan.
We've already visited the site.
Seeing it in person, it's clear
we can take this project
beyond the original idea.
If anything needs adjusting,
we can move on it right away.
No.
It almost got canceled, but…
I think Scene 27 feels
a bit flat. What do you think?
I don't think it's about the sharpness,
it's about the keyframe timing.
I don't think it's about impact.
The emotion isn't just coming through.
Emergency meetings, back-to-back meetings,
persuasion, even script revisions…
Hey, uh…
how's the background coming along?
Around 60 percent. But they want
another look at the main character.
- At this point?
-  Yeah.
Thank you.
Yeah?
Okay. We'll be right there.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Hey, they're asking for a script meeting.
Okay? Come on.
We didn't want to give up, no matter what,
so we all fought through it
with gritted teeth.
We agreed to revise the parts
that had differing opinions.
That's such a relief.
You said you worked on it
for over two years.
That's one thing…
Mmm…
But I really wanted to apply Won's costume
that you made in the animation.
And that's what got me through it.
Let's eat up and go.
Mr. Park's been waiting for you.
I want to spend more time with you.
Can you stay out late tonight?
I'll clear the table
and bring your dessert.
Thank you.
I should call Mr. Park.
Mr. Park, I'm here.
Genius, Chan is here!
- Why are you crying?
- He's crying?
I'm sorry I couldn't call.
No, no. It's fine.
I'm just so happy.
I thought I'd never see you again.
I was so upset.
Don't cry.
Now I can finally sleep easy.
Yes.
Yes. All right.
Make sure to have dinner
and take your meds. I'll visit later.
Okay.
He was so excited, wasn't he?
Mr. Park and the others
were waiting for you the whole time.
Our whole team, Genius,
and even Donggu came looking for you.
I'm so glad everything worked out.
Only good things
will happen from now on.
For real.
Everything's going to be fine now.
Everything's fine.
JAY YOON 2ND EXHIBIT
I missed you too,
but Haran would've had quite a hard time.
You're the one
who gave her the camera, right?
She seemed so excited
when she was taking the photos,
but after you left,
her eyes were always bloodshot
as if she wasn't sleeping well.
We'll do this line.
Please send us an email.
All right.
But is business not going well these days?
Our company?
Mr. Yeon came by in person yesterday,
so I wondered if anything's wrong.
Why would he come here in person?
He always paid upfront
when placing orders,
but this time, he asked to pay afterward,
saying he needed new materials.
New materials…
- Was it…
- Bio-silk.
Fermented protein fabric.
He said he didn't want money
to limit the designers' creativity.
He asked us to get the material,
no matter what.
It's been 10 years,
but I've never seen him
ask for something so earnestly.
- Mr. Yeon, where are you?
-  I'm on my way to a meeting.
Wait! Stop!
You rejected the idea at the meeting.
Why would you beg someone else to help?
What…
Ah.
I only focus on reality during meetings.
If I say it's possible
and it turns out it's not,
the designers will end up
dealing with the consequences.
You made me seem like an immature kid.
If I'd known, I wouldn't have gone on
about all that protein fabric.
It's okay, so you don't have
to go through all that trouble.
It's really, really fine with me.
So don't go anywhere pleading for help.
Why are you…
always saying you're okay?
This is why I didn't tell you.
I knew you'd say you're okay
when you're not.
It's my job to take care of such issues.
So you can be greedy about what you want
and tell people…
you're not okay
when you're not.
What…
When did I keep saying I was okay?
Mom…
I have to be okay.
I have to keep our family together.
Mr. Yeon.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
You're the first one to come here.
Go and say goodbye to Mom and Dad.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I can't believe
I slept for an hour at a restaurant.
You should've woken me.
Huh? Wasn't that restaurant your home?
You slept so comfortably,
I thought it was your house.
I slept while you're the one
who took a 10-hour flight.
Go home and get some sleep.
No, I'm wide awake now.
But didn't you come from the airport?
Where's all your luggage?
What luggage?
My suitcase!
DEPARTURE TEAM 1
All your important stuff must be in there.
How could you forget a whole bag?
I was just in a hurry to make it on time.
Don't worry.
The lost and found system's pretty good,
so I'm sure I'll find it.
Sir, please stop
in front of the coffee-colored gate.
Tell me when you find it.
Don't wait up for me.
I'll leave you a message if I find it.
Uh…
You might fall asleep in the yard
on the way inside.
I'll go to SHIM tomorrow morning.
Okay. I'll see you tomorrow, then.
What a shame.
I found it.
DESIGNER SONG HARAN
I'll see you tomorrow.
I told you not to wait up.
Did you check your stuff?
Is everything inside?
Yes, I checked…
That's great.
Didn't you say you hated the first snow?
The first snow?
I did, but I feel like
I'll start hating it less now.
But why do you ask?
You said you hated it,
but you're wandering about outside.
Do you even know where I am?
Can you see me?
Where are you?
You said you were home…
I thought I'd regret it.
After you suddenly disappeared,
I had a lot of regrets.
I kept remembering how harsh
I was on you when you were so nice to me.
I don't want to have any more regrets,
so can you help me out?
Is it okay if I be really nice
to you this time?
I'll start today.
I'll keep you company on the way to Seoul.
But where are you?
I found you.
This is bad.
What? What's bad?
I've been holding back until now…
I can't even explain myself to you,
and I shouldn't like you this much.
- Your bag…
-  I shouldn't keep wanting you…
- You should bring…
- …like this…
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
He spoke as if he knew me.
I may not be as good
for Designer Song.
You used to call him Chan.
Your old boyfriend, Hyeokchan.
Their names… were similar.
How much do you know
about Haran's past?
I'm sorry for leaving like that
and for hurting you.
Why is this pen here?
If I just play dumb
and be greedy until I go back,
would that be wrong?
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Translated by Juyoung Park