IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
CHARACTERS, EVENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND PLACES IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
EPISODE 9
Hello, this is the restaurant, Naum.
We found your pen while cleaning.
If you ever find it,
can you contact me through this number?
I remembered that you asked us
to contact you if we ever found it.
I think you owe me an explanation.
The location of the engraving,
and the font.
Both of them are my pen.
How can this happen?
I…
I bought it before.
What do you mean?
How could you have--
I bought the same pen
when I was in the States.
When I first ran into you at the atelier,
I was shocked when I saw your pen
because it was so familiar.
So you bought it when you returned
to the States?
You got the same one?
Yes.
You should've told me.
I was so confused when I got this.
I thought it was a special pen
made just for me,
but I guess it's common in the US.
You could've said you bought it.
Did you think I'd feel uncomfortable?
You really are an artist,
paying attention to so much detail.
The engraving's exactly the same.
It's just like you to go
and buy another one for me.
I'm sorry.
I…
lied to you.
You did it for me.
I'll use it well. Thank you.
It might be an ordinary pen,
but the thought
behind buying it for me is special.
So thank you.
What is it this time?
What on earth is going on with you?
Mmm...
You caught me.
I'm going to France soon.
France?
When?
Probably before spring.
Spring?
I was planning on retiring and going there
when I was around 60.
But my plans got postponed
because of my daughter and son-in-law.
I haven't told the kids yet,
but I really want a break now.
I've been working my butt off
for the past 50 years.
Is that…
really it?
Of course.
I wish I'd reunited with you sooner.
It's just too bad.
I have a lot on my mind these days.
There's so much
to take care of before I go.
That's why I wanted to go
to Chuncheon soon.
Why did you go to the hospital?
You weren't visiting a friend.
I saw a nurse…
calling your name.
You think it's easy
managing a company until this age?
My health is my asset,
so I get regular checkups.
I just didn't want you to worry.
Anyway, let's go to Chuncheon soon.
I wonder if our house is still there.
This is it.
You did it for me.
So thank you.
The more you gain with deception,
the less you can truly gain.
It may seem like
you're gaining something now,
but you'll probably end up
paying the price for it.
The price…
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Gosh, that's hot! I almost died.
Be quiet…
The porridge.
Ms. Song?
You're awake.
- What are you doing here?
-  Uh...
I came to drop off some documents,
but I guess you don't remember.
Are you feeling better?
What is all this?
How can you only have water
and candy at home?
So I ordered some pots
and dishes and stuff.
Delivery is awesome in Korea!
Sit down. The porridge is done.
It's late. You should go.
I'll take you--
Don't be silly. You're sick.
There's nothing more miserable
than being alone when you're sick.
So stay right here.
Ah, pardon me for a moment.
Okay. Your fever dropped.
The pear tea's almost done, too.
It's the best for a cold.
I don't think I should see Hayeong.
She kept talking about you.
I think she likes you a lot.
Really?
- Top of his year the whole time?
- Yes. The entire time.
Wow. He was a genius.
His nickname was Yeon Taeseop,
like Song Taeseop from Slam Dunk.
Yeon Taeseop? So?
Did he enter competitions and stuff?
Of course. For competitions, he…
Here. Unfortunately,
I can't guarantee the taste.
I'll eat it when you leave.
- It's late, so--
- No.
I'll leave after I see you
finishing the bowl.
You were the one who told me
to be honest if I wasn't okay.
Why didn't you tell me you were sick?
I…
shouldn't be sick.
Huh?
Why would anyone
not be allowed to be sick?
You just have to get better.
Eat up before it gets cold.
All right.
Mr. Yeon.
I'll get straight to the point.
I've been getting my hopes up these days.
I thought you were blushing and sweating
because you had feelings for me.
I didn't know you were sick.
But to be honest,
I was happy.
Mr. Yeon, even seeing you with bedhead
makes me curious.
I find myself overthinking
everything you do or say.
And it hurts to see you sick.
I guess I've been denying my feelings,
but I'm sure of it now.
- Mr. Yeon.
- Ms. Song.
I think I like you.
No, I'm sure I like you.
If…
I gave you the wrong idea, I'm sorry.
But I've never thought of you…
as more than a colleague.
Yes, of course.
I thought so.
Mmm...
Then…
start thinking of me that way.
I guess you'll only eat comfortably
once I'm gone.
Then I hope you get well soon.
I'll see you at work.
Ms. Song.
Don't forget
to take this three times a day.
I must be crazy.
I told him I like him.
But it's fine.
I was just telling him the truth.
Good job, Song Hayeong.
What do I do?
Please let Yougyum…
be okay.
Please…
Good job, Yougyum.
Yougyum, your foot.
What did they say?
I've recovered.
I'll be perfectly healed
after some treatment.
It must have swollen from exhaustion.
I'll be fine in a week.
You must have been shocked.
I'm so relieved.
You were in the nurse's office
because of your foot, right?
It was my fault.
I misunderstood and threw a fit,
and I made you worry about me.
Goodness.
I thought you were smart,
but you were a fool.
That's nonsense.
I thought you wouldn't
be able to play baseball again.
Hadam! It's an emergency. Get up.
What is it? Is your foot hurting?
No.
You're wasting your time here
when the CSAT is just around the corner.
Hurry home and get some rest.
I'm going to nurse you.
Really?
Then I should go home
instead of getting treated.
Okay, fine. I'll go.
Don't worry, and focus on the CSAT.
We'll take good care of him.
Don't think about coming before the exams.
I won't even let you in.
I'll get plenty of rest
and receive treatment.
So let's meet after the exams, okay?
Focus!
Focus.
I want you in charge of this.
The overall visuals
for a fashion editorial?
You always did this yourself…
This shoot is about showcasing
the brand's identity.
It's about time
we aligned it with your pace.
Plan the mood, color scheme,
and the flow of the looks.
As you said, we're showcasing
the brand's overall tone.
You should handle--
What do you think, Mr. Yeon?
Will it be hard for her?
I believe she can do it.
I'll support you with anything you need.
Okay. Then that's done.
From now on, prioritize Ms. Song's opinion
when adjusting colors and quantities.
What? Ms. Kim…
Why are you--
Don't make me repeat myself.
You should take some of my workload.
Let me get some rest, too.
Ah. And clear my schedule
for a day this week.
- Is there something…
- What…
Go ahead.
Is something wrong?
You never asked
to clear a schedule before.
It's just that I want some fresh air
before it gets too cold.
- Then I'll take you--
- It's fine. I can go on my own.
Yes, ma'am.
But, Ms. Kim,
I really don't think I should do--
Meeting's over.
Will I have enough time?
No.
I have to get it done.
Uh, she has a personal appointment.
All right.
Please postpone it to next week.
Good afternoon.
Are you feeling better?
Yes, thanks to you.
Song Hayeong, age 29, ENFP.
And ENFJ when I'm working.
I like my family, friends,
colleagues, work, driving,
listening to music while walking
on a windy day,
being honest, tasty food,
especially snack bar food.
Mmm... And watching
cute videos before bed.
- What?
- And what I don't like
are people who are frustrating,
cowardly, who pick on the weak,
stir up conflict, snitch, get paranoid.
And I hate losing people I love,
seeing them in pain...
Ah, and mosquitoes.
Oh, and I forgot one.
Recently, something was added
to the list of things I like.
What are you doing?
We don't know much
about each other personally,
even after all these years.
I told you to think about me,
but I thought you wouldn't have much info,
so I gave you some.
Ah, I'm not pressuring you.
You're always serious and prudent,
so you can take your time.
It's all right with me.
But everyone ends up liking me
the more they get to know me.
I'm just saying.
Having personal conversations
like this at work isn't really…
Mr. Yeon doesn't like
personal conversations at work.
Okay.
I just acquired
some more info about you.
Then have a good day.
So, what do you think about this scene?
Um...
Yeah, I mean, it's good overall.
A few things here and there
we could tweak.
Oh! Ben, how have you been?
I've been doing very well.
My mother-in-law's food is amazing.
We were having a meeting
because we got the additional script.
We'll send it to the design team later.
All right. I'll let you work.
Hi.
Sounds good.
Good meeting.
Should I raise the neckline a bit?
Mr. Park, the coffee.
Oh, gosh.
Goodness.
Uh, were you looking at this pen?
Mr. Seonu bought this for me.
This must be common in the States.
He got it for me
when he went back last time.
He even put a lucky sticker on it.
Right…
I'm glad you like it.
I guess you like Bach.
No. I just happened
to hear about the song.
Someone told me it's good for insomnia.
The music is a bit sad.
I should change it to a brighter song.
Let her feel joy again.
Tell me anything. I'll be your safe space.
Ta-da! I'm getting perfect scores.
I'm going to nail the CSAT.
How are you feeling? Is the food okay?
Ta-da! I'm cleaning
all my plates, and I'm in great condition!
Don't worry about me and focus.
Hmm!
Right. Focus.
"Won flew through the night sky.
"Below her, the Milky Way
was pouring down like a river."
Milky Way…
Won flew through the night sky.
Below her, the Milky Way
was pouring down like a river.
Hmm?
RAN
You haven't gone to bed?
Not yet.
But what are you up to?
There's a newly added scene
of the Milky Way,
so I wanted to go see it.
Should we…
Oh, it's pretty late.
Driving alone at this hour?
That's not fair. We promised
to work through your list together.
Stargazing was on your list.
Going alone doesn't count.
I'll take my car and head there.
So just wait.
I guess the moon's in a good mood today.
We won't be able to see the Milky Way
if it's so bright.
Hmm?
We can't see it because of the moon?
The moon's pretty bright,
so faint lights like the Milky Way
get washed out by the light.
Oh...
It's cold, isn't it?
Sorry, it's my fault.
Uh, can we use that?
- Here.
- Thanks.
Let's just go.
We'll come back
when the moon's less bright.
Oh!
It's so beautiful.
I feel like I'm in space.
I feel like I'm in a dream.
But…
those words sounded a bit sad.
The Milky Way being visible
when there's no moon.
The moon and the Milky Way
go so well together.
It sounds like
they're not meant to be together.
Hmm... That's a bit sad.
I feel like I'll never be able
...to forget this moment.
I've never really liked winter...
Don't you think so?
Hmm?
You were distracted, weren't you?
Sorry.
The stars and the person next to me
were so beautiful
that I spaced out for a moment.
Gosh.
I said I won't ever forget
this moment.
Ah, and in spring…
Uh, will you not be here in spring?
Anyway,
thank you
for showing me such a beautiful sky.
You're back late. You look tired.
Go and rest.
Goodnight.
Mr. Park.
Yes?
I…
want to stay by her side
in spring, in summer,
in fall, and in winter.
I want…
to stay by her side,
but I don't know what to do.
Do you need someone
to talk to?
"Surrounded by walls"?
You saved me as well.
Neon alien…
SUMMER, SEVEN YEARS AGO
IT STARTED WITH WALLS
I heard you going out late last night.
Were you meeting Chan?
Just for a bit.
Why did you meet at that hour?
Were you making out?
Does it show?
Goodness.
No, not at all.
Good job. Make out as much as you want.
You're coming downstairs already?
Did you not get enough sleep?
I did, I went to bed
at 9:00p.m. last night.
But what's going on here?
Ta-da. We're making you
a lunchbox for your CSAT.
We've been planning the menu
for the past three days.
Will it be safe to eat?
- Of course.
- I can just buy gimbap.
Mom would scold us harshly
if you did that.
Hang on. We just have to heat the soup.
I have to go now, though.
There's plenty of time.
I want to visit Yougyum at the hospital
before I go.
Hospital? Yougyum's in the hospital?
He told me not to say anything…
He's hospitalized because of his foot.
Was he hurt badly?
He's a baseball player--
He said he'll get better
with some treatment,
but I'm worried.
Anyway, he's my good luck charm,
so I feel like I should see him
before the CSAT to do well.
Hang on. I'll pack something for him, too.
Hadam, come here for a moment.
Sit down. I'll tie your hair for you.
That's so random.
When you have a lot on your mind,
brushing your hair calmly
will help you relax.
Yougyum will get through it,
and don't forget
that you're perfectly prepared.
You look beautiful.
Of course. I'm your granddaughter.
Don't worry.
I'm your granddaughter,
and Haran and Hayeong's little sister.
I'll do well.
We can take you.
It's really fine.
I want to do this on my own.
Our baby is all grown up
and taking the CSAT.
Did you prepare
your OMR marker and a clock?
Markers, clocks, and hand warmers.
You and even Mr. Yeon
gave me a whole heap of them.
She should go now.
Come on, let's give her some strength.
Strength.
He said I shouldn't come before the CSAT.
But I have to see him, no matter what.
The surgery is at 8:30 a.m.
and we'll fill the top of the foot
with bone taken from the pelvis.
Surgery?
- You're getting surgery?
- Hadam.
You said it'll get better soon.
Would a bone graft heal in just a week?
I'm sorry. Can I talk to my friend
for just a moment?
It must have hurt so much.
Why didn't you tell me anything?
How could I do that
when you're facing something so important?
I'm okay, so go take the exams.
No,
the most important thing to me is you.
I'm staying by your side.
Hadam.
How can I focus on my exams
when you're getting surgery?
I can enter college a year late.
You can just take the bone from my pelvis.
You play sports, but I just sit and study.
This is why
I couldn't tell you.
If you do this, I can't keep seeing you.
- I can take the CSAT next year.
-  No, that's not okay with me.
I…
want to be able to face you without guilt.
What do we do?
What if you end up
not being able to play baseball?
Hadam.
Give me your hand.
I'll recover perfectly
and be back on the mound soon.
I'm just taking a short breather.
You saw my room, right?
My life's goal is to be someone
you can be proud of.
Let's both focus on our own paths
and meet in a few hours.
Come see me after the exams.
You can do that, right?
I'll distribute the exam papers now.
Take one and pass them back.
Please let Yougyum's surgery go well.
Please let Hadam do well on the exam.
Let's begin the test.
SURGERY IN PROGRESS
Good morning.
And thank you.
You really are considerate.
You send Hadam a clock and OMR markers.
What are you doing after work?
I was thinking of getting snacks.
If you're free…
Ah. Take it.
Yes, Mr. Chae.
It's Mr. Chae?
Just a moment.
The materials company he mentioned
will do a material test in a few weeks.
He wants to visit the factory,
and asked if we'll join.
Of course, we should go.
That's great.
All right, we'll join you.
Okay.
Uh, and, Hyunwoo,
the chance of Ms. Song and I dating…
is zero.
I thought I should tell you
that there's no need to worry about that.
Okay.
I thought you'd keep waiting
for an answer.
You don't have to waste
your energy on me.
Aren't you getting in?
I left something at home, no, my car.
All right, then.
Zero…
You're getting ready?
Yes.
I'll tell her everything
and apologize to her.
At this rate,
I feel like I'll end up hiding more things
and lying to her even more, so I'm scared.
I want to tell her everything
and love her as my true self from now on.
I want to tell her in my own way
before it's too late.
The interruption in your hearing
must be from the stress of lying, too.
You know it yourself
that the truth cannot coexist
with false relationships.
It sounds like
they're not meant to be together.
Like the Milky Way and the moon…
These symptoms will occur
more frequently and intensely.
It could end up hurting you badly.
Let's stabilize your condition first.
I'll prescribe a short-term
sedative for you. Ah...
What did the new hallucination sound like?
Ah.
It was sharp, like the sound of metal.
And then something…
like this.
I'm not exactly sure what it was.
But I'm worried that...
there's something more behind it.
Like the bracelet sounds?
Yes. And if I want
to tell her about myself,
I think I should fill those gaps
in my memory first.
She's connected...
to what happened seven years ago.
Your memories
are like scattered dots right now.
They're not connected,
so you can't understand them.
But once they start getting connected,
they'll start forming a structure,
like this.
And once the gaps are filled
and you understand them yourself,
you'll be able--
To explain myself
to her better.
Do you think there's a way
to fill those gaps?
Mmm.
I think so.
Is there anyone else named Sujin
among the staff besides Lee Sujin?
Just a moment.
The day of the accident?
Why are you asking me that?
I heard the explosion seven years ago
in Hyeokchan's lab
was caused by a reagent error.
I was just outside the door at the time.
My memories are hazy from the shock.
Do you remember what happened?
I really want to protect something,
but to do that,
I need my memories.
I came to ask you for help.
I wasn't even a student at your college.
I was just a med student
at a school nearby.
I only visited BIT a few times
to meet Hyeokchan, so why…
Whenever I had glimpses
of my lost memories,
I heard the same sound.
Hey, Sujin. You're here?
I'll head out now.
I heard the sound of your bracelet
that you always wore
when you came to see Hyeokchan.
It seemed like a sign
that you're the person
who remembers everything.
I don't know why the gaps in my memories
are connected to you,
but can you tell me what you know
about what happened
seven years ago that I don't?
I wrote everything down
whenever I had glimpses of the memories.
- Stop it!
- I'm sorry.
You're in a dangerous state.
- It's not too late.
If there's anything you know…
No, there's nothing.
All I did was exchange
a few words with you.
I'm sorry I couldn't help you.
The sound.
Do you know nothing
about the sound I wrote about?
I think it's an important clue.
Uh...
It all started with a sound,
and all these memories--
I said I don't know!
What happened back then still hurts me.
I lost Hyeokchan in that accident.
What's going to change by digging into it?
Someone died.
Why would you torture someone
over just some memories?
You're alive and well right now.
- I…
- I don't know anything,
so don't ever look for me again.
Hyeokchan, you left your earphones
in my car…
So you're saying
you kept talking to Haran
while I was away?
Pretending to be me?
Stop it!
Genius, won't this look lovely on Chan?
You're so cute.
Where were you?
I didn't call in case you were
having a meeting with Ben.
Hey, why don't you look happy to see me?
I am. I'm so happy, I almost danced.
Is something wrong?
You look troubled.
I was, because I missed you.
But I came here,
and you're right in front of me.
Then look at me all you want.
Oh. Why aren't you sitting
in your usual seat?
You weren't here,
so I was waiting to see you coming.
Like a meerkat.
What did you sketch? Can I see?
No, this…
It's a trade secret.
Let me take those.
Customers have been asking for blankets,
so I washed them.
You should ask me to do chores.
I should put these in the baskets, right?
- Yes. Thank you.
- No problem.
Hmm?
Happy birthday.
I'm flying out for a seminar,
so I wanted to say it a day early.
I'll treat you for the watch soon.
Birthday?
I should make this soon.
SHIM
Coffee House
Keep your schedule cleared
tomorrow evening.
We're going to dress up
and have a nice dinner.
Sounds good.
Uh, but why all of a sudden?
Uh... I added dressing up
and having a fancy dinner
to the bucket list.
I'll treat you to everything,
and tell you the location later.
Hmm...
- What's going on?
- Anyway, dress up, okay? See you.
His size…
This is out of the blue.
Uh...
I have a habit of saying goodbye
the American way.
- Since when?
- Starting today.
I'll get going now.
Hmm?
FATHER
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
Gosh.
That was way too obvious.
Do you think there's a way
to fill those gaps?
-  Hadam.
- Yougyum.
How did you do?
I nailed it.
I kept my promise.
I'm glad.
I'm so glad.
Thank you.
They said the surgery went well.
You did it.
I keep feeling sleepy.
Okay.
Sleep. I'll stay with you.
I'll recover perfectly
and be back on the mound soon.
Oh, Mr. Yeon, we're heading out now.
See you tomorrow.
- See you tomorrow.
- You're working late again?
Hang in there.
I want to be on Hayeong's team!
- Me too.
-  Me too, me too.
Me too!
You all want to pair up with me,
the bowling genius.
Yes, Ms. Kim.
You postponed the meeting
with Most Korea's editor-in-chief, right?
Yes, I postponed it to next week.
Sorry, but could I ask
where you're going tomorrow?
- I should know
- I'm here…
- to feel more at ease.
-  Chuncheon.
I'm visiting my hometown.
Don't worry, and call me
if anything urgent comes up.
All right.
You're here.
You cleared your schedule
to go to Chuncheon?
Why Chuncheon?
I want to have some fun, too.
I want to visit
our old neighborhood with Manjae.
I see.
What do you mean, "I see"?
It's nothing.
And you look good in all the scarves.
Your beauty can pull off any color.
But I like the one on the left.
Keep smiling like that. You look pretty.
It's rare to find someone
who makes you smile. Hold onto him.
She has great taste.
She really takes after me.
Look at this.
All right. Is this better?
-  Or this?
-  I love you.
I know. I love you, too.
But I have to choose
which scarf to wear right now.
Look at them again. Which is better?
This train will soon arrive
at its final stop, Chuncheon Station.
Everything's changed.
I can't tell which is which.
I think… this is where your house was.
Yes, you're right.
But…
our house is gone.
Gosh.
It's been so many years.
Right. Even we've changed this much,
so they can't possibly still be here.
It's here!
The tree's still here.
You're right, it's still here.
The persimmon tree my dad planted.
I'm glad
that's still here, at least.
Nabong, let's go to school!
I'm going to school!
Manjae!
- All right. Let's go.
- Hold on tight.
Wow…
It's right here.
This tree is still here.
It hasn't changed at all.
Come on. Hurry.
Right.
This is so nice.
Hmm... Hang on, it's untied.
Mmm...
Ah...  Have some water.
- Manjae, there's something in here.
- Huh?
I got you!
Try and catch me.
Manjae! My goodness.
- I got my revenge.
- Unbelievable.
Stay here. I'll go get something warm.
- Okay.
I must've startled you yesterday.
It was the anesthetics.
I'm completely fine now.
No, it's the painkillers.
The second day of the bone graft
hurts the most.
The pain in your pelvis
will probably get worse tomorrow,
and you'll barely be able to walk
with crutches
after the drain is removed
on the third day.
- And--
- Wait.
Did I wake after 10 years of sleep
or something?
Did you become a doctor already?
I studied about bone grafting all night.
And here's your plan.
What plan?
A 12-week plan to pass
the New York Comets' physical.
I'm going to help you
with your rehabilitation now.
Huh?
I did well on the CSAT,
and I have time on my hands.
The first step is the hospital treatment.
Focus on recovering,
and once you can move, it's step two.
You'd better brace yourself.
I signed up for the study room again.
I guess I'm getting practice
as a future medical professional.
Yougyum!
Hey!
Why didn't you tell me
you were getting surgery?
Should I give you some time alone?
Hey, I'm getting a call.
Hello?
Hi, I saw this number
on this woman's necklace.
She doesn't seem to know
where she is right now.
I thought I should let you know.
Uh, right. Just a moment.
Can you buy me some tangerines?
I'm suddenly craving them.
Maybe I need vitamins.
Sure, I'll go buy some.
Yang Changmo, come with me.
I shouldn't leave you with him.
Call me if you need anything else.
I'll get it for you.
Where are you calling from?
Chuncheon?
Can you stay with her for a moment?
I'll call you back soon.
Have you seen someone like this
on the way here?
You didn't? All right, thank you.
- Hello?
- Is this Hadam's grandmother's phone?
Are you with Ms. Nana Kim right now?
I'm her youngest
granddaughter's boyfriend.
She was lost,
so someone called and said she's with her.
What?
I'm the only one who knows her condition.
Hadam and her sisters don't know yet.
- Hello.
- I called you earlier…
Ah. Over there.
Ah, yes, thank you.
Nabong.
Ms. Kim Nabong!
- Ms. Kim Nabong!
-  Wait, Na…
I was just visiting a friend there.
I'm going to France soon.
That's what it was.
This is what was happening
to you.
Nabong, come back to me.
Huh?
It's me,
it's Manjae.
I'm tired.
I'm so tired.
Okay, get some rest.
Keep resting.
Just rest.
I booked a table here.
Come by 8:00 p.m.
Hmm...
You always look nice,
but dress even nicer.
This is it.
You know it yourself
that the truth cannot coexist
with false relationships.
It's my friend's birthday.
Can you bring that with the candles lit
for the dessert course?
This much?
Gosh, why does it keep falling?
Your hand.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt anywhere?
I'm fine.
That's a relief.
Ah. Are you okay?
Yes...
I'm fine.
I'll clean up here. You should go.
Don't work so late like you did yesterday.
Let's talk for a moment.
I'll be there in five minutes.
See you soon.
I'm sorry, but that sound is bothering me.
Sorry.
It could end up hurting you badly.
And in spring…
It sounds like
they're not meant to be together.
I don't know anything.
You always look nice,
but dress even nicer.
I feel like I should hear
your honest thoughts
to be able to move on.
I have a meeting tomorrow morning.
I have some more work to do--
Just have one glass.
This could be
the last time we talk like this.
How did you know
I've been working late these days?
I don't head out until all the lights
are turned off in the office.
Then what about how you stopped the shelf…
A designer's hands
are their greatest asset.
I only did that to stop you
from getting hurt.
Because I'm a designer at the atelier?
Not because…
I'm Song Hayeong?
No.
But, Mr. Yeon,
I…
keep misunderstanding such gestures.
You got revenge on Cha Min for me,
brushed off those leaves with your hands,
and told me it's okay to say I'm not okay.
I keep replaying those moments in my head.
So I have to hear it today.
This will keep going on
if I don't hear an honest answer.
Am I really…
just mistaken
about all those situations?
Ms. Kim
is my savior.
And her family, Haran, you,
and Hadam,
are precious to me, too.
I have to protect all of you.
That's why I took care of you.
Even if Haran was in danger,
I would've done the same.
If those moments gave you the wrong idea,
then I'm sorry.
So I guess you're saying
you don't see me as a woman at all.
I'm sorry.
Okay. If you're that firm about it,
then there's nothing I can do.
I don't want to cause you trouble.
I can easily move on and let this go.
Easily.
How about a handshake?
Uh, it would be stupid
for us to grow awkward because of this.
So let's shake hands to end this
on good terms.
You can go now.
You said you have a meeting.
I'm going to eat some of this.
My stomach's been growling for a while.
I'll start the car now.
Excuse me. Sir?
Oh...
Yes, please go.
Sir.
Sorry, but can you open the trunk?
How did you hold out
with a fever close to 40 degrees?
Once the meds kick in,
your fever should come down.
Get some rest.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, Ms. Kim.
I should've driven you on your trip,
but I shouldn't drive in this state.
I'll get better soon
and pick you up once your trip's over.
I'm so sorry.
DAUGHTER OF KIM NABONG
AND HER HUSBAND HAVE PASSED AWAY
Sorry.
I have to be okay.
I have to keep our family together.
It's my fault…
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Where are you?
Why aren't you picking up?
Did something happen?
Why can't I reach you?
I'm getting worried.
Is there something wrong?
Hello?
Who is this?
Hey.
Did you cry?
I'm okay.
Let's go to the restaurant.
I'm really fine.
Why are you lying?
You're not okay.
I heard the doctors talking.
What's inside your head?
The shrapnel's still lodged deep
in the temporal bone.
It's right next to the facial nerve,
so there's a high risk of nerve damage.
These are the follow-up records.
It went through the petrous part
and even involved the IAC.
That's how he got his hearing loss.
Was it the accident
where you lost your hearing?
If there's something in there,
it's dangerous.
I'm not someone who will leave
in three months,
nor someone who might never come back.
Ms. Song, I want to stay
with you.
No, Haran.
So I'll tell you everything.
I'll tell you all about the shrapnel
in my head, my ear,
and about the scars on my body.
I'll tell you what happened,
But to tell you everything precisely,
I need some time.
It won't take long.
I'll tell you everything honestly soon.
I'll lay my heart bare.
So when I do,
please listen to everything.
What if you're not okay?
What if something else happens?
I've been okay, I'm okay now,
and I'll keep being okay.
So…
let's go see
the cherry blossoms in spring.
We'll have shaved ice in summer,
see the autumn leaves in fall,
and in winter…
it would be fun to go snowboarding.
You're awake.
Could you leave for a moment?
Stop crying.
I'll just get checked and leave soon.
THE SURFACES, BORDERS,
AND TRANSMITTING STRUCTURES
Are you okay?
Gosh.
No, just my roommate.
-  Here.
- Thank you.
I think you dropped your bracelet.
This is yours, right?
Oh. Hey, crybaby Song Haran!
Hmm?
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
I'll make your birthday
even more special next year.
I'm going to use that trial
for the rest of my life.
Don't play around when it comes to her.
I'm going to make everything okay.
I'm scared. I'm terrified.
I didn't know.
Why? How could you not know?
How about a date tomorrow?
We can watch a movie, have a nice meal,
and take a walk while we chat.
We'll do what other couples do.
Seonu Chan! Where are you?
I'm so relieved nothing happened.
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Translated by Juyoung Park