IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
CHARACTERS, EVENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND PLACES IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
Chan, I saw a vapor trail earlier.
But that made me want
to get on a plane to go see you.
Chan.
I love you.
I love you, Chan.
EPISODE 2
The accident in the US
happened last summer, right?
It has already been three months
since you came to Korea for treatment.
Have you recalled any more memories
after our last session?
No.
I just keep
remembering one person.
I keep remembering
how she called my name and woke me.
But no matter how much I try to remember,
I can't recall who she is
or why I'm remembering her.
Do you get images of her
in certain situations?
No, she's always just there.
She's buried in my brain,
just like that shrapnel.
Could it be someone you met
during that year before the accident,
back when everything's a blur for you?
I've always been alone.
There can't be anyone
who says they love me.
I'm not even sure if she exists,
or if it's an illusion in my head.
Or…
if I'm just crazy.
I wouldn't feel
so frustrated if I at least knew that.
What kind of person
does she feel like to you?
Someone I have to meet…
Sir, I'll just get off here.
Someone who brought me back to life
and seems to hold the keys to my life.
Try listening to it.
I saw a vapor trail earlier.
Chan.
Hold on. Let me start over.
Try listening to it.
Hey, engineering student.
Chan.
Hey, Chan!
Hey. Sorry, Haran.
Oh, that song?
Sure. Send it to me.
I'll listen to it.
I have to go in a hurry.
Can you message her back
and say I have to go to the lab?
Sorry. Do me a solid.
Tsk.
Sorry, I'm heading to the lab.
I was feeling trapped.
I feel like I'm surrounded by walls today.
I just messaged you
because I wanted to talk to someone.
But you're busy. Sorry I bothered you.
"Surrounded by walls"?
I FEEL LIKE I'M SURROUNDED BY WALLS TODAY
If it's okay with you,
you can talk to me.
I'll be away for a few weeks.
I'm traveling around the East Coast
during vacation.
Hyeokchan,
you took my laptop.
My research data is in there.
I must've confused it with mine. Sorry.
I'll send you the data.
- Just use my laptop for now.
-  I…
- How do I turn off that sound?
-  The messenger alarm?
Just mute it and ignore the messages
or tell her I'm at the lab.
Anyway, send me your email address.
Hey.
Kang Hyeokchan!
Chan.
I love you.
I love you,
Kang Hyeokchan.
Seonu Chan… who are you?
Oh.
Gosh, my eyes are so dry.
Don't get the wrong idea.
It's not like I have some big secret.
Dry eyes?
You follow me around, take photos of me,
then send them to my office.
Why are you stalking me?
- Stalking?
- I found an art museum ticket
in your shirt,
stamped with the date I went there.
I did go to the art museum,
but I wasn't following you.
I just received a ticket.
You're the one who called my name, right?
My name and my face.
You couldn't have known.
I guess you gathered a lot of info
while stalking me.
I…
I think this… will explain it.
I always check my partners' websites
before working with them.
You saw one photo and recognized me
from so far away? That's--
I saw you up close earlier,
looking at the Sisley painting.
Then why didn't you say so
when we met at our office?
I'm sorry if I upset you
by not telling you about it.
I guess… I misunderstood.
I'm sorry.
Then what are you doing at this hotel?
I'm staying here.
My company booked it for me
since it's close to Nana Atelier.
Uh… Here's my card key.
Room 3017.
Then why did you run away--
I wasn't running away.
I was just heading out…
Because I forgot to buy this.
It's my favorite.
I didn't even know you were in the lobby.
Yeah.
Once again, I'm sorry.
"Stalking"?
Darn it.
Then who could have sent those photos?
Song Haran!
It's the stalker!
Stalker!
You darn stalker!
Don't you dare touch my sister!
I'm reporting you!
What is he doing here?
Thank you.
What?
Stalker! Stalker!
I'll get him.
Are you okay?
Huh?
Answer me.
What was in that bottle?
You'd better talk.
Do you want to film a vlog in prison?
Song Hayeong, be quiet.
From the smell,
it seemed like
a diluted sodium hypochlorite solution.
Ah, I mean, NaClO.
Sodium hypochlorite…
I mean, it seemed similar to chlorine.
Oh, chlorine?
I guess you majored in that field.
Why were you trying to throw that at her?
I wanted to ruin her.
She was always getting on my nerves.
Do you know each other?
The design contest winner is…
Song Haran!
Thank you!
I'll treat everyone today.
I always wondered why
you were always at the center of attention
and why everyone loved you.
It was because of Kim Nana.
You're lucky
your grandmother's a famous designer.
I quit my job
because I hated the sight of you…
but it's all because
of your grandma.
You made me lose everything.
Weren't you great
at pretending to be the main character
and acting like you were happy
without a concern in the world?
So why…
Why now?
-  Are you crazy?
-  What are you doing?
I don't want to press charges.
Just end this here, please.
GEUMWON POLICE STATION
She ruined her own life.
You went through so much
while you were at that company.
But why were you here? And you, Mr. Yeon?
Oh... Well…
The photos really bothered me,
so I had to do something.
LOCATION TRACKER
- What are you doing?
- There's a smudge on it.
HARAN
Something could really happen to Haran.
I didn't dig through
your phone or anything.
I just downloaded a location tracking app.
But I saw you were here
when there was no meeting.
- I got a bad feeling, so I came--
- Are you mad?
Why would you do that?
What if it really was someone dangerous?
If something happened to you…
Come on. I'm fine.
Bad things don't come with a warning.
People can get hurt in an instant.
"What if I'd done something differently?"
You can regret it hundreds,
thousands of times after the fact,
but it won't change a thing.
That's it!
Hayeong,
if anything happens to you too…
Haran, look at me.
Look at me.
I'm right here.
I'm okay.
We're all fine.
Nothing will happen now.
It's okay.
It's all right.
You must have been startled. I'm sorry.
But why were you running
with my sister earlier?
Oh, well…
My hotel was nearby.
I spotted someone suspicious
following her, by coincidence.
Wow.
You're her savior.
Thank you so much for helping her...
Thank you.
Oh?
Your jacket got bleached.
Why did she have to throw…
I'm sorry.
I troubled you with a personal issue.
And I'm sorry about earlier too.
It's fine.
Then I'll head back now.
-  Bye, then.
-  Bye.
What did you mean by
"sorry about earlier"?
I grilled him,
thinking he was the stalker.
Geez. Ungrateful much?
He even ruined his jacket
trying to help you.
Huh?
Did the other guy leave?
He probably needs treatment.
Hmm? Treatment? He just left.
Hayeong, go home first.
No, take me with you.
I can't let you go alone.
I'm really fine.
And keep this a secret, okay?
Don't report this to Grandma.
Hurry home, okay?
And keep your phone on.
My heart…
I thought something might happen.
Are you all right?
Gosh.
Of course. I'm fine.
I'm always fine.
Did you need something
approved by Grandma?
Let's go. It's late.
It's that way.
Come on.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
No, not that way…
Mr. Seonu.
Oh…
You hurt your hand earlier,
didn't you?
I'm sorry I got you mixed up in this.
Charge me for the hospital fees,
your jacket,
and any inconveniences
caused by your injury--
Are you a lawyer?
I thought you were a designer.
What?
As you can see, I'm fine.
So you don't have
to draw a line like that.
I don't feel okay with it.
I hate causing trouble for others.
I'm really sorry about today.
Make sure to get your hand treated.
Why does this keep happening?
It's scaring me.
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
She rejected me firmly.
I want to live like this.
I feel comfortable this way.
I know I'm being stupid and weird.
But…
I'm too scared.
She's here.
Don't do this anymore, Grandma.
I'll handle things myself.
Pushing everyone away
and wasting time outside,
then hiding in a cave…
Is that how you handle things?
She…
She was with a guy.
- What?
- I was with them.
I came home early,
and she spent more time with him alone.
- Don't lie to me.
- I mean it.
Mom, Dad. You saw it, right?
I'm not lying, right?
Is it true?
I'll head upstairs first.
Tell me. Who is he?
And what's their relationship?
Uh…
Well…
- They're just talking.
- "Talking"?
Just leave her be.
Meddling will only ruin it.
Then good night.
Sleep tight.
"Talking"?
Gosh, Song Hayeong.
You've helped your sister again.
This household is ruined without me.
You're lucky to have such a great sister.
You made her get the wrong idea.
What? It's true that you were with a guy.
Won't it be good for her
to get the wrong idea?
Just pretend you're seeing someone.
That will save you from a lot of nagging.
No, there's no need to thank me.
I'll take this instead.
How is the animator's hand?
I gave him my business card
so he can charge me.
Business card?
Did I raise you like that?
If it weren't for him,
you would've gotten that chlorine…
Oh God.
Listen, Haran.
You should at least buy him dinner
and thank him in person…
But of course…
you're not the type to do that.
Ah. Give him some new clothes.
His jacket was ruined.
Right. Clothes.
Then next week at our meeting--
Next week?
He's here on a business trip.
He won't have many clothes.
Would that be too late?
- Then a delivery…
- Delivery?
You should at least say,
"I'm sorry, your jacket's ruined."
"I'm not sure if you'll like them,
but I got you some clothes."
Shouldn't you at least give them to him
in person and show some sincerity?
I'm tired.
I'm going to bed.
Hayeong.
Thank you for today.
You were telling me
to shut up earlier.
Good night.
Bad things don't come
with a warning.
People can get hurt in an instant.
If something happened to you…
What's this?
Why are all our shoes in the bathtub?
What do you mean? What shoes…
I'm going to wash them.
They were pretty dirty.
I have an exam in an hour.
What am I supposed to do?
What is it? Are our shoes gone?
How do I go to school today?
I have an important meeting.
You can all stay home today.
- No, I have to go.
- Don't go!
Just don't go.
What if something happens to you outside?
It happened to Mom and Dad.
So don't go, okay? Don't go!
Haran…
- Don't go.
-  It's okay. It's okay.
Haran, it's all right.
Just stay home.
Don't go. Don't go. Please. Please.
What?
You just looked ugly. Good night.
Meet him in person?
Yes?
What brings you here?
Someone dropped this off for you
at the front desk.
- Who?
- A young lady.
She asked me to give this to you and left.
How did she know my room number?
Ah. My card key.
I'm sorry your jacket's ruined.
I'm not sure if you'll like them,
but I got you some clothes.
Huh?
No.
Don't get involved.
Please, please, please don't be here.
You know that particular smell
before it rains?
I love that smell.
But it disappears so quickly,
so I just stand there smelling it.
But the catch is that
you always end up with a nasty cold.
From the smell,
it seemed like
a diluted sodium hypochlorite solution.
Ah, I mean, NaClO.
There's another guy
who speaks like him.
Ah…
You'll catch a cold.
You came here because of me, so take this.
No, it's okay.
I'm the one who's not okay.
Oh…
I have another one in my room.
I'll go get it.
- Hang on.
- No, I…
Hey! Haran!
Song Haran! You're actually alive!
Gosh.
You suddenly cut all contact with us
and said you were going to the US.
I went to your workplace, but you quit,
and your number wasn't in service.
I was so worried about you.
I'm glad I bumped into you.
I actually booked a wedding here.
It's next spring.
- You'll be able to see everyone--
- Sorry, Yujeong.
I'm in a hurry right now. Sorry.
Huh?
Haran, wait!
Haran!
- I'll come with you to get the umbrella.
- Pardon?
Huh? Why isn't it here?
Hang on.
Ben, my umbrella… Mmm…
Is he not here?
Oh, the concierge…
No, it's fine.
Hello?
Hello. It's Room 3017.
It's taking a while.
I'm sure they'll come.
Right.
Oh! The umbrella…
No, it's Ben.
- Ben.
-  Oh.
Where were you?
My mother-in-law wanted
to give me some chicken stew.
Oh? Ms. Song?
Hello.
I was dropping off something
and came to borrow an umbrella.
Oh! This is great.
You can have a meal with us…
An umbrella!
Here.
You can take this.
- It's pouring, so get home safely.
- Right.
I'll see you at our next meeting.
Bye.
What was that?
You become an idiot in front of Ms. Song.
Is there something going on?
Are you dating?
There is something…
But there shouldn't be.
Ben.
Don't you feel suffocated in this hotel?
Should we just rent a house
while we're here?
Is it the hotel or your own heart
that's suffocating you?
SHIM
Coffee House
It must be closed today.
We've been waiting,
but Mr. Park's not coming.
Thank you.
Where should we go?
Hey, Genius.
I'LL BE BACK SOON
Hello?
Isn't this Mr. Park's phone?
It is, but he's asleep right now.
I'll take that.
- Hello?
Give me your paw. Good boy!
Hi, I'm Genius.
Aren't I big and adorable?
Why is there a dog here?
The owner of a coffee shop
Big Sis is a regular at was hospitalized,
so she said she'd take care of him.
I wish I could keep him.
Song Hayeong, that little brat.
What? It wasn't Hayeong.
- What?
- You're here.
Park Genius.
Isn't that such a cute name?
He was named after the coffee shop owner.
- His name's--
- Hadam. Your academy.
Hey, Genius. I'll be back soon. See you.
See you, Grandma.
Were you close enough to someone
to look after their dog?
Sorry, I brought him without asking.
WE MISS YOU
GET PLENTY OF REST AND FOCUS ON RECOVERING
Should I get some toys for Genius?
You're a dog, and this is a yard.
Run around all you want.
-  Who is it?
-  Excuse me.
Hello.
Is my dog Genius here?
Hey, Genius!
Genius!
Good boy.
You must have been startled
being here without me.
- Good boy.
- Hello.
Ah…
My eldest granddaughter
isn't here right now.
Gosh. Where are my manners?
Thank you so much
for taking care of Genius.
It's fine. It wasn't hard
taking care of him.
But how did you…
I got discharged early.
I heard it was the house
with the coffee-colored door.
I was worried I'd come to the wrong house
for a moment.
I'll thank you formally next time.
- Let's go, Genius.
- Goodbye.
Bye.
Park Genius.
Isn't that such a cute name?
He was named after the coffee shop owner.
- His name's--
- Park Manjae?
Are you Manjae, who lived in Chuncheon?
Who…
It really is you.
It's me.
The house with the persimmon tree.
Who?
PARK MANJAE
Manjae!
Nabong!
The fashionista Nabong from Chuncheon?
Yes, it's me.
It's Nabong.
It really is you?
You're really Nabong?
Huh?
Huh? That's…
Mr. Park, the clutter box
you're throwing away…
Hello.
What are you doing here?
I'm going to live here. What about you?
You're living here? Why?
I'm close with Mr. Park.
- What brings you here?
- Why are you close?
Why?
The hotel's nearby,
so I came here every day.
And I actually received the exhibit ticket
from Mr. Park
after fixing the ice machine.
Then the regular
who fixed the ice machine…
But why stay here instead of a nice hotel?
You heard the doctor, right?
Make sure to take your meds
and get plenty of sleep.
And no overworking or drinking alcohol.
Enough with the nagging.
My ears are going to bleed.
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
There's nothing like being back home.
There are a lot of rooms here.
Oh. It's a bit big for one person.
Mmm-hmm. You must feel lonely--
Mr. Park, can you let me
stay in one of the rooms?
Just for three months.
Three months.
I was going to rent a house,
but he had some empty rooms.
And Ben is at his in-law's.
So what brings you here?
Then the regular
who called an ambulance for him…
Hang on. Then it was you
who answered the phone?
Ah. I heard the regular I talked to
on the phone was taking care of Genius.
Yes, that regular is me.
Ah. Regular.
Regular… Mmm.
I think Mr. Park
was around here somewhere.
By the way, is he all right?
I'm all right.
They said
it's variant angina or something.
I just have to take medicine.
By the way, it's been so long.
You suddenly disappeared
from Chuncheon one day.
It's been over 50 years.
But I'm quite famous now.
You really didn't know?
Well, I knew the name Nana Kim,
but I never imagined
it would be you.
Gosh, you were always
going on about la vie en rose,
and you really went to France
and achieved that dream.
But I've been running a coffee shop
in this neighborhood for over 10 years.
How is it that
we never ran into each other?
That's how the world is.
It can feel small at times
but big at others.
But how did you get so close
to my granddaughter?
She never lets anyone get close to her.
She's a regular at my coffee shop.
She stays there
almost every day until I close.
I wondered where she was staying out
so late every day.
She was there?
I guess she felt more at ease
at your coffee shop than at home with me.
I guess you did something for her
that I couldn't.
- Thanks.
- All I did was give her coffee.
I didn't do anything special.
It's been seven years,
but I never knew
she had a place to rely on.
Seven years?
That's around the time I first met her.
I think it was around summer.
I'm not sure if it's okay to ask this,
but did something happen to her
back then?
My gosh.
Hey, Genius.
It's raining cats and dogs.
It's pouring, isn't it?
It was a day when it suddenly poured.
But she was sitting in the rain,
crying.
Her boyfriend died back then.
He went to study in Boston,
but he suddenly died.
BEN
You're getting a call…
Can you…
Can you hold it
on the other side?
Yes.
Hey, Ben.
A meeting on Monday?
Okay. Bye.
Thank you. Can you put it here?
Right.
I'm back!
Genius, house!
Were you at our house?
You only just got discharged.
You should've called me.
It's the first time I've heard you talk
this much in seven years.
Are you all right?
Yes, thanks to you.
But it's a surprise seeing
my VVIP regulars here together.
Roomie, say hi. She's…
Oh. I know her.
She's a designer
at the company I'm working with.
You were working with Nabong…
I mean, the designer Nana Kim?
How do you know my grandmother's name?
It turns out she was my childhood friend.
Oh, really?
We lived in the same neighborhood
for 10 years, but I never knew.
I was so excited,
I almost did a backflip.
Right, I forgot.
Thank you.
You locked the doors for me
and even looked after Genius.
It's nothing.
And you can talk to me informally.
You're Grandma's friend.
Then should I start
talking to you casually?
Like a friend.
Ah. Yes.
This is the first time
I've seen you smile like that too.
But… you must feel comfortable
on your own.
Why did you let him live here?
I thought I'd feel safer
if there was someone with me.
And he's adorable.
He's a really good man.
Come sit down. I'll make you coffee.
No, it's fine. Get some rest.
Even if I don't drink coffee,
is it okay to stay here
until closing hours?
You're young.
You should be having fun outside.
You shouldn't stay cooped up
in this boring place.
This place is the most fun for me.
I can focus on work,
and I feel at ease
because it feels like nothing will happen.
Mmm.
Bring the dancheong data
I mentioned to my office.
I'll give you the files now.
If it's a work call, take it.
Mr. Yeon, take the files.
- Sure.
- Here.
- Hello.
- Here, Ms. Kim.
I called about the fabric materials.
Yes, I'd like the 0.8 mm ones.
SEONU CHAN
- Ah, yes.
-  She…
- Thank you.
-  She was with a guy.
It's an original character
that Chan created.
That character. Was it based on someone?
No, it just came to mind.
He drew his ideal type,
but he met her in real life?
Mr. Yeon, keep an eye on Ms. Song
and Seonu Chan.
Yes, ma'am.
That expression.
You look like a robot that's been given
an order you can't refuse.
It's not like that.
What is it? Did Grandma…
I mean, did Ms. Kim order you
to do something again?
No, she didn't.
"No, she didn't"?
All right. Then keep working
in your robot mode.
Beep, beep, beep.
It's pretty fun teasing him.
Let's take a photo.
One plus one is what?
Two.
I'm a huge animation fan.
Where did you learn art?
At CalArts.
CalArts? That's insane!
Sweetie, can you draw me a caricature…
- …with your professional skills?
- Sure.
Me too.
-  Me too.
- What?
-  I'll get some paper.
- When did they get so close?
Is he a capybara or what?
Is this better, or this?
-  The second one.
-  Is this better?
How should I pose for this?
Like this?
Hmm.
Using a dancheong pattern
to show that she's Korean
just with her outfit…
Wow. This might be a problem.
Because it's so good.
Then let's develop this
with dancheong as the basic concept.
All right. I'll send this to HQ
and schedule a video call.
I feel a bit hungry.
I'd like to continue our discussion
over dinner. Are you free?
Yes, I'd love that.
How about the new
Italian restaurant nearby?
It seemed really wild.
Your appetite must be wild too.
No wonder your jawline disappeared.
Have dinner without me.
What do you like?
You can eat without me. I--
You're joining.
I said we're discussing work.
They look good together.
What?
I said the interior is nice.
Hello?
All right.
Sorry, I have to go.
Something urgent came up.
Then let's--
Sit. I didn't mean you were going.
I'm sorry. Enjoy your dinner.
See you at the meeting,
Animator Seonu Chan.
Right. I'll see you at the meeting.
If you feel uncomfortable, we can just…
Here are the menus.
I'm sorry, but we'll just…
You should at least buy him
dinner and thank him in person…
Let's just eat.
I'll buy.
What?
Ah. Okay…
Can you recommend something?
- Take your time. Just look here.
- Ah.
Our rollatini is our signature dish,
made with sliced eggplants…
- She doesn't like eggplants.
- How did you know I don't like eggplants?
What? Oh…
Many people dislike eggplants.
Right?
-  Right…
- Me too.
I dislike them as well.
Can you just give me
something you can prepare quickly?
- Me too.
- All right.
The interior really is nice.
Repetition means
your heart has already stirred.
Instead of writing his name over and over,
follow your heart.
"Name"?
Mr. Yeon, take the files.
Let me apologize first.
SEONU CHAN
Oh? Why is my name there?
Well…
I wrote this when I thought
you were my stalker,
but I think Ms. Kim saw this
and thought I had feelings for you.
That's probably why
we ended up having dinner alone.
Ah…
I'll explain this to her…
Just pretend
you're seeing someone.
That will save you from a lot of nagging.
I should tell her…
But is it okay if I don't?
Pardon?
It's a bit complicated,
but I think
this will be a good opportunity
to put my grandmother's mind at ease.
Oh. Sure.
If it helps you, then it's fine with me.
Thank you. I'll make sure
this won't cause you any trouble.
All right.
There must have been
an issue with the connection. I'm sorry.
It's fine.
How did the two seem?
I'm not sure yet.
REPRESENTATIVE
KIM NANA
I set things up for them,
so we'll know soon.
- You can go now.
- I'll take you home.
I'm not a child. I can go home by myself.
You don't look well these days.
And you haven't gotten
any checkups for years.
At least take these. They're vitamins.
You're not my chauffeur
or secretary anymore.
If you've become the COO,
you should stop doing such things.
Why would a COO take care
of my granddaughters as well?
I'm doing it because I want to.
Then don't work too late.
I wonder what they're up to now.
Sorry, I shouldn't have asked
what I did earlier.
I'll take that back…
- Are you not feeling well?
- What?
Excuse me…
I'm so sorry. I'll pay for all this.
Can you put in the order again?
Just a moment, please.
All right.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Are you okay? Do you feel dizzy?
Is there a pharmacy nearby?
I'm sorry.
I don't do well in noisy places.
- Is it hard being around crowds?
- No.
Mmm…
I can't hear… on this side.
I'm usually fine,
but the sounds get mixed up
when it's noisy inside.
And I can't even hear
the person right in front of me.
It's hard to tell
the direction of the sounds.
Excuse me.
Excuse me! No, not that way…
Can you hold it on the other side?
But I'm a skilled artist, I'm friendly,
and with my looks…
What?
I'm a really lucky guy besides the fact
that I can't hear on one side,
so you don't have to look at me like that.
I'll go deal
with the mess I caused in there.
No, it's noisy in there.
I'll go bring our stuff.
I…
Hang on.
Excuse me for a moment.
I'm just taking care
of your ruined clothes, as a designer.
It's not because I feel bad or anything.
- Why are you drawing a line like that?
- Think however you want.
Thank you.
Thanks
for caring.
I took care of it for now.
There.
No, you'll catch a cold…
It was just to style my outfit.
I'll tell my grandmother
she had a misunderstanding.
It's a good opportunity.
It's fine with me--
I'm not fine with it.
I don't like feeling indebted.
Anyway, I'll bring our stuff.
How did you get close to Ms. Song?
What? Well…
I think we're close,
but I'm not sure about her.
But why do you ask?
Well…
It feels like she always draws a line
and doesn't let me cross it.
She didn't use to…
It just feels like it's hard
to get close to her.
I've seen her every day
for the past seven years,
but I had no idea what she did
or where she lived.
She never talks about herself.
She was always drawing clothes,
so I just assumed she was a designer.
She always came by herself
and stayed here quietly.
Did she ever come with anyone else?
No, never.
Not once in seven years.
She was always by herself.
Always.
Did you catch a cold?
No, I was just sneezing.
Huh? Where did it go?
Gosh, you're stirring up dust.
What are you doing?
I can't find my drawing pen.
Where did it go?
Where are you going?
It's time for our meeting.
I really liked
the, uh... the dancheong idea.
So could you tell me
a little bit more about it?
Of course.
Director Song will go over it for you.
Director Song?
The data overview.
Oh, the data…
Dancheong is
a traditional Korean coloring technique.
Thank you.
Commonly found in palaces and temples.
It involves painting
wooden architecture with…
Okay, so I'll see you at the next meeting.
We'll talk more about it then.
All right. Bye-bye, everybody.
Bye!
See you.
Great work, everyone.
What kind of attitude was that?
I'm sorry, but I have to go.
Gosh. It's not here!
Hang on. Where did I last use it?
Right. The restaurant!
The restaurant?
NAUM LOST-AND-FOUND LIST
We haven't found anything like that.
Could I search for it myself?
There are customers eating inside.
But if you dropped it,
we would have found it while cleaning.
I'm really sorry,
but can I take a look after you're closed?
Just for 30, no, 10 minutes.
It's really valuable to me,
so I have to find it.
Please.
No.
You're going downtown later anyway.
Just get me something I can gift.
Anything that a woman
in her twenties can use.
We're not close enough
to ask for favors like that.
Do that for me, okay?
Is it a gift?
I could engrave it if you'd like.
Did you find it?
I'll look for it after they close.
I'm sure it'll be there.
Let's go. We can stay at SHIM
and come back to look for it.
No, this is a personal matter.
I can find it by myself.
- Wear this for now.
- No…
I'm just trying to help
with your coughing, as an animator.
Plus, even if you dropped it here,
someone could have taken it.
Anyway, let's go somewhere warm--
I'll…
deal with this by myself.
Thanks for your concern,
but leaving is helping me.
What are you going to do, then?
Wait out here
when you're coughing like this?
It's just some pen.
You don't know anything about it.
I'm already upset
without you making it worse, so just…
Where are you going?
You won't leave me alone, so I'm leaving.
It might be "just some pen,"
but I have to find it, no matter what.
Fine, I'll leave.
- So wear this.
- Please, just…
Just take it.
"Just some pen."
I feel bad for saying that.
Hey, roomie.
- Yes.
- I'm sorry.
Gosh. Sorry.
Oh, my…
You must have gone through
something awful.
- You always seemed so cheerful.
- Oh…
Do you want to try touching it?
It doesn't hurt at all now.
It seems you got something drawn
on your chest.
Ah. My tattoo?
But why is it "memento mori"
of all phrases?
It's like a warning to myself.
- A warning?
- Yes.
"You never know when you might die."
"So live your life without regrets."
Something like that.
But what's that for?
Didn't you just pick this up somewhere?
Yes, it was snapped.
Well, it grew roots.
What?
I thought it would wither soon.
I think it's time
to take it out of the glass.
If I move it into a pot
and take good care of it, it'll grow well.
Here you go.
"Time to take it out"?
By the way, roomie.
- Yes?
- So, are you living without any regrets?
Why would you do that?
If something happened to you…
Gosh.
You suddenly cut all contact with us.
Sorry, Yujeong. I'm in a hurry right now.
It's really valuable to me,
so I have to find it.
It might be "just some pen,"
but I have to find it.
I think it's time
to take it out of the glass.
Chan, do you remember
how I said I felt like
I was surrounded by walls?
I suddenly found myself
unable to sketch anything,
and I had no energy.
I just wanted to give up on everything.
But when I first held the pen
you gave to me for my birthday,
I was suddenly able to draw something.
And I won first place
in the contest with it.
I would have run away
if I hadn't gotten such great results.
Excuse me.
So you saved me.
Thanks to you and this pen,
I realized how much I love my job.
It's a really precious pen to me.
- "Haran" is engraved on the lid.
- Thank you.
I'll draw lots of amazing clothes
and become a great designer.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry, but we have to go home now.
Right. I'm sorry.
If you ever find it,
can you contact me through this number?
So, are you living
without any regrets?
No.
I think I'll have a lot of regrets later.
Then what should you do
to not have regrets?
I want someone
to have joy in their life.
Instead of their bleak life now,
I want it to be vibrant, like before.
I lived like that thanks to her.
Then you can give her that joy.
I'd love to,
but I'm not sure if I have the right.
I don't think you need rights
to want someone to be happy,
as long as you're sincere about it.
- Hello? Did you find--
-  You're still there, right?
Are you there?
I have something to tell you.
No, I'm…
I guess you haven't found it yet.
Well…
I'm sorry. I was rude earlier.
Hang on…
"Let's live so I won't have any regrets
when they close my coffin."
That's my life motto.
But I thought I'd have regrets.
That's why I came here.
I didn't want that to happen.
I return to the US in three months,
and I probably won't come back to Korea.
Why are you telling me this?
I want to meddle in each other's affairs,
feel indebted,
and have fun together with you, Ms. Song.
What are you saying?
Let's not think about the past or future.
Let's just have fun
until I head back.
Just until next spring.
Let's have fun like we're on a picnic.
But I'm really curious.
Who is this person you want to be happy?
I was trying to die…
And I almost died.
But she brought me back twice.
A grateful disruption
that made me live again.
Is it okay if I start being
really nice to you from now on?
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
I don't think
we'll ever be friends.
Someone who's "talking" to a guy
is home at this hour?
I can't even go to the cafe
I love the most because of you!
I don't need any new variables.
A lot of them
just wither and die.
I'll move out
so we don't have to see each other again.
I'll be gone
once our contract is over in three months.
I'd like to step away
from this collaboration project.
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Translated by Juyoung Park