IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
CHARACTERS, EVENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND PLACES IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
Mom, don't go.
Let me come with you!
Mom…
Let me keep this, Dad.
Dad…
You shouldn't accept kids
without their parents' permission!
- I…
- Come with me.
Okay.
Dad! Dad!
I promise not to draw anymore, so…
So please let me stay in Korea.
EPISODE 3
I'll see you. Excuse me.
Are you using this room by yourself?
No, I have a roommate,
but he's traveling right now.
Do you want a drink?
Father…
That's just…
How long are you going to keep doing this?
What more do I have to do
to make you stop?
I kept forcing myself to hang on,
but I couldn't find
any reason to keep going,
so I eventually decided to end it all.
But then she disturbed me really loudly.
Ran
CHAN, CHAN, CHAN!
Oh…
The pen you sent me
for my birthday…
I used it to draw a design,
and it won in our company contest!
- Let's go!
-  It won?
Thank you so much!
You know,
you're my savior.
"You're…
my savior."
And that disruption
gave me an opportunity.
An opportunity to live again.
Ran
DARN IT!
Oh, gosh. They said it's a fake.
That Gold-something that helps you sleep.
I heard there's no proof.
I should've looked into it
before telling you.
Why did it suddenly get so lively?
It's like music to wake you up.
I'm so sorry.
Shocking news.
I was eating lunch with my teammates,
and there was…
dun dun, eggplant in it.
Gross.
Eggplant?
It's all mushy and squishy,
and it's neon-colored. Yuck!
The taste of a neon alien.
Mmm.
A neon alien…
I laughed properly for the first time
thanks to her.
I used to be trapped in a tiny world,
and it grew wider because of her.
But that person
who laughed and shone so brightly…
keeps crying now.
She keeps hiding.
I want to do the same for her now
and help her live joyfully again.
Because she was a grateful disruption
that made me live again.
Is it okay if I start being
really nice to you from now on?
No,
you can't.
What?
Why?
Oh, right.
I just want to repay you for what you did.
If it's because of those clothes,
it's fine.
I have no intention
of getting close to anyone.
What if there's a time limit?
I…
I just meant…
We can be friends while I'm in Korea.
Just for three months.
We'll keep seeing each other
at work and at SHIM.
So…
"Let's live so I won't have any regrets."
You said that was your motto.
"Let's not get close to anyone.
Then nothing will happen."
That's my motto.
I'll get along with you very well
as a colleague.
But I will never get close
to you personally.
A three-month trial!
You know, like free trials
in apps and games.
There's nothing to lose.
You can use me as a friend
when you're bored
or a misunderstanding for Ms. Kim.
Just try me out as a free trial.
As soon as the three months is over,
I'll disappear without a trace.
All right, fine.
You really don't want to be friends?
No.
Okay. I understand.
Then, I'll make you want
to become my friend.
- Excuse me?
- Mmm.
I hope you get better soon.
What…
HERBAL TEA
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Haran.
Geez. Are you a bear?
You're sleeping in the cave now?
I fell asleep.
Come downstairs.
I have something to announce.
First of all, thank you
for gathering early in the morning.
Please understand,
since I'm a busy high school senior.
I'm sleepy. Just get to the point, please.
Okay, I will.
I'm going to get married.
Mmm. You're always planning things,
but aren't you planning way too far ahead?
No, I want to get married in a few months.
- With whom?
- My boyfriend.
What do you mean?
How can you just get married…
Wait a minute.
I trust you,
but this is really sudden,
so I'm asking just in case.
- Are you…
- Don't be ridiculous.
We've been dating purely
without crossing the line.
Don't even think about it.
Tell me. Who is he?
I've known him since elementary school.
Cha Yougyum.
He's in our school's baseball team.
He should focus on baseball
instead of seducing our innocent Hadam.
He's an innocent guy
who only thinks about baseball and me.
I'm the one who suggested marriage.
Fine, let's say you get married.
How will you make a living?
He's joining the Major League.
He's joining the New York Comets.
It was on the news.
The Comets?
So are you saying
you'll give up your studies
and go to the US with him?
No, I'm going to medical school here
like I planned.
I want us to get married
so I won't feel anxious when he's away.
Things won't change much right away.
She planned everything already.
Hey, Hadam.
You don't know much about life yet, so--
Wait.
Let me meet him first.
Grandma!
All right.
He's in Jeju Island for a competition,
so I'll bring him home after.
Okay. We'll discuss this after I meet him.
I have to go study now,
so I'll see you later.
Song Hadam.
Hey. How…
Haran. Sis!
Shouldn't you say something
as the eldest sister?
Grandma said she'll discuss it
after meeting him.
Go get ready for work.
What?
How are they all so relaxed
when a teenager said
she's getting married?
Mom, Dad. Isn't this crazy?
Then, I'll make you want
to become my friend.
I'll make you want
What is he trying to do?
Do you have a meeting here?
No, I just wanted to get everyone coffee.
Coffee? Nice!
I'll be back in a second.
Oh. Ms. Song, what are you doing?
It's nothing.
Mmm.
This is good.
Where's Ms. Song?
She disappears at 12 on the dot.
Is she Lunch Cinderella or what?
Where is she even going?
Does she think I'll get curious about her?
Since you're here, have lunch with us.
Sorry, I'll pass today.
Next time. Enjoy your lunch.
Genius.
Are you visiting, too?
Aww.
I can't go to SHIM for a while.
I'll see you later.
Ugh...
No way.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'll order the same one for you.
Okay. Let's run the meeting
with Lafayette like this.
Is there anything else? If that's it…
I want to say something.
Go on.
I want to be excluded
from the animation collaboration.
Why?
Well, I don't know much about animation,
and I don't think I'm skilled enough--
Stop.
That's a long excuse.
Prove yourself instead.
Just do it, no matter what.
That's it for today.
Thank you.
Mr. Park. Oh…
Is she not here?
Do you need to see her?
It's nothing.
I'll head upstairs.
All right.
Ah.
- I'm heading out for a bit!
- Okay.
He just got here. Where is he going?
Mr. Park, I'm going upstairs!
Mr. Park, I'm heading out!
- Where are you going?
- Just buying something!
- Good boy. Wait.
-  I'm going upstairs!
-  Is it broken?
- Did you break something?
No, it's fine.
I'm going upstairs.
Genius, do you know why he's so busy?
- Yes, this is Nana Atelier--
-  Help me.
Hayeong?
It's 39,000 won.
I'll transfer the money.
It's fine.
It's okay. Eat as much as you want.
Here.
YUMMY SNACK BAR
Okay.
Then I'll treat you next time.
Here. Have one.
- It's fine--
- Come on. Try it.
I mean, no one carries around
cash these days.
I was about to transfer the money,
but I left my phone
at the office.
So I borrowed the owner's phone
and called,
hoping someone would pick up at work.
And, wow, the man
who always goes home last
picked up and saved me.
Applause.
Hang on.
Hey, Chaewon.
A blind date?
Okay, send me his profile.
Okay.
Someone saw my photo
and asked my friend
to set us up on a date.
He said I'm his type.
I always end up just being friends
with guys on blind dates.
But this time, it might be different.
He's handsome, right?
"Cha Min."
Even his name is nice.
What do you think, Mr. Yeon?
I'm not so sure.
You're not so sure?
Mmm. He looks okay.
Thank you.
Bye!
-  Come again next time!
-  Okay.
Right, my phone!
Bye!
CHARACTER "WON"
I want to be excluded
from the animation collaboration.
Did they argue?
Hang on.
No…
I'm going on a blind date.
Okay.
Were you two deceiving me?
What?
You're seeing someone,
but you're at home on a weekend?
You were lying to me, weren't you?
We weren't lying.
Didn't you say you were meeting him today?
What?
I… Gosh, it's time to go.
We can head out together.
See you later.
Bye!
That's suspicious.
Is it really true?
Hayeong, why do you keep doing this?
Shh! This is for your sake.
Mr. Yoon won't be
the only one on Grandma's list.
Just spend some time outside.
You can go to Genius' coffee shop.
I can't go there.
- Maybe I should go to the office.
- No.
Don't you know Grandma?
I bet she checks all the entrance records.
Hang in there, okay?
Bye!
Mr. Cha? Hi.
Darn it.
I have nowhere to go.
The course was so tough today.
Gosh.
There's a large variety.
Then I'll make you want
to become my friend.
I'll make you want
Geez.
You ran around a lot today,
so this is on me today.
So have anything you want.
I'm going to have
something expensive.
Who are you?
What? I…
Ah.  I have a girlfriend.
No, it's not that.
Sorry. I'll just sit here for a second.
You were amazing, Mr. Seonu.
How were you so good on your first day?
I was just doing my best
not to fall behind.
Number 26, your order's ready.
You can have this.
Number 26, your salad is ready.
Number 26?
Number 26, your order is ready.
It's only 5:00 p.m.
Tsk.
You're good!
You're so good!
- Right?
-  You're amazing!
Then I'll make you want
to become my friend.
I'll make you want
What is he doing here?
I want to do it, too.
-  You're so good.
-  I want to do it.
I want to do it, too!
- Oh no.
I'm sorry!
Where do I go?
Where did she go?
I'm sorry!
Then, I'll make you want
to become my friend.
Again?
Oh? Ms. Song!
It's nice being neighbors.
I was going to call you to give you this.
Aren't they pretty?
Green tangerine, lemon, beet…
They're good for…
Hey, you're not coughing.
I'm sorry, but I have to go…
I have to go. Sorry.
Watch the traffic lights!
Are you okay?
Uh… Why were you in such a hurry?
Are you hurt?
Let me see.
Wait.
Sorry, sir.
We should go to a hospital.
It's fine.
No, it's not. You hurt your hand,
and you're a designer.
I'm sorry.
- Let's go get you treated.
- Why did you…
I told you I have no intention
of getting close to you.
It makes me uncomfortable
when you act like we're close.
It may have sounded weird since I'm a guy,
but I didn't mean anything like that--
Whether you're a guy or not,
I don't want to get close.
I can't even go to the cafe
I love the most because of you, and…
I can't keep avoiding you
in the same neighborhood,
so let me be frank.
I'm really sorry,
but I'm a bit weird.
I feel at ease
only if nothing happens in my life.
I hate people entering my life,
and I hate my daily routine
getting disturbed.
I…
I don't need any variables in my life.
Please.
I understand. I get it.
I'll just stand quietly next to you,
so let's go to the hospital.
Your wrist's swollen.
Please.
Uh… It's a Grade 1 sprain.
There's some irritation
to the soft tissue,
so try not to move your wrist too much
for the next two weeks.
The nurse will treat you.
All right. Thank you.
- Just a moment, please.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Come out when you're done.
I'll be waiting outside.
Do I have to keep this on?
My family's going to worry.
You can switch to a brace
and take it off from time to time.
Wearing it for too long
will slow down natural healing,
so check your condition for a few days
and take it off if there's no pain.
Okay.
Number 26, your salad is ready.
I can't even go to the cafe
I love the most because of you, and…
I'm sorry.
I didn't think what I said
bothered you that much.
If I was an uncomfortable variable,
I'm really sorry.
Oh…
So just come to SHIM whenever you want.
It would be a shame
not to be able to go there.
I'll move out.
And walk around the neighborhood
as you want.
I'll leave so we won't
run into each other.
Just give me a few days.
And at work,
I'll pretend nothing happened.
I promise to never create
any variables for you…
or bother you again.
I…
Oh. Sorry, sir. She's getting in.
Go on.
SHIM
Hmm?
Mr. Park, hi.
Hey there.
Sorry for calling you.
You've been coming here every day
for seven years,
so I've been worried
since you haven't come in a while.
Are you sick or anything?
I'm just busy with work.
I'll be back once it's settled.
Yes.
I'm here!
You're late.
You had dinner, right?
Of course.
I enjoyed the stew you cooked for me.
How are you such a good cook?
What about your medicine?
I thought I'd feel safer
if there was someone with me.
And he's adorable.
He's a really good man.
I'll move out.
Of course, I took my medicine.
I get a harsh scolding
from someone named Chan
if I don't take them.
Oh?
This guy must be
going through a transplant shock.
A transplant shock?
When plants are suddenly
put in a different environment…
they go into shock,
thinking, "Where am I"?
Just like humans.
They need time to adjust
to an unexpected variable.
A variable…
What if… they can't adjust?
A lot of them just wither
and die in the end.
It's a pity.
I should clean up.
Wait, I'll do it.
I said I'd kick you out if you do this.
It's my job to do that.
I love cleaning windows.
It's a habit of mine.
My gosh.
All right…
I can't even go to the cafe
I love the most because of you, and…
Come to SHIM whenever you want.
I'll move out.
Mr. Park.
How can you be so adorable?
I feel like I've suddenly gotten a son.
Thank you for being here.
Oh, right.
Weren't you about to say something to me?
I…
I'll clean up here,
so you can go to bed.
All right.
And…
sleep tight.
Okay.
- Good night.
Oh, my.
Tsk.
cafe SHIM
I should have just left her be.
It wasn't my business.
Good work, everyone.
Go, Cheongsol!
-  Great work.
-  Great job.
Great job, everyone.
Why are you taking off your pants?
Take my uniform.
Cha Yougyum!
Where are you going?
I'm going to see Hadam!
Hey, Hadam.
I'll be there in three minutes.
It's a green light!
Don't run. I'm still on my way.
LAUNDRY DETERGENT, WHITE MUSK
What is it? Yougyum.
Cha Yougyum!
Hadam!
Song Hadam!
What's wrong, Hadam?
I heard a thud over the phone…
Oh… Sorry. Someone was in danger,
so I had to help them.
It's fine if you're okay.
Is that person okay?
Yes, thankfully.
I promise not to worry you again.
I'm really sorry.
You must have been angry.
No, I like you even more now.
You're so kind.
Grandma told me to bring you home.
Hmm?
My heart's going to explode already.
What do I wear? A suit?
Our school uniform?
Not my baseball uniform.
Should I do my hair?
I should get new socks, and…
First, let's eat something.
I'm hungry
after all that running.
Okay.
Ah.
But do you really think
we can get married before I go?
Yougyum, did you ever see me
failing to carry out a plan?
- No.
- We just have to stick to my plan.
You're so cool.
The game was tough, wasn't it?
It wasn't that tough,
but I feel like I aged 10 years
from missing you so much.
I aged 20 years.
Here. Hang on.
Wait.
Now, this drawing…
will turn into real candy.
- No way.
- That's nonsense.
I mean it.
All right… Mmm.
Look.
- Where did they come from?
- What was that?
They're real.
They're real candy.
Take them. Take them.
These actually are real.
-  How did you do that?
-  Unbelievable.
Hi.
This is some kind of trick, right?
Chan, tell me how you did it.
I want to show my friends.
-  Okay.
- "Chan"?
I'll send a video to our group chat.
Yes!
Right, Chan. We need a revenge match.
- "Group chat"?
-  Let's go bowling again.
Sure. Anytime.
- I want to join, too!
- Me too. Me too.
-  Are you sure?
-  This will be fun.
How will we divide teams?
-  Our teams?
-  Well…
♪ Flip your hands ♪
-  What?
-  What is that?
Let's be friends while I'm in Korea.
Can I be really nice to you?
Sure. Of course.
Of course.
I really wanted to get close to you.
- Sure.
- Yes, sure. I'd love that.
No, you can't.
Whether it's a guy or not,
I have no intention
of getting close to anyone.
Rock, paper…
Okay, rock.
- One, two, three.
-  Okay!
-  This is a revenge match.
-  We won.
Did I overreact
when he asked everyone to be friends?
Then let's select some
dancheong references that will suit Won
and put together a few rough drafts.
Sure.
I'm visiting some palaces
for some research tomorrow.
I'll take a lot of photos.
- Really?
- Yes.
You're going too, right?
- Me?
- Yes, you.
Shouldn't you do something
to show me results?
Well, I have a fabric meeting tomorrow,
- and I have to go to the factory--
- Send Raemee.
Go with him. It's for work.
You can bring Ms. Song with you, right?
Well…
Then can I go to the palaces instead?
Ms. Song can go to the factory…
I would love to go to the factory.
I'll go there, and Ms. Song can go
to the palaces.
Okay. Then let's gather
at our next meeting.
Ms. Kim, when should I go
to the factory tomorrow?
If you feel uneasy,
I'll go on a different date.
You can tell Ms. Kim--
No, let's go. It's for work.
Right. It's for work.
Then I'll text you the details.
And I'm sorry,
but give me some time to move out.
I haven't told Mr. Park yet.
Then I'll see you tomorrow.
I…
Yes. I'm heading to the Lafayette meeting.
I'll call you after.
-  Oh, gosh!
-  What? What is it?
Oh, my gosh!
-  What is it?
-  What's with those flowers?
I received them.
What?
Your date treated you to lunch
and gave you flowers?
Hang on, aren't these ranunculus flowers?
They mean "You're beautiful."
Am I beautiful?
Geez. What's with you?
Are you dating? It doesn't suit you.
Not yet, but we'll meet often.
His workplace is nearby.
So I won't be able to have lunch
with you guys for a while.
-  I'm so jealous.
-  Congratulations!
-  When are you meeting again?
-  Tomorrow.
-  No way.
-  I'm so jealous.
Just to confirm,
do you want to tweak the details
on the Lafayette coat line one more time?
Yes. If you don't mind, we'd appreciate
pushing the delivery back a bit.
I got a boyfriend.
- What do you think?
- Let me see.
- He's so handsome.
- Isn't he?
- What does he do?
-  Let me see. Oh, my gosh.
Hello.
Do you know the meaning
of these ranunculus flowers?
I don't know.
"You're beautiful."
What?
Thank you.
You said you couldn't come today.
Surprise.
He's handsome, right?
"Cha Min." Even his name is nice.
I got these for you.
- What?
- Did you eat?
Mr. Yeon,
would one more week be okay with you?
Oh, yes.
Would you like some coffee?
Thank you.
Hey, you look nice.
It's been a while
since I wore a hanbok.
SINGPUNGNU
Wow, it's so cool.
This is going to be awkward.
You've got to be kidding me.
You're here.
Your outfit…
Ah. The fee is free if we wear a hanbok.
If you want,
there's a rental shop over there…
No, it's completely fine.
All right.
- Let's go, then.
- Okay.
Wow. Aren't they beautiful?
Thanks to the dancheong,
the wood doesn't rot in the rain
and is protected from pests.
Isn't it awesome?
Mmm.
It's just basic knowledge.
I'd like to brag,
but I studied that in advance.
I like showing off my knowledge.
This is my bucket list for Korea.
I'd feel upset if I didn't do all these.
I don't know whether I'll be back
in a decade or two,
or maybe never again.
Wow, hanbok looks so cool.
Can I take a picture?
Of course, why not?
Okay. Guys, come on.
- Okay.
- Kimchi.
Kimchi.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
Have a great day.
Wow, man, it looks good.
Can we take a photo with you, too?
One, two, three.
Thank you.
-  Thank you.
- Thank you. Thank you so much.
-  Have a nice day.
- You too.
Bye.
Ah, sorry,
I wore this to break the ice,
but I didn't expect this.
My clothes are in the locker,
so I'll get changed.
It's the king!
Ice breaking…
Ran!
Huh?
BONGSUDANG
Hmm?
Where did she go?
Did she go to the restroom?
Huh?
She left her phone here?
Where in the world is she?
What…
Ms. Song!
You just disappeared.
What is it?
Let's go. We have to work.
What's wrong?
- It's nothing.
- I…
I know you hate others meddling,
but let me meddle just this once.
What's wrong? I'm honestly worried.
Then, let's sit for a moment.
My legs…
Let's sit for a while.
I heard a voice.
Ran!
Someone called my name,
so I went to look.
Ran!
KIM RAN
- I'll try it first.
- Okay.
But her voice
was so similar to my mom's.
Ran, come here.
It sounded like
my mom was actually calling me,
so I burst into tears.
Mom.
Ran, Ran.
My mom always called me like that.
-  I like this song!
-  Mmm?
It's Hadam's favorite song.
It is.
Hadam, do you want
to say hi to your sisters?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Hi!
-  Hi.
-  They look so excited.
Mom.
Dad.
Dad…
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
Mom!
Mom, get up! Mom!
Please!
- Mom!
- Dad.
Dad!
Help us!
They said the driver
suddenly had a cardiac arrest.
Both my parents died on the spot,
right in front of me.
I know she wasn't calling me,
and that I was mistaken,
but when I heard her voice,
I think I felt happy for a split second.
I know that sounds strange.
Well, you felt like someone you miss
called your name.
Chan.
I love you.
I love you, Chan.
It's not strange at all.
Ah…
I guess I was showing off again.
I'm sorry.
What?
Oh. It's fine.
I was almost done looking around.
I'm really sorry
for lashing out at you until now.
You did nothing wrong,
but I was so harsh on you.
And those fruit syrups last time…
I'm really sorry.
No, it's all my fault.
I shouldn't have said all that stuff
about being friends.
I'm sorry.
Look, you're doing it again.
I'm the one who's weird.
I keep making other people apologize
when I'm the one who's sorry.
I know I'm being rude and cruel,
and I want to change,
but I don't know how.
Getting close to someone
is really difficult…
No,
it's scary for me.
Losing someone you care about
without warning
is already painful enough…
...but it happened to me again…
so cruelly.
So I run away before it happens.
Because I feel like I'll crumble
if that happens again.
If no one is special to me,
then at least nothing bad will happen.
At first, I put up walls
to protect myself,
but now, I feel like
I'm trapped behind them.
Darn it. I must be crazy.
What am I doing?
You're so strange.
Me?
As soon as the three months is over,
I'll disappear without a trace.
Maybe it's because you'll leave soon.
Hm.
Huh?
That's beautiful.
I should take photos.
Huh? My bag.
I left my bag behind.
I'll go and get it…
Wait. What are you doing?
- What?
- Don't you need your bag, too?
My bag! Oh, gosh!
Come on.
I also just got off work.
Oh.
You're coming here?
Sure, let's meet up.
But, Mr. Cha, are you walking here?
Wow, that's so close. I'll see you in 10--
Ms. Kim wants you in her office.
Me? Um…
Oh. Sorry, but can you wait--
She wants to see you immediately.
And it will take a while.
Why?
I'm sorry, something came up.
I don't think we can meet today.
I'll call you later. Bye.
Why is she asking for me?
You'll know when you get there.
Did I do something wrong?
Excuse me.
I heard you were…
looking for me…
Where is she?
Mmm… Then I'll refer to the dancheong
we saw today and…
- Hey, Donggu.
- Hey!
Were you practicing soccer?
- Yes. But, Chan…
- Yes?
This thing you did with the ball.
Can you show us again?
Again?
Hmm.
Since my dear Donggu is asking,
- of course, I'll do it for you.
- Yes!
Watch.
Here.
- You're so good. Wow!
- You're amazing.
You're like Son Heungmin!
Nice, Donggu.
But my shoes aren't comfy,
and I'm with someone today,
- so that's it for today.
-  Okay.
Here you go.
- See you later.
-  Okay.
Bye.
- Bye.
-  Bye.
Bye.
Let's go have pizza!
He's Kim Donggu.
He lives in the neighborhood.
We started talking and grew close.
We really clicked.
Hang on.
It's Je Raemee.
It's about our bowling game.
You really are a human capybara.
A capybara?
The animal that looks like a huge rat?
Well… I've never heard
that I look like a rat before.
Oh. I just meant how you get close
to everyone around you.
Look it up. You're exactly the same.
Anyway, thanks for everything today.
Let's head home now.
I'll get going.
Let me make it clear
since you seem to have misunderstood.
It's true that I want
to get close to everyone.
But I meant something else
when I asked us to be friends.
I wanted to show you…
that there's another way.
At first, I was curious
why you were standing
in front of that winter painting
by yourself.
And while working with you
and watching you,
I thought that perhaps…
you thought the person standing alone
in that painting was you.
So I know it's not my place,
but I wanted to show you something…
that someone else showed me before.
You know, I used to go to bed
every night as a child
hoping that day would be the last.
But I kept waking up,
and I lived like a corpse…
He's so weird.
Welcome him.
No, he's a crazy guy.
…with no hope, expression, or color.
Then when I truly thought
it didn't matter if I died
and decided to end everything…
...someone suddenly talked to me.
Purely by coincidence.
"You're…
my savior."
Congratulations, and…
you…
saved me as well.
That coincidence made me stop,
and my daily life
started changing as well.
I finally got the sketch sample
for my design.
Make some noise!
It's all thanks to this pen.
The words that person said to me
made me smile.
Thank you for helping me
not give up on what I love.
For giving me a reason to keep going.
For the first time,
I started looking forward to the next day.
And…
I wanted to find a reason to keep going...
...thanks to that person
who kept reaching out and talking to me.
So… you can overcome it.
Once you know how,
you'll be able to escape on your own.
I learned it through that person,
so I wanted to show you, too.
I've also been trapped
in a long winter all by myself.
Is his name Mong?
You're so cute, Mong.
Let's take a picture.
I can't hear on this side.
I wanted to get close
because you reminded me of my past.
I'm sorry
if I made you uncomfortable.
Three. Hey, Mong.
Look at the camera.
- But I guess that doesn't matter.
- One, two, three.
Excuse me!
What?
What is it?
Take this.
Oh…
You didn't get to drink your favorite milk
because of me.
Is your suggestion still valid?
What?
Hang on, I'll go over there.
No, I'll go.
Sorry, I didn't hear you.
What did you say?
And what's with this milk?
Is it still valid?
What?
Oh. The expiration date?
Not the milk.
I mean… being friends.
The three-month trial.
Is that still valid?
I'd like to learn.
Can you show me?
You said someone showed you
how to escape from winter.
Uh…
I guess I'm too late.
I understand.
I was so cruel to you.
I'm so pathetic,
going back and forth like this.
I'm just curious
whether I can change as well.
And I thought it would be okay
if there's a time limit.
Never mind. Just forget--
It's valid.
It's still valid.
Ah…
It's valid…
Well, I…
The nurse told me
that if I keep this on for too long,
I wouldn't be able to heal naturally.
So I thought
I shouldn't stay trapped
behind my own barriers…
I'm saying this because I…
Then, it's okay
to be really nice to you now, right?
Just three months.
A trial period.
I'll do my best to learn, too.
Okay.
Then let's do this.
It'll be like we're on a spring picnic.
Let's have fun.
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
It was my first time
hearing that sound.
What if there is still
an empty spot in your memories
that you're not aware of?
I told you a secret,
so next time it's your turn.
It seemed like
she might have dementia.
So please…
Keep this a secret for now.
It can't be, right?
You have a crush
on Ms. Song, don't you?
"That person"?
I…
...shouldn't have asked you for a ride.
As long as she becomes happy,
I don't care what happens.
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Translated by Juyoung Park