IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
CHARACTERS, EVENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND PLACES IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
I found you.
This is bad.
Why are you…
I'm just copying you.
I have a habit of copying other people.
-  But I can't breathe…
- Oh.
Sorry.
You said you hug people
you're happy to see.
EPISODE 7
We're here.
Sir?
Yes?
Can you open the trunk?
Just keep riding this to SHIM.
Mr. Park will be waiting.
Ah.
Yes, Mr. Yeon.
Producer Ben?
He just informed me
that the collaboration project
will resume.
Huh?
The animation team
will return to Korea soon.
All right. That's good.
My roommate!
Oh. Mr. Park!
Mr. Park.
How have you been?
Sorry, I couldn't call you.
You're here, so it's fine.
Why are you standing out here in the cold?
You didn't know when I'd get here.
I just came out 10 seconds ago.
Goodness. But look at you…
You must have been through a lot.
You look so gaunt.
Do I?
That's awful.
I should get prettier now.
You didn't forget your meds, right?
And your cardiac enzyme levels?
It's cold. Let's go inside.
Genius, Chan is here. Come on in.
- It's cold.
- Are you running away?
Mr. Park!
Genius!
Genius.
Hey, Genius.
Aren't you going to show me your face?
Hey, Grouchy.
You were waiting for Chan the whole time.
Are you protesting?
Leave him.
He's sour because you left
without telling him.
Go upstairs. You must be tired.
Oh… Yes, Mr. Park. Come in.
Oh?
Genius.
Want to sleep with me today?
Hmm?
Dogs should sleep at this hour.
Me?
I have a lot on my mind.
Genius, you know
that Haran should become happy, right?
That's all I wanted for her,
but what do I do now?
I want her to be happy beside me,
and I want her to be happy because of me.
I keep getting greedy.
IF IT'S OKAY WITH YOU, YOU CAN TALK TO ME
The fact that I was fake,
and the reason I became a fake…
The fact that I lived
while he died from that accident…
I keep wanting to do as I want
as if I'm clueless to all that.
Until I go back,
if I play dumb and be greedy,
would that be wrong?
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Here's today's dress code.
Comfy shoes and warm clothes.
See you later.
I can't travel too far today.
CLOSED DUE TO PERSONAL REASONS
Oh?
Hmm?
Mr. Park…
- Oh! Ms. Song.
- Ms. Song.
- Hey.
- Hello.
What are you all doing…
Ben, when did you get here?
Have you been well?
I visited as soon as I arrived,
and now I'm trapped.
We came when we saw Seunggyu's photo
in our group chat.
I wanted to get the coffee
you bought us last time,
and I saw that Chan was here.
As soon as I saw the photo,
I rushed over with my sheet mask still on.
Things worked out,
so he's staying for two months.
Isn't that great?
Right…
Let's play.
Oh, I gave them to Genius as a gift.
If he presses the buttons,
we can communicate.
I have soccer class,
so I'll be back later.
- Bye.
-  Bye, Donggu.
Bye.
- See you later.
- Ms. Song, sit down.
Right.
We'll need some wine for a welcome party.
Roomie, please get the wine glasses.
Sure.
Mom, I'm going home late today!
Raemee, you live with your mother?
Not alone?
Can I help with anything?
What? Oh…
Ah. It's okay. Sit down.
Please let us clean up.
Please.
The host should clean up.
Just come have some coffee next time.
-  Okay.
-  All right.
-  Then, we'll come have coffee.
-  Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Still, shouldn't at least one of us
stay back and help clean up?
We're going for another round,
so you can help out here, Lightweight.
- Me?
- Yes, you. Song Haran.
- The lightweight.
- Ah.
Then I'll stay and help too…
Come on. You'll just break the cups.
We'll come back next time. Bye.
- See you next time.
- Okay, bye.
-  I should--
-  Let's go.
My gosh.
I didn't expect them
to all swarm in here.
Yeah.
Sorry. We're going to drink this later.
But it's suddenly so quiet
with all of them gone.
Right. It was pretty noisy in here.
But, Ms. Song--
I love you.
Genius, you shouldn't just
keep pressing those.
What I meant to say is…
I love you.
Has he not been trained yet?
I was trying to say
that I thought you'd be startled
to see everyone here,
so I sent you a message.
Oh. I see.
I'm so full.
I'm going to take a walk with Genius.
You can clean up the rest, right?
Sure. Ms. Song and I--
I love you.
Oops.
My mistake.
See you later. Let's go.
Let's clean this up, then.
You got it on your sleeve.
It'll get stained
if you don't wash it off.
I'll go get changed.
Training on the weekend?
I'm wasting my youth.
Oh? It's Song Hadam.
Oh? It's Cha Yougyum.
Hi.
I'm Kim Seokhyeon from Class 1.
I've been interested in you,
but I don't have to give up
because of Yougyum now.
Can I have your number?
Hey, what is he saying?
Did you two break up?
Cha Yougyum,
are you just going to watch?
If you don't come until I count to three,
I'm giving him my number.
One, two…
All right. I'll give it to you.
Text me.
You got her number.
-  What's this?
-  What?
Please call me if you see her.
If you ever see my mother,
please give me a call.
MISSING ELDERLY WITH DEMENTIA
Kim Nabong.
Hey, Manjae.
Park Genius.
Genius, how have you been?
Were you taking a walk?
Yes, this is a good place to work out.
- I walk a few laps every day.
- No way.
I walk him every day here, too.
Well, I guess we wouldn't have
recognized each other until now.
We can be walking buddies from now on.
Hey.
I think he needs to poop.
He has his own poop area over there.
- Gosh.
- Go and let him poop.
Okay, I'll see you later.
Hey, Genius! Slow down.
All right. Goodness.
Slow down. Okay.
What was she doing here?
- Are you sick or anything?
- I was just visiting a friend there.
MISSING ELDERLY WITH DEMENTIA
Is that you, Yougyum?
Hello.
Why are you wearing glasses?
I almost didn't recognize you.
My eyes are swollen.
How swollen can they be?
My goodness.
They really are incredibly puffy.
How did your eyes get like…
Are you crying?
I had a fight with Hadam,
and it feels like
my whole world just fell apart.
How do I live from now on, Ms. Kim?
Follow me.
What? Where…
Fighting won't make the world fall apart.
It only exhausts you.
Eat up.
I don't have an appetite.
To me, Hadam is my whole world
and my whole universe…
You're out. Just break up with Hadam.
- What?
- I'm not letting a guy
who bawls after one fight
about the world falling apart
date my granddaughter.
How will you survive the big leagues
with that mentality?
You're out.
No…
I'll eat.
Too hot!
I'm only weak when it comes to Hadam.
I push myself hard when I'm training.
I'm the ruthless Cha Yougyum.
Right. At your age, you think the world
falls apart with the smallest things.
I did, too.
But once you go through
something really serious,
you'll realize
that the issues you thought were huge
were actually just tiny specks.
And you'll regret not facing
those issues head-on back then.
You'll think, "Why was I such a coward?"
Anyway, there are dozens of more serious
problems waiting for you in life.
So stop being weak.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I was absorbed in my own issues.
Ah. What about your checkup?
Something came up at work,
so I rescheduled.
I got scolded
for disappearing from the hospital.
I learned that abalones contain ta…
Ta…
Taurine.
They contain taurine,
which helps with cognitive function.
All right. Give me all the abalones.
I still have a lot to do,
so I have to stay strong.
You eat up, too.
You need the energy to make up with Hadam.
Right. Energy.
Gosh, that's hot.
Mr. Seonu.
Mr. Seonu, there's someone calling you.
Someone keeps calling…
Is he not here?
I'm sorry.
Right.
What is it?
I…
Someone kept calling,
so it seemed important.
- I'm sorry.
- Wait.
Yes?
I mean…
We shouldn't do it here…
- I mean…
- No, I…
- Why are you turning off the lights?
- You…
You're the one who turned them off.
With your back.
Oh. My back…
You've got something on your lips.
Crumbs or something.
It was the crackers…
But why did you close your eyes?
Honestly, anyone would have
misunderstood that situation.
You held my hand and hugged me yesterday,
so I thought…
You thought what?
I just thought you were moving fast
since you're from the States.
This is getting weird.
Stop teasing me.
I wasn't teasing you.
I just thought I saw the old you.
It was cute.
My old self?
What do you mean?
I think I heard you used to be
much more cheerful.
From who?
Was it Hayeong?
Anyway,
I really wasn't teasing you.
I'm sorry.
Ah. I forgot to give you this.
A welcome drink.
I almost took back my word
about being nice to you.
Can we do it now?
Do what?
I meant…
The photos.
Let's check your homework.
You have a talent for this.
Oh, my gosh.
You liar.
You said there were just 10 shots.
Hmm? My Destinations List…
It's yours. I took a photo of it.
- When did you take this?
- What?
This!
I just took this for fun
when I was bored…
Wow. That's not fair.
You promised to do that with me.
That doesn't count. I'm confiscating this.
Everything you did alone is invalid.
We'll do everything together.
Geez.
But what's that last thing
you scribbled out?
Mmm.
I thought it would be impossible,
so I scribbled it out…
but it might be possible now.
It's a secret, though.
Why did you tell me
to wear comfy shoes today?
I thought we'd just walk around a bit
without any specific plans.
Just go wherever the wind takes us?
I wanted to try that with you.
Go somewhere and try things
without thinking of what happens next.
No,
that may have messed things up.
If things get messed up, we can fix them.
It's the same for knots.
Sometimes they seem impossible to undo,
but if you loosen one strand at a time,
they'll unravel.
You can find a way,
no matter how impossible it seems.
Shall we do it tomorrow?
Try going wherever the wind takes us.
Sorry. Next time.
I have to go somewhere far
with my family tomorrow.
Far? Where?
Ah.
THE LATE SONG JUNHO
THE LATE MIN HYEWON
Dad's favorite crab stew.
Remember when Dad chipped his tooth
eating crab stew?
Right, he visited the dentist
for a long time after that.
Hadam, wait.
Put the castella on Mom's favorite dish.
Wow. That's a real antique.
We've had that since I was a baby.
Whenever we were in a bad mood,
she gave us snacks on this.
Mom always said,
"When you're feeling down,
having sweets on a pretty dish
- will make you feel sparkly."
- Sparkly.
-  Let's greet them now.
-  Okay.
This might be
my last time coming here.
If, by any chance,
I start acting too strange,
just call me home to you quickly.
I don't want to embarrass myself
in front of them.
Okay, Hyewon?
Okay, Junho?
I will take you all home safely.
Let's go.
Ah…
My bad feelings are never wrong.
I forgot my phone.
- I'm riding with Haran.
- Eh?
You're really going to betray me? Hey!
She's so cold.
♪ I dream a little bit of red alone ♪
No, I had it then.
And then, Grandma…
I greeted Mom and Dad,
then I got up, and my phone…
Where did I leave it?
-  I'm really sorry.
- Eh?
Who's that?
I'm sorry.
Excuse me, that's my parents' grave.
I think you came to the wrong…
Mr. Yeon?
Why are you…
Are you crying?
Oh… No.
You are. Your eyes are red.
People would think
you're their son…
Thank you.
How pretty.
You don't need to do this
for Parents' Day.
You always welcome me
and pack me side dishes.
I'm a bit awkward
with expressing my feelings,
but I really wanted to thank you today.
Goodness. Thank you.
My friends brag about their sons.
I can brag to them that I got
carnations from my son, too.
Since we're all dressed up,
how about a family photo?
That sounds great.
- Let's take a photo over there.
- Okay.
- Oh, sure.
-  Let's take a photo.
- All right.
-  Mr. Yeon.
- Let's take it together.
- Come on, Mr. Yeon.
- Join us.
- Come here.
It's okay.
It's a family photo. Come here.
Sir, can you take a photo of us?
All right.
One, two, three.
Mom, Dad.
Our former chauffeur, Mr. Yeon,
became our COO.
He's a core figure now,
like me in our household.
So send him lots of energy.
Thank you for taking care
of our parents, too.
I'm sorry.
Why do you keep saying sorry?
I…
I'm really sorry.
Oh. I dropped my phone somewhere.
Can you call my number?
Where is it?
I hear it. Where is it?
Is it here? Is it here?
Is it here?
I…
It's coming from your butt.
My butt?
Darn it. I came all the way
back up here for nothing.
Since we met here,
should we go eat something?
Eat?
I promised you I'd treat you last time.
It was 39,000 won last time,
so I'll treat you to up to 80,000 won.
There's an amazing
oxtail soup place nearby.
What do you say?
Let's go!
It's okay…
No, it's not okay.
Have we eaten together before?
Who do you normally
have lunch with at work?
What do you usually do on the weekend?
Wait.
Your hand.
You might slip
since you're wearing heels.
It's fine, I can wipe them.
Be careful.
You really are considerate.
You always look out for our family.
Why did he cry, though?
How was your visit to your parents?
Hey.
Whose message
is making you smile like that?
What?
What took you so long?
Weren't you looking for your phone?
I was hungry, so I got some oxtail soup.
I'm so full.
That's good.
Hey, Hayeong.
Did you ever tell Mr. Seonu about my past?
Like how I was different before
or something like that?
Like how you used to be
really bubbly and friendly?
Something like that.
Mmm? No, I didn't…
Wait, did I?
I'm 29 now.
My memory isn't so good…
- But why do you ask?
- He spoke as if he knew me.
Really?
But are you two really close?
Mr. Seonu, Ms. Song…
You're so formal.
Then what should I call him?
You're the same age.
Use your first names.
You can just say, "Hey, Haran. Hey, Chan…"
I should go shower.
Why did you suddenly stop?
Well…
You used to call him Chan.
Your old boyfriend, Hyeokchan.
I just realized their names were similar.
Oh…
Right. I didn't think about that.
Make…
MAKE HER HAPPY AGAIN, NO MATTER WHAT!
Their names… were similar.
All right…
What was that?
EMPTY SPOT IN MEMORY - FOURTH
A waste container…
and that sound again.
The lab…
The sound of metal…
The explosion.
The missing gap
started with that sound, too.
And the second memory
had that sound as well.
And the third memory
had the same sound.
Why did those missing memories
start with the sound of her bracelet?
Sorry, Ran.
My professor's calling.
I'll call you back later.
Hey, Sujin. You're here?
Why are they all connected to this person?
SUJIN?
Sujin?
This is Cha Sujin.
I've arrived in Korea.
I'll head to the hospital straight away.
It's my fault for causing
the misunderstanding.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about everything.
I'm sorry about everything…
I'll give it to you. Text me.
Cha Yougyum?
Hey, what are you doing here?
What are you doing? Give it.
Are you okay?
Oh?
That's Mom's dish.
Song Hadam.
Don't you know we never use that?
There are dozens of dishes. Why did you--
Then why are you making a fuss
over one dish?
Hey. Why are you talking like that?
Don't you know what that dish is?
- It's Mom's--
- I don't!
I don't know.
I'm the only one who doesn't know.
I can hardly even remember
Mom and Dad's voices or faces,
so how would I know
how special that stupid dish is?
I want to remember, too.
I want to miss them too,
but I can't remember.
Whenever you talk about Mom and Dad,
I feel like I don't belong.
I feel like I'm the only one
who wasn't their daughter.
- Hey…
- I was only six.
I…
I didn't know anything…
Hadam.
We're sorry.
I'm sorry, Hadam.
I'm going to school.
I'm really sorry…
I broke Mom's dish.
You said you have a meeting.
Go get ready. I'll clean this.
Okay, thanks.
We'll talk to Hadam when she comes home.
Hey, Hadam.
Let me see your hand. Where is it?
Gosh.
I just got this at a convenience store.
It's just a temporary fix,
so go to the nurse's office, okay?
But what do we do
about Mom's dish?
That dish isn't the problem.
You hurt your hand
when the CSAT is coming up.
I'm ambidextrous.
You are? Since when?
I practiced using my left hand
because my hand hurt
when I studied too long.
But I was a natural at it.
Our baby sister.
You take after Mom.
Mom?
Mom was ambidextrous.
We wondered
where her genes went.
I guess they all went to you.
Did you want to find out
what she meant by feeling sparkly?
Is that why you took it out?
Huh?
Didn't you want to eat sweets from it
and feel better?
Hadam.
Let's talk more about Mom and Dad
from now on.
I was actually worried
we'd forget about them when time passed.
But I guess we can tell
our smart baby sister about them
as a backup file.
I do have a good memory.
How long are you going to follow me?
I'm escorting you properly today,
all the way to school.
Aren't you the least bit aware
of your current condition?
- Are you embarrassed of me?
- A bit.
Hadam!
Oh? It's Yeongju.
Bye.
Jeong Yeongju!
Go to the nurse's office!
You'll catch a cold. Go home.
Bye!
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Let's go on a walk.
-  Genius.
-  Let's go on a walk.
You seem to be abusing that.
And you're such a chatterbox.
Watch your mouth, okay?
-  Let's play.
- Okay.
Let's go on a walk.
Mr. Park, I'll go on a run with Genius.
Don't you have a meeting?
I still have some time.
Right.
Something arrived from the US
while you were away.
I forgot about it.
It's in the counter cabinet.
Ah.
Mmm?
Hello?
What was that message?
Why is it a secret from Ms. Song?
Ah.
Okay, I'll keep it a secret. All right.
What did you receive?
It's nothing special.
I'll clean up. Go. He's so eager to leave.
- Genius, let's go. Come on.
- Go on.
Let's go, Genius.
Let's run!
What is this?
"Newbury Street, Boston…"
What was the package?
-  Hello, Mr. Park.
- Oh!
-  Hello.
- Welcome. Come in.
You mean there will be
more parts on Korea?
Yes, the interim feedback
was really positive.
The response to Won's outfit
was incredible.
The cloud motif, Korean color palette,
dancheong, and the hanbok panel.
Wow. Everyone was impressed
by the details that represented Korea.
The most Korean things
are what end up being popular worldwide!
So we'd like to request another outfit
once we get the revised script,
if that's okay with you…
Don't be silly. Of course, that's okay.
If it will help with the project,
anything's fine.
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
Right. We just have to push
straight ahead now.
Let's pick up the pace again.
How about a round of applause?
Everybody, clap!
Plans? Is it about work?
Mmm…
I think it's a secret.
There should at least be
one pen that you like.
I guess she didn't find
any that she liked.
What?
It's nothing.
Bye, then.
Bye.
See you later. I'll text you.
Who is he meeting, though?
Then are your parents
in LA as well?
Oh… No.
My mother passed away when I was nine.
My father's probably teaching in Daejeon.
We don't really keep in touch.
Well…
Every family has its own issues.
Go on and eat.
Thank you.
Right.
Will you stay in LA again
once the collaboration is over?
Yes, I believe so. But why do you ask?
Should I establish a branch in LA
and send her there?
Excuse me?
Ah. I was just talking to myself.
But why aren't you eating? Hmm?
I wanted to treat you to something
after all that trouble at headquarters.
Eat up.
Why did you only ask for me?
Ben went through a lot, too.
- Who?
- You know, with the…
Oh… Producer Ben?
Well,
I'm sure his in-laws
will take good care of him.
Just think of this as a meal
from your in-laws.
In-laws?
I'm just saying…
Darn it. I can't do this.
I'm sorry.
Beating around the bush
isn't really my style,
so let me be blunt.
Oh. Sure, be blunt…
I mean, feel free to say what you want.
How much do you know about Haran's past?
Quite a lot.
Did you hear about her losing her parents?
I heard.
And losing her boyfriend seven years ago?
I know that, too.
Even after losing her parents,
she stayed strong,
but that incident left Haran
trapped in winter,
just like you said.
Haran's not eating.
Again?
She's not eating or sleeping.
She'll die at this rate, Grandma.
She no longer smiled
or showed any expressions…
- Eat a sausage, Hadam.
- …even in front of her sisters,
and even in front of me,
when we used to be like friends.
Just don't go.
What if something happens to you outside?
It happened to Mom and Dad.
So don't go, okay?
It's okay.
Haran, it's all right. It's okay.
If I let her stay buried
in all that anxiety,
I felt like I would lose her.
Come out.
I'm not eating.
Just leave me alone.
Get up. Right now.
I knew I had to do whatever I could
to pull her out.
You're working here from now on.
I'll give you a month
to organize the storage room.
Why are you doing this?
I don't want to. I'm leaving.
That's an order.
If you want to keep sleeping
under my roof,
do as I say.
I had to grow cold,
and I had to stay strong.
I had to save her first.
Come out.
She could hardly move an inch,
but she finally started moving
little by little,
and her eyes started shining.
She was living again,
little by little.
She's alive now.
Come to work on the third floor
starting tomorrow.
You'll be the rookie assistant
for Design Team 1, 2, and 3.
I was relieved at the fact
that she held on once more
without crumbling down.
But then, she changed.
- This is an apology for taking a leave.
-  Thank you.
She started smiling again recently.
I know I met a great person.
I feel grateful.
She learned how to cry again, too.
Mr. Seonu.
Why would you…
Thank you.
I wanted to speak to you today
as Haran's grandmother,
not the head of the atelier.
Thank you so much for letting me see Haran
crying and laughing again.
No, I…
I didn't do anything…
They say that if it's fate,
you'll meet
no matter how far apart you are.
You came all the way here.
I don't think
you were meant to just work here.
Thanks to you,
I'll be able to leave in peace.
Are you going somewhere?
Well,
I'm planning to stay in France
after I retire.
If you stay by Haran's side,
I won't be that worried about her.
Ah.
But, Ms. Kim,
I may not be as good for her
as you believe.
My heart is throbbing,
and tears keep flowing.
My heart
hurts more than my foot.
Do you think it's serious?
Cut the drama and go to a bigger hospital.
I can't treat that properly here.
I'm sure it's just because
I trained hard these days.
Just give me something for the bruise.
Can you move aside?
Huh? Oh…
Can I help you with anything?
Why did Yougyum come here?
Is he hurt?
That's personal information.
Is she sick or something?
She has to stay healthy.
Mmm.
Hey, you came back.
I finished my first appointment,
so I'm here for the next one with you.
Seriously, what are we doing here?
You'll see.
KIM SEON POTTERY EXHIBITION
Pottery exhibition?
No way.
-  Oh. You're here.
- Grandma!
Goodness.
-  I missed you.
- I feel neglected lately.
-  How are you?
- It's okay.
Have you been well?
You should have told me
we were seeing her.
It's not my fault. She told me not to.
If I'd known, I would've gotten flowers--
That's why I told him to keep it secret.
And why would I need flowers
when such a precious guest is here?
Are you two dating?
You little brat.
You should've told me
you were going to the States.
- I was worried when I couldn't reach you.
- I told you.
- I suddenly had to go--
- Still, you should have told her.
Right?
Wow. You're teaming up on me?
That's so mean. I'm leaving.
Come and look around.
And get the cup you made last time.
It looks so beautiful.
Really? I'm so excited.
My hands look pretty, don't they?
No one's coming for me?
I want to be doted on, too!
Oh. This one looks a bit different.
The lines seem pretty rough,
but it's so cool.
The lines are where I mended them.
I put together the shattered pieces.
You can put shattered pieces together?
You know lacquer trees, right?
The sap acts as a natural adhesive.
Once I attach the pieces
and let them dry carefully…
Then they become a new art piece.
They shatter, get hurt, then heal,
and in the process, they gain depth.
It's similar to people, right?
Oh… Would it be possible
to restore a broken plate?
It's a dish my mom treasured,
but they don't sell it anymore.
Bring it over sometime.
I'll do my best to restore it.
Ms. Kim.
You're here. Hang on.
Look around.
We shouldn't meet like this anymore.
I just get lonely.
Shouldn't you go and greet them?
They seem like her friends.
Chan, come and say hi.
Okay.
I'll be back soon.
Oh. The kid who visited during vacation?
- Yes.
- You've gotten so handsome!
Thank you.
I turned out pretty well, didn't I?
Oh my. Look how cheeky he's gotten.
You used to call him Chan.
Your old boyfriend, Hyeokchan.
Seonu Chan?
Seonu…
Chan.
He's shameless, like me.
Oh? There's no one here.
Everyone went home.
Is Hayeong not here?
We were going to discuss
the new material today.
She was feeble all day,
unlike her usual self,
and went home early.
Try calling her.
Bye, then.
Ms. Song.
Hello?
Are you a friend of hers?
She's been drinking and sleeping nonstop.
You should come and take her home.
Ah.
Good morning.
When did I come to work, though?
You got off work. This is a wine bar.
I'll take you home.
What? To where? Home?
No, I can't.
I can't face Hadam.
I should have told her more
about Mom and Dad.
I should have known how she felt.
I should have known
so no one would get hurt.
Hadam was only six at the time.
But she was in the car with Mom and Dad
during…
the accident…
It's cold.
It's just that you were crying…
It's just drool.
Let's go.
All right.
The GPS…
Wait.
Seongsu-dong?
Was I mistaken?
Did you go to Seongsu-dong last Thursday?
You were with Grandma, right?
- No. I'll start the car.
- Wait.
I saw Grandma that day.
I'm sure I saw her crying.
She was crying?
So you did go to Seongsu-dong, right?
That woke me right up.
Is something going on?
What is it?
I'm sorry, but just let this go for now.
Please.
MISSING ELDERLY WITH DEMENTIA
You can't stop looking at it.
Are you that impressed?
Are you sure I really made this?
Did you make it again
because it was a mess?
Of course not.
I'd love to have dinner with you,
but I'm meeting the people who helped me.
I'll stay in Seoul for a few days,
so let's have a meal sometime.
And bring your mother's dish then.
All right.
Her mother's dish? What do you mean?
Why are you curious about everything?
Grandma, don't do that in front of her.
Your cheeks are so squishy.
The weather's so nice.
How about dinner--
Sorry, but you should go home first.
- I'll see you later.
- Where are you going?
Ms. Song!
Being overly polite
will hurt her feelings.
But I should at least give her
some hand lotion.
Huh?
Oh? Did she leave?
Hang on.
- She's not here?
- Did she leave?
We can come back…
Hmm?
Dad. Dad!
What more do I have to do
to make you stop?
Let's just go.
- Wait, I…
-  Chan.
You're back.
He had business nearby
and dropped by to greet me
when he saw the sign.
It's been a while.
There was
an international conference nearby.
Your school…
No, your former school
and some other schools--
That's enough.
I'm not even curious.
- Let's go.
- How are you?
How is your condition these days?
Are you going somewhere?
Why are you taking your passport?
I don't want to stay in Korea.
You made a good decision.
You received enough treatment,
so you can return to school--
I'm not…
going back to school.
I'm not studying anymore.
What? You've already wasted so much time.
Are you going to give up everything
just because of some accident?
Stop acting like a child
and be reasonable.
You should finish your master's
and move on to a PhD program…
Do you not see me?
I'm covered in burn scars,
and I can't hear on one side.
- You call that "some accident"?
- It's in the past.
Blaming it won't change anything.
Enough with the pathetic self-pity!
I get it now.
This is why she left you.
It was because of you.
She didn't just leave,
you made her leave!
I'll leave too.
I'll live my own life,
so just think
that your stupid, obedient son…
died…
in that explosion.
Why are you acting like this?
You never worried about me before.
I saw you here earlier,
so I left,
in case you'd feel uncomfortable.
I didn't know you'd come back.
You're right.
I do feel uncomfortable.
So if you ever see me anywhere again,
don't even say hi.
Chan, don't do this!
Are you going to keep acting
like you're strangers?
Since you've met… Hmm?
Give her the flowers. I'm leaving.
- Chan, let's talk--
- Stop!
Chan! Don't. Stop.
Let him go! Let go of him!
Let him go.
Don't do this!
Chan, let him go!
Go. Everyone, just go!
Oh, dear. Let me see.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I didn't even notice. I'm really fine.
Grandma, take care of her for me.
Wait…
He won't be able…
to face you right now.
Darn it…
I'll be able to fix the shattered pottery,
but I can't do anything
about their relationship.
They've had a deep rift for a long time.
You can take it.
Sorry, hang on.
Yes, Director.
Yes.
Of course.
PROFESSOR SUNWOO SEOK
"Science University"?
From the smell,
it seemed like
diluted sodium hypochlorite solution.
Because of the diffraction of sunlight,
the cloud particles…
Petrichor.
Your former school
and some other schools…
I guess
you majored in that field.
It seems like
you majored in engineering.
He never tells me
what he did before entering CalArts.
I lived like a corpse.
Laundry…
Is there any laundry?
What happened to the pen you always use?
I lost it, and I never found it.
I'll just use a new one now.
It's nothing special.
Wait.
Why is this pen here?
Huh? Genius.
Mr. Seonu.
Oh? You're in here.
Yes, I was collecting laundry.
But why did you come upstairs?
Sorry, I came without asking.
I just wanted to see Mr. Seonu.
I have something to give him.
He hasn't come home yet.
Let's go. I'll make you coffee.
- Okay.
- All right.
What happened?
Did you get hurt?
It's just a small scratch.
Let's go on a walk.
We didn't get to go
on a walk today.
You can go. I don't need coffee.
I'll wait here for Mr. Seonu.
Are you sure?
Hey, Haran…
About before…
No, never mind.
I'll be back soon.
Wait a moment.
cafe SHIM
Why isn't he coming?
Oh?
You're here.
Where have you been this whole…
Let's go inside. You look exhausted.
I'm sorry.
For leaving like that
and for hurting you.
It's okay.
I'm totally fine.
It's all my fault.
I was being selfish,
trying to stay by your side.
What are you saying?
Just make me some tea
instead of saying such nonsense.
I've been thinking…
I don't think it's a good idea
for us to be this close, so--
You saw this, right?
Wow. I was so surprised when I saw it.
These lines are where she mended
the broken pieces.
Don't they make this look more beautiful?
It seems admirable, too.
- Ms. Song.
- To me…
you're these lines.
Ms. Song!
The first snow…
Vapor trails…
Wow, it's beautiful.
Jamsugyo…
And a certain name…
They were all sad memories,
so I thought I'd never get over them.
But I found myself feeling okay,
thanks to someone
who covered them with good memories.
But you say something like that
over a tiny scratch?
It's a relief I met you here.
Thanks to you, I found a way,
so this time, why don't you try it…
with your father?
That's impossible.
You remember when we first met, right?
I was cold and avoided you.
I thought it was impossible too.
But I guess there's no such thing
as never in a relationship.
Aren't I a good example of that?
I picked this up at the exhibit.
He must wear this all the time.
It's in the photo as well.
I've never seen it before.
Really?
The drawing here looks similar
to the one I saw at your grandma's place.
He must have kept wearing it
even when it was broken.
I bought that for him a long time ago
at a stationary store
for Parents' Day.
Maybe…
he wanted to mend things.
He's been wearing this broken watch
the whole time.
I should give you some time alone.
Thank you.
I have a habit
of hugging people I want to comfort.
That's my thing.
Why do you keep copying me?
I wish we'd met earlier.
Then we could've gotten close faster,
and I would've been nicer first.
I would have at least given you a hug
when you were scared to open your eyes.
You saved me as well.
You already did that for me.
Genius, you know
that Haran should become happy, right?
The fact that I lived
while he died from that accident…
Her boyfriend died back then.
He went to study in Boston,
but he suddenly died.
"Newbury Street, Boston?"
I've only
received things from you.
I should be really nice to you
from now on.
Then…
I might end up liking you even more.
It's okay…
if you like me more.
If I like you more…
I might get more greedy.
It's okay
if you get more greedy.
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Why do you keep saying
it's greedy to like me?
-  You mean it, right?
-  Yes.
How about letting time
with your dad start moving again?
The past is the past,
and what matters is the time you have now.
There's nothing wrong with her, right?
What on earth is happening to you?
Seonu Chan found this pen for you.
And this is a lucky charm.
No way. What is this?
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Translated by Juyoung Park