"Love Like a Bike"
(Episode 1)
Excuse me, where does this path go?
Get off me.
Don't touch me!
Are you okay?
What's with the attitude?
Watch out!
Get away from me!
Mister? Are you alright?
Don't touch me!
Please calm down. I just...
Go away!
Where is he?
Sailom, what's wrong?
You don't look well.
I was hit by a bicycle.
What?! Hit by a bicycle?!
Damn, are you alright?
I'm fine. Don't worry.
Are you sure?
Oh, no!
What's wrong?
My…
necklace…
My necklace's gone!
I've found it!
Is this yours?
James, look at it.
Would he wear something like that?
Hey, we've been searching
for some time now.
Did the one who hit you take it?
Yeah, what does he look like?
Watch out!
He's a man.
Quite handsome.
Not like that. Remember what makes
him stand out? Something like…
protruding ears,
big eyes,
or small eyes?
Yes, I can remember!
Bicycle!
He rides a bicycle,
wearing a tight cycling suit!
Dude…
Most people ride bicycles in Pattaya.
Yep.
So, what's next?
Where is that doctor who treated my wife?!
- Please calm down, sir.
- Where is he?!
I'll talk to him.
Damn you! Did you tell
Duean to break up with me?!
Mr. Kong, please calm yourself down.
Why must I?! My wife has been
arguing with me since she met you!
I think you told her to break up with me!
That's the patient's decision.
Mr. Kong,
I want you to listen what she really wants.
You both might understand each other better.
Believe me.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
We're sorry for what happened.
Are you all okay? It's been
a tough day, but we'll get through it.
Do your best.
Isn't there any cake today?
Our baker recently
quit. We're really sorry.
Then I'll have coffee.
One hot Americano. Less sweet.
Certainly.
Hot Americano. Less sweet.
- I'll bring it over to your table.
- Thank you.
Did Nabnueng put the ring here, sweety?
Yes, Mom. He said he forgot the ring
around here, but I haven't found it.
Yeah, it's taking you a while.
Have you checked between the cushions?
Mom,
have you found it?
No, dear. Where did you put it?
I really don't know.
It isn't in my car or the bathroom.
Bro, I couldn't find it. What should we do?
It's okay if you can't find it, Looksoh.
Or… did you put it in your backpack?
Nope, I already checked it.
Maybe you missed somewhere.
Huh? What's this…
necklace?
Did you buy it for Yanin?
It's beautiful. Better than the ring.
Go for it, bro.
Yanin's gonna accept your proposal.
Thank you for remembering
I wanted to try this place.
- I have something to say.
Go ahead.
How long have we been together?
It's been a long time.
Since our student days.
I have something to say.
Consider it as bad luck.
But that necklace is expensive!
My mom gave it to me!
Relax. At least you weren't hurt.
This isn't good at all!
Come, let's have a toast.
Mister? Are you alright?
Don't touch me!
Please calm down. I just...
Go away!
Wait! That's my necklace.
Huh? Where?
Lemon. James. Call security for me.
You thief! Give it back!
Thief?
Please mind your language.
That necklace in your hand!
This necklace?
I saw you dropped it when we collided.
So, I took it.
I see. You admit you took it.
What? Wait, wait.
This is going too far. I shouted
for you, but you just ran away.
So, I kept it to return it to you.
So what?
Why didn't you give it to the police?
Just know that I'm not a thief.
Give my necklace back.
I'm returning it to you, and that's it.
Is there a problem here?
Don't touch me.
- Go away!
- What's wrong with you?!
- Are you okay, Sailom?
- Go away! Don't touch me!
- Take it easy.
- Get away from me!
Please step back. I'm a doctor.
Give him some space.
Everyone,
please step back.
A little bit more.
I'm a doctor. I'll help him.
Mister,
please calm yourself down.
Can you hear me?
If you can, let's try breathing together.
Just follow me. Breathe
in, deeply and slowly.
And breathe out, long and slow.
Gently now.
Now, place one hand...
right here on your stomach.
Feel it rise as you breathe in.
And feel it fall as you breathe out.
Just stay with your breath.
Don't tell me you're… a doctor.
Yes, I am.
Don't…
tell me that... you're a psychiatrist?
You're right.
I'm Nabnueng.
What's your name?
Sailom.
I see.
You handled that well for tonight.
If you feel overwhelmed,
please feel free to stop by my clinic.
At "Term Suk" (The Happiness) Clinic.
Thank you for your help,
Doctor.
Why was it okay when he touched my hand?
I have something to say.
Let's get married...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I do love you,
but… I just got a new job
and need to move to Vietnam.
Let's get everything sorted out
first and then we think about marriage.
Hey, I'll put lots of my photos here,
so you can always think of me.
How much longer? I'm in a hurry.
It's almost done. Please have a seat.
It's taking too long! I'll miss my trip!
I'll be as quick as possible.
- I'm in a bit of a hurry!
- Right away.
On this day last year, a Bangkok-Chiang Mai
flight crashed while landing.
And sadly, a child
under 10 died in that accident.
We're so sorry for the child's family.
Hey there.
Cheer up.
It's okay. Take your time.
Thank you.
This ship goes to Koh Larn!
All aboard!
Thank you. Please board the boat.
Ticket, please.
Pay your debt, Dindin.
Come on, I told you I'll pay soon.
Right now. Pay up.
I need to work now. I'll pay it later.
Trick me again and I'll kill you.
Don't you see there are customers?
Is this ticket for this boat?
Yes, sir. All aboard.
Oh, mister. Here's a giveaway hat.
Whoever has a ticket can
board the boat right away.
What?! He's gone?!
I told you to watch him! Damn it!
He's over there!
After him!
What the hell?!
Sorry, sorry.
Hey, what's up?
Can you cover for me and sing at the bar?
Fine, send me the time and place.
I can only go after the transfer. Bye.
Hey, wait...
Damn.
Where the hell is he?
What are we gonna do?
Should we wait at his bakery?
No need to go there. He's broke anyway.
Find and squeeze the money out of him. He
hasn't even paid the first month interest.
If the boss finds out, I'm dead.
Yeah, he must be around here somewhere.
Let's check over there.
Goddamn brat.
(Baker Needed. Urgent!)
Bakery, huh?
P'Nabnueng, wake up!
Mom calls you for lunch!
What's wrong?
P'Tawan, come and help me here!
P'Nabnueng looks terrible!
Look at him. P'Nabnueng
looks like death warmed over.
Are you okay, bro?
Gimme a sec to be sad.
Yanin doesn't love you, but we still do.
Sleep a bit more.
I'll get some fish from
the market and grill them.
Looksoh, ask Mom to get the stove ready.
Yep, I'll do it right away.
I'm gonna pass you.
Pass me if you can.
I beat you twice already.
Just zip it.
Do you think I'm stopping for you?
You're slow.
So what? Who threw
something at me this time?
- Are you okay, Sailom?
- Go away! Don't touch me!
You need to feel the game.
A little silence wouldn't kill you.
I think you're too slow, Lemon.
You two…
About last night…
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
But why were you like that last night?
Yeah, you can tell us your problems.
Thanks a lot…
but… I'm fine, really.
Sailom…
We understand if you don't want to tell us.
We just want to understand you better,
so we know what's okay and what's not.
Sorry.
I'm not ready to talk about it.
Hey, didn't you invite
us to eat? I'm starving.
When will you order some food?
Or should I eat your table's legs?
What's so funny? Order something.
Okay, I'll do it.
If you're in a hurry, do it yourself.
Fresh seafood here. Come and get it.
Live fish and crabs right here.
Want some, handsome?
How much for a kilo of squid?
300 baht per kilo. How many kilos?
- Is this all that's left?
- Yes, just three left.
- I'll take all three.
- Alright.
Anything else?
- Just squid.
- Alright.
Look at these squid.
Shellfish are fresh here.
Oh, captain.
How do you do?
Yes, I'm okay.
I heard you're not flying anymore.
Yes, I'm not.
How have you been?
After that day, my husband and I
moved here to Pattaya to run a business.
I'm truly sorry.
It's okay.
I'm not here to blame you.
Dear…
Look there.
The captain likes squid...
just like our daughter used to.
Thank you.
Here.
Thanks.
Hey.
Why are you spacing out?
It's nothing.
Where's Sky?
Working, maybe?
He's been busy lately.
Been out since this morning.
Meeting with customers.
Feel better, dear?
Yes, Mom.
That's life. Nothing's certain at all.
You're right.
Still heartbroken, bro?
Yep.
Now I get what it feels like to be dumped.
She's been stringing
you along all this time.
I know.
But when seeing it for myself...
I'm just lost.
Yeah… give it some time, doctor.
Even a psychiatrist needs his mom's care.
Look who's talking, Tawan.
Don't think I don't know.
It's okay to tell me if something's
upsetting you. Don't be shy.
What? I'm fine!
Yeah, right.
Alright, let's have a toast!
Okay, cheers!
Bottoms up, shall we?
- Are you sure, Mom?
- Look at your brother.
I'm sorry…
I couldn't help you at all.
Hey, Ben.
I almost got my ass kicked
by the debt collectors today.
They were hunting me down.
Didn't you say you
transfer the money today?
Don't give me that crap! I saw your IG!
You took a girl out for omakase!
Borrowing was easy for you.
Don't make returning it so damn hard.
Send me the money now,
or you'll deal with me.
Ben?
Hello?
You bastard.
Damn it!
Ouch! Who did this?!
Was it you?
What's your problem?
What the hell is wrong with you?
You brat.
Bastard.
You started it.
You want a piece of me?
What if I do?
Take this.
Fine.
Does it have to be this early, Mom?
Keeping busy is good. It'll help
take your mind off your heartbreak.
I'm not that heartbroken.
This is the best way.
Here, deliver this drink.
I've sent you the address.
It's not that far.
Yes, now hurry, or it'll get cold.
- Okay, Mom.
- See you.
How long will you be
at Chiangmai this time?
Maybe…
a week?
I'll buy sai oua for you.
Okay.
Have a safe trip, Dad.
Call me when you're there.
Of course.
Yes, Mom?
How's everything in
Pattaya? Are you doing okay?
I'm good, Mom.
You're alright staying by yourself?
Of course, Mom.
But…
Mom…
don't worry. I'm grown up now.
I can take care of myself.
Right. If there's something wrong,
you can call me anytime. Okay?
Alright.
I gotta go.
Okay. I love you, dear.
I love you too, Mom.
Hello!
"Love Like a Bike" delivery here.
Oh, doctor.
Oh, Sailom.
You're a doctor. Buy why…
are you delivering coffee?
Oh, it's my family's café.
I help out at the café after my day job.
Here's your coffee.
The payment's been processed.
Okay, thank you.
Go away! Don't touch me!
Why was it okay…
when he touched my hand?
Don't hurt me!
Mom, help me!
No!
Don't hurt me.
Get out!
Sailom.
It's okay.
Stay with me.
Breathe in deeply.
I'm… sorry.
It's totally fine.
Oh.
Sailom.
Put this shirt on quickly.
Thank you.
By the way, I ordered you new coffee.
I'll bring it over to you soon.
It's okay. I spilled it.
Well…
I'll wash and return your shirt later.
Don't worry. I can wash it myself.
Please, I insist.
It's totally fine.
It's really okay.
Don't you have other places to deliver?
There's no orders now.
Can I ask you a qquestion?
How many jobs do you have?
Not many. Just the clinic and the café.
Feel free to visit the café.
Coffee's on me.
I'll borrow your pen.
"This man can have everything for free.
From Doctor Nabnueng."
Thank you, doctor.
You're welcome.
Yes, Mom?
Nabnueng, can you
deliver another cup for me?
Right away, Mom.
I've got to go now.
Alright.
It reeks of coffee now.
Can I get this stain out?
Hey.
You can't be serious.
There are many places to go in Pattaya,
but you chose to come here?
Don't they have cafés in the US?
I just got back. Spoil me a little.
Don't you want to chill out on an island?
We can go later. The summer's long anyway.
Here's your receipt.
Thank you.
Are you on vacation?
I've never seen you before.
I'm a local, but this
is my first time here.
My friend just came back
from the US and took us here.
Did you read reviews from somewhere?
Not at all.
I only want to use this.
Here.
Oh…
you're P'Sailom, right?
P'Nabnueng mentioned you.
Everything's on the house today.
Just a cup of coffee is enough.
I can pay for the rest.
Don't worry.
P'Nabnueng said you all can eat for free.
Tell Doctor Nabnueng
that I say "thank you."
Isn't…
Doctor Nabnueng here?
He works at his clinic today.
It's not far from here.
I see…
Please stop by tomorrow.
We'll have baked goods again.
Alright.
Excuse me, can I have a menu?
Wait. Doctor Nabnueng?
Is he the guy who took your necklace?
When did you get close to him?
Come. Let's go somewhere else.
Let's split up here. I've
got something to do.
Wait…
What's this? You invited us here, then want
to leave, and now you've got something to do?
You're suspicious.
It's nothing much!
I just wanted you two to try coffee here.
How did you get that "name card?"
When did you get close to that doctor?
Didn't you two fight that night?
His name is Nabnueng!
I asked when you two get close.
Well…
not that close.
Yesterday, Doctor Nabnueng delivered
coffee to my house and I spilled it.
He gave me the card with his
signature to make up for it. That's all.
Really?!
Yep!
Do you like him?
Come on! I only just met him!
It's love at first sight.
I'm done talking with you guys.
I'm out of here.
What's next?
Let's just go home. Your house, my house.
- Come.
- Okay.
Mom, I have some gossip.
"This man can have everything for free.
From Doctor Nabnueng."
Oh, who's this?
He's P'Sailom from the US.
P'Nabnueng can finally move on.
- Isn't it too soon?
- Not at all.
I'd better text P'Nabnueng.
Mom,
when is the 'yummy treat' baker coming?
He'll be here soon.
Good afternoon, Mrs. Phailin.
Oh, Dindin. You're here.
I prepared the ingredients.
Let's get started.
Yes, right away.
Tawan! Come here!
What is it, Mom?!
You brat.
You started it.
You want a piece of me?
What if I do?
Good afternoon, P'Tawan.
Hello.
Do you have an appointment?
Ah, no... I don't.
I'm actually to see Dr.Nubnueng.
Oh,
he's out for field work today.
Field work?
Yes.
Sailom?
What brings you here?
Oh... I was just passing by.
What about you? What are you doing here?
I'm out doing field work
with the SWING Foundation.
Providing counseling for nightlife workers.
They deserve the same
protections as everyone else.
I see.
I thought you only saw
patients at the clinic.
I didn't expect to see you out here.
I just want to help out however I can.
Are you hungry?
Huh?
Hungry for what?
Hungry for dinner. Want to go grab a bite?
(Next Episode)
Take it slow, or you'll get drunk.
I'm fine, Doc.
I can handle this much.
This is my first time.
Didn't know it'd... feel this good.
Do you like it?
I do.
Seriously, have you ever even
baked before? I don't think you have.
If you're an expert, do it yourself.
Oh, no…
Don't tell me the Doctor…