(Previously) I agreed to the treatment
because I thought you could make me better.
But you refused to treat me yourself.
If you don't drink with me,
I'm cutting your pay.
Do whatever you want.
You two are quite something. The other
day you almost wrecked the kitchen.
When did you two become so close?
I'm thinking about quitting the host job.
I usually eat alone.
But... having you here
as a friend isn't bad either.
Even if I can't be your doctor,
I promise you.
I will do everything
in my power to help you get better.
Please, trust me.
"Love Like a Bike"
(Episode 5)
Here, this piece is perfect.
- Have one more.
- Thanks.
- Is that enough?
- I'll come back for more.
P'Doc,
thanks for inviting me to…
your family party.
Your family is...
quite big, isn't it?
You bet it is.
Actually, my siblings are
over there. That's Tawan.
Tawan!
Show your hand!
And that guy posing over there,
not sure if he's drunk yet,
is Sky.
And the youngest one is Looksoh.
But...
how come you and your siblings…
don't really look alike?
I knew you were going to ask.
Tawan, Sky, and I…
Mom adopted us when we were little.
Only Looksoh
is her own daughter.
That's so heartwarming.
Heartwarming?
We've been fighting since we were kids.
Sky!
You're asking for it!
I'm scared.
And what about him?
Is he P'Sky's boyfriend?
Oh, this is Nava.
We're just friends.
And Mr. Singer,
are you going to sing here tonight?
This “Mr. Singer?”
He's the pastry boy at my café.
Dindin.
Hi, Sailom.
Hey, Dindin.
Go grab some refills from the car.
Sure thing, old man.
- Does my shirt smell?
- Let me see.
- Hmm... smells like heaven.
- Wanna hear me singing?
Yeah.
Any song you can sing.
I'm just background noise.
Gonna be an extra one day.
I used to have a family like yours.
Used to?
What about now?
I'm on my own now.
How?
Well…
My dad was a funny guy,
and my mom was the kindest person.
Dad always said
he wanted me to live a happy life.
But...
how can you be happy without money?
True.
And why did they…?
A car accident.
I can be your family.
And...
what kind of
family would you be for me?
I…
Can be anything.
Whatever you want me to be.
A father figure,
a confidant,
a brother,
or even just a friend.
What about a boyfriend?
I want to know…
what it feels like to have one.
You've never had a boyfriend before?
I just work to make money.
Never had a single one.
So...
give me a kiss.
The vibe is just right.
But no “business kiss.”
That kiss was free of charge.
And this one...
a kiss between boyfriends.
Boyfriends kiss?
Uh-huh.
What are you doing?
Planning to take
leftovers home every day?
Geez... don't be so stingy.
What are you doing?
Cooking.
Know how to stir-fry?
What do you think?
Here.
Take this home, so your
grandma can have a warm meal.
Why are you so unusually nice today?
You want it or not? I'll just eat...
I want it!
Whoa…
I want it.
Thanks, old man.
Grandma, I'm home!
Oh, you're back?
Yeah. And I brought some curry too.
Here.
Let's eat.
Oh dear, I'm already full.
Let's save it for tomorrow.
- Alright?
- Please eat with me.
- But I just ate.
- Please? Just a little bit?
Alright.
- Just a bite or two then.
- A bite or two is perfect.
Let me help you unwrap these.
- Just a second, you must be starving.
- Yes, I am.
Let me get the plates ready.
Smells okay, I guess.
Give it back then.
No way. It smells amazing.
Thanks again.
Who do you live here with?
I live with my dad.
But he has businesses all over,
so he's rarely home.
Actually, he's never home.
Since I got back from the States,
I've barely seen his face.
Like last week,
he was working in Chiang Mai.
When he got back...
he had to fly
to Singapore for a meeting.
And now, he's in
Hat Yai for another project.
I'm not sure if he works this hard
because he wants to provide for me
or…
if he just doesn't want to see me.
Well...
my parents split up when I was a kid.
And back then,
I chose to stay with my mom.
Maybe my dad is still mad at me
because I didn't choose him.
So now, he's getting back at me.
The truth is...
I never wanted to choose at all.
Because no matter who I chose...
I would still being the one at fault.
But not choosing...
wasn't an option.
I'm sorry for
rambling on about my problems.
It's okay.
I'm right here,
and I'll listen to everything you say.
Grandma!
What's wrong, Grandma?
Hello.
Hello, Tawan!
Help me! My grandma collapsed!
Grandma!
Dindin.
Don't stress too much.
What if something happens to her?
Dindin.
Your grandma is going to be okay.
You can hold it.
My hand is free.
Welcome to Love Like a Bike.
Phailin.
Phailin,
I want to see Nabnueng.
Hello? What's up, Papp?
Sky! What the hell are you doing?
Are you quitting or staying?
Come talk to
Madam Amy and clear this up.
Alright, I'm coming in.
Where are you going?
To the club.
I need to clear things up.
I'll be back soon.
Clear things up?
About what?
About my resignation.
I want to settle everything.
Let me know what I can do to help you.
Be right back.
If you've decided to quit,
I won't hold you back.
A job like ours
requires your whole heart.
If your heart isn't in it anymore,
there's nothing I can do.
Good luck with everything, son.
Thank you so much, Madam,
for understanding.
I do. But leaving so suddenly
puts me in a tough spot.
Man pre-ordered 500 drinks,
and I've already accepted the payment.
Since you're here tonight,
could you work one last shift for me?
Madam, I just…
Please.
I will do it.
Good luck, son.
And thank you.
I heard you're quitting the host job.
Yes.
Is it because of that guy?
P'Man,
I know how you feel about me.
And I'm truly grateful
for everything you've done for me.
But I've…
never felt anything for you beyond...
a host and a customer.
What makes him better than me?
Why choose him?
He's not better than you,
and you're not better than him.
You're just different.
But you of all people should know
that love doesn't need a reason.
If this is your last night...
can you give me your all?
I will.
Are you really quitting?
Are you sure about this?
I'm not sure.
A host and a customer.
Is it really possible?
Customers and hosts are human beings.
We just have to give it a shot.
Alright. Do whatever makes you happy.
But if you ever get hurt,
I'm always here to open a bottle for you.
Thanks.
Hey, Nava. You still awake?
I miss you too.
I'll be there soon.
I'm heading out.
Clear this for me.
(Tanwarin Hospital)
Who was that?
Just an old friend.
Why didn't you pick up?
Don't feel like talking.
A morning kiss.
I've quit the club last night.
From now on,
I'm no longer “Sky the host.”
I'm just Sky...
your boyfriend.
So...
what's your plan now that you've quit?
For now?
Just resting.
I want to spend every
moment with you like this.
So sweet.
I do have a plan.
I want to go help with the family cafe.
Business hasn't been great lately.
I'm thinking of…
expanding the bike shop.
Instead of just repairs,
I'll turn it into a biggest hub
for bike parts in the neighborhood.
The biggest? That shop is tiny.
It's just a thought.
But you never know.
What about you? Any plan?
None.
Oh, wait…
What did you do before this?
I mean, what was your job?
I was in... production.
Really?
That's perfect.
Once I turn the shop into a big hub,
you can handle the production
and promote the café.
It'll help get our name out there.
By the way,
we could even turn the shop into a studio.
Why don't we open it together?
It'd be awesome.
Sky...
give me a kiss.
Can you kiss me...
like it's our last day together?
Where is this coming from?
Well…
nothing… lasts forever, right?
Eventually, everyone must part ways.
Why are you crying?
Because I'm so happy to be with you.
You're being dramatic.
Don't cry, okay?
See you soon.
It's raining over here.
Is it raining there too?
It's just a bit cloudy.
Please hurry up.
Hey,
don't catch all the fish in the sea.
Leave some for me.
See you.
Nabnueng! This is me!
Sailom...
It's been a long time, son.
Don't you dare tell anyone about this.
Or I'll kill your mother.
Oh, wow...
you've become much cuter than before.
Did you miss me?
I love you, Sailom.
Come and give Daddy a hug.
Sailom!
I'm so sorry
for not taking care of you all these years.
Back then,
I wasn't ready to be a mother.
So I gave you to Phailin
when we were nurses together,
then I went to start
a new life in Bangkok.
Can you forgive me?
I've never been angry with you.
I understand.
Everyone has their own reasons.
Thank you…
so much, son.
But there is something...
I need you to help me with.
Your grandmother has Meniere's disease.
It's not too serious,
but she needs to avoid stress
and get plenty of rest.
I'd like her to stay one more night
for observation, in case of emergency.
If everything looks good,
she can go home tomorrow afternoon.
Thank you, Doctor.
Are you feeling better?
Yeah.
Sorry for calling you last night.
I didn't know who else to turn to.
I get it.
Are you free tomorrow?
Why?
Look after my grandma for me.
What?
I have work in the morning.
I'm afraid she'll wake up alone
and get stressed again.
Fine.
Just tell me what your job is tomorrow.
I'll go do it for you.
You can take her home yourself.
You? Doing my job?
Can you handle it?
Looking down on me?
Nope.
Dindin.
Grandma.
How are you? Feeling better?
Oh, this is Tawan. He's my boss.
Hello, Grandma.
Hello. Thank you so much.
Sailom!
P'Doc, can you reach Sailom?
Not at all. I've been knocking,
but there's no answer.
Should we break in?
Or call the police?
James! Get a grip!
- Sailom!
Sailom!
Wait! I remember now.
The tree pot.
Found it!
Come, let's get inside.
Sailom!
- Found him?
- No. What about the backyard?
Yeah, let's go.
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
Mom, help me!
Sailom!
Sailom.
Don't come in.
Sailom, it's me.
- Sailom.
- No! Stay away from me!
I missed you, son.
Come give Daddy a hug.
No! No!
No! Don't hurt me! No!
Stay away!
- Come out! I'm your dad!
- No! No!
I am your dad!
No one can help you!
No! NO!!
Get away from me!
- Sailom, take it easy.
- No!
Get out!
Go away!
Sailom,
if you can hear me...
take a deep breath in.
And slowly breathe out.
Inhale deeply.
Exhale slowly.
Deep inhale.
Slow exhale.
Just stay calm, Sailom.
I'm right here.
Sailom,
I'm at your house now.
You're in your house.
And I'm here in your room with you.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
When you're ready,
slowly come out to me.
You're safe now.
Let's go with me, okay?
Tawan,
please take me to the toilet.
Of course.
Hey. Hey.
Boyfriend.
Oh...
Look who's here.
How did you know I was here?
Dindin told me.
Come on, let's go home.
I need to settle the tab.
No need. I already took care of it.
You're so sweet.
Let's go.
Can you walk?
Careful now.
Nava? What's wrong?
Nava. Nava.
My stomach hurts.
(Next Episode)
What's happening to Nava?
The patient's condition
has weakened so much.
Let's… try traveling abroad together.
If that's what you want,
you need to get better first.
Do you think I can't afford the bill?!
Is it a tradition to throw
a punch before we kiss?
The best form of healing is
rebuilding trust in humanity.
Is it going to be a burden
to be with a broken man like me?
In that case... do we try kissing?