(Previously) The view is beautiful.
It would be even better with a lover.
And… do you have one?
Just broke up with her. I proposed to her.
And she said she would work in Vietnam.
So, she denied me.
- When will you stop picking on me?
- Your banana cake is trash!
That's it!
Did you see him?!
He was trying to screw with me!
Nava, stop!
Ever thought? If you weren't like this,
you might've already been his boyfriend.
But I don't know how
he feels about me.
What made you decide
to seek treatment with me?
I want to get cured from this condition.
He doesn't seem ready at all.
"Love Like a Bike" (Episode 4)
(How are you doing?)
(You can tell me anything.)
(I'm sorry, P'Doc, )
(but I don't want to do this anymore.)
Thank you. See you next time.
(Come to my shop, or I'll cut your pay.)
What the hell is wrong with him?
You're wasted.
What do you want?
Nothing.
Can't I just want you to be here?
Just spit it out. I've got work to do.
Drink with me first.
Or else…
I'm cutting your pay.
What the hell is your problem?
I just want someone to drink with.
Go ahead and cut my pay.
I'm not drinking.
You…
You want a piece of me? Hmm?
Do whatever you want.
I just wanted someone to drink with.
Can't you stay and drink with me?
Oh, Auntie Phailin. Tawan, wake up.
It's okay. No need to wake him.
Let him sleep.
I just came to check if he was here.
He didn't pick up my calls,
and he didn't call back either.
He probably had his phone on silent.
But he's been here with me.
Not going anywhere.
I see.
You two are quite something.
The other day
you almost wrecked the kitchen.
When did you two become so close?
But it's good. Stay on good terms.
Now, get me a drink, dear.
On the rocks.
Coming right up, Ma'am.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Tawan might act tough on the outside,
not as gentle as his siblings.
But he's actually a very kind person.
If he ever does anything
to hurt your feelings,
please don't take it to heart.
Sometimes, he just doesn't know
how to show kindness to others.
I won't.
I don't mind it at all.
Thank you.
Please take care of Tawan.
Yes.
I'll take care of him, Auntie.
Thank you.
Come, lie down properly.
I went to therapy...
but it's not working.
Treatment doesn't work in just one go.
It takes time.
We're all rooting for you, man.
Come on, you can do this.
Look, there's your P'Doc.
P'Doc! Over here!
James, hold this for me.
What?
Sailom!
Where are you going?!
Please look after this for me.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
Something's up with those two.
It's so obvious.
You could see it from Pluto.
Now we have four bikes.
How can we practice cycling?
We wait.
Sailom, what's wrong?
Nothing!
Even if something was wrong,
why would you even care?!
Sailom, calm down and listen to me.
Can you tell me what happened?
Why did you decide to stop the treatment?
Whether I continue...
or not,
it's my business. Stay out of it.
But you told me before...
that you wanted to get better.
Are you afraid the treatment won't work?
If that's the case,
please trust me.
Once we start,
you will definitely recover.
Look at it like it was riding a bike.
If you have a clear destination,
you might face some
obstacles along the way.
But if you don't stop
riding and keep going,
you'll reach the finish line one day.
You have to be brave enough
to leave the past behind.
P'Doc...
I agreed to the treatment because
I thought you could make me better.
But you refused to treat me yourself.
If this treatment is like
riding a bike, just like you said.
Now,
you've cycled
far away and left me behind.
Doc.
P'Doc.
Hey.
Hey, Doctor!
- Yeah?
- Why are you spacing out?
Yeah, what's up with you?
I don't even know where to start.
You're acting weird.
Sailom wants me to be his doctor.
Then what's the problem?
Just treat him.
If only it were that simple.
It's just...
He thought of me
more than just doctor and patient.
What did you do?
I transferred his case
to another doctor.
I can't do it.
It's medical ethics.
But now he's furious
and refusing all treatment.
I'm at my wits' end.
Listen, Doc.
If he refuses treatment,
that's on him. It's his life.
But I want him to get better.
Because if he doesn't recover,
I don't see how he'll survive out there.
I don't want to see him suffer anymore.
Guys, listen.
When I said I wanted to quit
being a host, I meant it. I'm done.
Why? You've earned a lot from that.
Yeah.
Nah,
I feel like I found something
more important than money.
You dating someone?
I can't really say that I'm dating him yet.
I just want to prove to him
that he's the only one for me.
Damn...
I wanna see the face of the guy
who tamed the legendary Sky.
I met him at the club.
He's a client nothing like the others.
Get it? It's like...
- A client?
- Yeah.
Are you sure you want to date a client?
I don't know if it's a good idea or not.
All I know is...
I like him.
Thanks, man.
Wait a sec...
One loves his patient.
The other falls for a client.
And you say thanks?
What the heck?
It's simple, Tawan.
If you love someone,
you must let them know.
Don't leave them guessing
how they feel about you
or you feel about them.
Otherwise, that love
might turn into hate.
Hey! Are you lagging?
Why?
Got someone on your mind?
Tell us.
I do.
But I'm not into “talking.”
- I'm into “doing it.”
- Whoa, damn!
Which is your favourite position?
That's wicked.
It's them, Tawan!
Get'em!
Ouch!
Hold still, will you?
Then be more gentle, will you?
Man… you shouldn't have messed
with his girlfriend. You almost got killed.
How was I supposed to know?!
She said they were already over!
Gosh, you shouldn't have done that.
So what?
Stop moving. Let me fix your wound.
That stings!
Dammit! I wouldn't have helped you!
And who asked for your help?
I didn't ask for it!
Look at yourself!
And you're still cocky!
So what?!
Both of you, stop arguing!
Fine, fine!
But don't you dare tell Mom!
I don't want another lecture!
Deal. If we tell,
we're all dead anyway.
Whoever breaks it does
the dishes for a whole month!
Promise.
Cheers!
(Thanyawarin Hospital)
I'm thinking about quitting the host job.
Why?
I just... don't want to do it anymore.
How are your wounds? Still hurting?
A little.
Have you eaten yet?
Not yet.
Want to grab some food?
Aren't you still mad at me?
I am, but I'm hungry.
Thank you.
Here, the rice vermicelli.
- What did you order for yourself?
- Instant noodles.
No seasoning needed, I think.
None. This place is legit.
I must try.
Hmm. This is great.
I never thought of eating a meal
with you without alcohol.
It's nice.
What nice?
Just…
eating in peace,
no loud music,
no one bothering us,
and I don't have to
keep entertaining anyone.
I usually eat alone.
But... having you here as a friend
isn't bad either.
Wait... friend?
So we're friends now?
Yeah, of course.
Say “Ah.”
Eat this.
Feeding you as a friend.
Friend?
If you weren't my friend,
I wouldn't share my meatballs with you.
Then have this.
Liver.
If you weren't my friend,
you wouldn't get this either.
Like it?
Love it. How did you know I like liver?
You like it, huh?
And it's sweet.
And Nava,
let's go on the bike trip this Saturday.
Sure, I'm in.
It'll be much more fun if you're there.
What are you doing here?
Why?
Can't I come and watch you sing?
You can.
I'm heading back after this can.
Need to check on my grandma.
She's not well.
Mm-hmm.
If you love someone,
you must let them know.
Don't leave them guessing
how they feel about you
or you feel about them.
Otherwise, that love
might turn into hate.
Dindin,
are you coming on the bike trip with me?
I have to go anyway.
I'm your employee.
No... I mean, yeah, I know that.
What I meant was...
do you want to go biking with me?
Like riding right by my side.
If you want me by your side,
then I'll go.
If this treatment
is like riding a bike,
just like you said.
Now,
you've cycled far away
and left me behind.
Sailom!
Wait!
I'm sorry!
Sailom,
I know I let you down.
I failed you by not being your doctor.
But know this…
I never had any intention
of leaving you behind.
The reason I'm here today
is to apologize.
Even if I can't be your doctor,
I promise you.
I will do everything in my power
to help you get better.
Please, trust me.
Yes, P'Doc.
If therapy is like riding a bike,
are you ready to ride along with me?
Yes.
Let's do this together.
- Beautiful, isn't it?
- Yeah.
The view or the person?
The person.
I brought you some water.
Are you this kind to everyone?
Nope. Just you.
What's your name?
I'm Soda.
- And you?
- Lemon.
We're a good match. Lemon and Soda.
- Are you imagining things?
- No.
Haven't you ever had
a “Lemon Soda” drink?
And do you like it?
I love it.
Don't you?
I do.
Aren't you going to have some water?
I already did.
Drink it?
Nava…
look at you.
Can you get up? Come on.
Oh, my.
Look,
you're covered in sand.
Are you really okay?
I'm fine. Gotta sit down.
Thanks.
I didn't think... I'd make it this far.
Why? Are you exhausted?
Yes, I am.
But...
it feels good.
First time seeing this side of you.
Which side?
You know... the side that isn't a host.
The athlete side. The cyclist side.
And...
is it a good side?
Yeah... it's good.
Do you like it?
I do.
Like it how?
As a friend.
Then...
let's keep riding together like this.
Mm.
For as long as I can handle it.
Let's go.
Careful there.
Alright, everyone! It's time!
Now, it's time to head back!
And remember, this is very important!
Check your safety gear
and make sure everything is ready!
Alright! Let's go!
Whoa! Hey!
Are you okay?
You alright?
Let me go!
Whoa, calm down!
Go away!
What's wrong? I'm just trying to help.
- Don't touch me!
- Relax, I'm just helping.
Get away from me!
- Hey, take it...
- I said don't touch me!!
Tawan, move back!
Sailom.
I'm right here.
Can you hear me?
I understand you, Sailom.
Take a deep breath. Slowly...
Look into my eyes, okay?
Look at me.
Breathe in...
and breathe out slowly.
I'm sorry.
I'm… so sorry, P'Doc.
You don't have to apologize.
You did nothing wrong.
I'm right here with you.
Hey, Sailom.
Are you still stressing about
what happened at the bike trip?
Of course I am.
I totally ruined his trip.
Ruined it how? Everything went fine.
Everyone made it back home safely.
Nobody got hurt.
But they were all shocked because of me.
If it wasn't for my condition,
P'Doc's trip
wouldn't have been so disrupted.
You're overthinking it.
P'Doc didn't even say a word about it.
Or maybe he did,
but we didn't know?
If your mouth is so free,
just stuff it with this!
Damn you!
Ugh! What am I going to do?!
- Thank you for coming.
- Yes.
Thank you.
What can I get for you?
A cheesecake and a Thai tea, please.
A cheesecake and a Thai tea… and?
- A pink milk, please.
- Got it.
Wow, we're really busy today.
It's been non-stop
since the bike trip ended.
Oh, please help make some more desserts.
Sure thing. As soon as I
finish making this cup.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
Does the chain come off
when you're picking up speed?
I think it's an issue with the gears.
Please have a seat and wait.
Thank you.
You can wait over here.
Or if you'd like some coffee,
we have a café over there.
I think I'll wait at the café.
Certainly. Right this way.
How long will you stand there?
Help me fix these.
Stop posing already. Hurry up.
Fine.
Help me take this wheel off.
Hey, Tawan!
Can you edit a clip for our page?
Look at all these bikes around you.
Ever since your bike trip ended,
the shop's been flooded!
Forget about editing clips.
I don't even have time to breathe.
By the way,
how's that kid doing?
Which kid?
The kid who freaked out.
Oh, you mean Sailom?
You saw it yourself.
He can't be touched.
Is this the patient
you told me and Sky about that time?
Yep.
That's a tough one.
Good luck with that.
How many more bikes are left?
Give it a try in the next couple of
days. It should be working fine now.
I just had the mechanic
double-check and test everything.
Thank you so much.
If you run into any more issues,
just let us know. We're happy to help.
Yes, thank you.
You're welcome.
Sailom?
You're here to see me, right?
If there's anything you want to say,
I'm listening.
I'm so sorry for ruining your trip.
I really didn't mean it.
Please don't be mad at me.
If there's anything I can do to help,
please tell me.
I don't want to feel guilty anymore.
You didn't do anything wrong.
If you're worried that I'm angry,
don't be. I'm not mad at all.
I actually understand.
Really?
Really.
I actually am looking for some help.
Know how to edit videos?
- Edit videos?
- Yes.
I need someone to edit
the bike trip clips for our page.
Can you do that?
Yes! I can do that!
Hurry up!
Yeah, I'm on it.
Wait! Keep this part.
This shot is beautiful.
Put this clip right here!
Geez.
Why don't you do it yourself?
Here's the mouse.
Please, continue.
I promise I'll be quiet.
Not a peep from me.
If you can't even edit,
why did you volunteer?
P'Doc couldn't find anyone to help.
I must do anything
I can do to help him. Right?
Want to help your boyfriend, huh?
Come on!
We're just doctor and patient!
We're not dating.
Really?
But the doctor's necklace
is around the patient's neck.
You better buy me beers after this.
Fine. I'll buy you a whole factory.
Perfect. Now, I'm motivated.
Keep the orders coming.
Oh, this music isn't quite right.
- This one is better.
- Copy that.
Time really flies, doesn't it?
It feels like just yesterday
we were all having dinner together.
It really does, Mom.
Remember what your dad told you?
No matter what happens,
love one another.
Because family
is the most important thing.
We remember, Mom.
But we still fight all the time.
It happens.
I know.
You can fight, but once it's over,
always forgive each other.
I miss Dad.
I miss him too.
So, what's for dinner tonight?
A seafood BBQ by the beach?
Can… I invite my friends over?
If you do, I'm inviting mine too.
Good. I'll invite the kids
from the shop to join us.
Who do you live here with?
Well...
my parents split up when I was a kid.
And back then,
I chose to stay with my mom.
Maybe my dad is still mad at me
because I didn't choose him.
The truth is...
I never wanted to choose at all.
Because no matter who I chose...
I would still be the one at fault.
(Next Episode)
Never had a boyfriend.
Then... give me a kiss.
A host and a customer.
Is it really possible?
Take this home, so your
grandma can have a warm meal.
Grandma?! Grandma!
Your grandma is going to be okay.
I want to see Nabnueng.
It's been a long time, son.
NO!
Sailom!