(Previously)
Watch out!
Oh, no!
What's wrong?
My…
My necklace's gone!
Did the one who hit you take it?
Wait!
You thief! Give it back!
I'm returning it to you, and that's it.
Why was it okay when he touched my hand?
Damn it!
Ouch! Who did this?!
You started it.
You want a piece of me?
What if I do?
"Love Like a Bike" (Episode 2)
Mom,
since when did we hire this baker?
And when was the tasting?
How come I wasn't told?
You weren't here when
he came for the tasting yesterday.
His desserts are amazing.
He even has experience
in a Thai dessert shop.
P'Tawan,
his desserts are to die
for. You've got to try.
No thanks.
Your loss.
Suit yourself.
Dindin, let's get to work.
You got it.
Something going on… between you two?
Nothing!
Ooh, suspicious…
Don't think I've
forgotten about that night.
Not my fault. I tried to wake you,
but you wouldn't budge.
Are you a "hit and run" guy?
It was just a "friends
with benefits" thing.
Haven't you heard of it?
But you left me there alone,
completely naked.
You wouldn't wake up.
I even covered you with your clothes.
The wind must've blown
them away. I had to get to work.
Unlike you, I actually have a job to do.
- Are you pissing me off?
- I'm not. You're the one nagging me.
Do you want these croissants or not?
We've got a rush order!
Ten boxes of eclairs for a regular, ASAP!
Right now? I'm making croissants.
It'll have to wait. Baking takes time.
Please?!
Come on…
Please, please, please?
Fine. I'll get right on it.
Thanks!
Why are you still here,
old man? You're in my way.
Just do your job. I'm staying right here.
Nothing better to do?
I do now.
I don't trust you. Who knows
what you might steal from here.
You're nuts.
Hello. Do you have an appointment?
Ah, no… I don't.
I'm actually here to see Dr. Nabnueng.
Oh, he's out for field work today.
Field work?
Yes, our doctors take turns going out.
To support those at risk
of mental health issues.
Including the homeless,
nightlife workers, and those…
with limited access to care.
Interesting.
May I ask, are you one of his patients?
N-no... not really.
Actually, yes. I just became one.
Do you happen to know where he is today?
Yes, I do.
Doctor, I'm so scared.
There's no legal protection for people
like us. Only criminal laws that punish us.
The recent events have left us terrified.
I don't know where to turn or what to do.
I hear you.
What you've been through...
must be traumatizing.
Yes. But it's worse when we're alone.
With no way out, we feel more depressed.
What makes you feel
that way at those times?
Maybe we're just exhausted from work.
Society, the economy, the unstable income.
No one will hire us for any other job.
I'm at the end of my rope, doctor.
I understand.
You have every right to feel exhausted.
Everyone here…
has the right to feel
whatever you're feeling.
But the most important thing is:
Please don't carry it all alone.
Reach out to those
around you—friends, or even me.
Talk about it. Share your burdens with us.
We'll find a way through this together.
If anyone has something
too personal for a group setting,
you're welcome to speak with me privately.
Thank you.
Sailom?
What brings you here?
Oh… I was just passing by.
What about you? What are you doing here?
Field work with the SWING Foundation.
Providing counseling for those in nightlife.
They deserve the same
protections as everyone else.
I see.
I thought you only saw patients at the
clinic. I didn't expect to see you out here.
I just want to help out however I can.
Are you hungry?
Huh?
Hungry for what?
Hungry for dinner. Want to go grab a bite?
Still not done?
Not even close. They're bickering like crazy
in there. The filling's taking forever.
What are they fighting about?
P'Tawan's been hovering
in the kitchen all day.
They've been at it for an hour.
So many éclairs wasted.
Are we gonna make it in time?
No clue. See for yourself.
Nah, P'Tawan will just yell at me.
So... what now?
How much longer are you gonna stare?
Damn it…
Look! It's ruined because you keep staring.
It's all messy now.
How can I finish them on time?
Seriously,
have you ever even baked before?
I don't think you have.
If you're an expert,
do it yourself.
Me?
If I could, why would my mom hire you?
If you're still staring,
I'm not doing it.
How long have you been
away from Thailand for?
About… seven years or so, I think?
Why did you move to the US back then?
Come and play with me.
No, I don't want to!
- It's just your dad!
- Let go!
No! Leave me alone!
- I am your dad!
- Let me go!
I said, stay still!
Let me go!
Get over here! Now!
I'm sorry. If it's too personal,
you don't have to tell me.
Let's eat. You must be starving by now.
Order whatever you like.
It's my treat.
Menu, please?
Can you eat this?
Thank you.
Honestly,
it would be great if sex work
were fully decriminalized.
The workers wouldn't have to be
victims like in those tragic news items.
Yes, I agree.
It would be much safer for them.
They'd have welfare,
the state would get the tax,
and they'd be protected
from being exploited.
Most importantly:
They wouldn't be lured and killed.
It's devastating.
Let's toast.
No more heavy talk.
Cheers!
Whoa, easy!
Take it slow, or you'll get drunk.
I'm fine, Doc. I can handle this much.
"Not drunk at all," huh?
Look who finally decided to show up.
I thought a customer had locked you away.
No one can cage me, and you know it.
Can't be too sure. You're way too hot.
Everyone was dying to see you yesterday.
Especially that hottie at
that table over there.
You mean P'Man?
That influencer from Suphanburi.
Go charm him tonight.
He might drop a 500-drink bid on you.
In your dreams.
Just give it a shot.
Welcome to The Loner Club.
We're here to cure your loneliness.
Let the drink bidding begin!
Okay, here's Number 88 from Table V2.
10 drinks for Number 88 from Table V2!
Going once… going twice… SOLD!
Ice, Number 88, you're heading to V2!
Any more bids?
Number 69, 50 drinks!
Ooh! 50 drinks for 69!
Going once... twice...
going...
- 100 drinks!
- 100 drinks from Table 27!
Going once…
twice...
- Make it 120!
- 120 drinks!
120 drinks. Going once… twice…
and finally...
200 drinks.
200 drinks! Alright!
Going once… twice…
Sold! Table 17 takes the whole set!
Sky is officially off the floor
tonight! Congratulations!
Thank you so much, sir, for...
You're hot.
Number 28, 100 drinks!
Number 28. Going once… twice…
SOLD! Off to P'Man's table!
He's off the floor as well!
What are you drinking?
Want me to fix you a glass?
Whiskey with soda, or just water?
Whiskey and water...
Alright.
Number 8? How many drinks for Number 8?
- Two drinks.
- Oh, two drinks from Table 27.
Going once... twice... SOLD! To Table 27!
Have some water first.
You can really hold your liquor.
This is my first time.
Didn't know it'd... feel this good.
- Your first time drinking?
- Yup.
- First time at a host club too?
- Mm-hmm.
Do you like it?
I do.
So, what can you do besides mixing drinks?
I can…
play games, mix drinks…
Basically, I can do whatever you want.
Anything I want?
Then… show me what you've got.
Good boy. Here's your reward.
Easy there.
You should have some water.
Drink up. You'll feel better.
You okay?
The whiskey... it's gone. I need...
Hey. Another bottle over here.
- Let's stick with water for now.
- No. I want another bottle.
Please have some water first.
You bastards!
I'm just an old woman!
How can you be so heartless?!
Shut up, old hag!
It's your own fault for not paying us back.
If we did, we would've paid you by now!
And why is the interest so damn high?!
We pay so much,
but the debt never goes away!
You've got a big mouth!
Hey!
Get your hands off my grandma!
Are you okay?
Like mother, like son.
A deadbeat, just like your mom.
No, Dindin! Please don't!
I was gonna give you more time.
But on second thought,
taking your house is much easier.
You can't do that! We had a deal!
But you've got nothing for my boss.
I have it.
I'll transfer it right now.
3,000?! That doesn't
even cover the interest!
Just take it. That's all I have.
Let's go.
Better than nothing, I guess.
Are you hurt, Grandma?
Hey, is that that pilot?
Which one?
The one who botched
that landing and killed a kid.
The guy from that viral TikTok?
Oh, right. That girl was
the same age as my sister.
Feel bad for her parents.
She was at such a sweet age.
But she's gone because
of one pathetic pilot.
The hell you looking at?
Oh, we got a tough guy here?
You're so thick-skinned! Killed a kid and
still have the nerve to sit here drinking!
What the fuck is wrong with you people?!
Take that!
What the hell?
What are you doing?
Getting lucky.
I don't just sleep with anyone.
Just lie down next to me.
Catch!
Whoa!
P'Doc! Come play in the water with me!
What?! I can't hear you!
Come on! Get in here!
I don't have a change of clothes!
Come on!
He's quite a dork when he's drunk.
Come dance with me!
No! I don't know how to dance!
Dance with me!
I don't know how!
Then let me teach you!
P'Doc, come swim with me!
Don't let me be alone!
P'Doc!
Sailom!
Gotcha!
Here! Grab this!
Hold on tight.
What if the waves wash you away? Let's go!
What?!
Pajama?!
Oh, no…
Don't tell me the Doctor…
Your shirt is all soaked.
Let me take it off for you.
Please do.
I really like your lips.
How much?
I want…
to kiss them.
Can I?
Yes, you can.
But…
But?
I've never been kissed before.
It's okay.
I'll show you how.
Just follow my lead.
Never kissed before?
You said you've never done this before?
Do you still need a lesson?
Hey, you.
Hey…
Wake up!
James!
Dude...
I think… I slept with the doctor!
He pinned me down, then…
he stripped me and...
He must have seen everything!
Everything…
He even saw my nipples!
Look! And then he changed...
Stop!
Your imagination is out of control.
Imagination? What do you mean?
You were wasted last night,
so he dropped you off.
He just called me to take over. That's it.
Wait...
how did he get your number?
He used your phone.
Sailom.
Is there anyone I should call?
A friend, or...?
Who should I...
Sailom!
Who should I call for you?
Hmm?
James.
Jam?
James!
Okay, okay.
Call him for me.
Your phone's locked. Ah…
I need to unlock your phone.
Let me scan your face.
Sailom.
I need to scan your face.
Oh!
Sailom.
Okay.
Open your eyes! One, two, three!
Wait, wait! Stay with me! Sailom!
Oh, boy…
Sailom!
Finally…
It's Jam?
James…
Jam?
It's James…
There's only a “James.”
Come get me…
- James, I guess.
- Take me home…
Then... who changed my clothes?
It was me and Lemon.
- You and Lemon?
- Yep.
Just the two of you?
Hey, stop daydreaming already!
Shaddup!
How am I supposed to
look him in the eye now?
Like a puppy?
Screw you!
What am I gonna do?!
What's that look for?
None of your business.
Doctor!
Oh, Sailom.
Here for coffee? It's a bit late for that.
Want something? I can order for you.
No, thank you. I'm just…
here to return your shirt.
I've washed it! It smells really good!
Thank you. I totally forgot about it.
Oh, I'll get your shirt back to you soon.
No rush. Another time is fine.
Are you free this evening?
I am.
Why?
Let's go for a bike ride.
Doctor.
Err, well…
About last night... I'm really sorry.
What are you sorry for?
I…
Tend to act a bit weird when I'm wasted.
I don't know if I did
anything embarrassing.
Quite a few things, actually.
You kept begging me to go swimming.
What?
But it was pretty cute.
And you even called me "P'Doc."
No way!
I wouldn't...
I have proof.
P'Doc!
Come play in the water with me!
Don't let me be alone!
P'Doc!
Whoa!
Delete that! It's so embarrassing!
Why should I?
Please? Just delete it?
No.
Pretty please?
Please?
Nope.
Delete it for me, please?
No.
Come on, Doctor.
- Just delete the clip!
- Nope.
- Doctor!
- No, no, no.
I won't.
Stop teasing me! Give
it here! Just delete it!
- Doctor!
- Stop. Wait, wait.
I won't delete it.
Like I said, it's cute.
What's so cute about it?!
The part where you called me "P'Doc."
From now on, you have to call me...
P'Doc.
Nong Sailom.
Okay, P'Doc.
But… don't show it to anyone.
I promise.
It'll be for my eyes only.
Come on, let's take selfies.
- Mama, how's it going?
- Oh, hello.
Look who's back again.
- The usual?
- Thank you.
Okay, I'll get someone to bring it to you.
- Mama.
- Yes?
Is Sky working today?
He's here. He's upstairs getting ready.
So, how many drinks for him tonight?
Hmm…
How about 800 drinks?
Ooh, fabulous!
Don't forget my tip, okay?
- Of course, Mama.
- No problem.
- The staff will bring you a drink.
- Thanks you.
Welcome back for Round 3, everyone.
Let the bidding begin.
The first one is Table 22.
Oshi, 10 drinks.
Going once… twice… SOLD!
Off you go to the table.
Number 69, a hundred drinks!
Number 69, 100 drinks.
That's Sky, our top star!
Any higher bids?
Because he'll off the floor tonight.
Going once…
120.
120 drinks. Going once…
- Make it 150!
- 150! Going once… twice…
- 200
- Oh, 200!
200. Going once…
- Going...
- 300 drinks!
300. Going once… twice… and SOLD!
Sky, off to Mr. Man's table.
Huh? Mr. Boom's table? Oh, right.
Number 28, Papp, 2 drinks.
Going once… twice…
100 drinks.
Oh, 100 drinks! Going once… twice… SOLD!
Papp, you're going to that table.
Congrats! He's officially off the floor.
You can raise your hand! Okay!
Number 22, 100 drinks. Off you go!
Alright, to that table, you go!
Looks like we have another big spender!
Thank you to all my big spenders tonight!
Care for a drink?
Papp, kiss me on the cheek.
Right away.
Hey!
What? Don't you like it?
I said just a kiss!
What?
Prefer that table more?
Then go join them!
It's not like that, P'Man.
You know you're my only one.
If you love me...
how about a kiss?
Sure thing.
Give me a kiss too.
But NO mouth contact. Make it look intense.
Like a camera trick in a drama.
Can you do that?
Of course.
I told you NOT to touch my lips.
I'm so sorry.
Whoa, mister! Take it easy!
Thought I was "important" to you.
He's wasted. Again.
It's okay. I'll deal with him.
Just take him home.
I want to close up and sleep.
I know, I know.
Nava,
wake up. It's closing time.
- Is that you, Sky?
- Yep.
We barely talked today.
Come, come. Let's have a drink.
That's enough. You've had way too much.
What enough?
Life's too short, anyway.
We're all gonna die.
Just enough already.
Let's go home. I'll take you back.
- Get up.
- Don't wanna…
Easy. Take it slow.
You're heavy.
See ya.
Get home safe!
Do you do this for all your clients?
No, you're the first.
Why are you wiping me down?
Worried about you.
I didn't want you to die alone at the bar.
You should go.
I didn't pay for your time today.
I'm staying because I want to.
How many drinks?
No need.
I just want to be with
someone I care about.
Can I have your hand?
Can you…
hold my hand the whole night?
(Next Episode)
The whole city view is beautiful.
It would be even better with a lover.
- 400 drinks!
- Oh, my!
Did you really have to
compete with P'Man that much?
I don't like people touching what's mine.
I hired you, but you're sleeping in
working hours?! I'm docking your pay!
You can punch me if you want, just don't touch
my salary! I don't even have enough to get by.
It's okay to be scared, Sailom.
There's nothing wrong with that.
Fear just makes you more careful
about starting a relationship.