Chanwoo, I'm so glad you came.
I'm here.
I will not leave you.
Do you love me?
I love you.
I've been calling you for a while now.
Angel was already downstairs.
He also called you.
But you didn't answer.
Oh, right.
What else do you want to buy?
What are you buying now, K-pop stuff again?
Gosh, no wonder you don't have any savings.
With all the stuff you buy that isn't even important.
It's concert tickets again, right?
Oh, Melody.
It's expensive again.
It's not that expensive, ma'am.
And Chanwoo only came here once, so for me, this is important.
I told you, Melody.
Save.
Don't be like me who never saved before.
This is the last one, Mom, I promise.
I will save up after this concert.
Okay, right?
My child.
Can you really save money with all that freelance work you do?
Look for a decent job.
My job is real, ma'am.
Wouldn't it be better if I worked from home all the time?
And staying up late like that is not good for you.
You keep watching the Korean guy's video.
Okay, Bu.
I will apply for a job after this concert.
You won't be able to escape me with sweet talk, Melody.
You only said that so I wouldn't get mad, right?
I'm serious, ma'am.
George said there was a vacancy.
I will try it.
So, don't be angry, okay, ma'am.
Please don't be angry.
Yes!
Completed work!
It's baby time!
Hello, Chanwoo!
Chanwoo! Chanwoo! Chanwoo!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Chanwoo.
It took me a long time.
I'm still working.
So, I can,
so I can support you.
Okay.
Parasocial relationships.
This is what is called a fan's feeling towards a celebrity.
Even if you don't really know them,
It feels like you know them so well.
However, it is also sad to think about it because all of this only happened from one side.
Chanwoo, I'm so glad you came.
I'm here.
I will not leave you.
Do you love me?
I love you.
Their coffee is absolutely delicious.
I swear, I have no bad words to say.
I think I'm excited enough to go back to Bebe's time.
Hopefully we get tickets, right?
Okay. Your tablet is fast anyway.
My laptop is so bad.
So, we will definitely buy tickets.
Well, here it is! It's about to start!
- This is so stressful. - Hey, come on.
Just relax! Do your best, son!
There it is, there it is! Click, click!
Click, click!
VIP! VIP! VIP!
Uhh, ah, top box! Top box.
Please, start.
- Okay, go ahead. - It's gone too.
No, wait. There might still be some on the other side.
The others. Bottom box, bottom box.
There is nothing left.
Oh, what happened?
It's sold out, it says sold out, ma'am.
What does that mean? Everything is lost?
Yes, everything is gone.
Fifteen thousand seats, and we still didn't get a single one.
Hey, Tita!
Oh, whose face is that?
The tickets are sold out.
Just like this, you better just eat.
What's the time now?
Didn't ticket sales just start?
Did you know, not even a second has passed and the tickets are already sold out!
It all happened so fast!
Correct?!
That's exactly why I bought gelato, because I had a feeling,
You won't be able to get a ticket.
You are so evil!
You say that we will get nothing?
Oh, you don't want it?
Okay, I'll just take it home.
Oh, give it to me, give it to me. I'll eat it.
What is gelato?
It's like ice cream, Tita.
This is good.
This is for you.
Don't be sad about it.
That's actually great, you can save now.
Better to just buy a laptop.
I don't believe it.
Is there really nothing left?
Please check again, Angel.
There are none left, they are sold out.
What should I do now?
How can Chanwoo pay attention to me now?
Why would he pay attention to you?
And why not?
Your daughter is very delusional, Aunt Esther.
What is “delulu”?
He said I was hallucinating, Mom.
I remember, it hurt!
This hurts!
🎶I love to see the beauty of the sea and the moon shining above it🎶.
You play the song again.
You know, you've played that a thousand times this week.
Actually, it's been two thousand times.
This is the most beautiful song in the world.
And this is the song that helped me.
Every time I hear him, I feel like he knows me.
That's right, right?
Yes, he knows you very well.
That's why you don't have a ticket.
You're so mean. You're really ruining the mood.
You know, one day, I'll hear it live.
Then, he will turn around.
And then he will realize that I am his number one fan.
Remember my words, okay?
That's not possible.
Fifteen thousand seats sold out, and he's going to stare at you?
Shut up!
You are too sensitive.
I am just kidding.
It's not something to joke about.
You already know that's the only thing I want.
And you're still joking about it.
My mood is ruined.
I didn't even get a ticket.
Then you treat me like that.
How about this?
We can still wait outside the concert hall, right?
Maybe he will come out.
Or maybe we'll see the car.
That's right!
You're right!
- Let's wait for him. - Let's go!
Come with us, you and Angel, if possible.
Sure, okay.
George, what job was that you told Melody about earlier?
Maybe he can just register there.
He might lose his job.
Unemployed?
I have a job, Mom.
You still have to apply there.
George, please take care of this, son.
Yes, Tita.
I think the position my contact mentioned is still open.
That's a sign that you can't get a ticket.
So you better stop being obsessed with Korean things.
Ya, Bu.
- Let's wait for him. - It's yours.
Thank You.
- What flavor do you get? - Well, here's the spoon.
Well, that's basically it.
Thank you for meeting me here, Melody.
I apologize that this interview must be conducted outside the office.
Our entire team is currently out of the office with some clients.
So, basically we work with our bags at the moment.
It's okay, ma'am.
No problem.
I appreciate your flexibility, but just to be clear.
If you get this position, most of your work will be like this.
Outside the office, at event locations, and joining tour events.
This is not your ordinary office job.
Do you think you can handle it?
Yes.
Pleased to hear it.
OK, we will contact you via email to let you know the results.
And thank you for your time.
Okay, I'll start first.
And you can stay here to finish your food and drinks.
But I really have to go.
Okay? Thank you, Melody.
Why, thank you.
Hot!
Hello, ugly!
How are you? I just finished my interview!
Where are you now, ugly one?
Are you ready, George?
Yes.
Hey, hey everyone.
My name is George Villoria.
And the first song I'm going to sing is a personal story.
It's not over yet because we still don't have an ending.
But I just wanted to share it with you all.
This song is titled, Space.
🎶Round and round, constantly in my heart, in my mind🎶
🎶Only you are inside🎶
🎶My gaze remains fixed on you🎶
🎶I can feel the signs🎶
[Congratulations! You've been hired!]
[Congratulations! You've been hired!] Yes. But
My days as a die-hard fan are over.
The universe answered me so quickly.
🎶I just wish you would tell me how you feel🎶
🎶Maybe you can give it a chance🎶
🎶Expressing what my heart feels...🎶 Secret.
The brand hired you to do research on Chanwoo?!
Chanwoo's fan base in the Philippines will bring about brand collaborations.
Your first strategy...
Oh my god.
Wait?
Brand collaboration?
So Chanwoo is my client?!
Chanwoo...
Chanwoo is my client!
Is this a sign, universe?
I'm so close to giving up!
I have received it.
So this is a sign. I should love Chanwoo even more!
🎶...maybe you can give it a chance🎶.
Okay. 🎶...maybe you can give it a chance🎶
I am very proud of myself.
🎶My heart that only knows how to love🎶
🎶We will reach the vast universe🎶.
Calm down, Melody, calm down. Melody, not yet.
Cheers!
Wow.
Congratulations, ugly.
You got a lot of cheers and requests earlier.
I don't think you've even watched my original composition,
the first song I sang,
- Ahhh. - Did you hear that?
Sorry.
I was distracted earlier.
But the songs you sang after that, I already knew.
Why are you distracted?
There isn't anything.
I was accepted into the job you recommended.
Truly?
- Are you accepted? - Mhmm!
Wow, my friend.
You know, it's okay.
Even though you can no longer idolize someone as often as you used to,
At least you will have a new routine again.
That's right.
You'll be able to save— For your new laptop!
Correct.
So don't be sad about it.
What do you say, George?
I'm not sad.
Do you know the reason?
Because I will be working with Chanwoo!
That's crazy, that's crazy.
Even though I didn't get the concert tickets,
Instead, I will approach him.
Can you believe it? That's crazy!
What kind of sign is this?!
Wow. You're amazing.
Correct?
But you know, all this happened because of you.
So, thank you, ugly.
Thank you for encouraging me to apply here.
That's why you're my best friend!
Best friend.
Yes. Best, best, best friend.
Congratulations, ugly.
I'm happy for you.
Thank You.
But I'm so happy.
I've reviewed your initial report, Melody.
And I have to admit, I'm very proud.
Your insights into Chanwoo's fan behavior and fanbase are very detailed.
Thank you, ma'am.
I just make sure that our data is accurate for the strategy.
You know a lot about fangirling culture.
And details about Chanwoo's past schedule and preferences.
I was thinking, Melody, are you a fan of Chanwoo?
Ah, I just did some really in-depth research for this project.
To understand the market, yes.
Good.
Because work is still work, Melody.
And fan idolization activities are not allowed on site.
Especially, we will have a show.
So, tell me, Melody, what does our first content feel like?
Oh, first content, yeah.
So, based on my research, we need to make it easy for the general public to understand.
- Oh, Chanwoo. - Annyeonghaseyo.
- Annyeonghaseyo. - How are you?
I'm fine. Can I sit here?
Of course, Melody.
Oh, sir. Here. Sit here, sit here.
Okay, this is the chair for you.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Please move aside.
Can we continue in a few minutes?
I just need to go to the bathroom.
Okay.
Relax.
I will use White Rose Papaya only.
Operation "Be More Radiant."
Hoping my crush will notice me again.
I want to eat first.
Is George not here yet?
He is very old.
What's the time now?
Very delicious!
Okay.
Later.
He came a long time ago.
Look who finally showed up?
What makes you so enthusiastic, you ugly bastard?
You're so annoying. Sit here.
I told you, there's something I want to tell you.
I couldn't hold back my excitement any longer.
I have to let this out, it's so ugly!
You're crazy again.
Of course, crazy about Chanwoo.
So, we've met, me and Chanwoo.
Have you guys met?
Earlier.
And it was so embarrassing because he caught me.
When did you guys meet?
This is how it is, like this.
Come on, come on, come on.
Stand up, stand up. Like this.
Well, hug me, hug me.
Then pull me, okay?
Is that really the case?
You're really close to Chanwoo, aren't you?
But not for that long.
Because I left as soon as Helga was there.
And you know, he told me that being a die-hard fan is not allowed.
And before that happened, he even asked me if I was a fan.
Of course, I lied because I was afraid he would kick me out.
Why would he kick you out just because you're a fan?
Okay, that's it. That's what I said,
I can't take my words back.
Oh.
Sit down.
George.
Actually I need something.
So what next?
We need original music for Street Food Challenge content.
Original music?
Why me?
Your company is very big.
Why not just take someone from there?
Of course.
You are the best songwriter I know.
Now you are just flattering me.
But come on, just agree.
Come on, say yes. I see you smiling.
The best songwriter in the Philippines.
You know it,
I will go anywhere with you.
While I don't have any shows.
So, put me on your team.
You're the best, you ugly bastard.
Let's put it this way, I'll tell Helga that I'll take care of the music.
And I'll also tell him that you're part of my team, so you can come.
Okay?
I am very happy.
Wait, wait, wait.
But you have a lot of music saved, right?
Yes, there are a lot.
I already knew, you were perfect for this.
Okay.
Okay, this works.
Sir, it's not ready yet.
I still can't show you this.
Okay, one pose.
Next, please.
This is the last one from me.
Okay, that's great, Chanwoo.
For the next setup, we need a 30 minute break.
So, let's come back at 3pm, okay?
Thank You.
Thank you, Melody.
- Ugly. - What?
I thought we just changed the settings? Why?
Did everyone disappear?
Ah, they're just hungry.
They will be back soon.
This is a 30 minute break.
30 minutes?
Then, let's eat first.
I saw something there, it looks good.
I still need to send something.
- Wait, let me get something first. - What do you want to get?
I'll take care of it,
so you can finish what you are working on.
- Are you sure? - Yes, what is it?
The hard drive, my bag is in the van.
- Hard drive? - Yes, get it,
Photographers may be looking for one of these looks in the future.
- Okay. - Take it,
- I'll clean everything up here. Hurry up. - Okay.
Is this true?
Ah, there's one missing.
Melody.
Can I speak to you privately?
Uh, we have, we are talking.
Do we have a problem?
Problem?
What's the problem?
I can't help
but felt something was wrong.
Or maybe.
I did something that upset you.
You're acting a bit cold.
And because I really appreciate the energy of our team,
I just wanted to let you know.
Did I do something wrong?
I'm not cold, sir.
I don't know.
I just feel like you're always on guard around me.
Is there any reason for that?
Where...
This is from three years ago.
Actually, four.
Oh, I see.
You are a fan.
Please don't tell Helga.
Don't worry.
I won't tell him.
I actually think so
You can't stand being around me.
So, I'm glad to know that I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
Good to know.
This is the sound of duck duck.
These are quail eggs with orange batter.
This one, his name is Isaw.
This is chicken intestines.
Did you know? You should try it.
It's absolutely delicious, I promise.
- I see? - Yes, it's clean.
Okay.
Is this good?
- Try it. - Okay.
I believe in you, Melody.
You have very good taste.
And since you've been a fan for a long time,
I assume you know personal things about me.
Oh. Hi, ugly.
Come here. Come here.
Come here. I'll introduce you to my friend.
Yes.
Take the chair.
This is George.
He is the songwriter I told you about.
He is also responsible for the music.
for Street Food Challenge content.
Nice to meet you, George.
I'm George.
You must be very, very great.
I have great respect for songwriters like you.
Your work makes my work feel real.
To be honest, I also want to write my own songs.
Can you give me some pointers?
No. No, I'm just a small songwriter.
Oh, no. He sings too.
I think every Filipino can sing.
Now, I'm starting to feel nervous about my upcoming concert.
No, Chanwoo.
Yours is very different.
We are Filipinos, we only sing in karaoke.
But your voice is the best, I promise.
You always say that.
Because you are my fan.
Don't let Helga hear this, okay?
My concert is next week.
Hope you enjoy it.
In fact, you are so famous here that my friend and I failed to get your tickets.
The tickets are sold out.
- Really? - Yes.
I'm sorry.
You missed it.
Here's what if you can't get into the main show.
I'll be doing some short shows and press conferences around town.
I really want you to come.
Invite your friends.
George can come too.
My assistant will send the details.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Ugly! Thank you, thank you, thank you.
But before that, I think we should go back to the past.
With our content.
Okay, so what was this again? Do you remember?
This?
- What is this? - Quail eggs?
What is the name for this?
It sounds like a quack.
Quack-quack.
🎶 I love to see the beauty of the sea and the moon shining above it🎶
🎶Alone on the sand, looking at the stars🎶
🎶Hopefully one day I will find true love🎶
🎶How beautiful it would be to see the morning🎶
🎶With the person you love the most🎶
🎶Would it be nice to say good night to the person you love so much🎶
🎶For your heart🎶
🎶The wind that flies the dove is the wind that flies my love🎶
🎶May this song reach you wherever you are🎶
🎶May this song reach you, wherever you are🎶
🎶The wind that flies the dove is the wind that flies my love🎶
🎶I hope I can reach you wherever you are🎶
🎶Wherever you are🎶.
Chanwoo!
What are you doing now?
I'm working on the props you'll be using for this challenge.
Make sure it will be fun.
Yes of course.
- Can I see it? - Yes, of course.
Here.
So, this is our first activity.
- Do you like it? - Yes.
I like it.
And for our second activity,
I think this will be a moment to strengthen your relationship with your fans.
- Do you like it? - Yes, I like it.
So, do you have any suggestions?
George, do you agree with the music?
Actually,
I'm still working on it.
Just get it over with. What are you doing?
Come on, quickly.
Okay, me.
I just need to take care of something here.
- Chanwoo. - Ya.
It's so funny, right?
Lots of flowers. Look at this one.
So...
Can we take a picture?
Yes.
Okay.
Okay, smile!
Then, weird things. Can you do weird things?
- Strange? - Yes, strange.
Ah, okay.
Then, don't smile.
No smiling allowed.
Can you make a greeting video for me?
- Yes. - Okay,
Say, Hi Melody, always take care of yourself.
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait.
One, two, three, go!
Hi Melody, always take care of yourself.
Can you also...
Oh, I forgot I still have things to do.
Uh, I'll go.
Melody,
I warned you about the fan craziness.
Oh,
I only went to a few other shows.
Let's not fool each other here, Melody.
I've seen you before.
I've seen how you guys exchanged glances.
And it's not just me who noticed it.
And as a reminder, this is risky for the brand.
I'm in touch with the management.
And he needs to focus, Melody.
He must remain professional.
Because fans can be too possessive.
And you should know that, right?
Because you are also a fan.
And you are part of the team.
Don't drag him down, Melody.
Besides, it's not that deep.
After the brand collaboration, she will return to Korea.
He will return to his life as a celebrity.
So don't waste your career, Melody.
Just because of that momentary temptation.
Melody, you are just a fan.
The launch of this collaboration was a huge success!
Congratulations to the whole team!
Cheers!
And of course, this is because we have the most artistic,
the greatest artist.
We have Chanwoo!
NO.
It's not just me who feels it.
It's all because you all have done your best.
I enjoyed every minute I spent in the Philippines.
Kamsahamnida.
Thank You.
So, George, you're the singer here, right?
You are the one who brought us here.
So, why don't you sing for us?
- George, sing a song for us. - Oh, no.
- Come on, George. - Let's go.
Sing for us.
Come on!
Do the best.
Go for it, George!
Congratulations to the entire team.
The song I will sing
called "Please Tell Me."
🎵I want him to know that I love him🎵
🎵That's the only dream I have🎵
🎵I just want to tell her, but I can't start🎵
🎵If you meet him, please just tell him🎵
🎵Please tell him that I love him🎵
🎵Even though he loves someone else🎵
🎵Tell him not to worry, I don't expect anything🎵
🎵I know this is impossible, I can't change it🎵
🎵Even so, please just tell him🎵
🎵Hopefully he knows that I'm still happy🎵
🎵Even though my heart is aching🎵.
Yes, he is very great.
This is surprising.
🎵...that there might be an easier way🎵
🎵If you meet him, please just tell him🎵
🎵Please tell him that I love him🎵
🎵Even though he loves someone else🎵
🎵Tell him not to worry, I don't expect anything🎵
🎵I know this is impossible, I can't change it🎵
🎵Please just tell him🎵
🎵Please tell her that I love her and she will always be in my heart🎵
🎵Is this okay?🎵
🎵Please tell him that I love him🎵
🎵Even though he loves someone else🎵
🎵Tell him not to worry, I don't expect anything🎵
🎵I know this is impossible, I can't change it🎵
🎵Even so, please just tell him🎵
🎵Even though he loves someone else🎵
🎵Tell him not to worry, I don't expect anything🎵
🎵I know this is impossible, I can't change it🎵
🎵Even so, please just tell him🎵
🎵Even so, please just tell him🎵.
Thank you, thank you.
- Halo? - Oh, Melody?
Uncle Bong?
Yes, I am here, in front of your house.
Locked.
There are no lights on either.
Oh no, Melody. George isn't there.
He has a show out of town. He'll probably need a few days there.
A show?
Oh, I see.
He didn't reply to my message.
He also didn't reply to Angel's message.
Where did he perform?
Uhm... I don't remember where.
He's probably busy. Just leave him be for now.
Go home for now, Melody.
Please tell him to reply to my message.
Okay. I'll tell him.
Okay.
Please also tell him that I stopped by.
Okay, okay.
Thank You.
[Hey, ugly. I miss you! Let's talk.]
Mel.
What's your order?
I have no problem with anything.
Good grief!
Chanwoo?
Is this really Chanwoo?
Oh my god, this is Chanwoo!
Good grief!
Chanwoo!
Chanwoo, can you take a picture?
Are you alone?
Are you with someone?
Are you with him?
No, I'm alone.
Oh my God! Can we take a picture?
Chanwoo!
This is the best day of my life!
Thank you so much, Chanwoo!
[Mel! Have you seen it? George is going viral!]
[Isn't that George? [That's his voice! Listen]]
Let me check.
🎶Round and round, constantly in my heart, in my mind🎶
🎶Only you are inside🎶
🎶My gaze remains fixed on you🎶
🎶I can feel the signs🎶
🎶I can't stop thinking about you🎶
🎶I'm losing my mind, wondering🎶
🎶About You🎶
🎶I just wish you would tell me how you feel🎶
🎶Maybe you can give it a chance🎶
🎶According to what I feel from my heart🎶
🎶Who only knows how to love🎶
🎶We will reach the vast universe🎶.
Which hurts more, Mel?
Rejected by Chanwoo in public or
Avoided by George?
What kind of questions are those?
Why are you acting like that? I'm already in pain here.
Just answer.
This might help you.
Truly?
It feels like they are all the same.
But I am more than that,
more surprised by George.
How could he love me?
He is my best friend.
Is it really real?
Is he sure?
Oh, maybe it's just inspiration.
We're best friends, right?
We are like siblings.
You really don't know anything.
I am your best friend.
George loves you.
Then why didn't he ever say so?
That's obvious, Mel.
You are not very smart.
When did George ever say "I love you" to you?
Never.
Because he shows it in another way.
He is always there for you wherever you go.
He does everything you want even when it's hard for him.
You're too stupid, Mel.
That's why you don't understand.
Or maybe you're too focused on Chanwoo.
The same Chanwoo who once rejected you.
Look at this.
I took this photo while we were watching Chanwoo.
Look at his face.
What do I have to do?
I don't want to lose George.
Only you can answer that, Besh.
For now, you need to feel everything you feel.
This is very difficult.
I didn't mean to overhear your conversation,
But I recognized my daughter's cries.
I'll take my leave now, Tita.
My child.
What should I do, ma'am?
Love doesn't have to be noisy.
The true measure is when, even in silence, you feel happy.
But I'm confused.
It feels like no matter what I do, there's nothing I can do.
There is something you can do.
Choose.
That's not what you want,
but what you don't want to lose.
The person you don't want to lose.
Hey, Mel.
How are you?
About the last time...
It's okay, sir.
You don't need to explain.
You resign.
And you will leave after this.
So it's none of your business.
Thank you for making my dream come true.
I've been wondering what it would feel like for a long time,
You know, to actually meet you in person so
Thank you for the experience.
I will remain a fan forever.
Just a fan.
What are you doing here?
What a jerk.
You even dragged your father into lying that you weren't here.
You won't even reply to my message, huh?
You just keep uploading songs.
Why?
I knew nothing would happen even if I uploaded the song.
Are you not happy now?
Happy because of what?
George,
you suddenly confess your feelings to everyone and then,
But not for me?
Why didn't you tell me?
Your song about me became so famous, and I was the last to know?
Would anything change if I told you?
Are you here because the song became popular?
Is that how you see me?
George, I have resigned from the company.
I also said goodbye to Chanwoo.
Just answer my question honestly, Mel.
Don't you love your Chanwoo so much?
So what's next?
Are you here now?
What will happen?
Do you know exactly what you want to happen?
I'm sorry, George.
Look, let's take a break first.
Try it first and find out what really suits you.
I will find out if
I still love you.
I will play during the sound test.
There might be a lot of people there.
Coffee latte for Melody.
Thank You.
Miss, may I share?
Oh, this...
George.
I guess you are busy?
I heard
You will go on a world tour.
Hey, you're looking for my name, right?
It touches the heart.
Even if I don't look, you're already famous.
I hear and see you everywhere.
You know, Mel,
Being known by everyone has always been my dream.
Correct?
But to be honest,
There is only one person I want to please.
Until now, you still don't know how to say something directly?
I'm sorry.
Here.
Okay.
My song now has a new ending.
And in this version, I won't let go.
I will not hesitate any longer.
And I will not be afraid.
About what?
By saying that only you are like that.
That it's still you.
That I still love you.
And whatever your answer, Mel,
That will never change.
Love doesn't have to be noisy.
The true measure is when, even in silence, you feel happy.
Not what you want, but someone you can't afford to lose.