ALL FIGURES,
INCIDENTS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS,
AND OTHERS ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
WERE FILMED SAFELY
IN ACCORDANCE WITH GUIDELINES
Ghosts don't exist.
Every ghost denies it at first.
Then prove that I'm a ghost.
All right.
Tell me who you are.
Me? I'm…
Who am I?
It's okay. Most ghosts
show this kind of reaction.
Maybe I lost my memory.
Did I get into an accident or something?
If it's simple memory loss,
tell me why you're floating in mid-air.
I'm floating in mid-air?
What the heck?
This can't be.
Has another ghost come?
Is he here?
Who is it this time?
It's a man in his thirties.
He doesn't accept that he's dead.
I'm not dead, I tell you!
He's now in the second stage.
Anger.
- Oh, my.
- Let's say that I'm dead.
Next, bargaining.
Theoretically speaking,
spiritual beings are impossible.
Wow, a theoretical approach?
This is new.
Listen. In the 1880s,
the British physicist, William Crookes,
the Nobel Prize winner in Medicine,
Charles Richet,
and the Great Inventor, Edison,
tried to prove the existence of the soul,
but they all failed in the end!
W-What is it?
Is he upset?
He seems too educated
to believe in ghosts.
Ignorance is bliss sometimes.
Too bad for him.
Why don't we sit down
and give him some time?
Are you people kidding me?
Fine, I'll prove it then.
What the…
What's going on?
What is this?
Maybe we should take him home
and feed him something delicious.
I hope he isn't a pork or coffee lover.
That won't be good at all if he is.
- Music.
- Right, music.
What should I play?
What would be a good choice?
For a ghost to exist,
it needs to have a physical entity
and create energy.
But this is against
the basic laws of physics,
the law of conservation
of mass and energy.
One more thing.
For a ghost to exist,
it needs to transcend time and space.
This also is against
the basic laws of physics.
In conclusion,
no scientific evidence proves
the existence of ghosts…
He seems to have majored in science.
I…
I found him.
DR. JEON SANG-HO ON THE PODIUM
AS SCIENTIST OF THE YEAR
INFORMATION
ON VICTIM JEON SANG-HO
Jeon Sang-ho was the next leader
of the life sciences field in Korea.
He was the Scientist of the Year
for three years in a row.
He was outstanding enough
to be called a genius.
KEY FIGURES
RELATED TO THE VICTIM
Congratulations.
Chief Kim Tae-jun was fond of him
from the beginning.
7 YEARS AGO, YEAR 2018
Say hello. This is Dr. Jeon Sang-ho.
He'll be joining our lab soon.
And this is my daughter, Kim Su-jeong.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
I read your paper from last month.
It was impressive.
EVEN ON HIS BIRTHDAY,
JEON SANG-HO PRESENTS NEW THEORY
We've got his name and date of birth.
He was 26 years old in 2018.
He was born in 1992,
the Year of the Monkey.
What's wrong?
What is it?
Take a deep breath.
Excuse me?
Inhale.
Exhale.
Wait.
I'm sensitive to dust particles.
And breathing too fast
will cause my cerebral blood flow--
One more time.
The moment I tell you
your name and birthday,
you'll regain all of your memories.
If you're trying to hypnotize me,
it won't work.
Hypnosis is a state of trance where
hyper-immersion distorts your perception.
It, instead, reduces
the accuracy of your memory.
In the field of science, it's very--
Don't worry
even if you feel like throwing up.
Ghosts can't throw up.
All right, now.
You were born on July 10, 1992.
Your name is Jeon Sang-ho.
JEON SANG-HO
SCIENTIST OF THE YEAR
AWARD CEREMONY
Chief Kim Tae-jun spared no expense
in supporting Jeon Sang-ho who was poor.
Jeon Sang-ho and Kim Su-jeong
quickly became close,
having a shared interest in life sciences.
After a year, they got married.
Congratulations on getting married!
Shortly after, they had a son.
The successful husband and the wise wife.
And with an adorable child, he had
all he needed to make a happy family.
Until one day…
Jeon Sang-ho went missing.
His parents found it odd that they were
unable to reach him and called the police.
Come and check this.
- This is blood, isn't it?
- Yes.
Bloodstains found in the grout lines
on the living room floor
turned out to be Jeon Sang-ho's,
and the missing person case
turned into a murder case.
I was out running that evening.
Right over there…
Based on her psychiatric records,
the prosecution arrested Kim Su-jeong
on suspicion of murdering Jeon Sang-ho.
There were no suspects other than her.
Kim Su-jeong admitted
that they had an argument,
but she claimed it was
no worse than any other lovers' quarrel.
She also said she saw a psychiatrist
for minor postpartum depression.
Besides that, his body wasn't found
and neither was the murder weapon.
Most of all, no concrete evidence proved
that she murdered Jeon Sang-ho.
After that, she was found not guilty,
but the prosecution appealed.
It means they found something,
which we haven't figured out yet.
What's your solution to this?
Kim Su-jeong is the one who knows
what the prosecution has against her.
I'll have to meet Kim Su-jeong.
Are you feeling better now?
Yes.
I'm sorry to ask
in this situation,
but do you remember
who killed you?
The prosecution filed an appeal.
That means they found something crucial,
whether it be evidence or a witness.
What do you think it is?
All my conversations with you
will be confidential.
So, please tell me honestly.
Is the culprit your wife?
I…
did not kill my husband.
…was murdered by my wife.
You must be at ease,
being clueless and all.
But I'm walking on thin ice.
I'm not sure if I should stop I-rang.
What if I leave him be
and something bad happens?
I'm on pins and needles every day.
It seems like I-rang is paying the price
for what you did.
It's maddening.
So, don't smile like that.
PITTER-PATTER BUTCHER-STYLE BBQ
SHIN I-RANG LAW OFFICE
Goodness, there we go.
They're staying at her parents'.
Figures.
It wouldn't be easy to stay
at the murder location.
U-ju…
I get that you're heartbroken,
but don't cry.
You have to be strong at a time like this.
I apologize.
You have nothing to apologize for.
Why do all my ghost clients
have to be so good-natured?
Geez, I hate this.
Thank you.
RESTRICTED AREA - POLICE LINE
UNDER INVESTIGATION
Are you going to be okay?
This is where you got killed.
Objects, locations,
smells, and such things
can be of great help
in regaining one's memory.
I want to remember anything I can.
What did you do
after you came home from work that day?
I had an argument with Su-jeong.
Why?
Why aren't the results out yet?
I'm tired. Let's talk tomorrow.
Are you taking your time
because it's none of your business?
What?
This isn't my business?
Are you saying I'm not your family?
I'm done.
- What?
- I quit.
You don't even consider me as family.
It's foolish
to be the only one giving their all.
Honey.
Are you really trying to kill me?
I don't care if you die or not!
I'm sick and tired of this.
It was just
a common lovers' quarrel.
And then?
Su-jeong and U-ju seemed to be asleep.
So, I went to wash up.
Are you sure it was only you,
your wife, and your child in the house?
Yes.
What else do you remember?
Well…
I did see something.
But the mirror was so foggy…
I couldn't see clearly.
I'm not sure.
I don't know…
This is the info on Shin I-rang, sir.
NAME: SHIN I-RANG
ADDRESS:
OKCHEON BUILDING, SEOCHO
His office is in Seocho-dong?
He's way out of his league.
And we have a criminal trial scheduled
for the Glory girl group case.
PLAINTIFF'S LEGAL REP:
SHIN I-RANG
DEFENDANT: MOON JU-HYEON (EMMA)
Shin I-rang?
He's the legal representative
of the victim Kim Su-a.
What's with this punk?
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT
PROSECUTORS' OFFICE - APPEAL
ERROR OF FACT
ERROR OF LAW - NEW EVIDENCE
What on earth did they find?
DAD
Hello?
Hey, she picked up.
Come on and take the phone.
Really?
Dad?
Talk to her before she hangs up.
Hello?
Na-hyun.
N-Na-hyun, it's Dad.
Yes, I know.
Are you having a drink?
Yes, I met up with Chan-u today
who I haven't seen in a long time.
We were having a drink together
when I was suddenly thought of you.
Mom must be waiting.
Stop drinking and go home.
Na-hyun, make time for your dad.
Your dad is practically pining here.
Don't be ridiculous.
Na-hyun is extremely busy.
She's not just any attorney.
She's a partner attorney at Taebaek.
Oh, come on.
Stop with the act. You were whining
about how much you missed her just now.
Be quiet.
Hello? Na-hyun.
Dad, I have to work.
I see. I'm sorry to disturb.
I'll let you work.
Yeah, I'll go home now. Let's hang up.
Dad.
Yes? What is it, Na-hyun?
No, nothing.
What?
Well, okay.
Let's hang up.
I was about to head home anyway.
Hanging up now.
Be careful on your way home.
Geez, you startled me.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, but I can't sleep
when I'm curious about something.
Ghosts don't sleep.
Have you forgotten what the contract says?
"A ghost client does not invade
the attorney's privacy."
Sleep is my absolute privacy.
Right.
Fine. I'm awake anyway.
Ask me your question.
What happened
to all your former ghost clients?
Their resentment was lifted.
A child was set free
from her sense of guilt.
A family reunited too.
- And then?
- They went to a better place.
Don't worry, Sang-ho.
I'll make Kim Su-jeong pay the price
and help you pass on.
I don't want you to.
What do you mean?
Make Su-jeong pay the price.
What?
Why not?
You had a bright future,
and she killed you.
Even if she gets punished,
I won't come back to life.
You're right, but--
I…
get why she did it.
She must've dreamed
of a happy married life
with a husband who had the same goals.
But I couldn't make her happy.
Ouch.
I was always preoccupied with research.
It was the same even after U-ju was born.
I was afraid of dropping him
or hurting him.
Su-jeong.
Goodness. Why are you
just staring at the baby?
I couldn't bring myself to touch him
in case he got hurt because of me.
She was struggling just as much
with her first experience as a parent.
But all I did was calculate and hide
instead of following my heart.
She must've thought
I was frustrating and pathetic.
There, there.
Here you go. Have just one spoonful.
U-ju, let's eat. Have your food.
I'm off to work.
It's an excuse… to say I didn't know how.
I ruined her life.
Su-jeong was so depressed
that she even tried to kill herself.
I'm mostly to blame
for her postpartum depression.
Su-jeong.
If she had died back then…
- Su-jeong.
- …I would've been the murderer.
What's going on? Su-jeong.
- I brought it upon her.
- Su-jeong.
- I can't possibly blame her.
- Su-jeong!
That's really hard to believe.
Anyway,
at least for U-ju,
I want Su-jeong to be found not guilty.
Sang-ho. His dad is dead.
If his mom goes to prison…
I would feel so bad for U-ju.
I couldn't be a good dad
while I was alive,
but I want to be one now
even if it's late.
For that to happen,
we shouldn't take his mom away from him.
Even if she's the one who murdered you?
She's warm and sweet at heart.
Now that I'm gone,
she'll go back to how she used to be.
Then, U-ju will be raised well.
So, there are fathers like you after all.
Others have fathers who don't give a damn
about his child or family.
What?
I'm talking about my dad.
He did whatever he wanted
in his carefree life
until he died,
leaving the mess for us to clean up.
Compared to him,
you're an admirable dad.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
Anyway, tomorrow is the appellate trial.
Let's wait and see
how the result turns out.
Okay?
Okay.
Why is it so bright, though?
The sun came up.
I'm sorry.
Stop with the apologies!
COURTHOUSE
Is Sang-ho here?
No, I told him to wait
in case he possessed me.
I see. Good job.
You seem tired.
That's Attorney Han.
I'll be inside. Take your time.
What was that?
Well…
I'm glad to see you.
So, you pulled my hair?
Pulling hair can be a way of expression.
What brings you here, by the way?
An attorney comes to the courthouse
for obvious reasons.
COURT 401 ENTRANCE
Don't tell me Kim Su-jeong is your client.
That's none of your business.
Wait.
What now?
Your nose.
It's bleeding.
- Why do I keep having a nosebleed?
- Rest when you can.
Thanks for the advice.
And don't work too hard on this case.
The truth is bound to be revealed.
What does that mean?
Kim Su-jeong murdered her husband
brutally in the bathroom.
Her denial is a lie.
How do you know?
I briefly told you the other day.
A ghost told me.
Let me ask you a favor.
If you see me again,
pretend you don't know me.
We aren't close enough
to exchange happy greetings, you know.
Oh, one more thing.
No one knows where or how Mr. Jeon died.
I-rang, over here.
Why do you have that thing?
Well…
What the heck?
Attorney Han is the defense counsel?
Yes.
Why the long face? Did she tell you off?
She wants me to act like I don't know her.
Are you upset?
I'm just a little sad.
All rise.
Please be seated.
Let the trial commence.
Case 2025-Noh-1361775,
Defendant Kim Su-jeong.
DEFENSE TABLE
Yes.
During the first instance of this case,
Defendant Kim Su-jeong was acquitted
as no evidence was provided
that Jeon Sang-ho was murdered
and the defendant didn't have
the motive to murder him
along with the lack of evidence
that the defendant murdered him.
But after the first verdict,
evidence has been found to prove
that Jeon Sang-ho was murdered
and that the defendant murdered him.
Thus, I set forth
that Defendant Kim Su-jeong is guilty.
Please take a look
at evidence exhibits one and two.
A shower curtain?
I said it was the bathroom.
These two exhibits were found
at the incineration site on the outskirts
of the defendant's residential complex
after the first instance.
The carpet and shower curtain
weren't destroyed by fire
as they were highly noncombustible.
And the blood analysis result
confirmed it to be the victim's blood.
The murder took place in the bathroom.
The body was moved to the living room,
wrapped in the carpet, then moved outside.
…DNA MATCH
WITH THAT OF JEON SANG-HO…
It really was the bathroom?
She should've believed me.
Based on the forensic analysis results,
more than two liters of blood
was absorbed by the carpet,
and Jeon Sang-ho was assumed
to be already dead by then.
He really died?
Your Honor, the prosecution's claim
is all an assumption.
I respect the defense counsel's opinion.
Thus, I'd like
to present additional evidence
that proves Jeon Sang-ho was murdered.
BLOODSTAIN PATTERN ANALYSIS
We conducted a blood pattern analysis
after installing a shower curtain
at the assumed place of murder.
The area of origin
was determined to be very high
with the expiration pattern
to be very small and round.
Based on this analysis,
I contend that Defendant Kim Su-jeong
has an accomplice.
Silence.
Let us hear the prosecution's
legal grounds in more detail.
The area of origin is
higher than 170 cm from the floor,
which assumes that the culprit is
around 180 to 185 cm tall.
The expiration pattern is small and round
with a diameter of less than 3 mm,
which assumes that the act was done
with a quick and powerful force.
This isn't good.
Thus, I've concluded
that the defendant has an accomplice.
That's not true.
Let me ask you, Ms. Kim.
Who is your accomplice?
I object to the evidence
submitted by the prosecution.
The evidence means there's a culprit.
It doesn't indicate the defendant as one.
The only suspect at the moment
is Kim Su-jeong who was in the house.
But she couldn't have done it alone,
so I contend that she has an accomplice.
The prosecution's additional evidence
rather--
I…
I killed my husband.
Ms. Kim, sit down.
I…
I lied.
I did it alone. I killed my husband alone.
The bloodstain was high up because
I was on a step stool when I attacked him.
A kids' step stool.
You murderer!
- You think murder is a joke?
- How could you kill my son?
How dare you!
What's gotten into you?
Why did you make that confession?
It's the truth.
You're protecting your accomplice,
aren't you?
Who is it?
Think of your child, Ms. Kim.
You're a mom.
Think only of your child and tell me.
We need to prove
that you didn't murder your husband
for you to go back to your child.
Who is the accomplice?
The accomplice…
I don't have an accomplice.
Who are you?
Let's have a seat, shall we?
I'm Yang Do-kyung,
the managing partner of Taebaek.
MANAGING PARTNER YANG DO-KYUNG
I have a few questions for you.
Do you remember the man who was with you
when you got arrested?
Damn right, I do.
That damn lunatic.
Will you tell me
what exactly happened that day?
What happened and why you ended up
confessing unnecessarily--
Damn it!
Again?
Just the thought of it pisses me off.
You better tell me
if you don't want
to rot in prison for 20 years.
Twenty years?
You'll be back outside
after all your good years are gone.
Did that man perhaps
behave unusually?
How did you know?
That man acted like Su-a.
Actually, he spoke and acted like Su-a.
He wasn't just like Su-a.
He was Su-a himself.
Ms. Kim.
Could you find me
where Attorney Shin I-rang's office is?
It was Lee Gang-pung.
My underling back in the Oseong Gang,
Lee Gang-pung.
That man acted like Su-a.
NAME: SHIN I-RANG
ADDRESS:
OKCHEON BUILDING, SEOCHO
SEARCH
OKCHEON BUILDING
A shaman's house?
MALE SHAMAN
SHIN I-RANG LAW OFFICE
PITTER-PATTER BUTCHER-STYLE BBQ
That Kim Su-jeong…
She seems to have confessed
to protect her accomplice, hasn't she?
Yes.
Goodness, Sang-ho might go crazy
if he hears this.
- Bong-su.
- What?
We must keep it from him.
It's bad enough that he was murdered.
If he hears that
the culprit is another man, not his wife,
he'll go dark for sure.
Of course, he won't be able to tolerate it
no matter how kind he may be.
What will you do, then?
We can't catch the culprit
with the truth hidden.
And I have to go to work now.
Will you be okay alone?
I'll try to find a way somehow.
A way to catch the culprit
without provoking Sang-ho.
Anyway,
I wonder who visited the shaman.
Maybe his parents did.
In hopes of finding their son's body.
That must be it.
In the SBS drama, Showboating Detective,
which I played a part in,
parents resort to all kinds of means
to find their child's body.
And when the body is found, it has
tons of clues about the perpetrator.
- Bong-su.
- What?
That's it.
A way to catch the culprit
without Sang-ho finding out.
How did it go?
There was nothing much.
Then why was the case retried?
The prosecution appealed.
Your parents must've wanted it.
They asked Kim Su-jeong to tell them
at least where your body was hidden,
but she remained silent until the end.
They probably visited the shaman
to find your body.
Since your body is still missing,
they must be devastated.
Finding my body…
won't change anything.
In some cases,
seeing is the only way to move on.
Perpetrators usually abandon the body
in a place familiar to them.
A place familiar enough for Kim Su-jeong
to abandon a body.
Does anywhere ring a bell?
The places she'd go are home,
her parents' house,
and the lab.
- Oh, right.
- What is it?
Right next to the lab is a potter's field.
It's a small hill,
but no one goes there
because rumors say it's haunted.
Su-jeong and I didn't believe in ghosts,
and it was a nice place to be alone,
so we often went there.
It's perfect for hiding a body.
Let's go right away.
Attorney Han?
How did you know?
Excuse me?
How did you know
that the place of murder was the bathroom?
You won't believe me.
That's right. A ghost told me.
- Then prove it to me.
- Come on.
How am I supposed to prove
what scientists can't?
In the movies,
ghosts lift chairs and break windows.
I won't ask for chair-lifting.
Tell him to lift that.
He can't.
Then tell him to say something to me.
Who is this woman?
Ghosts who visit me
aren't capable of doing such stuff.
They can neither hold nor move things.
I'm the only one who can hear them.
So you have no way to prove it.
Then how am I supposed to see
if you're not talking nonsense?
I have proof.
Look.
Sang-ho wrote this when he possessed me.
Possessed?
You have no intention
of telling me the truth.
Check the handwriting
if you can't believe me.
Ask Sang-ho's family…
Oh, ask Kim Su-jeong. That will do.
I hoped you'd be better than this.
You seriously are the worst.
Attorney Han, watch what you say.
Mr. Shin.
I get that you love money,
but you shouldn't use others.
Those people are already having it hard
even if not for the likes of you.
I'm not like that.
You probably think you have a strong case
now that Ms. Kim came clean.
Dream on.
Su-jeong came clean?
I'll explain it later.
Are you kidding me?
I'm not kidding!
I'm not joking around. I swear.
I'm only trying to reveal the truth.
Can't you just believe me?
What matters to you
is revealing the truth.
That's right.
I will reveal the truth.
So try me with all your might.
I will
crush
all your lies.
What…
She wanted me to prove it,
so I even showed her proof.
Why is she getting worked up?
Check the handwriting
if you can't believe me.
Can't you just believe me?
Hello, Ms. Kim.
Please call Silverwell Laboratory
and ask if I can have access
to Mr. Jeon's office.
Well,
why didn't you tell me
about Su-jeong's confession?
I didn't want you to be heartbroken.
And the credibility of her confession
is in question.
Quite a lot of people
make false confessions in court.
Anything else?
Is there anything else
you couldn't tell me?
No, that's all.
Anyway, aren't we getting there still?
We're almost there.
It's over there.
Come in.
I've contacted the laboratory.
They say you can visit them anytime.
That's good.
This is the number
of a researcher named Gu Hyo-jung.
He wants you to call him when you arrive.
Okay, thank you.
YOU CAN VISIT THE LAB ANYTIME
PLEASE CALL ME BEFORE YOU ARRIVE
It's too big.
I doubt we can find the body.
At least, it's fortunate
that there's only one road
near the potter's field.
And this certainly is
the shortest route to the potter's field.
If I were the culprit,
I'd find somewhere with no CCTV cameras.
Somewhere remote.
CCTV: O
STREETLAMP: O
Somewhere with a side road for cars.
CCTV: X
STREETLAMP: X
Just like that.
The culprit must've taken the body
out of the trunk.
If he dragged the body,
the weeds must've been crushed.
It may have left traces.
I found it.
Gu Hyo-jung speaking.
How many on-site employees are there?
Around 30 researchers.
The management staff and janitors add up
to around ten.
We have a dorm for researchers.
We can't go home often due to work.
I see.
I saw you at the trial this morning.
Yes. I'm a long-time friend of Su-jeong's.
Did you volunteer to be my guide
to tell me something?
Su-jeong
isn't the culprit.
I think it's nearby.
I'll go alone from here.
I don't want you to see.
I'm all right.
It's only an empty shell.
Let's go together.
Okay.
Wait a second.
The color of the soil here is different.
I think it was recently dug up.
Mr. Attorney.
I wonder how Su-jeong moved me
all the way here.
Wait. There's something here.
I was slim, but I weighed 70 kg.
She transferred me in and out of the car,
moved me, and buried me alone?
It makes no sense.
Maybe
she wasn't alone.
If not…
It actually was the Chief's plan
that Sang-ho was to become his son-in-law.
SCIENTIST OF THE YEAR
AWARD CEREMONY
Thank you.
Sang-ho had the best research outcomes,
and the Chief used him to save his wife.
Thank you for considering…
Why didn't I think of it before?
Su-jeong has an accomplice.
Were you aware?
That's not certain yet.
Is that why the trial was held today?
What did Su-jeong say?
You said she confessed.
Did she admit to an accomplice?
Did she admit
to having an accomplice or not?
No.
- She said she killed you alone.
- Why…
Anyone could see that
she has an accomplice, so why…
To protect them.
It was my father-in-law.
Kim Su-jeong refused your visitation.
The truth is, his wife…
Su-jeong's mother is dying
from a rare disease called Concello.
- Then…
- Yes.
Sang-ho was working on a cure
until he suddenly called it quits.
That must've caused it all.
And Su-jeong took the blame.
What are you talking about?
Ms. Kim took the blame for whom?
Isn't it obvious?
The Chief.
Are you saying
Chief Kim Tae-jun is the culprit?
And Ms. Kim confessed for her dad's sake?
No, not for her dad.
For her mom.
Her mother's disease is
paralyzing and atrophying her muscles
as well as destroying her brain cells.
Mom, it's time to eat.
It's me, Su-jeong.
Honey.
- She doesn't recognize anyone…
- I'm right here.
…except her husband, Chief Kim.
When all the evidence pointed to him,
that foolish girl…
…the culprit is around 180 to 185 cm tall…
…the act was done
with a quick and powerful force.
Thus, I've concluded
that the defendant has an accomplice.
I bet Su-jeong couldn't afford
to suspect her dad of killing her husband.
All she had in mind was her mom
who couldn't live without her dad.
I get it now.
That's why she confessed.
Sang-ho, are you okay?
Why…
Will you be able
to testify the same in court?
Yes, I'll do anything for Su-jeong.
This is Sang-ho's office.
I got the temporary passcode.
LAB DIRECTOR: JEON SANG-HO
Look. Sang-ho wrote this
when he possessed me.
- Bong-su.
- Yes?
Where is I-rang?
He's probably in his office with Sang-ho.
He wouldn't answer his phone.
Oh, really?
He texted me.
Bong-su, I've found out
where Sang-ho's body is buried.
I'm on my way to find it with him.
Call me if you read this.
- A body?
- Oh.
He said he'd find Sang-ho's body
to catch whoever killed him.
That must be why.
Alone with the ghost?
Hello, Father.
Yes, I think so. Why do you ask?
He would go ballistic
at the sight of his own dead body.
His rage will be on another level
from that of previous ghosts.
M-Mother, where are you going?
It certainly is Mr. Jeon's handwriting.
I-rang!
Attorney Han?
Attorney Han, have you seen I-rang?
No, I haven't.
Father, where do you think he is?
If he really is possessed,
it would be a place
where Mr. Jeon would go out of rage.
Mr. Jeon is dead.
She might know.
Jeon Sang-ho's wife is her client.
Tell me.
Where would he go if he were alive?
- So, it's--
- No.
Just imagine.
Let's say Mr. Jeon came back to life.
Where would he be at the moment?
Wouldn't he have gone
to the person who killed him?
To take revenge.
Then, he must've gone to Kim Su-jeong.
No.
He must've gone to Kim Tae-jun.
Ms. Attorney,
I need your help.
Who are you?
Don't come any closer.
Stay back.
Why'd you do it?
What are you talking about?
Do what?
Why did you kill me?
W-Who are you?
Did you kill me
because I dropped the research?
Did you get rid of me
because I was no longer of use?
- What are you saying?
- Never mind me.
How could you…
How could you do that
to Su-jeong and U-ju?
Su-jeong is locked up
in a cold prison cell.
My poor son…
My son has lost both his parents.
Do you care only about your wife?
Who are you?
Grandpa.
Grandpa,
I want to pee.
- U-ju!
- U-ju.
U-ju, stay back.
Please show mercy.
I'll give you anything you want,
so don't harm him.
Don't touch my U-ju.
Please show mercy!
Give me back my U-ju.
Give me my son!
Give me U-ju.
Give him to me.
Give me back my son!
I-rang!
I-rang, stop.
No.
Get off me!
I-rang.
Are you back in control?
Mom.
Where…
What…
What have I done?
It's okay now.
Everything's okay now.
It's all right.
I'm Prosecutor Kim Hyeon-u
from the Seocho Branch Office.
Mr. Shin I-rang, you're under arrest
on suspicion of murdering Jeon Sang-ho
and abandoning his body.
You have the right to an attorney
and the right to remain silent.
M-Murder?
- Arrest him.
- No, wait.
My son killed whom?
We found Jeon Sang-ho's body,
and his fingerprints were found
on the gloves that were dropped nearby.
It's a misunderstanding.
You're mistaken.
I can explain it all.
No, please wait.
- Hold on.
- Please, what in the world…
- It's not me.
- Mother.
- Let go of me. I didn't do it!
- I-rang!
Why did my son-in-law's attorney
come here?
Did you think
the culprit was your father-in-law?
- Then, why did you turn yourself in?
- Mom will die without Dad.
I'm only saying it
because there has been no progress!
You must've hated him enough to kill him,
Mr. Kim Tae-jun.
I'll find the real culprit.
If that's Kim Tae-jun,
I'll put him behind bars.
With his farsightedness
and fogged-up glasses,
he must've had to attack several times.
Your father killed me.
How could you do that to me?
How could you possibly do that to me?
Subtitle translation by:
Eunjin Erica Kim