ALL FIGURES, INCIDENTS,
LOCATIONS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND OTHERS ARE FICTITIOUS.
CHILD ACTORS
AND ANIMALS WERE FILMED
SAFELY IN ACCORDANCE
WITH GUIDELINES.
Could one of these talismans
be my husband's?
Perhaps, but you should not
be too quick to touch it.
We don't know how your son
is connected to the talismans yet.
Oh, right.
Anyway,
what is it that you want to find here?
I-rang told me something before.
How did you come to see that ghost?
There was a desk
that used to belong to the shaman.
I found an old incense burner
in the drawer.
That incense burner seems to be the cause.
But I can't find it.
Then, what?
I better look for the male shaman
who used to summon spirits here.
Let me.
I can do it myself.
It's better to be safe than sorry.
Sorry?
You could say otherwise later.
I'm not like that.
It doesn't matter what you're like.
It's just that I don't trust people.
Why? Why don't you trust people?
It was dangerous back there.
The cross light was red.
Oh, that.
I go out of control from time to time.
What were you doing here?
Glory Entertainment is my new client.
What about you?
Are you hired for a case or something?
No, that's not it.
It's an entertainment agency, you know.
Where artists are.
I was there to see my favorite artist.
- What?
- An idol.
That's on nice and snug.
Was he serious or joking?
He certainly is an oddball.
Who was that woman earlier?
Oh, she's an attorney.
She defended the other side
during my previous case.
Do you have a crush on her?
Are you interested
when you shouldn't be into her?
What are you saying?
Your face was super red like an apple.
That was because I was possessed!
I'm not angry.
I know.
I'm just sorry.
You almost got into an accident
because of me.
I didn't, so it's okay.
Anyway, why did you
run after Ko Jong-seok?
His ringtone was
the one I heard when I died.
What?
Excuse me.
Who are you?
I'm an attorney
working for Glory Entertainment.
Could I check the footage
of the security camera in the hallway?
Nice timing. I was meaning
to call the police anyway.
- The police?
- You say you're an attorney.
Isn't this why you're here?
PITTER-PATTER BUTCHER-STYLE BBQ
Why are you taking that?
Luckily, this truck
was parked by the road.
Something must've been captured.
Da-bong!
- Welcome home.
- Uncle!
It's so nice to see you.
- Did you have a good day?
- Yes.
Uncle, what happened to your hand?
Did you get hurt?
I-rang.
Did you hurt your hand?
What? Who got hurt? I-rang?
No, it's nothing.
Yes, it's something.
Look. It's wrapped in a bandage.
It's a slight scratch. I'm okay.
- I'm really okay.
- But…
I-rang, let me see your hand.
Goodness.
Geez…
Mother.
What is it? Do we have a large party?
No. I-rang got hurt.
Got hurt?
I was too complacent.
Mother, relax. Calm down.
I'm only letting you know
in case you're curious.
It's not a serious injury.
I'll look into what happened.
Okay.
It may be related to the ghost,
so go and watch him closely.
Yes, Mother.
A ghost?
Well…
Customers love our new dish?
Yes, Mother.
They're obsessed with our new dish
like ghosts. They love it.
What are you two playing at?
STORAGE DEVICE
I-rang.
What happened? Did something happen?
Well, it's nothing.
But…
- One moment.
- Okay.
It starts from here.
What is he doing?
Isn't that the attorney from Taebaek?
Yes, it's Attorney Han.
Right, Attorney Han.
Him…
I told you. He's the vocal trainer.
It looks like
Attorney Han was going after him.
Wait, what?
You were going after him too.
But,
that… wasn't me.
Are we with her?
Hello.
What a nutjob.
I know, right?
Is this enough to find that lunatic?
What?
Yes.
Excuse me for a moment.
Hi, Na-hyun.
When you arrested Cho Gi-cheol,
Attorney Shin I-rang was there, right?
Yes, he was.
Did you interview him as a witness?
Yes, I did.
How did he know about that place?
I asked him the same question,
and he said he got the info
from an unidentified source.
- A source?
- Yes.
He didn't tell me who until the end.
I couldn't question him more
because he helped our investigation.
But why do you ask?
It's nothing. I gotta go.
Wait!
Attorney Shin?
What made him get so worked up?
Did he argue with Ko Jong-seok?
BACKGROUND CHECK REPORT
CRIMINAL RECORDS CHECK REPORT
CHARGE:
COPYRIGHT INFRINGEMENT
NOT GUILTY
COUNTERSUED FOR FALSE ACCUSATION
FAMOUS SONGWRITER KO JONG-SEOK
SUED FOR COPYRIGHT INFRINGEMENT…
"Copyright infringement"?
Something smells fishy for sure.
But he's a really nice guy.
He cooked for us trainees at his house.
He gave us private lessons too.
Is your phone an Android?
Yes.
Give me your account ID and password.
The ID is "cheerupsu-a."
"Cheer up, Su-a."
The password is "grandma0314."
Let's see.
What are you trying to do?
If her phone is connected
to this web portal,
it can be tracked
even if it's out of service.
But I doubt the culprit has Su-a's phone.
It's possible if something important
is saved on her phone.
You said you visited his house, right?
Where is that?
It's near Riverland.
Wait.
KIM SU-A'S PHONE
No way.
RIVERLAND
Should we report it to the police?
Not yet. We need to gather more evidence.
How?
I better look more into Ko Jong-seok.
Do you know
what tamed the wolf to be like the dog?
Pardon?
A chunk of meat.
A chunk of meat thrown to a wolf
that was cast out from the group.
After getting a taste of meat
without having to make an effort,
the wolf became a loyal dog.
Now,
what will happen if it only takes the meat
and doesn't show its loyalty?
Let's say it even bites the giving hand.
What should be done to that dog?
Yes, I'm listening.
Would you take in that bastard
if it were you?
P-Please show mercy.
Memorize this.
It's your script in court.
You'll be released before you turn 70.
It's because of that damn attorney!
That punk
was unhinged. I'm telling you.
Everyone is unhinged in this crazy world.
It was Lee Gang-pung.
My underling back in the Oseong Gang,
Lee Gang-pung.
Who?
I know…
it sounds ridiculous and crazy.
The name.
What's the name again?
Lee Gang-pung.
The truth is, Lee Gang-pung was…
a gangster.
Keep talking.
That damn attorney was a weakling
until his eyes suddenly changed.
Who are you?
Me?
I'm gangster attorney, Lee Gang-pung!
It made no sense at all.
It turns out that punk--
He died…
while getting surgery for his snoring.
Keep your mouth shut until I come back.
Look more into Shin I-rang Law Office.
Everything including its location,
employees, and clients.
Yes, sir.
MR. KIM'S REAL ESTATE OFFICE
- Hello.
- Welcome.
Well…
I'd like to get in touch
with the male shaman,
the former tenant
of Okcheon Building's Unit 501.
Why would a priest want to reach a shaman?
Beats me.
Things just turned out that way.
Have a seat.
PITTER-PATTER BUTCHER-STYLE BBQ
Can you go check
if Ko Jong-seok is inside?
Okay.
But…
Well, good luck then.
You can do it.
She left already.
How fast.
Good luck to us too.
What's taking her so long?
What if something happened?
This won't do. I'm going inside for a bit.
Wait, let me go with you.
One of us has to stay here just in case.
I'll call you if something happens.
Then, take this at least.
What is it?
I bought it online.
W-Why do you carry this with you?
I bought it for Sa-rang.
It's a frightening world, you know.
Whoa, man!
Sorry.
You shouldn't be spacing out here.
- Let's get out for now.
- You're a flower
With a scent that has yet
- What are you doing?
- To bloom
- It's my song.
- You're a flower
What?
- I wrote that song and even its lyrics.
- With many dreams that have yet
To be dreamt
- I want you to dazzle like a day in spring
- I want you to hold the blue sky
I wrote this song
in hopes for people to feel happy
when they listen to my music.
GLORY ENTERTAINMENT
LOANNE
I'd work part-time at night
after practicing all day.
I thought it was unfair.
BEAUTIFUL FLOWER
I wasn't like other trainees.
I didn't have what they naturally had.
But I didn't want
to waste time complaining.
Even though I was born poor,
I believed I could change my life.
I was going to live differently.
This is why he killed you.
And why your phone was gone from the roof.
But how did he know?
People don't know
that my songs are saved on my phone.
Songwriting is a piece of cake.
Which song should be next?
My phone.
That piece of trash.
He deserves a taste of burning hell.
What the heck?
Hey.
Did you know that there are
others who know that Su-a wrote songs?
And you didn't…
I better meet with her first.
Who is he talking about?
Emma.
It talks to me
I used to tremble all night long
But I'm going to be a star now
The end!
Are you for real!
How do you write such lyrics?
Stop. You're making me embarrassed.
Emma, you have to keep this
from everyone else, okay?
I'll give it some thought.
You know what?
I'm suddenly craving some milk tea.
Oh, come on!
Don't tell anyone!
Emma knows almost all my songs.
Of course!
I can't use any of Su-a's songs
if someone else knows about them.
Who is he talking to?
It's someone who knows you and Emma
and that you wrote songs.
It's probably Abel.
Three, four, five--
Hey!
Move to the left.
To the left, not to the right! Must I keep
repeating myself? Are you an idiot?
I'm sick and tired of this.
You piss me off.
I often got mad at Abel
because she kept making mistakes.
She probably hated my guts.
Does she know about your songs too?
EVERYWHERE YOUR FOOTSTEP TOUCHES
She saw me write songs.
She must've told Mr. Ko about it.
Ask her to meet up immediately.
I'll be there too.
She's in danger.
- Let's hurry after him.
- Okay.
Who is it?
I'm Attorney Han Na-hyun.
- An attorney?
- Attorney Han?
I'm from Taebaek Law Firm,
which recently signed
a partnership with Glory Entertainment.
Wait a moment, please.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Are you alone?
- Yes.
What brings you all the way here?
Do you remember the man
who barged into the company yesterday?
Yes, what about that wacko?
He assaulted a guard.
The CEO asked me to secure his information
in case of future trouble.
And?
I checked the footage
and saw you two talk.
Did you notice anything strange?
Yes, I did.
He acted like Loanne.
He was totally into her.
You mean, the trainee who died of a fall?
Yes.
It happens. Perverted wackos
that approach us acting like they're fans.
That little…
Perverted wacko…
How dare he humiliate that poor girl
who committed suicide.
You were in the building
the day Loanne died.
Did you perhaps meet her?
No. I didn't even see her that day.
Is that right?
Then, I guess you're clueless
about why she made her choice.
Hold on.
Why are you suddenly asking me this?
Aren't you after that perverted wacko?
I am.
I apologize if it offended you.
I'm busy right now.
Please leave.
Thank you for your cooperation.
- Yeah?
- Bong-su.
Ko Jong-seok left home.
Please follow him and keep me updated.
- Is it Ko Jong-seok?
- Oh, my goodness.
Is he your favorite artist?
How did you know I was here?
It was hard not to know.
PITTER-PATTER BUTCHER-STYLE BBQ
Anyway, why were you in the house?
It's a long story.
I'm a bit busy right now.
You still have to explain.
Or I'll report you for trespassing.
It's about Su-a, the girl who fell
from Glory Entertainment's rooftop.
So, Ko Jong-seok killed Su-a
over her songs
and he still has her phone?
You have quite the imagination.
It's a fact, not my imagination.
I see, a fact.
Then, let me fact-check something too.
How did you know all these details?
That's…
It's not only this time.
You knew that the hard disk was
with Cho Gi-cheol
and that Attorney Byeon
and Managing Partner Yang met in private.
How did you get your hands
on such secret and private information
known only to the parties involved?
It's natural you'd find it strange.
I'd love to tell you everything
and get it off my chest.
But I have no time.
I must go now, or it'll be dangerous
for the girl who knows about Su-a's songs.
Who is that girl?
Emma, a Glory trainee.
Let's go together.
Glory artists are my clients,
and I'm obliged to protect my clients.
Then, can you find Abel?
She's another Glory trainee
involved in this case.
Please stop her
from committing more crimes.
I'll go to Emma.
Do you even know where they are?
Oh, I need you to locate them too.
I'll get their locations
through the prosecution.
- Thank you.
- In exchange,
be honest with me after this case
about who you work with
and who's helping you.
Okay.
By the way,
could I borrow…
You mean, my car?
Turn right ahead.
That's Emma's car.
Thank goodness,
we arrived before Ko Jong-seok.
Who is that?
Attorney Shin?
What are you doing here?
Did you follow me?
No, listen to me--
Don't come close.
I'll call the police.
Okay.
I'll talk from over here.
You…
were asked to come here by Abel, right?
What?
What are you talking about?
Su-a left her self-written songs
on her phone.
How did you know?
I heard her phone was missing.
And in her phone,
there's even video of Su-a singing them.
The one you took.
So, how did you--
What matters more than your question
is that Ko Jong-seok committed murder
for Su-a's songs and took her phone.
He even saw the video you took.
It can't be.
He's trying to kill you too
for knowing that.
He can't use Su-a's songs
as long as you know them.
Mr. Ko couldn't have done such a thing.
Su-a said the same.
When?
Were you acquainted with her
when she was alive?
Well, it's too complicated to explain.
Oh, no. He's here already.
Here. Keep this with you.
I'll try talking to him,
but if he acts violently,
don't hesitate to…
Okay?
Okay.
Mister, watch out!
What the? What's going on?
Wait. This punk…
Why? Do you know him?
He's a wacko Loanne fan.
Why is he sprawled out here?
I took care of him.
He knows that you were with Loanne
on the day she died.
What are you talking about?
No one else was there except us.
Exactly!
I don't know how,
but he even knows
about the songs saved on that cow's phone.
We have to act quickly. Where's the phone?
Here.
Found it.
With fingerprints as perfect evidence.
Give it back to me now.
But I definitely…
I expected it
and removed the battery in advance.
You expected it?
Oh, one more thing.
Can you go to Glory Entertainment
and find me the Tomorrow Idol scorecard?
ATTORNEY HAN NA-HYUN
ROUND 9 SCORECARD
2ND LOANNE
8TH EMMA
I get it now.
What?
With only the final round left,
you were ranked second
while Emma was ranked eighth
and Abel was ranked 12th.
According to the rules,
only the top seven can debut.
Emma can be part of the group
only if one of the top seven is gone.
And Abel was not likely to debut at all.
So?
In most cases, the culprit is…
whoever benefits the most.
And that's Emma in this case.
Geez. I hoped otherwise,
but a bad hunch always hits the mark.
Ko Jong-seok!
See?
It's way too obvious.
What do we do now, I-rang?
Ko Jong-seok will come to where I will be.
I want you to wait nearby
and get him when he runs away from me.
Y-You want me to get him?
You must've played a detective role.
You know the Miranda warning, right?
Who are you?
Detective Yoon Bong-su
from Gangnam PD's Violent Crimes Unit 1.
You're under arrest for
aggravated robbery and gangster murder.
You have the right to consult silence.
And you have the right
to remain an attorney.
Don't move.
Mister, hurry up!
Don't move!
Running away won't do.
Who are you to lecture me?
Me?
I told you. I'm Su-a's attorney.
She doesn't have an attorney. She's dead!
A dead person also needs an attorney
if they died a wrongful death.
Let's go get you punished
for what you did.
Mister, wait.
Can you ask her why she did it?
It's useless now.
We were friends.
I want to know why she did it.
Okay, I'll ask her.
What's with him? He's scaring me.
Su-a wants to know why you killed her.
You really are nuts, aren't you?
You were friends once.
Why did you kill your friend?
Friend?
Bullshit.
Not once have I considered Su-a a friend.
You make friends with those at your level.
Do you think she was at my level?
I took all kinds of lessons
thanks to my parents' support.
And I always got satisfying results.
I was so happy
until Su-a joined the agency.
Hello, my name is Kim Su-a.
I hope we get along.
She was wearing clothes
that my family wouldn't even use as rags,
but that didn't faze her.
I'll do my best!
She was rather proud
that she had three part-time jobs.
APPLE JUICE
I'm sorry about earlier.
I was rash and lost my temper.
I'm sorry.
If you're sorry,
teach me how to play the guitar.
I hear it's easy to write songs
knowing chords.
Okay.
Su-a would get worked up
without knowing her place,
but strangely, the girls were fond of her.
They easily accepted her apology.
They understood and liked her.
It was annoying.
EMMA
FINAL RANK: 7TH, B
- Loanne!
- You're amazing, Loanne!
1ST, 96 POINTS
LOANNE
Su-a was always better than me.
She was just born
with what I couldn't have
even after I gave it my all.
It was so unfair.
Emma, congratulations.
We'll be able to debut together.
I wanted to tear that mouth of hers.
Let's have tteokbokki today.
I got my paycheck.
It's on me to congratulate you.
- Sweet.
- What do you say?
You're a devil.
A filthy devil
who rattles me all the time.
It talks to me
I used to tremble all night long
But I'm going to be a star now
The end!
Are you for real!
How do you write such lyrics?
Emma, you have to keep this
from everyone else, okay?
I'll give it some thought.
BEAUTIFUL FLOWER, STAR, DON'T STOP,
STREET FULL OF SUNSHINE…
Maybe you really are a genius.
No, I just wrote these in my spare time.
Can you send me this song?
It might cheer me up
when things are tough.
Okay.
But don't share it with anyone else.
- I collected her songs one after another.
- These too.
You wrote all these?
I wrote them in my spare time.
A little childish, right?
Childish? No way. They're amazing.
Actually, this can be your debut song.
- Really?
- Yeah!
From that moment, I started
to have more reasons to get rid of her.
She isn't even our leader.
I can't stand watching her act up anymore.
Let's tell them we'll all drop out
if she doesn't.
The CEO won't be able to ignore us
because of my dad's investment.
I threatened the girls
and forced Su-a out of the audition.
Everything went as I wanted.
I followed her up to the rooftop
because I wanted to see her sob.
I thought I'd feel great
to see her in despair.
Why the heck is she smiling?
She got removed from the audition,
but why is she looking happy?
Push her off there.
What?
Push her off.
This isn't the end of her.
That girl will crawl back up
and get on your nerves for sure.
What if people find out
that she wrote all those songs?
I can't let that happen.
That's right. If she dies,
all her songs will be yours.
Push her off and take her phone. Now!
- Did you just…
- No.
…push Su-a?
I said, no!
I have to report this. You killed Su-a!
Are you sure I killed her?
What?
Or maybe you killed her
to snatch her songs.
What are you saying?
Su-a is the one who wrote that debut song.
You said you wrote it.
Did I?
I don't remember.
Report me.
Then, I'll tell them you stole her song.
You think I won't do anything about it?
Go ahead, do whatever you can!
I doubt the police will believe you
with all those suspicions
of copyright infringement.
Su-a trusted Mr. Ko.
But he… Su-a…
What do you think?
You've lost your mind.
A lot of her songs
are saved on this phone.
You can't even write songs
without plagiarizing.
With this,
you and I don't have anything to fear.
How could you…
How could you do that?
I thought we were friends.
What's wrong with you?
Are you crazy?
Is it my fault for being poor?
Is it my fault for doing
all that I can for myself?
Get back, you lunatic.
Shut your damn mouth!
I was excited
at the thought of debuting with you.
I was so happy that it felt like a dream.
What are you saying, psycho?
Who the hell are you?
Me?
Your agency's attorney.
My agency's attorney?
Don't be glad.
I have no intention of helping a murderer.
Who are you calling a murderer?
Ko Jong-seok confessed it all.
And we got Su-a's phone too.
You won't get away this time.
What are you doing? Get up.
Are you crying?
Who's crying?
You got many texts mourning you.
It was Abel.
What was?
She knew that you were writing songs.
Dear Su-a.
Su-a,
I loved the songs you wrote
because I could always feel
warmth and hope from your songs.
I didn't know she was feeling this way.
Sincerity is bound to reach someone.
Now, should we find your mom's number?
I guess it's the one from your last call.
Right.
CALL HISTORY
MOM
Here it is.
Mister, wait.
What is it?
Do you think
she should be informed that I'm dead?
Don't you want to see her?
I do, but…
How about this, then?
I'll use this number
to find where your mom is.
Then you can just look at her from afar.
Okay.
HOSEONG SEOUL HOSPITAL
All right.
Things aren't looking good.
I see.
You have a month at the longest
until you go completely blind.
It's not enough time to find a donor.
Right.
Oh, did you meet the person
you wanted to meet?
Not yet.
You need to hurry.
Your sight will get worse and worse.
Okay.
Mom…
Her medical record says
that she was diagnosed
with viral keratitis 18 years ago.
Eighteen years ago?
That's when I was one.
BABY FORMULA
Ow!
Su-a, are you okay?
Oh, no.
- I'm so sorry.
- She sent me to Grandma…
Su-a.
…to protect me.
GLORY'S NEW FACE, TRAINEE KIM SU-A
MY SU-A IS THE BEST
MY SU-A
Su-a?
It's Mom.
My dear Su-a,
you grew up to be such a pretty girl.
Thank you.
Su-a.
Will you…
meet me just once?
The reason she called was…
because she wanted to see me
one last time before she lost her sight.
Mister.
Yes?
I have one last favor to ask of you.
Will you do it for me?
Name anything.
I'm…
your attorney.
Kim Su-a registered herself
as an organ donor when she was alive.
And after her death,
four precious lives were saved.
Our organization is keeping her corneas.
Family donation is perfectly legal.
I see. Thank you.
I want to…
give my eyes to my mom.
I got them from her.
It's only right
that I give them back to her.
Now, try to open your eyes slowly.
Mom.
Yes, can you see me?
I can.
I…
I see you so clearly.
What do I do?
I feel so bad for our Su-a.
I don't know what to do, Mom.
Live your life to the fullest.
For Su-a. That will do.
I will.
Good.
To the fullest,
I'll live a happy life for sure.
Good.
That will do.
My precious daughter.
- Mom.
- I'm proud of you, my daughter.
Thanks to you,
I can rest in peace now.
There's no need to rush.
You can stay with your mom and grandma
and take your time to pass on.
It's okay.
This is enough already.
My daughter.
Thank you, Su-a.
Now,
my mom will protect Grandma,
and Grandma will protect Mom.
I'm ready to pass on.
The shaman wasn't home.
I asked the neighbors,
and they said they didn't see him lately.
It might take a little longer.
He'll be okay
since your son is not alone.
"…for his outstanding performance."
"Presented by Yoon Da-bong."
Here you go.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
- Thank you, Mother.
- Congrats, Bong-su.
It wasn't me alone.
He has his beloved family.
And he seems to have gotten someone
he can open up to.
Thanks to you, Su-a's case was resolved.
Thank you so much.
You should rather be sorry.
Because of you,
I had to report my own client.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
Well,
it didn't seem intentional,
so forget the apology.
Now, tell me.
You promised you'd tell me
who you worked with after the case.
It's not hard to tell you,
but I'm afraid you won't believe it.
I've been through
countless unbelievable cases.
So don't worry.
This one is completely different, though.
Ghosts.
What?
I can see and communicate
with dead people.
This time, it was Su-a.
Last time, Lee Gang-pung's spirit told me.
So…
Easily put,
spirits of dead people
tell me their resentful stories--
Enough.
And my office used to be
a shaman's house--
I said, enough.
Okay.
Let's stop here.
It's a waste of time
dealing with you anymore.
This is why I was reluctant to tell you.
You're the one who urged me.
Actually, it's better not to believe me.
Oh, I'm late.
LOANNE,
I'LL REMEMBER YOU FOREVER
WE LOVE YOU, LOANNE
LOANNE IS MY WORLD, MY LIGHT
WE'LL BE WITH YOU UNTIL THE END
You're a flower
With a scent that has yet
I WANT YOU TO HOLD THE BLUE SKY
To bloom
You're a flower
With many dreams that have yet
To be dreamt
I want you to dazzle like a day in spring
I want you to hold the blue sky
How beautiful you will look
How splendid your tomorrow will be
I know
I know it all…
THANK YOU FOR YOUR WARM COMFORT
I LOVE YOU
YOU'RE ALIVE
AS LONG AS WE REMEMBER YOU
I HOPE YOU DANCE WITH ANGELS NOW
LOANNE!
I MISS YOU!
WITH YOUR MUSIC
UNTIL I SEE YOU AGAIN
Bloom like a flower
You're so beautiful
In my eyes
You have become even more beautiful
LET'S MEET AGAIN FOR SURE
Farewell, Su-a.
I'll listen to your songs every day,
and I'll remember your voice.
You better. I'll be watching from above.
Thank you, mister.
I'm sorry for causing you trouble.
Su-a is looking at the two of you.
Bye, Su-a.
Goodbye, Su-a.
Oh.
I'll miss you.
Be happy in heaven.
Thank you.
I'll miss you so much too.
She says she'll miss you so much too.
Goodbye.
Take care.
ATTORNEY SHIN I-RANG
I'M SORRY ABOUT EARLIER
AND TRY LISTENING TO THIS!
He's tiresome.
BEAUTIFUL FLOWER
Tteokbokki, sundae,
and fish cakes. Agreed?
- You're a flower
- And fried dumplings on top, agreed.
- Agreed. Sounds great.
- Sounds great.
With a scent that has yet
To bloom
You're a flower
With many dreams that have yet
To be dreamt
I want you to dazzle like a day in spring
I want you to hold the blue sky
- How beautiful you will look…
- Sweet dreams.
GOING TO A CONCERT WITH NA-HYUN!
How splendid your tomorrow will be
I know
I know it all
CERTIFICATE OF COMPLETION
JUDICIAL TRAINEE HAN NA-HYUN
Beautiful flower
Beautiful you…
THE 48TH JUDICIAL TRAINING
COMPLETION CEREMONY
Bloom like a flower
You're so beautiful
In my eyes
You have become even more beautiful
- I miss you more especially today.
- Beautiful flower, beautiful you
Bloom like a flower…
You're here again.
I handed over all the documents
related to Glory Entertainment.
Noted.
Here.
What is it?
Of all the cases that Taebaek has taken,
this one is the biggest headache
in the very center of the media spotlight.
Shouldn't you be reflecting on yourself?
I hear the Chairman is recovering fast.
That's none of your business.
If we win this case,
there would be nothing better
as a welcome back gift for the chairman.
I'll gift wrap it with care
so that you can take the credit.
A gift?
- What if we lose?
- Then,
you'll have a reason to kick me out.
You won't suffer any losses either way.
Don't let me down this time.
I won't.
WOMAN FOUND NOT GUILTY
FOR BRUTALLY MURDERING
HER HUSBAND…
Welcome.
It must've been a long way coming here.
Who are you?
I'm your attorney, Shin I-rang.
Who is it this time?
He seems to have majored in science.
Is the culprit your wife?
Are you really trying to kill me?
You had a bright future,
and she killed you.
I'll have to meet Kim Su-jeong.
A place familiar enough for Kim Su-jeong
to abandon a body.
Does anywhere ring a bell?
He would lose his cool
at the sight of his own dead body.
Wouldn't he have gone
to the person who killed him?
Then, he must've gone to Kim Su-jeong.
Why did you kill me?
Subtitle translation by: Eunjin Erica Kim