[Episode 3]
Dad.
- Save him!
- Stop rushing me.
Hurry up!
Chu San, who exactly is this person?
This is a gunshot wound!
- Are you hurt?
- I'm fine.
Hurry up and save him, Dad!
The angle of this bullet is tricky.
My presbyopia is making it hard to see clearly.
How about you help him take it out?
I...
Saving him is more important! Hurry up!
Give it to me! Hurry up!
Be quick!
Come on!
Find it first.
Disinfection.
Dad.
It's okay. Take a deep breath.
Deep breaths.
You need to push the tweezers
all the way to the bottom in one go.
When you feel it touch the bullet,
immediately squeeze it tight
and pull it out quickly.
Be quick and decisive.
We can't worsen the wound.
Hurry up.
Pull it out.
Stop the bleeding.
All done.
How did you get involved with such a person?
And you brought him home?
He saved me before.
What happened to you?
He saved you?
I was robbed before.
He chased them away.
I already told you before.
Just give robbers the money.
Dad.
Didn't you teach me to repay kindness?
I've done everything I can.
Next, we'll see if this little brat
is tough enough to survive.
The triads.
They're all debt collectors.
You should rest early, too.
Aren't you the mighty Dual Blades Xia?
How did you end up like this?
Chu San, he still hasn't woken up?
No.
[He Chu San]
This damn kid.
Wild horse splitting its mane.
Your horse stance has to be firm.
Right.
Good. Next move.
Listen up!
White crane spreads its wings.
Raise your hands higher.
Right.
This is it.
Don't wobble your legs.
Good, now continue.
Wave your hands like playing the lute.
Good.
Next move.
Come on, keep going.
Focus, stop looking around.
Master, you can go on.
I have to get to school.
All right.
You're awake.
How do you feel?
What exactly happened?
How did you get hurt like this?
Where are Xiao Ma and the others?
And your sister?
Beef tripe.
I want beef tripe.
Okay.
- Is it ready, Fei?
- Coming right up, I'll serve it to you.
I'll beat you to death.
Let's go.
Seen this person before?
No.
Fei, hurry up!
Seen this person before?
- No.
- Look carefully.
- Never seen him.
- Really?
- No.
- Fucking hell.
Your dad had cancer back then.
Your mom went door to door begging for money.
We spent money and effort to help.
Now you're acting all high and mighty.
Trying to show off, huh?
Ask your dad's spirit in heaven
if he recognizes you.
You bitch, what did you say?
Come on, say it! Say it!
What did you say? Say it louder!
She'll never let go of that few bucks.
- Exactly.
- No wonder you're poor.
Say it louder, come on!
Come on, let's go.
Hao, did I hurt you?
A real man doesn't mind a small injury.
This tiny scratch is nothing.
Sister, don't worry.
Even if it's just a scrape,
I'll still be worried about you.
Hao, does it still hurt now?
Sister, it doesn't hurt anymore.
Before you eat the beef tripe,
take your medicine first.
Open it.
There are a lot of gangsters outside
looking for you.
They said you are a traitor of Xiaoqi Hall.
Water.
- Why...
- Cigarettes.
No cigarettes.
You're injured.
You can't smoke.
Give me cigarettes.
If you smoke, the medicine will be useless.
Cigarettes.
No cigarettes.
It's bad for your health.
Recover.
Then leave.
Bro.
Sister.
Bro. Sister.
How did you bleed so much?
Sister.
I'll get Dad.
Don't go.
I'm not leaving.
I'll get you some water.
You were calling for
your brother and sister in your dream.
Where are they?
They're dead.
Before, I lived in Xitou Lane.
When I was little,
I was always thinking about
how to fill my stomach.
My dad...
He was a drug addict.
He sniffed drugs.
He gambled.
He drank heavily.
And my mom.
After giving birth to me,
she ran off with someone else.
My sister is three years older than me.
When other children were still clueless,
she already knew how to cook noodles
to comfort me.
My dad often beat us.
He made us steal things for him.
If we couldn't steal,
he would beat us severely.
My sister always stood in front of me.
She got beaten so badly
she couldn't get out of bed.
When I was ten,
my dad wanted to sell my sister
to be a prostitute.
I grabbed her and ran away.
He caught us and brought us back.
It happened in an alley.
He almost beat me to death.
Dad, stop hitting me.
I'll kill you!
Get out of the way!
Move!
Trying to run again?
You still want to run?
Still running?
I'll kill you!
Long!
- Long!
- Hao, are you okay?
Are you all right?
It was Qing Long who saved me.
He just glanced at my dad.
My dad immediately knelt and kowtowed to him.
Let me treat you to some cake, okay?
Long!
Long, please spare me!
Eat up.
What are your names?
I'm Xia Xiao Man.
He's called Hao.
I'm not called Hao. He gave me that name.
Be good, Hao.
If you dislike the name Hao so much,
what name do you want?
Call me...
Call me Cake. I like cake.
I'll be called Cake.
There are so many
delicious things in the world.
But you just want to be named
after what you like to eat?
I don't care, I don't care.
I'll be called Cake.
Because I like cake.
How about this?
You are Liu Yi from now on.
Every day, we'll celebrate Children's Day.
And I'll treat you to cake every day, okay?
Okay.
He said...
June 1st is Children's Day.
It belongs to me.
It's a holiday for me and my sister.
Later, we moved into the old house.
Here.
Where do you want to reach by next year?
This year, you're at this height.
Here.
This tall?
Then I'll lift you to this height.
Xiao Man wants to grow this tall.
Hao wants to be taller than you.
Bro knew that sister loved singing.
So, he sent her to study the arts.
Knowing I liked to play with knives and sticks,
he found a master to teach me.
When I grew up,
I begged him to let me
perform rituals in the hall
and acknowledge him as the boss.
In the first few years,
he wouldn't let me go out on tasks,
saying I was too young.
I could just stay by his side, that was enough.
When I was 18, he was ambushed.
He only had a few men with him.
They were trapped in an alley.
I went crazy, grabbing two knives,
and rushed in to save him.
When I rescued him,
he slapped me.
He said...
even if he died,
he wouldn't want me
to risk my life to save him.
After that,
he told the elders,
that I should be promoted to Red Rod.
That guy...
He can be so contradictory.
My sister grew up.
She got more and more beautiful.
Many bigshots took a liking to her.
Qing Long tried to matchmake for her.
She didn't want any of them.
One day,
she secretly told me
that she was in love with Qing Long.
She wanted to be Qing Long's woman.
And shortly after,
it would be my 20th birthday.
Qing Long asked me what I wanted.
I...
I said...
I wanted my sister to be his wife.
Liu Yi.
Brother, you're here.
What's on your mind?
Nothing.
You're about to turn twenty.
What birthday gift do you want?
Birthday?
Will you agree to anything I want?
Of course. I care about you so much.
I want...
my sister to be your wife.
I hope the three of us
can be like a real family.
Forever together.
Okay.
I promise you.
Brother, I knew you were the best to me.
He agreed.
He married my sister.
He even made me
a new pair of Qing Long dual blades.
He also took me to meet the elders of the gang,
and told them
that from now on, part of the gang's business
would gradually be handed to me to manage.
After that,
I became his right-hand man.
He was my boss.
And my sister became the missus boss.
I thought it would be like this forever.
That day,
I went to pick up my sister.
She jumped off the building.
And Bog Brother was killed, too...
He was killed with...
the Qing Long dual blades
he gave me.
I failed to protect them.
I failed.
It was...
that bastard Xu Ying.
He swapped my sister's medicine,
causing her to relapse.
He killed my brother
and tried to frame me.
The people chasing me
were his men.
So...
what do you plan to do now?
Kill him.
Avenge my brother
and my sister.
Take revenge.
Then what?
Then...
You joined Xiaoqi Hall for Qing Long.
You want to kill Xu Ying to take revenge.
And after that?
Take care of the men Qing Long left behind.
And grow Xiaoqi Hall
into the biggest gang in the city.
[Earn big money and buy a huge house for Dad]
Innocent student.
Dad, I'll bring the medicine up.
Okay.
You walk so quietly.
You scared me to death.
Liu Yi.
Your eyelids seem a little swollen.
Rub them with an egg.
Don't get me wrong about last night.
I wasn't whining.
I know.
I'm not looking for your sympathy either.
Okay.
I...
I just wanted something to talk to.
There isn't even a single chicken here.
I want beef offal for breakfast.
Dad said you should
take this medicine before meals.
Here.
I won't take it. It smells awful.
- Beef offal.
- No.
Dad said the herbal medicine
must be taken before meals.
Three times a day.
Not a single dose can be skipped.
Three times?
That's enough to kill a rat!
Go away.
Throw it out!
Dad, someone's trying to
feed your medicine to the rats.
Who dares to mess with my medicine?
Him.
Gangsters have no education.
Don't you have any education either?
If the patient refuses the medicine,
can't you do something?
Why study so much?
When people get sick,
how can they get better without medicine?
Bitter medicine is good for you.
Chu San.
Chu San, don't laugh.
Hold his hands down.
Don't move.
Dad, you really know what to do.
How could a doctor be stumped by a patient?
Chu San, remember to change his dressing.
You little punk.
You better hope I never get better.
If I do get better,
you'll be the first on my hit list.
It might hurt a little.
It'll be over soon.
Liu Yi.
You need to sit up a bit.
Put more strength into it.
What?
I said, put more strength into it.
What are you doing?
Wiping your butt.
Stick your butt out.
Why are you gripping it so tightly?
Do you want me to wipe the front for you?
I can do the front myself.
Do you want me to help?
I can do it myself.
Chu San.
Time to get up.
I'm coming in.
Chu San, I made bone soup
for you and your friend.
Come down and drink it.
Take it easy. Be careful.
Is this your friend?
Very handsome.
Hello.
Wash up and come down to eat.
The food will get cold.
Why did you kick me?
Who kicked you?
Fei, this is so delicious.
I'm going to eat everything for breakfast.
Fei, what you cooked is even better
than what the most expensive chefs
in Harbor City make.
Chu San, your friend really knows how to talk.
Hey, come help a bit.
Okay, sure.
I'll help.
I didn't expect you'd be so good at talking.
Here, a snack for you.
No way.
Open the door!
Open up!
- Hurry up.
- Who is it?
Why are you raising a fuss so early?
Where is he?
Sirs!
Who are you looking for?
Sir!
Where is he? He's not here?
Boss, only my son lives upstairs.
Don't get in the way.
Sir! Please!
Nobody else is upstairs. Just my son alone.
Hey! Sirs!
Sirs, let's talk this out.
My son has gone to school.
Old man.
Your son is that university student
from the city fort, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
He's loved reading since he was a child.
Besides going to college,
he hasn't really achieved much.
Sirs, let me treat you to something.
There's noise downstairs.
Fuck!
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Then why are you moving around?
My back hurts.
Sirs, I told you, no one's here.
Go back.
Let's go.
They must be around here.
Search house by house.
- Are you okay?
- Don't make a sound.
Quiet.
Move.
Okay.
Are you kidding me?
Running away with that crappy backpack?
I have my final exam today.
I'm afraid I won't make it in time.
Your wound has reopened.
Xia Liu Yi, I...
Don't call me that.
It's Big Bro Liu Yi.
I'm not your underling.
So many people begged to be my underling,
and they couldn't.
Plus, I'm three years older than you.
That clearly makes me your big brother.
Did you grow taller?
I've always been taller than you.
Just not as strong as you.
Take off the clothes.
Take whose off?
Ours.
- I...
- Help me stop the bleeding.
Also, help me with something.
I can help you.
But I'm not your underling.
Shut up.
[Ganglong Walled City]
Xia Liu Yi's knife?
Why is it here?
I don't know. I know nothing.
Don't know?
Tell me, where is Xia Liu Yi?
I-I don't know.
Do you want to be stabbed?
He forced me to throw this knife away.
He said to wait for me at Xiaoqi Studio.
You better not play tricks.
Go tell Brother Xu.
Tell him Xia Liu Yi has been found.
At Xiaoqi Studio.
Then what about this kid?
I've told you everything.
Can you let me go?
What?
Take him with you.
If we fail, at least we have him
to report to Brother Xu.
- Come on.
- Get moving.
Move.
Walk.
Hurry up.
Qing Long really hid the ledgers with you.
You had a student help you
get rid of the bloody clothes,
making me think you left the city.
Xia Liu Yi, how could you be so stupid?