Han Seol-ah?
That woman killed her.
It was Han Seol-ah.
I saw everything.
That night,
I went to the archive after the event
to organize the catalogs.
I waited a long time for the elevator,
but it didn't come,
so I decided to take the stairs.
Then I saw Han Seol-ah
rushing down the stairs from the rooftop,
like someone trying to run away.
I thought it was strange…
until I went outside
and found out someone had fallen
to their death from the rooftop.
I know she did it.
Why did you try to hide your identity?
Because I was scared.
If she finds out I provided the tip,
she'll come after me.
And I was worried my brother
might end up like all the other men.
He used to be an underwater photographer,
but now he just shoots events
at the auction house.
Han Seol-ah manipulates
everyone around her.
What are you trying to say?
I'm curious.
You've seen this video, right?
Yes.
Do you know who recorded it?
No, I don't.
It wasn't me.
You were part of the Auction Team staff
that night, right?
I was setting up for the auction
the whole time.
If you don't believe me,
go through my phone.
The statement she gave
aligns with Han Seol-ah's movements
caught on CCTV.
She followed Kim Yun-ji to the rooftop.
Is Han Seol-ah a suspect now?
CHARITY AUCTION TO SUPPORT EMERGING
ARTISTS IN PARTNERSHIP WITH TAEMYUNG
-Hello.
Can we talk? It'll only take five minutes.
I don't have time for that.
The event is about to start.
Didn't it ever occur to you
that Kim Yun-ji knew too much?
How did she meet Yoon Seung-jae
and find out about the policy?
Don't you want to know?
Does knowing that change anything?
The next lot is
The Abyss by Kim Seung-min.
We'll open at 850 million won
and take bids in 50 million increments.
850 million?
We have 850 million.
Anyone at 900 million?
900 million on the floor.
950 million?
At 950 million.
We have 950 million.
The next lot is
Vanished Sensation by Fabien Leclerc.
This emerging talent has been making waves
among European collectors.
We'll open at 300 million won
and take bids
in ten million won increments.
300 million?
We have 300 million.
310 million?
We have 310 million.
320 million?
We have 320 million.
330 million?
We have 330 million. 340 million?
We have 340 million.
350 million?
We have 350 million.
360 million?
Among the lots in today's special auction,
I've set aside these five
to show you privately, sir.
Is this what you mentioned before?
Overseas collectors
are already showing interest.
Just like Stiller,
these artists here, especially Leclerc,
are going to blow up soon.
Whatever you suggest
is guaranteed to rise in value.
It's not too late for Taemyung
to lock down these pieces.
You'll see their value increase tenfold
within the next several years.
The Taemyung Cultural Foundation
is about to open a center in Busan.
You should stock it
with lucrative artwork.
Tenfold, you say?
So I suppose it's in my best interest
to win the bids at any cost.
When have I ever made a suggestion
that wasn't in your best interest?
1.45 billion won.
Anyone at 1.45 billion? 1.45 billion.
We have 1.45 billion.
1.46 billion?
At 1.46 billion.
We have 1.46 billion.
1.47 billion?
We have 1.47 billion.
This special auction is for a good cause,
so the competition seems to be heating up.
Anyone at 1.48 billion?
1.48 billion.
We have 1.48 billion.
1.49 billion?
Anyone at 1.49 billion?
We have 1.49 billion won.
This is the highest bid so far.
Do we have anyone at 1.5 billion?
1.5 billion?
Anyone at 1.5 billion?
We have 1.5 billion.
Anyone at 1.51 billion?
I'll call for 1.51 billion again
before closing the bidding.
1.51 billion?
1.51 billion.
Sold!
Vanished Sensation by Fabien Leclerc
has been sold to Chairman Park Min-cheol
of Taemyung Group.
A portion of today's auction proceeds
will go toward supporting
emerging artists.
Thank you.
Ms. Han Seol-ah.
Please come with us to the police station.
I'm on the clock. What is this about?
We're asking you
to come with us voluntarily.
I refuse to comply.
Then, as of now,
you're under arrest
as a suspect in the murder of Kim Yun-ji.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney.
Let's go.
Didn't it ever occur to you
that Kim Yun-ji knew too much?
How did she meet Yoon Seung-jae
and find out about the policy?
Don't you want to know?
Does knowing that change anything?
Eun-hyuk.
Eun-hyuk!
Don't go.
What can you possibly do there?
Why are you doing this to Seol-ah?
Why?
I just told them what I saw and know.
The truth has to come out!
Why didn't you tell me?
What if I had?
Would you have believed me?
Move.
Eun-hyuk.
Hey, Do Eun-hyuk!
Hey, did you unlock it?
Come on now, they don't call me
Yongsan's Dr. Shin for no reason.
I may not have money,
but I do have skills.
Jeez.
Who's the insane owner
of this burner phone?
They installed a spy app on it.
-A spy app?
-Yes.
It's a stealth app
that records calls and surrounding audio.
It's pretty expensive,
and you have to pay monthly fees.
Does it still work?
Just a sec.
AUDIO FILE LIST
It uses fingerprint recognition,
so I don't think so.
It doesn't work,
but whatever was saved are audio files,
so I'll try to unlock it.
PLACE YOUR FINGER ON THE HOME BUTTON
TO VERIFY YOUR IDENTITY
Hurry up and send them to me.
How about if you hurry up
and get a new phone instead?
I'm hanging up.
GANGHA POLICE STATION
Ms. Han Seol-ah.
You gave a false statement
during the witness interview
and refused to accompany us
for questioning, right?
This is the result of all that.
From now on,
think carefully before you answer.
Think about the consequences
of the statement you make
from here on out.
I'll ask you again.
When did you last see Ms. Kim Yun-ji?
In the dressing room after the party.
Why didn't you mention your argument?
Were you planning to keep that a secret
if the video hadn't spread online?
Where were you
at the time of the incident?
Last time, you said
you were in the Auction Team office.
Is your answer still the same?
I'm not sure.
Is she trying to test us?
At 21:58,
Ms. Kim Yun-ji got off on the 12th floor
and went to the rooftop to vape.
At 22:02,
you followed her
and got off on the 12th floor.
About 9 minutes later, at 22:11,
Ms. Kim Yun-ji fell to her death
from the rooftop.
We have a witness.
They saw you running away
from the rooftop.
Just confess now.
Where were you
at the time of the incident?
You're right.
That night, I went to the 12th floor
and up to the rooftop to find Ms. Kim.
I didn't mention it because I was afraid
it might cause a misunderstanding.
But by the time I reached the rooftop,
Ms. Kim had already taken her life.
I was scared.
And I wanted to get out of there.
That's all.
Ms. Kim was already dead,
and my statement
wouldn't have changed anything.
Don't most people call 119
in such a situation?
They don't run away
and lie about not having been there
like you did.
So are you saying…
that's evidence I killed Ms. Kim?
Look, Ms. Han Seol-ah.
You assume you have the upper hand
because there's no direct evidence.
But there's an autopsy report
suggesting the possibility of murder,
along with CCTV footage and a witness.
Given this much circumstantial evidence,
even a judge can't rule it out.
Let me make this clear.
You're not getting out of this
unless you have a solid alibi.
ROYAL AUCTION CHIEF AUCTIONEER
ARRESTED ON MURDER CHARGES
YOUR HOME
CEO PAEK JUN-BEOM
ROYAL AUCTION CHIEF AUCTIONEER
ARRESTED ON MURDER CHARGES
GANGHA POLICE ARREST ART AUCTIONEER MS. A
ON CHARGES OF MURDERING HER COLLEAGUE
MS. B WAS FOUND DEAD
AFTER FALLING FROM THE COMPANY'S ROOFTOP
MS. A HAS BEEN NAMED THE PRIMARY SUSPECT
VISITATION ROOM
You've done nothing wrong,
so it's going to be okay.
Just because you were in the same place
doesn't mean they can--
Is Eun-hye the witness?
I believe you.
You know that, right?
I'll do whatever I can to help you.
Think it over again.
Did you see anyone at that time?
You know it's illegal to record
outside the interrogation room, right?
The sister is the tip caller,
and the brother is the helper.
How interesting.
What are they saying?
Was there anything else
in the studio apartment?
No.
Maybe she found out
Kim Yun-ji was stalking her
and got into a fight.
We just need
that one decisive piece of evidence.
Hey, Woo-seok.
When did you get here?
How've you been?
You want to join us?
The captain isn't here.
What are you doing here?
I heard you needed the insurance files
for the deceased men.
It's not too late to back out
if you can't handle it.
I hate being stabbed in the back, you see.
Who asks for a favor so rudely?
A favor is something you ask for
from someone who has more info than you.
I'll decide
whether to reinvestigate or not.
If you're done, get the hell out.
It's been over 12 hours already.
You sure you can get a warrant
at this rate?
Hey.
Are you crazy?
You made the arrest,
so make sure to see it through.
I'm sorry.
Here…
It's been a while, Soo-yeon.
What brings you here?
Am I not allowed to come here?
Oh, I didn't mean it that way.
When did you get here?
Just now.
I brought you some underwear.
Don't mind him.
He's here on a different insurance case.
Looking for this?
I'm guessing Han Seol-ah
passed by here that night
and asked someone to get rid of evidence
she'd overlooked.
That someone being Do Eun-hyuk,
her helper.
How did you know to come here?
Good question. How did I know?
I barely managed to ask the call center's
sign language interpreter for help.
They sent me the lip-reading via text,
so take a look.
Okay.
AHN YOUNG-SOO
"Check the monitor
in the exhibition room."
Under Article 155 of the Criminal Act,
a person who destructs,
conceals, or forges evidence
will face up to five years of imprisonment
or a fine of up to seven million won.
You've got guts, given how you could've
ended up as an accomplice.
I came here to find out the truth too.
I'm not going to protect Seol-ah
just because she's my friend.
I want to help her
because I trust her.
Then let's find out…
who she really is.
What is it?
She submitted footage of herself captured
in an art installation as an alibi.
The metadata timestamps her at 22:11,
which matches the time
when Kim Yun-ji fell.
The higher-ups
want us to close the Kim Yun-ji case
as a suicide
and wrap it up quietly.
Thank you for uncovering the truth.
Did Kim Yun-ji seem like the type
to commit suicide?
Is there really a "type" for such a thing?
It's just one of those moments
when you have no other choice.
FRAUDULENT & MISSING INPATIENT CASES
Look.
You deal with a case,
forget about it, and move on.
You know,
some people are cursed in a way
that brings harm or death to those nearby,
like a deadly omen.
Maybe that's the case with Han Seol-ah.
It obviously can't be.
What is it?
Where are you off to now?
I heard you walked out of there
before Attorney Kim even arrived.
It was all thanks to you.
Why do you say that?
Because of Artist Hwang's
media art display.
I was against it,
but you insisted that we bring it in.
I guess you're right.
Oh, no. I spilled it.
Thanks.
I didn't think you'd get out,
so I was going to bring this to you.
Here.
Take it with you.
Thank you.
You haven't been sleeping well, have you?
Your eyes are so sunken.
I'm sorry.
I should have some coffee.
Here.
Spit it out if it's bitter,
but swallow it if it's sweet.
Nobody rewards you
for tolerating something bitter.
It's sweet, right?
You'll feel better.
Yes.
Thank you.
-Hey, over here!
-Here!
-Come on!
-To the front!
-Block him.
-Keep going!
-To the side.
Nice! Steal the ball like I just did,
and pass.
Take the ball.
-Block him!
-Hey!
And kick! Darn it!
Kick it!
Come on, louder!
Yes!
-Look at you.
-Sir.
Running and everything.
TRACKING REQUESTS WELCOME!
JUST CALL DR. SHIN
Here's some water, sir.
-Thanks.
-Enjoy.
How do I sign up?
-Oh, come on.
-Jeez.
What is it now?
I did everything you asked!
I'm serious.
There's absolutely no way you can join.
Why not?
Because I'm the president of this club.
Did you unlock the audio files?
Oh, right.
I only pulled the parts
where Han Seol-ah's voice was recorded.
-I just sent it to you.
-Okay.
HAN SEOL-AH
Nice work.
You're leaving?
"Affairs, ghosting, runaways"?
EXPERIENCE ASSISTING INSURANCE COMPANY SIU
-Run.
-Yes, sir.
This is what you're doing now?
It's just that people
don't get new phones these days, so--
"Experience assisting
insurance company SIU."
This is just unbelievable.
What about it?
It's a legitimate experience I gained
from being at your beck and call.
Experience, my foot.
I need you to find someone.
Why is a former detective
asking me to find things all the time?
His name is Ju Hyun-su.
I have his details,
but he's not at the listed address,
and he uses a burner phone.
Oh, so he's a shady guy?
-Give me his email address.
-Email?
I don't know who he is,
but surely he orders in sometimes, no?
These days, it's faster and more accurate
to go through delivery app brokers.
Okay, I'll text it to you.
Hey, find him as soon as possible.
Okay.
By the way,
can I get an advance or something?
Right.
-I'm counting on you.
-What's this?
What's this?
He works at an insurance company
that offers reimbursements,
but he never reimburses me.
I ought to reimburse him
with a slap in the face one day.
HAN SEOL-AH RECORDINGS
HAN SEOL-AH(1).M4A
Hi, Suk-ji.
I just got home.
Okay, I'll stop by the bar tomorrow.
HAN SEOL-AH(2).M4A
Who is it?
I'm from the management office.
It's about the amendment
to the management regulations.
Can you please cast your vote?
You're the only one who hasn't.
Oh, I've been coming home late from work.
That's okay.
This proposal is to convert
part of the storage room
into a break room for the security staff.
That's good to hear.
It always bothered me seeing them eat
in a corner of the basement parking lot.
I hope this makes things
a little more comfortable for them.
Thank you.
Have a good night.
Thank you. Goodbye.
She rented a studio apartment
and even spied on her.
What was she trying to find out?
Did she really choose…
to take her own life?
I thought it was rather strange
when she left the TV station
and suddenly decided to work
at an auction house.
Do you know…
the man Yun-ji was seeing?
A man?
PARKING PASS
ION MENTAL CLINIC
SHOCK AS DOCTOR IN 30S DIES
IN SUSPECTED PROPOFOL SELF-INJECTION
NFS REVEALS, "CAUSE OF DEATH WAS
PROPOFOL OVERDOSE, NO SIGNS OF FOUL PLAY"
Dr. Choi was so head over heels for her
that he even dumped his girlfriend.
Do you still struggle a lot
without medication?
Yes.
Considering
we're a family medicine clinic,
we can't keep prescribing tranquilizers.
Even for your own sake,
maybe we should transfer you
to a mental clinic.
No.
It's the same as any hospital.
-If you put aside your prejudice--
-It's not prejudice.
It's from experience.
ION MENTAL CLINIC
DIRECTOR CHOI YOUNG-HO
One that I don't want to remember.
I'll write you one more prescription.
But I can't help you after this.
NONORGANIC INSOMNIA
Is this the woman
Dr. Choi Young-ho was seeing…
before Han Seol-ah?
How did you find out?
You're pretty good.
The information I have
is worth an omakase.
I'll treat you again next time.
She was a local TV anchor.
What is she doing?
What are you doing here?
Sit down and eat with me.
It's over between us.
Just accept it.
Let's not make it harder
than it needs to be.
No.
I can't end things this way.
What if I die?
Will you still break up with me
even if I die?
Kim Yun-ji.
Give that to me.
What do you think you're doing?
Give it to me!
Hand it over!
It was absolute chaos.
Apparently,
Dr. Choi just broke up with her
soon after he started consultations
with Ms. Han.
Was Han Seol-ah
unaware of their relationship?
Probably not.
Dr. Choi made sure to keep it a secret
because he was afraid of losing her.
He liked her so much
that he ended their official consultations
after just two months.
What do you mean?
In psychiatry,
doctors are prohibited
from meeting with patients privately.
So he had to make sure
she was no longer his patient.
Countertransference is when a psychiatrist
develops strong feelings for a patient.
It was one of those cases.
Countertransference…
But did you know
many patients
also seduce their psychiatrist?
Here.
Please give that to Chair Kim.
This exhibition was only possible
thanks to her.
Okay, I'll deliver it to her myself.
I'm sure she'll be delighted.
The media is already showing
huge interest.
The Leclerc piece in particular
is getting much attention.
Just as I thought,
trusting Chair Kim really paid off.
I was surprised at how you secured
five bids that day.
I guess someone gave you a tip beforehand.
I did push it a bit,
but they were Chair Kim's recommendations.
In the end,
it was a worthwhile investment.
He said the five lots he secured
during the special auction
will be exhibited
at the Taemyung Art Center in Busan.
Busan?
Yes.
What's the important thing
you wanted to tell me?
You knew Kim Yun-ji
was stalking you, right?
Do you know why?
It wasn't because of Yoon Seung-jae.
It was because of that psychiatrist,
Choi Young-ho.
Before Choi Young-ho met you,
he was Kim Yun-ji's man.
She probably dreamed of a glamorous future
as an anchor-doctor couple.
But then you showed up
and took everything away from her.
That's why she followed you
to Royal Auction.
So she committed suicide because of him?
I'm not sure.
We still can't completely rule out
the possibility of murder.
But what I'm really curious about
is why those three men had to die.
And what you gained from it.
I'd like to ask that myself.
What on earth did I gain from it?
I didn't gain anything.
I only lost.
Ms. Han!
Her blood test results show
a high level of benzodiazepines.
It seems she took too many tranquilizers.
Tranquilizers?
She needs complete rest for the time being
and should try to stop
taking her medication.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
You're Ms. Han Seol-ah's guardian, right?
Oh, yes.
TRIAGE STATION
ENTRY RESTRICTED TO THE PUBLIC
Ms. Han Seol-ah?
Mr. Paek asked me to escort you
to the conference room.
Oh, sure.
Welcome, Ms. Han.
You don't look very well.
Is it because
you've been through a lot lately?
I considered sending my legal team,
but you were released with no charges.
Thank you for the thought.
Not at all.
Please take a seat.
I reviewed the sales consignment proposal
you sent over.
The terms are great.
But why am I not tempted by this?
Are you looking for anything
beyond profit?
You know,
I find myself being more attracted to
people than numbers lately.
Especially…
to people like you.
It seems I misread you.
I didn't expect someone
running a unicorn company
to mix personal feelings with business.
Men like that…
aren't appealing to women.
I don't do deals like this.
Please excuse me.
If you leave like this,
I'll come off as a pathetic guy.
All right.
We'll handle this matter
strictly as business.
HAN SEOL-AH(34).M4A
Suk-ji, can I get another drink?
You've had enough.
We're out of alcohol.
You stubborn thing.
Just cry it out.
Even when you came to stay with me
after your parents passed,
you only cried for a day.
I couldn't believe you.
Now I finally understand.
You can't show your pain to anyone,
so you bottle it all up,
leaving you completely broken inside.
Seol-ah.
If you continue
to keep everything to yourself,
you won't even know that you're in pain.
You'll hold yourself together
until one little thing
makes you fall apart.
I don't have the right to fall apart.
Because I survived…
instead of my parents.
Stop.
A bit higher, please.
Stop. That's good.
Can you move the lights in a bit?
Okay, next piece.
Have you been working on
any projects lately?
I have a private studio in my hometown.
I go there on the weekends.
What brings you here?
I noticed you trust Han Seol-ah
more than you do your own sister.
I was just wondering how that's possible.
Have you never once suspected her?
If I also suspect her,
Seol-ah will be completely alone
in this world.
Completely alone, huh?
Only a soulmate could say
something like that so confidently.
Then you must know what happened
to Ms. Han Seol-ah's family.
Should I just go ask her?
They died in an accident
when we were 15 years old.
What kind of accident?
Seol-ah…
lost her parents at a young age
and had a hard life.
Please stop reopening old wounds.
It can feel as painful as getting stabbed
for the person involved.
Yes, I know.
That's why I'm being careful
and asking you instead.
It happened a long time ago, and it has
nothing to do with your investigation,
so please stop.
A fire broke out in their house.
It was widely known as
the Cheongun family fire fatality case.
Han Seol-ah was the only one who survived.
Eun-hye.
She brings misfortune to those around her.
I hope she gets arrested
for insurance fraud or whatever
and stays away from my brother.
We need to talk.
CHEONGUN FAMILY FIRE FATALITY CASE
FIRE FATALITY CASE INVESTIGATION REPORT
At the time, the police concluded
the family committed suicide together.
POSSIBLE ARSON
RESULTING FROM A SUICIDE ATTEMPT
I didn't gain anything.
I only lost.
Even if it's true
that she survived that tragedy,
it doesn't excuse her.
What if…
it was nothing more
than a string of bad luck for Han Seol-ah?
It makes me wonder
if I'm putting her through hell.
Do you have any other reason
for thinking that?
Not really.
It just reminds me of my sister.
And the truth is,
everyone has a painful memory
they want to forget.
Even though I knew
how much pain it'd cause…
I still pushed her.
Getting to the truth
sometimes means being ruthless.
Do you know what it's like…
to feel like a scumbag?
Don't even think about
going there tomorrow.
Nobody will welcome you.
It'll be the last time.
This is so frustrating.
Do you like torturing yourself
or something?
Think about yourself first for once.
I still need to pay my respects.
TRANQUILIZER
THE LATE YOON SEUNG-JAE
MEMORIAL TABLET ENSHRINEMENT CEREMONY
If only he hadn't met you…
If only he hadn't met you,
my Seung-jae would still be alive!
He defied his parents,
got involved with a no-good woman,
and ended up dead!
My poor baby!
How dare you come here?!
How dare you?
Seung-jae…
I'd like a word with you.
My poor Seung-jae…
INSURANCE POLICY
Why did my brother
take out a life insurance policy?
He canceled it soon after,
but I just don't understand it.
Why did he spend
200 million won on a policy?
You know why, don't you?
No, I don't.
You were the beneficiary,
so how could you not know?
I don't know why Seung-jae
took out an insurance policy.
Then what did that woman mean?
Get out.
Get out right now!
You'll end up dying at her hands too,
just like Young-ho.
Go get some professional help.
You're not right in the head.
Do you think I'm joking?
Get out.
Are you insane?
You also took out
a life insurance policy, right?
You'll regret it.
She definitely mentioned insurance,
and in less than two weeks,
the accident happened.
Seung-jae died,
just like the woman said he would.
If you don't tell me,
I'll go to that woman and ask her myself.
You won't be able to.
Because that woman…
also died.
What?
The policy was canceled
before the accident,
and the premium
was returned to his account.
That's…
all I know.
Who exactly are you?
I had my suspicions,
but this must be why
the SIU investigator kept calling.
You killed them, didn't you?
You're the one who killed Seung-jae
and that woman, aren't you?!
Tell me!
Who are you?
I'm the SIU investigator.
THE LATE YOON SEUNG-JAE
I wonder how far
a string of bad luck can go.
A work colleague.
A significant other.
And even your parents.
Did you really just lose everything
and have nothing to do with their deaths?
Do you still think…
I killed someone?
I suppose…
you wouldn't believe a word I say.
What are you doing? Are you insane?!
All I have to do is disappear.
Then it'll all be over!
What?
I don't care!
I want to die! Why are you stopping me?
Why are you doing this to me?
What do you want to know?
What more do you want to know?
You.
I want to know more about you.
I want to know about the person
who could die right now and not care!
SPECIAL THANKS TO YOON JONGHUN
FOR HIS APPEARANCE
Obsessed?
I just want to know the truth.
Did you do it on purpose?
You're suspicious,
but you have no evidence.
Was it really necessary
to get on your knees?
Do you think money
will make that pain go away?
These three men
follow the exact same pattern.
Can you really call it a coincidence?
There was someone else.
Are you saying
someone deliberately targeted
Han Seol-ah's men and killed them?
If the culprit thinks I'm your man…
I'll either die…
or find out who the real culprit is.
Subtitle: Jenny Kim