[pensive music plays]
[Woo-seok]
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
If I could just disappear,
it would all be over!
I want to die.
Why are you stopping me? Why?
Why are you doing this to me?
What do you want to know?
You.
Han Seol-ah, I want to know you.
[sighs] It bothers me…
EPISODE 5
[ringing tone]
Mr. Do Eun-hyuk?
I'd like to meet with you.
I have nothing more to say to you.
I'm hanging up.
[sighs]
[dramatic music plays]
How far can a string
of unfortunate events go?
A coworker.
An ex-boyfriend.
And your parents too.
SALES CONSIGNMENT PROPOSAL
6-WEEK EXECUTION ROAD MAP
RISK MANAGEMENT & PARTNERSHIP STRATEGY
Well, you'd be hard-pressed
to receive a better offer than this.
I understand your concerns,
since a Stiller piece
isn't everyone's expertise,
but we'll lock in that final price,
even if we need a house bidder to do so.
If I consign this piece to you,
what happens to Ms. Han then?
Well… as I'm sure you're aware,
Ms. Han has had a few issues lately.
She won't be in that position
much longer anyway,
and so you should work with someone
you'll be dealing with long-term.
Oh, I see.
You're trying to take this opportunity
to crush her, aren't you?
Well, that's how this business works,
doesn't it?
[scoffs] That's cutthroat.
Is this why Ms. Han agreed
to do me that favor?
[whimsical music plays]
Oh, oops.
Looks like the meetings overlapped.
Since this has happened…
why don't we get this sorted out?
I'm working to launch a new venture
that enables co-buying of artworks
through Fintech.
BUSINESS PLAN
YOUR ARTWORK
I needed an expert for guidance
on the lineup,
and Ms. Han agreed to take charge.
Chair Kim also encouraged me
to give it my best shot.
I need to return the favor, so…
You understand my position, right?
Yes, of course.
[breathes deeply]
Those two are ganging up on me.
If I may take this further,
I'd like to get something even bigger
than just consulting.
How about you take the lead as the head of
the "Your Artwork" venture from now on?
Thank you for the offer, but I have
something I must attend to at Royal.
I can give you 5% in stock options,
along with twice your current salary.
I won't be easily swayed by money.
Ah, neither honor nor money.
Then what is it?
What exactly are you after, Seol-ah?
[ominous music plays]
[pensive music plays]
[Eun-hye] It was a famous case,
the Cheongun deadly family fire.
Han Seol-ah was the only one who survived.
[no audible dialogue]
Excuse me. Oh, yes, hello.
Do you remember anything about this?
CHEONGUN FIRE KILLS COUPLE IN THEIR 40S,
LEAVES TEENAGE DAUGHTER CRITICALLY INJURED
- Oh, this? Yeah, there was a big fire.
- Do you know where this was?
Yes, over there. It was huge.
I thought you wouldn't come
I only came
because I knew you'd stir everything up.
Do you know how hard Seol-ah
has tried to put all this behind her?
Digging up the past like this
is just torture for her.
Then why don't you just tell me?
I don't wanna rely on old news articles
or the neighbors' fading memories.
You tell me, Mr. Do.
I don't want to torture anyone, either.
Have a seat.
It's ginger tea.
When you work in cold water
for a long time, your body gets stiff.
Now I drink this out of habit.
Her father was…
a poor artist
who worked out of a small back room.
He struggled so much
that he borrowed from loan sharks.
[sobs] Please, I'm begging you.
Don't do this.
What'd you think? That we wouldn't
be able to find you if you ran?
No, sir. Please, sir.
[sobs] I'm sorry. Please, I'm sorry.
Oh. Oh, no!
Please don't touch him. Please.
I'll take the punishment.
Do it to me. Do it to me!
- Do it to me! Please! Please!
- Please, sir, don't do this.
She didn't cry.
She endured the whole thing
without letting out a single scream.
While I watched from outside,
clenching my teeth till they'd break.
Seol-ah just…
endured it.
Shortly after that, the fire broke out.
He figured
they might as well all die together.
And the child survived alone.
She survived, but it wasn't living,
not after seeing her family burn
before her eyes.
And you couldn't turn your back on her.
So, you've been by her side ever since?
That is quite a friendship.
Or, should I call it love?
[Eun-hyuk sighs]
Don't act like you understand
everything that we've been through.
Our relationship isn't something
you can just reduce to labels
like friendship or love.
Let's end this here.
About Seol-ah, stop misjudging her
and stop bothering her.
[Gounod's "Je Veux Vivre" plays]
Emil Stiller has been confirmed
as the main piece.
Stiller?
Are we aiming
for the highest bid this time?
We should.
When someone puts their whole heart
into something,
the universe just responds.
Well, that must be why all the finest
artworks find their way to you, ma'am.
True effort
always adds up in one way or another.
We have a long way to go
before I'm satisfied.
You should get back to work.
Ma'am.
- So distracting.
- [music stops]
[sighs]
Oh, life
Running through
The vast, desolate wilderness
[continues humming melody]
[lock clicking]
[sighs]
I'll have a glass of this.
May I join you?
[jazz playing]
Well, since you already know about
what happened with her parents,
there's nothing left to hide.
Yeah, that's when Seol-ah
started staying at our place.
I was her senior in high school
and I bombed the college entrance exam,
so I never went to college,
but I've been looking out for her
ever since.
So it's not an ordinary connection.
So I take it that you two are very close.
I think we are, but she's not the type
to just lay her heart completely bare.
Maybe it's because
she's been hurt so much.
When she's sad or in pain,
she just hides it.
That's why people misunderstand her.
Mr. Do Eun-hyuk said the same.
He told me not to bother Han Seol-ah.
She's not like that.
She just wouldn't commit insurance fraud.
She became an orphan at 15,
lost her first love in an accident,
and she even had to see a psychiatrist…
[sighs]
Was Mr. Lee Su-ho's death hard for her?
After he died in that accident,
she started relying on meds,
and now she feels nothing.
[sighs deeply] That poor thing.
She's had the worst luck.
And why did you open your bar here,
next to the auction house?
Sorry?
I figured it'd be smart
to cater drinks to the auction house,
maybe even meet a good guy along the way…
[sighs]
Why am I even saying all this?
You must've been hungry.
I'll get you some more.
[scoffs] Didn't even touch it.
[melancholy music plays]
If I could just disappear,
it would all be over.
I don't care anymore!
I want to die.
Why are you stopping me? Why?
HAN SEOL-AH(38).M4A
[Eun-hyuk] Staying up all night?
Even if I go home,
I won't get any sleep anyway.
His work is so realistic,
it actually freaks me out a bit.
Exactly why I look at it.
If I face the horrible reality head-on,
it feels like nothing can get worse.
When I sleep,
that day keeps replaying in my dreams.
[Seol-ah, through earbuds]
The dock, the last time I saw him.
Waking up makes it even more terrifying
because I know it actually happened.
[Eun-hyuk, through earbuds]
Seol-ah, what can I do for you?
Want to take a day off?
Should Suk-ji and I stay with you?
I'll let you know if it gets too hard.
All I can do is just stay right by
your side, and that's so frustrating.
That's how I get through it,
because you're there. You stay by my side.
That's what keeps me going.
[sighs]
Isn't she cold?
[tense music plays]
[sighs]
[sighs] What the hell am I doing?
[upbeat music plays]
CAPTURING LIGHT:
KIM JOON-YOUNG SPECIAL EXHIBITION
THIS GLASS SCULPTURE EVOKES A SINGLE BLOOM
EMERGING IN THE STILLNESS OF NIGHT
- [employee 1] What was that?
- [employee 2] Oh, no! What happened?
[employees murmuring]
I'm sorry. It slipped from my hands.
[tense music plays]
Are you okay though?
- Yes.
- Oh, man. This is the main piece.
What do we do now?
- The opening's in just two days…
- Are you crazy?
What are you gonna do now?
Do you even know how much this is worth?
Na-hee.
I'm sorry, Ms. Han. I'm sorry.
First, leave everything as is
and get the claim started.
Sure.
And you, Ms. Do Eun-hye.
I need a word with you.
[Tae-seok] Wow…
Whoa.
It was a mistake, right?
Think whatever you want.
Was it intentional?
You have a hunch, but no evidence.
And you're pissed.
I felt exactly the same way.
My brother Seung-jae and Ms. Kim
were both killed
but there's no evidence.
You're really delusional.
What? "Delusional"?
I don't care whether you report me
or go public, but this is unacceptable.
Understood?
How can someone who studied art
do such a thing?
We handle artworks
as if they were our lives.
And you call yourself a specialist
but you can't even show them respect.
Think about whether
you even deserve that title.
Then fire me.
I'm really sorry, Mr. Kim.
Even if we have to push the schedule,
- we'll--
- [line disconnects]
Mr. Kim. Mr. Kim?
We've checked the security footage
and will go ahead
and file the insurance claim.
Well, I'll leave it to you then.
Can we talk?
I don't have time right now.
I'm dealing with an emergency.
- Damage control?
- If you know better, please step aside.
Well, we're both busy,
so let's talk on the way.
[pensive music plays]
What is it?
- It was you.
- You told me to set Ms. Han up.
But I never told you
to sabotage the exhibition.
This girl's got more guts than I expected.
In any case,
I'm getting a permanent position, right?
I did just as you said.
[sighs]
How long have you been an intern?
My six months are up next month.
Okay. Okay, but listen.
Just don't slack off,
and make sure you do exactly as I say.
Do you understand?
Yes, I do. But…
But what?
If I get fired, I won't go down alone.
[scoffs, laughs]
Geez, from top to bottom, how did we
only hire brats like her?
Goddamn it!
GANGHA POLICE STATION
YOON SEUNG-JAE
35 YEARS OLD, RESTAURANT CEO
DEATH BY DROWNING
CHOI YOUNG-HO
SUICIDE
LEE SU-HO
ACCIDENT
[Gong] What are you trying to do
with a case that's already closed?
These three men follow
the exact same pattern.
Can this really be a coincidence?
Coincidence or not, we know
Han Seol-ah didn't kill Kim Yun-ji.
Could there be an accomplice?
When we reviewed the security footage
and dashcam footage,
we were focused on Han Seol-ah.
There's got to be something we missed.
Do Eun-hye was the one who broke it.
Are we sure it wasn't intentional?
Things like that happen from time to time
on the job. Just a mistake.
- I guess you're always suspicious.
- Yeah.
You're free to have your suspicions
but I won't tolerate you
crossing the line again.
What line is that?
Luen Palace.
[tense music plays]
So? Could you see me well?
[sighs] How long have you known?
LEASE SIGNING FOR LUEN PALACE UNIT 702
[Seol-ah] So you've been
watching me from there all along?
I was just trying to follow
Kim Yun-ji's trail.
So you knew about that apartment too?
I saw you
coming out of that building once.
And you figured it out just from that?
I'm really sorry.
I should've been more careful.
But, uh, could you please reconsider…
Just go announce
that the exhibition's canceled.
Fire it up.
[sorrowful music plays]
[breathes heavily]
[coughing]
I know you're the last person who
wants to give this up right now, Mr. Kim.
But we still have some time left.
You can never make
the same piece twice with glass.
Each piece is unique.
But it's "Twilight Blue," isn't it?
Doesn't the sky at dusk change every
moment? Making it always unique.
What if I can't get the right color?
I'll take full responsibility and cancel
the exhibition if it comes to that.
I'll stay up all night if I have to
and help in every way. Please…
[sighs]
Back there,
you'll find cobalt and gold ruby.
Go grab them.
Sure.
COBALT
MARINE BLUE
Thank you.
Did you really have to
get down on your knees?
It could've gone through the insurance.
To an artist,
their work is like their own child.
You poured your blood and sweat,
and now it's gone.
What good is insurance money?
Do you really think
money can erase that pain?
[uplifting music plays]
Here you go, Mr. Kim.
Okay.
Can you bring me that sack?
I'll go grab some coffee.
- Can you give me a hand?
- Sure.
The other way.
[gasps]
[coughs]
[breathes deeply]
[sighs]
How are you feeling?
Are you all right?
I'm okay now.
Oh, man…
[clicks tongue]
I honestly can't figure you out, Ms. Han.
One moment you seem
like you could just let everything go,
and the next,
you won't give up on a thing.
You seem strong, yet at times,
it feels like you're barely holding on.
So what? Does that earn me any sympathy?
[gentle music plays]
At first, I wondered if it was the
insurance money that you were after.
Or maybe it was those three men's deaths
that you truly wanted.
But now I wonder if you're just a victim,
and I'm the one doing
something terrible to you.
I couldn't help but feel guilty.
Now, I must find out
why such misfortune
keeps befalling Han Seol-ah.
You said there is no such thing
as a third coincidence.
That's when it all became clear to me too
that something wasn't right.
So someone specifically targeted
Han Seol-ah's men and killed them?
Possibly?
Do you have any guesses?
I need to know in order to help you.
Do you…
really trust me?
I want to try trusting you.
Han Seol-ah.
I want to trust you.
[alarm system beeping]
Cha Woo-seok!
The phone you are trying to reach
is turned off.
You will be directed to voicemail
after the beep…
What's going on?
I can't reach him, and he's not home.
KIM YUN-JI
AUCTIONEER AT ROYAL AUCTION
BURNER PHONE
[pensive music plays]
HAN SEOL-AH(34).M4A
[Seol-ah, on recording]
I don't have the right to fall apart.
Instead of my parents,
I'm the one who survived.
[Suk-ji, on recording] Just cry.
[alarm system beeping]
[door closes]
Another stakeout around here?
Sorry for coming in when you weren't home.
Why? It's nothing new.
You said you were going
to the auction house.
What happened? Your phone was off.
I had to run out of town and
didn't get a chance to charge my phone.
With Han Seol-ah?
Yeah.
You know, maybe the real culprit
is someone else in Han Seol-ah's circle…
Do you feel bad for that woman?
What?
I bet you felt sympathy
after listening to this.
"Maybe she's not the culprit.
She must've been in pain and struggling."
And then the obsession started.
What obsession?
I just want to know the truth here.
Do you know why you're so intent
on finding the truth?
It's just because you hope
she's not the culprit.
This counts as evidence tampering.
You're interfering with an investigation.
I can't let this slide.
I'm doing this by the book.
[dramatic music plays]
[sighs]
HAN SEOL-AH
[Woo-seok] So someone
specifically targeted Han Seol-ah's men
and killed them?
Anyone who loves Han Seol-ah dies.
YOON SEUNG-JAE
CHOI YOUNG-HO
LEE SU-HO
Someone new will die as well. A new victim
But that man…
can find out the truth.
Huh? Oh. Look at this.
[dramatic music plays]
This was caught on the security camera
near the auction house.
Judging by this angle,
he was filming the rooftop.
We'll have to track him down.
Hey, Gong. You're on fire.
Look right here.
CAPTURING LIGHT:
KIM JOON-YOUNG SPECIAL EXHIBITION
The artist asked for all
the broken pieces to be displayed
as part of the exhibition.
He also said there's no need for a claim.
[sighs]
He said that he wanted to show
that light cannot be trapped.
Hmm…
Thank you for that day.
Oh…
Ah, you know, I've been thinking,
if what you said is true,
it means the culprit targeted those men.
It's probably someone who knows me well.
Every crime has a motive.
What could this be?
My misery?
To find out…
Han Seol-ah has to meet a new man.
[dramatic music plays]
If the culprit thinks I'm your boyfriend,
I'll end up dead,
or I'll find out who the killer is.
Let's do it.
Do you mean that?
Now, I'm really curious what kind
of face you'll make
when you learn the truth and look at me.
[secretary] The auctioneer is here, sir.
- Welcome.
- Thank you for your invitation, Mr. Paek.
I'm really touched
that you came in person.
I have you to thank
for giving me this opportunity.
I'm a little late.
My name is Cha Woo-seok. I manage
your insurance account.
Nice to meet you. I'm Paek Jun-beom.
I guess you're left-handed.
Oh, it's just a habit of mine.
I like the left hand too.
It's the closest to the heart.
I think it'll look empty
when that spot's left bare.
It's said that letting go brings in the
chance to welcome new things to your life.
So, I picked out a few pieces
as alternatives.
There's no fee for this, of course.
Hmm, just as I thought.
You've got a knack for picking great art
and reading people well.
This will probably take a while.
How about a glass of wine?
The Stiller piece
has well-documented provenance.
Is there a specific reason
for the insurance company to check it?
Since it's such a high-value piece,
there are protocols that must be followed.
The truth is, I'm a bit of a skeptic.
Insurance is able to turn both art
and human life into money,
and I've seen too many people
give up their humanity because of it.
[tense music plays]
Money brings out
the real nature of people.
Or also, we're all seeing things
only from our own perspective.
Anyway, that's sad.
You have trouble trusting people.
It must be a bit lonely.
[snorts]
If I want to trust someone, I trust them…
without running the numbers.
I just follow my heart.
[scoffs]
I noticed the logo on the business card.
Does it mean anything?
I'm not really sure, but my boss liked it.
[ringing tone]
Name is Paek Jun-beom.
Dig up everything you can on him.
Boss? Hello? Hello…
Ugh, what the hell? Like I'm just
gonna dig and find this stuff?
That lowlife doesn't even cover the costs.
MESSAGE
DEPOSIT: 1,000,000 WON
CHA WOO-SEOK
No, he's not a lowlife at all.
[groans] Paek Jun-beom. Okay.
[Jun-beom exhales deeply]
Now it's really hitting me.
Does it feel empty?
But it's also a relief.
That piece came to me
for a particular reason.
Perhaps so that we could meet.
[pensive music plays]
My feelings are sincere enough
to give you Stiller.
I don't expect an answer right away.
I just wanted to tell you
before it's too late.
Looks like it's a bit late.
We need to check the piece in.
This business deal is important to me.
Wasn't I supposed to be Han Seol-ah's man?
I didn't realize I had to wait in line.
Don't jump to conclusions.
If that's not it,
then what's your reason for testing him?
Because he seems to know you real well?
Do you find that guy suspicious?
Then let's find out right now.
Let's do this right then.
The ball's been thrown.
Let's see if he reacts.
[dramatic music plays]
Just a touch more light on the red…
Eun-hyuk, can we take a look without
cropping the frames on either side?
Hey, what's going on that we need
to meet in the meeting room?
Once a company shuts down,
there aren't any records.
I need your network for this.
ELECTRONIC RECORDS FOR GW LIFE INSURANCE
DO NOT EXIST DUE TO ITS BANKRUPTCY
[sighs] Right,
as an insurance investigator,
you have to check this.
[clicks tongue]
- Thank you. I'll just take a quick look.
- Yes. Sure.
[Woo-seok] Maybe the real culprit
is someone else in Han Seol-ah's circle…
[Joo-young] Do you know why
you're so intent on finding the truth?
It's just because you hope
she's not the culprit.
What?
NONGHYUP LIFE INSURANCE
[clicks tongue]
- What is it?
- Well, here's what you asked for.
Take a look, and you'll see.
These are old records.
They were hard to dig up.
[sighs]
Oh…
What's going on now?
Well, I think he got hit right here.
- Right here? Like this?
- No, no.
Like this.
[dramatic music plays]
[engine revs]
[tires screech]
[screaming on video]
This video was captured by
a witness at the scene of the incident.
VIP INVITATION SPECIAL AUCTION…
Did you see? On the rooftop.
VIP INVITATION SPECIAL AUCTION
AUGUST 26, 2025 - ROYAL AUCTION
Oh, that's…
There was someone else on the rooftop.
[knocking at door]
What brings you here at this…
You found out something else.
INSURANCE PAYOUT STATEMENT
Two months before the fire,
the artist happened
to take out life insurance.
Payout went to his daughter.
She used the money to pay off
his high-interest loans.
This is even more surprising.
The mother also had life insurance,
and the payout went to the daughter.
POLICYHOLDER: PARK YUN-JEONG
BENEFICIARY: HAN SEOL-AH
140,000.
You knew your parents
had life insurance, didn't you?
Han Seol-ah, you were at the scene
and are the only survivor.
Even if no one else knows…
you know the truth.
[sorrowful music plays]
Who started the fire?
It can't be.
That's right.
[dramatic music plays]
I did it.
I killed them.
[gasps]
[dramatic music plays]
[Woo-seok] As if you were asking me
to uncover the truth.
[Seol-ah] It was my choice.
Are you sure you're not letting your
emotions keep you from seeing the truth?
[Woo-seok] What if I'm truly worried?
Were you following me?
You wanted me to trust you,
isn't that right?
[Joo-young] This is the person Ms.
Kim Yun-ji was last seen with that day.
If he's the one who killed those men,
there's only one answer.
- He wants Han Seol-ah.
- No!
[Woo-seok] I no longer suspect you.
[Seol-ah] But in the end,
won't uncover anything at all.