INSURANCE PAYOUT STATEMENT
You knew your parents
had life insurance, didn't you?
Han Seol-ah, you were
the only survivor at the scene.
Even if no one else knows…
you know the truth.
Who started the fire?
It can't be.
That's right.
I did it.
I killed them.
[sighs]
You have to tell me exactly what happened.
I killed my parents
to collect the insurance payout.
[sighs]
What? Isn't that enough?
I had those men take out insurance
but my plan failed.
- I killed them all.
- Did you actually do it?
That's what you wanted to hear.
Am I wrong?
Tell me the truth.
The truth?
I've always spoken the truth.
You're the one who refuses to believe it.
[sighs]
[Seol-ah] I wonder.
If your secret came out
for the whole world to see…
SIU INVESTIGATOR CHA WOO-SEOK
…would you still be this graceful?
How long are you going
to keep defending Ms. Han?
How long?
I can't show my face in front of the team.
[Chair Kim] But she's invaluable
to me to me.
If there's darkness,
there has to be light to keep the balance.
Ma'am.
I heard something
that really gave me chills.
You see, Ms. Han…
[Seol-ah] You think I killed my fiancé
for just 140,000?
Do you know what all insurance scammers
have in common?
Once they get a taste of money,
they want more.
What is it that you really want to know?
Your fiancé
and Kim Yun-ji…
Did you kill them?
Even if no one else knows,
you know the truth.
EPISODE 6
[Mr. Koo] Detective experience
comes in handy in situations like this.
When the back of your neck tingles,
there is always a reason.
Big data proves it.
What's the problem now, huh?
Hey, you should be excited
about finding new evidence.
Has big data ever steered you wrong?
Or ever wished it was wrong?
What?
You're kidding.
You still believe that woman?
[stammers] This is insane.
But…
back then, why did you stay by my side?
When I was young,
no one wanted to be near me.
They said I reeked of smoke.
So I'd go to the cafeteria alone
and you were always there waiting for me.
You'd sit across from me
and you would always eat with me.
Remember?
Day after day…
That's what actually gave me
the courage to go to school.
It wasn't our fault, you know.
I think that was the day it all started.
- [thuds]
- [parent] Hey! Find your mother.
I said go, find her. You little brat. Go!
She's been running around
saying she's busy with her sales job,
and just ditches her husband
like some dog poop.
You're just like your mother,
you ungrateful little brat.
You little bastard.
- Get over here.
- [Eun-hye whimpering]
Get over here.
[grunts]
Eun-hye, run.
- Get back here!
- Eun-hye, run.
Get back!
You little…
Damn you!
- Goddamn you!
- [groaning]
[sobbing]
[grunting, groaning]
Get up, Do Eun-hyuk.
Here, try this.
Slow down, slow down.
Here.
You're eating so well.
Come on, stay still.
[Eun-hyuk] That night,
I realized for the first time…
what it really meant
to have someone by your side.
Even when I was beaten so badly,
it hurt less, and I could endure it.
I could keep going.
You know, no one gets to
pick their parents before they're born.
Not you, not me.
So, it's not our fault.
So, it's not my fault?
The fire that day, that wasn't your fault.
That guilt you feel for
being the only one who survived it's…
time you let it go.
[Suk-ji] Hey, stop.
Stop drinking.
Why do you guys always drink
on empty stomachs?
So, you don't mind
if the bar smells like food?
Who cares? It's my bar.
Mmm…
Maybe I should
just turn this place into a diner.
GANGHA POLICE STATION
VIP INVITATION SPECIAL AUCTION
We've been given the okay
to reinvestigate the Kim Yun-ji case.
[chuckles] Really?
Yes!
On the condition that I'll resign
if we mess up again this time.
Consider everyone
who was the auction house a suspect,
and check each and every
one of them thoroughly, got it?
[sighs] Then we'll have to
get our hands on the VIP list first.
- There's someone who can help us.
- [line rings]
PORTRAITS OF A WOMAN: SPECIAL EXHIBITION
This exhibition, Portrait of a Woman,
seeks to capture
the artistic spirit of female artists
who confront the injustices of life
and challenge convention
through their artistic work.
This piece in particular
attempts to subvert
the traditional image of the siren.
Shedding the symbolism
of the witch who lures men to their deaths
and instead portraying the femme fatale,
a modern woman whose allure is undeniable,
yet who never relinquishes her agency.
That's exactly like you, Ms. Han.
I'm glad to see you looking bright
after all you've been through.
I heard about your fiancé
and his accident.
That must have been really hard.
Thank you very much for your concern.
If I had known,
I wouldn't have written about Ms. Kim.
Back to back funerals… [sighs]
- Shall we wrap it up here, then?
- Sure, thank you.
You've suffered enough.
[Eun-hyuk sighs]
Ms. Han didn't bite, not once.
I'm not surprised.
Here you go.
Just give me the source,
and I'll turn it into a killer story.
ANNUAL ADVERTISING CONTRACT
THE CLIENT SHALL PAY THE SERVICE PROVIDER
A FEE OF 30,000,000 WON
Wow.
That's an expensive bill.
You got anything bigger?
Bigger?
Gossip is only fun
when it's in the present tense.
Something bigger.
Just wait a little.
Here's the insurance certificate
for the Stiller piece.
These documents
hold a great deal of information.
Who, when and why
someone obtained the policy.
With a nonexistent company
and hardly any evidence,
is that why you confessed?
Let's face the truth.
You won't uncover anything at all.
Because I'm the only one who knows
what happened.
You wanted me to trust you…
isn't that right?
[phone buzzes]
UNREAD MESSAGES
[phone buzzing]
[Seol-ah] Who are you?
[mysterious voice] Felix Storage.
45, Saebit road,
Yeonho district, Cheonin, Gyeonggi.
If you do not arrive within an hour,
your secret will be revealed to the world.
[Seol-ah] I'm looking for this unit.
[beeps]
Is it possible to find out
who left this here?
I cannot disclose that,
security regulations.
Hello. Someone from Royal Auction
just went in, right?
I'm with her.
NONGHYUP LIFE INSURANCE
SIU SENIOR MANAGER CHA WOO-SEOK
Thank you.
- [beeps]
- [door unlocks]
There are separate units for artwork
and wine in this high-security wing,
so you can check them out later.
This is the live security cam feed.
You can monitor the entrance and interior
of our storage facility 24 hours a day.
[gasps]
[panting]
No!
[grunting]
Are you okay?
Oh, shit.
What…
All done now.
I'll give you some extra
hydrocolloid bandages.
If it swells up,
just replace it with a new one.
Thank you very much.
Does she need to go to the hospital?
It's just a superficial cut,
if she takes good care of it,
it should heal without scarring.
She used to be a nurse.
She's an expert,
so you don't need to worry too much.
That's unusual for a secretary.
I hired her on purpose.
I'm still recovering from an accident.
[manager] We can't disclose the
owner's information due to privacy.
It's not an accident. It's an incident.
Someone just got hurt here.
Then call the police.
If the police open an investigation,
won't other customers' ID's
be exposed too?
If that's the case,
I'll have to rethink my contract.
Gosh. Come on, sir.
Seems like it would be a win-win
for both of you
if you just tell him who the
owner of that unit is.
[sighs]
Mr. Paek, may I ask you
what brings you here at this hour?
I was considering signing with them for
a warehouse I need for our new venture.
And what about you two?
[Seol-ah] We're here because the
auction house does business with them.
Thank you for your help, Mr. Paek.
Oh, you'll be all right? Let me drive you.
I'm fine, and I still have
some work to take care of.
Then I can drive her.
So, could you just have your driver
bring her car?
If you insist.
Were you following me?
Why did you come here?
Why did you go into that warehouse?
You think this is a coincidence?
Someone set a trap on purpose.
I mean, why would you come here alone?
[sighs] You should've told me first!
Come on, tell me what's going on.
It's the only way that I can help you.
Help me?
So I'm not your suspect?
What if I'm truly worried?
You said you killed your parents,
but I keep looking for reasons
it couldn't be you.
- [key clicks]
- [Gong] Who's this one here?
Oh, her name's Hwang Suk-ji.
She's a friend of Ms. Han from school,
and across the street
from the auction house.
- What about her?
- Oh, that's Ko Sang-mi.
Our assistant manager.
This is the person Ms. Kim Yun-ji
was last seen with that day.
Oh. [gasps] Ah…
ROYAL AUCTION VIP NIGHT
PAEK JUN-BEOM
Here he is.
Mr. Paek Jun-beom.
He made a fortune with a start-up.
Lately, he's been getting close
to Ms. Han.
Not him.
I mean, why would a unicorn CEO
do something like that?
Huh. There's something off about this guy.
[Gong] Mr. Do Eun-hyuk?
Yeah.
Well, there's a lot of gossip at work.
Apparently, he worships Ms. Han
like a queen.
[sighs] Had I known they knew each other,
I wouldn't have hired him.
Do Eun-hyuk was in Cheongun
on the day of Yoon Seung-jae's death.
And also at the scene
when Kim Yun-ji died.
On top of that, he's the one
who vouched for Han Seol-ah's alibi.
Han Seol-ah and Do Eun-hyuk
working together as accomplices?
That sounds like a plausible theory.
If there was an accomplice,
we could dispute Han Seol-ah's alibi
for the time of Kim Yun-ji's fall.
[sighs] It would be great if we had just
one case we could use to pressure him
before calling him in as a witness.
If we feel the Kim Yun-ji case
has reached a dead end,
we can find another lead.
Let's take another look at the
Yoon Seung-jae death first.
I thought this person would show
themselves if I came alone.
This isn't something you can handle alone.
They lured you right into danger
but then I showed up
and ruined their plan.
Do you think Mr. Paek
orchestrated all of this?
There was a suspicious guy
in the warehouse.
Paek Jun-beom came running
as if he had been waiting.
So, you think that he could be
watching us right now?
[engine turns off]
[tires squeal]
Let's go in together.
And let's see how they react.
[door closes]
[device beeps]
[Seol-ah] In this house, there's only
water and alcohol. Take your pick.
Same as you.
[liquid pouring]
[Woo-seok] I noticed the logo
on the business card.
Does it mean anything?
[Jun-beom] Anyway, that's sad.
You have trouble trusting people.
Is this wine easy to find?
No.
It was his own private label actually.
He only sold it at that restaurant.
I saw the same wine
at Paek Jun-beom's place,
so it's clear he's been
to that restaurant then.
Aren't you afraid of me?
It's possible that I did kill those men.
And that I'm just lying about it all.
Well, that's possible.
I told you I was the one
who started the fire.
Those words stuck with me…
and sounded different.
As if you were asking me
to uncover the truth.
Usually, it's the adults
who create tragedies.
It was my choice.
- [clattering]
- [parent groaning]
[Seol-ah] Those who've
hit rock bottom know
that misfortune tends to fall hardest
on those who have nothing.
My father's debts
to loan sharks snowballed
and there was no way out
at least not until we died.
[parent 2] Go watch a movie.
You said you wanted to see a movie.
[chuckles]
Go on.
[Seol-ah] One day, my mom told me
to go to the theater and watch a movie.
Something felt off.
DUMARI CHICKEN
So, instead of going to the movies,
I bought fried chicken
and headed back home.
When I got home,
my parents had already
swallowed pesticide…
Seol-ah.
…and they poured gasoline everywhere.
I realized they had planned
to make it look like an accident.
I was going to die with them too…
but I didn't.
[crying]
Just like that,
I was left all alone in hell.
Later, I found out
that my father
planned to pay off his debts…
with the life insurance money.
When my mom found out about his plan,
she decided to die with him.
And it's at the cost of their lives
that I am alive today.
I'm a terrible daughter.
At that moment, you must have
wanted to ease your parents' suffering.
The world was so cruel
that even a child wanted to end her life.
[sighs]
Don't hold back.
It's okay to cry.
GANGHA POLICE STATION
The cause of death is drowning,
and the injuries appear to have
occurred after entering the water.
YACHT REPAIRED THE DAY BEFORE THE ACCIDENT
There's record of the yacht being repaired
the day before the accident.
Yes, Cheongun Police
checked with the company
and they said
there were no particular issues.
The scene could say otherwise.
Let's go take a look.
Hello.
Uh, Sang-mi.
You're in charge of our external
storage providers, is that correct?
Yes.
Send me that list right away please.
Sure, I'll send it over now.
OFF-SITE STORAGE PROVIDER CONTRACT STATUS
[voice] Within an hour.
[knocks on door]
Do you need to contact
one of the companies?
Uh.
Can you tell me which pieces are stored
at a warehouse called Felix Storage?
That warehouse has been reserved
for Chair Kim's personal use.
Even though there's a contract, I'm pretty
sure nothing has been stored there yet.
Really?
At least officially.
No orders have been given.
All right.
[opera music playing]
Hmm, hey. You're here.
Is it going to Hannam-dong?
Mm-hmm.
She spent 2.1 million
on those random paintings,
she must be waiting
with her neck stretched out.
It's about time I sent the invitation.
Once that lady receives your kimchi jar,
she will finally be able to
buy the paintings she really wants.
Mm-hmm.
Even with luxury brands,
you have to spend thousands
just to get that bag, you know?
They're so full of themselves,
thinking they've been chosen.
They'll throw their own money around
and still not come to their senses.
How did you know you'd get
2.1 million dollars from Hannam-dong?
You need to look at their eyes.
Greed shows itself. They can't hide it.
I see it sometimes too. Those eyes.
Hmm.
Seriously, what is this thing?
They're that desperate to get it?
Good grief.
Oh, and I've emailed you the media art
video for our next exhibition.
- Please take a look.
- Hmm.
Did it turn out well?
Nothing really catches my eye these days.
The artist reinterprets
Andy Warhol's work,
showing the boldness
of an emerging artist.
It's a bit provocative,
but aligns well with current trends.
Hmm, that right?
INBOX
Let's see.
Mmm.
I like the colors in it.
The cuts feel a bit fast I think.
Kids these days
have such interesting ideas, huh?
I'm glad to hear that.
Then we'll refine it a bit more
based on your feedback.
All right.
[Eun-hye] Who is it?
I'm here from the auction house.
[boater] The Katarina?
It had a few minor issues but…
the thing with yachts is
they may look big but they're sensitive.
The Katarina. The Katarina was, uh…
Yes. Here it is.
BOAT MAINTENANCE ESTIMATE
The connection between the engine
and starter was a bit loose.
If you think of it in human terms,
it's like being on the verge of divorce.
The engine wouldn't start properly
and sometimes it would
just cut out unexpectedly.
- Well, then--
- You see,
I made sure to fix all of that, you know?
It had nothing to do with the yacht.
Look, my pride is on the line here.
I mean, you think I can't fix this?
Well, then did Mr. Yoon Seung-jae
say anything that day?
If I remember correctly,
his friend came instead.
I think Mr. Yoon said he was busy.
His friend?
Was it a guy?
Yeah, the both of them
used to come by my shop together.
Is this him?
[boater] Was it him?
Looking at his face, I think it was him.
Yeah.
So, can you do the repairs
even if the owner isn't there?
Well, I was able to do it
because that guy had the keys.
The keys?
The keys for the yacht. The Katarina.
You're leaving early?
That's why I told you
not to come in today.
Take this and get some sleep, okay?
Or you wanna go to the hospital?
Want me to come?
I don't have time. I need to hurry.
Where are you going?
I thought you were going home.
There's a problem
with the catalog we sent over.
I need to stop by the print shop.
But that's the Auction Team…
Han Seol-ah told you to do it?
That Auction Team's busy, so…
Brother, are you an idiot?
Why do her words leave you frozen?
The catalog has my photos. It's fine.
I'll stop by the print shop
and then head home, all right?
[Eun-hyuk coughing]
At the next major auction, one of you two
will be standing next to me.
I've let them know that the associate
auctioneer will be chosen internally,
so give it your best.
- Will do.
You can go.
Lunch?
Did you eat?
[chuckles] Not yet.
Then shall we go eat?
[Na-hee] I'm telling you,
it's really suspicious.
Come on. What, that… Are you suggesting
they've got a thing going on?
Ms. Han? No way.
It's in their eyes.
Their eyes were full of romance.
They even went out for lunch on their own.
Oh, my. Could they already be dating?
Hey. Only for yourself?
I was saving this.
Yeah? Here.
As usual, this gets me through the day.
This one's on the house.
They say fighting brings people closer.
It's nice to see you two getting along.
- [chuckles]
- Thanks. We need to talk about something.
Oh, sure.
By tomorrow, even the cleaning lady
at the auction house
will be able to recognize you
as the subject of all the gossip.
What? No way.
Hey. Come on. Come on.
[chuckles]
That'll do the trick.
Tell me everything.
Anything that could be connected
to Paek Jun-beom.
I met him roughly a week
before Yun-ji's accident.
It was at the preview exhibition.
Are you sure?
Yes. I had never met him before then.
But,
for some reason, it felt like he knew me.
I can't explain it,
but it was like he could see through me.
It's very likely that he already knew you.
I bet he'd been watching you
and approached deliberately.
Why would that be?
[sighs]
If he's the one who killed those men,
there's only one answer.
He wants Han Seol-ah.
HAN SEOL-AH(28).M4A
[Eun-hyuk] Seol-ah.
Where are you?
Why?
Seung-jae…
He was in an accident.
Uh, can you…
Can you come to the harbor right away?
"Come to the harbor right away?"
According to the report,
Han Seol-ah and Do Eun-hyuk
showed up at the scene
less than an hour
after the police called them.
By the way,
why wasn't that on the list of evidence?
I just discovered it a little late.
Well, did you report it?
Of course.
YOUR HOME
[Eun-gyeom] See.
This is normally
where the CEO's photo goes,
and there isn't one.
So, this jerk must be insecure
about his looks, right?
But get this.
Totally blew my expectations.
He's seriously handsome.
I mean, really. He's unreal, you know?
Handsome, tall, smart,
built a killer app and ends up super rich.
Why didn't you make one too?
I know, right?
Why does my brain
only work well on bad stuff?
Hey, zoom in a bit.
PAEK JUN-BEOM08.JPG
- Which one?
- This one.
- This?
- Yeah.
"OnWorld"?
[newsreader] On the 14th,
amid a terrorist attack
by the IS armed group in Raqqa, Syria,
a Korean aid worker was killed,
adding to the tragedy.
It took place in an area controlled
by IS civilian forces.
Lee Su-ho died there while with OnWorld.
ONWORLD VOLUNTEER WORK PHOTO BOOK
[staff] Sorry to keep you waiting.
[chuckles] It took me a little while
to find it.
- That's all right.
- Please have a seat.
Well, there's no record of anyone
named Paek Jun-beom in the staff logs,
but if he was wearing one of our vests,
he was probably a volunteer.
- A volunteer you say?
- Yes.
There are so many and most of them
only do it as a one-off.
Oh, I can ask
the volunteer group about him.
Okay.
And Mr. Lee Su-ho was indeed
one of our staff members here.
I heard there was an incident in Syria,
but it happened
before I joined the organization.
Is there anyone still around
who knew him well?
Hmm, Manager Lee Kwang-jin from the
relief team probably knew him well.
He's been on all the overseas missions.
Then he might remember
Paek Jun-beom as well.
Well, if they went together, yes.
Is he here now?
Ah, he left on a work trip to Laos,
but he'll be back soon.
PERSONNEL FILE
NAME: LEE SU-HO
Yes. Up here.
We're looking for accomplices
and trying to identify suspects
among people close to Han Seol-ah.
I'm here today
to ask for your cooperation.
Detective Gong, it's your request.
Of course I can hand over
her parents' files.
What else do you need?
For the time being, SIU should stay put
and leave everything to the police.
Gosh, where have you been?
- Why?
- Detective Gong is here.
Over there.
We'll ask you to join the investigation
once we apprehend Kim Yun-ji's killer.
Well, sure. That's fine by us.
Why are you doing all this?
Do you even know what I had to do
to cover up the spy phone?
Do you really trust Han Seol-ah?
She even collected
her parents' insurance money.
It was a family suicide.
Her family tried to die together,
and only Han Seol-ah survived.
She went through that at only 15.
She is just a victim here.
Are you sure you're not letting your
emotions keep you from seeing the truth?
Syria…
[paper rustling]
BOAT MAINTENANCE ESTIMATE
This?
Seol-ah asked me to.
She was worried because the yacht
wouldn't start properly,
and since Seung-jae was too busy
to deal with it…
she asked me to get it fixed.
I called the mechanic and it was repaired.
And the accident happened
the next day, right?
Who gave you the keys?
Seol-ah.
If it were me, I probably
wouldn't have done that favor.
Mr. Do Eun-hyuk.
It seems like Han Seol-ah
comes first in everything you do, huh?
[phone buzzing]
SEOL-AH
Go ahead and answer it. It's okay.
[sighs]
SEOL-AH
Why? Is there a problem?
No.
There isn't.
MISSED CALL
SEOL-AH
NONGHYUP LIFE INSURANCE
I'm Lee Kwang-jin,
manager of OnWorld's relief team.
I hear you were asking for me.
Oh, yeah. Hello.
Um, I'm investigating
Mr. Lee Su-ho's acci--
Su-ho's death. It's all because of
that woman, Han Seol-ah.
I'm getting on a flight
to Korea right now.
I'll tell you everything when I arrive.
Mr. Lee Kwang-jin?
Yes.
We spoke on the phone earlier.
[Kwang-jin] Yes, of course.
I remember Jun-beom.
He started volunteering with OnWorld
back in college.
Even though his family
was pretty well-off.
he was interested
in helping people in need.
Did he do volunteer work?
Yes.
He even took a break from school to do it.
[scoffs] If only that hadn't happened
in Syria…
Syria?
So, he was there with Lee Su-ho?
[both exclaim]
[groans]
Is there anything you remember at all?
[Woo-seok] It was my fault.
What if there's another accomplice?
Someone with money, time,
and the ability to pull it off.
I've seen him before.
YOUR HOME
CEO PAEK JUN-BEOM
[Chair Kim] If you've lost everything,
you have nothing left to lose
and nothing left to fear either.
[Woo-seok] The accident happened
while tracking the suspect.
[Seol-ah] What if ended up
just using you and ditching you?
I don't care.
You can just use me.