NEULSAEM GENERAL HOSPITAL
[tense music plays]
[Woo-seok] Syria?
[tires squealing]
[exclaiming]
[pants]
[exhales sharply]
[groans]
[winces]
[sighs]
[mysterious music plays]
[pants]
EPISODE 7
Han Seol-ah was the first to call it in.
She even gave a witness statement.
I'll call you back, all right?
[line disconnects]
[Gong sighs]
You happened to be at the scene
at that exact moment?
Another coincidence?
Here's the dashcam footage from my call.
Got an alibi this time too.
There seems to be a misunderstanding.
I'm just offering this
in case it helps with the investigation.
[Gong] So, you're confident?
We'll find out with the forensics.
MISSED CALL
SEOL-AH
Captain, you need to see this.
APPROVED TRANSACTIONS
DOMESTIC & INTERNATIONAL
Do Eun-hye submitted this. They were
together at the time of the accident.
Their parents' house and his studio
are both in Cheongun,
so they were there every weekend.
LIST OF EVIDENCE: RECEIPT
DAEYONGRU CHEONGUN BRANCH: AUGUST 17, 2025
- Since Woo-seok's accident…
- [sighs]
…happened while he was here too,
could it be that we got it all wrong?
[sighs]
[tense music plays]
What if there's another accomplice?
What about Do Eun-hyuk?
It's possible Han Seol-ah
has been dragging him
to every crime scene for an alibi.
[gasps]
So, the real player is somewhere else?
[huffs] Are you an idiot or something?
Why would you fix
someone else's yacht, huh?
- You just do as you're told.
- [line rings]
What would have happened
if it weren't for me?
[scoffs] Seriously?
Hey!
[knocks]
[dramatic music plays]
[Kwang-jin] Jun-beom, he started
volunteering with OnWorld back in college.
Even though his family
was pretty well-off.
He was interested
in helping people in need.
Did he do volunteer work?
[scoffs] If only
that hadn't happened in Syria.
[Woo-seok] Syria?
[sighs]
You could've ended up just like that.
I'm telling you
you could've just died.
And you still trust Han Seol-ah?
INTENSIVE CARE UNIT
What? You think that woman saved you
or something?
- [sighs]
- It's just like with Kim Yun-ji case.
Han Seol-ah was at every scene
but her alibi is solid.
So what?
Just a coincidence?
Shouldn't we assume there's an accomplice?
[sighs]
It wasn't Do Eun-hyuk.
He was at the police station
being questioned.
Well…
she's the type who could control
anyone she wanted to.
And there might be another person
involved as well.
But what would she gain
by getting rid of me or Lee Kwang-jin?
Huh?
Are you so convinced it's Han Seol-ah
that you're blinded by it?
What if the real culprit is someone else?
[sighs] So, you're saying someone targeted
only the people around Han Seol-ah?
You have something else, don't you?
[sighs]
The accident happened
while tracking a suspect.
Who's that?
Paek Jun-beom.
But why him?
He sold the wine exclusively
at Yoon Seung-jae's restaurant,
and was at the scene
the day Kim Yun-ji died.
That's not all.
Paek Jun-beom was in Syria as well.
Syria?
That's where Lee Su-ho died.
Are you saying there's a connection
between those two?
Lee Su-ho worked for OnWorld,
and Paek Jun-beom was a volunteer there.
Paek Jun-beom is the one
tied to all the deaths…
surrounding Han Seol-ah.
PAEK JUN-BEOM (35 YEARS OLD)
CEO OF YOUR HOME
Someone with money, time,
and the ability to pull it off.
Someone who crossed paths with Kim Yun-ji.
HWANG SUK-JI (37 YEARS OLD)
CAFE THIRD NIGHT, HAN SEOL-AH'S FRIEND
Maybe an uninvited guest
who snuck into the auction house
that night.
Whose trail should we check first?
[door opens]
Isn't it too soon for you
to be moving around?
I'm okay.
[sighs]
I'm more worried
about Mr. Lee Kwang-jin though.
What brought you
to the scene of the accident?
Is there anything you remember? Anything?
I got the hint from that painting.
[melancholy music plays]
[sighs]
Syria…
I passed your message on to Mr. Lee,
but don't wait for a response.
He wanted to tell you
he has nothing further to say, Ms. Han.
I'm so sorry.
When will he be back
from his trip to Laos?
Oh…
Actually,
he's flying back from Laos tonight.
[Seol-ah] I was on my way to meet
Mr. Lee Kwang-jin at the airport,
when I saw your car.
[ominous music plays]
Behind you, I saw the same black car
that had been following us
right on your tail.
[exclaims]
I had a bad feeling,
so I immediately turned the car around.
Woo-seok!
[sighs]
[sympathetic music plays]
You saved me, Seol-ah.
Anyone passing by would've done the same.
But…
what was the culprit trying to do?
He was trying to silence Mr. Lee.
Paek Jun-beom
had been an OnWorld volunteer
since college.
He was in Syria with Lee Su-ho as well.
An Orphan from Syria.
He sent that painting on purpose too.
[sighs] Probably.
Why?
Just because he worked with Su-ho. Is that
really enough reason to go this far?
Mr. Lee may be the only one
who knew why Paek Jun-beom approached us.
[sighs]
He will be the only one who knows,
unless Mr. Lee wakes up.
NEULSAEM GENERAL HOSPITAL
[phone buzzes]
SENIOR MANAGER CHA
[Woo-seok] Mr. Ahn, stake out
the hospital until Mr. Lee wakes up.
Keep it discreet.
[inquisitive music plays]
[chuckles]
My first mission as an SIU member.
NONGHYUP LIFE INSURANCE SIU
ASSISTANT MANAGER AHN YOUNG-SOO
I'll make sure to see it through.
[gasps, moans]
[clears throat]
VIOLENT CRIMES UNIT 1
The dashcam results are finally in.
- [taps keyboard]
- Take a look at this.
[intense music plays]
That's who caused the accident.
It may take some time
to identify the license plate
- but we've confirmed the make and model.
- Was the accident recorded?
[taps keyboard]
Right here.
[both sigh]
[sighs]
She went to save him.
I think she really is just a witness.
PORTRAITS OF A WOMAN: SPECIAL EXHIBITION
[footsteps approaching]
[Seol-ah] For this auction,
I'm placing the artist who had that
intense bidding war towards the beginning.
And I've scheduled the Stiller
as the 30th lot--
With this lineup, it's going to be intense
right from the start.
You're really determined to hit a record
price, aren't you?
- [chuckles]
- [client speaking in Spanish]
[continues speaking Spanish]
[Na-hee, in English] Oh, uh, Spanish, huh?
Just a moment, please.
[in Spanish] Sir?
- Can I help you?
- Do you speak Spanish?
Yes, just a little.
[client] Thank goodness.
I like this painting.
Is it possible to negotiate the price?
You're a valued guest
who has traveled a long way,
so of course, we can do that for you.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
[in English] He's going ahead
with the payment. Get everything ready.
Of course, ma'am.
- [Chair Kim, in Spanish] Thank you.
- [client] Thank you.
[in English] So,
did you study art in Spain, ma'am?
When I was pushed out of the company
for selling a forgery,
not a single person
reached out to help me.
So I packed my bags and flew out.
I scrubbed floors at first
and I learned that if I wanted to survive,
then I had to learn the language first.
I picked it up by ear
and copied what I heard.
And thanks to that,
I managed to secure a few art pieces.
That became my leverage
to return to Royal Auction,
and that's how I survived.
So, I packed my bags and left.
You're truly remarkable, ma'am.
To be able to rise again
after losing everything like that.
Most people would just give up
after losing all they had.
That's usually how it goes, ma'am.
If you've lost everything,
you have nothing left to lose
- and nothing left to fear.
- [elevator dings]
[elevator doors open]
[tense music plays]
TAEMYUNG GROUP
[mouse clicks]
FIRE BREAKS OUT ON A TRUCK TRANSPORTING
TAEMYUNG CULTURAL FOUNDATION ART
DAMAGE WORTH TENS OF BILLIONS OF WON,
NO CASUALTIES REPORTED
[Seol-ah] 1.5 million, any takers?
- [crowd gasping]
- Vanished Sensation by Fabien Leclerc
is sold to Chairman Park Min-cheol
of Taemyung Group.
Please make sure
to give this to Chair Kim.
This exhibition was only possible
thanks to her.
The five pieces he won
at the last special auction
will be exhibited
at the Busan Taemyung Art Center.
Busan?
[dramatic music plays]
PLEASE ENTER YOUR PASSWORD
TO UNLOCK THIS DRIVE
TAEMYUNG GROUP AUCTION ARTWORK LIST
VANISHED SENSATION,
THE REMAINS OF ECSTASY
THE ABYSS, ECHO, TURBULENCE
GANGHA POLICE STATION
The suspect's vehicle is a black sedan,
plate ending in 4549.
A ghost car fitted
with a canceled license plate.
It came out onto Yeongjong Bridge
and headed toward Gangseo-gu.
4549 MOVEMENT ROUTE
When was the car last seen?
[Gong] Here.
[dramatic music plays]
I've seen him before.
[elevator dings]
[worker] Flower delivery
for Ms. Han Seol-ah.
- Oh, right there. That's her office.
- Oh. Thank you.
Flower delivery.
Who is it from?
One moment please. [sighs]
It was sent anonymously.
Have a good one.
[Su-ho] Happy birthday.
[contemplative music plays]
[dramatic music plays]
[sighs] My gosh.
I though Mr. Cha was just good-looking,
but it turns out
he's a total romantic too.
Ms. Han even gets a confession like that.
I'm jealous.
Confession?
You didn't you know? The meaning
of lisianthus flowers is eternal love.
[Na-hee exclaims]
So, that means
you like flowers too, ma'am?
[scoffs] What woman doesn't like flowers,
hmm?
[mournful music plays]
[sighs softly]
S-Seol-ah.
If I disappear…
you'd be happy, wouldn't you?
That's…
It's what you want, isn't it?
I no longer have a reason to live.
Even if I had to die to stay with you…
I would do it.
[Su-ho laughs]
I know. I know I'm crazy. [sniffles]
But if it means
you'll remember me forever…
I'll be the bad guy.
[Seol-ah] You and I…
want different things.
I just barely got the internship
at the auction house.
And this opportunity
means everything to me.
So, are you saying
I'm not worth fitting into your life?
Su-ho…
Who are you with right now?
Why didn't you answer?
I'm working.
Hey. Aren't you with that
photographer bastard now?
Just stop it please.
So it's all over now, huh?
That's like telling me to die.
Fine.
Then just die, okay? Stop tormenting me.
Is that what you want?
Do you understand what it means to die?
[line disconnects]
[phone buzzes]
[drilling]
[breathes shakily]
Don't forget…
I'm…
[Su-ho laughs]
You killed me.
[laughing]
[laughing continues]
[video stops]
THE LATE LEE SU-HO
MAY 7, 1991 - JUNE 14, 2018
FAITHFUL TO DUTY, FAITHFUL TO THE PEOPLE
The captain thinks Paek Jun-beom
and Han Seol-ah were working together.
In Kim Yun-Ji's case and this accident.
I still find that woman suspicious.
Won't we find out who's behind this
if we find that car?
Yeah, let's find that ghost car first then
we'll deal with the rest.
It's been a while since we teamed up.
You cover the East side.
I'll take the West.
Deal.
[determined music plays]
[gasps]
SANJUN JUNKYARD
JUNKYARD
[Gong] Geez, he's fast.
I think it's that car over there.
Hey.
[Gong] There's nothing but trash in here.
1-HOUR FREE PASS
- "Alpha Tower"?
- I know where this is.
Call KCSI for fingerprints.
I'll go see what Paek Jun-beom is up to.
[GPS] You've reached your destination.
Ending navigation.
ALPHA TOWER
[dramatic music plays]
[Jae-min] He's unreal, you know?
Handsome, tall, smart.
Built a killer app and ends up super rich.
[Woo-seok] Mr. Paek, may I ask you
what brings you here at this hour?
CEO PAEK JUN-BEOM
I'm Paek Jun-beom.
Nice to meet you. I'm Paek Jun-beom.
I guess you're left-handed.
Oh, it's just a habit of mine.
[doorbell rings]
[stammers]
Will these do?
[chuckles] I've never done this before.
What's this?
I mean… I thought our operation
was still ongoing, right?
Oh.
You're right.
I should react like this then.
[stammers]
Anyway, happy birthday.
It is your birthday, after all.
Thank you.
Come on in.
It was sent anonymously.
These are the flowers
Su-ho always used to send.
They even know details like that.
I have no idea either
how they found out something like that,
or what they could possibly want from me.
Any other messages?
[groans]
[grunts]
[sighs]
Whoever wrote this is left-handed.
Mr. Paek is left-handed too.
I mean, she always
spent her birthday with us.
This is the first time she doesn't.
[clicks tongue] It kinda stings.
You went all the way to Daejeon
to buy this?
That is some serious dedication.
Geez, I'm a picky eater,
so I don't eat much else,
but I like strawberry tarts.
And you've never got me one
on my birthday.
You can have it all.
Hmm, can I?
[chuckles, gasps]
Look at this color.
[exclaims]
- Is it good?
- It's so good.
Cheers.
[sighs]
We found the car thanks to your dashcam.
It was a ghost car,
and we tracked it entering
and leaving your complex.
Then the flowers
were definitely Mr. Paek's doing.
We can't leave him be.
INSURANCE POLICY
POLICYHOLDER: CHA WOO-SEOK
BENEFICIARY: HAN SEOL-AH
If we move first and set a trap,
he'll fall for it.
[scoffs]
MAIN COVERAGE:
NATURAL DEATH, GENERAL INJURY
So, I'm a pushover?
Why does everyone do whatever they want?
Seol-ah, listen.
Think about this calmly.
If we do this,
the real culprit will show up.
Do you have any idea
how cruel this is to me?
Seol-ah.
What if I ended up just using you
and ditching you?
What if you really end up dead?
I don't care.
You hear me? I don't care.
[sighs]
You can use me instead.
Have you ever lived with guilt
because someone's death was your fault?
Do you know how painful that is?
I know how that feels.
I lost my only family.
After my parents divorced…
I was raised by my grandmother.
After she passed away,
it was just the two of us.
[scoffs, chuckles]
Brother, when you told me
you were becoming a cop,
the first thing I bought
was a first aid kit.
Please don't get hurt again.
I was supposed to be Woo-hee's big brother
and her mother and dad as well.
But she took care of me instead.
She was always strong. Stronger than me.
After becoming a cop,
I ran around day and night
chasing criminals.
But I couldn't protect my own family.
[Woo-seok sighs]
If I had checked on her one more time,
I wouldn't have lost her.
[Woo-seok breathes shakily]
After I lost my sister, I threw myself
into cases like a madman.
I worked myself to death,
thinking it would help even a little
if I caught someone,
but it… [scoffs] …but it never did.
I realized this guilt…
isn't something that goes away
just by saving someone else.
It's not your fault Woo-seok.
You're wrong.
It was my fault.
I couldn't protect my sister.
[chuckles]
We're both trapped in the same prison,
living each day with the person
we couldn't protect in our hearts.
NEULSAEM GENERAL HOSPITAL
[intense music plays]
You caught me.
I was trying not to show it.
You can't run auctions
without having a sharp eye.
[chuckles]
Did you get hurt in the accident?
Yeah.
Then don't…
get hurt again.
[romantic music plays]
[phone buzzing]
- [buzzing continues]
- [groans]
AHN YOUNG-SOO
I'm sorry.
- Hey.
- [Mr. Ahn] Mr. Cha.
Mr. Lee Kwang-jin just woke up.
He'll be moved to a regular ward.
Ahn, where are you?
I'm outside the ICU right now.
Listen carefully now.
[thrilling music plays]
Mr. Lee's awake. He's conscious again.
No, just stay here.
It's better if you don't come with me.
Who knows what might happen?
And the police keep suspecting you.
I don't want them to accuse you anymore.
That sounds good. Give me a call.
[line ringing]
ROOM 2102
LEE *****-JIN
[intense music plays]
[both grunting]
[straining]
[car alarm blaring]
[groaning]
[sighs]
[groans]
[Woo-seok] Are you awake?
Hey! You should've followed him!
What? This was terrifying enough.
- Hey. Did you do what I said?
- Yes.
Geez, he really scared me.
Hey, hey, hey.
[exclaims]
Hey, hey! Why that…
[sighs] This bastard is 4549.
Wow. I totally knew
I'd pull this off to him.
He didn't have a doctor's coat on.
Wow.
"Pentobarbital."
What is it used for?
An anesthetic used to put animals down.
Huh?
Honestly,
if it weren't for your foresight,
Mr. Lee would've been in real danger then.
Where is he now?
Upstairs.
The top floor.
VIP1
AHN *****-SOO
Do you recognize him?
Yes, it's Jun-beom.
[dramatic music plays]
Was this taken in Syria?
They were practically like brothers…
until that accident.
That day, an air strike wiped out
the entire refugee camp.
Su-ho was killed on the spot.
Jun-beom barely made it out alive.
After being brought to Korea for surgery,
he vanished.
What's Paek Jun-beom
trying to hide, really?
Are you sure it was Jun-beom who did it?
But why?
Mr. Lee, you know something important,
don't you?
After Su-ho got dumped by his girlfriend,
he said he wanted to die.
He didn't even bother taking cover.
Honestly,
I think it was basically suicide.
Jun-beom got hurt
while trying to save him.
[phone buzzes]
CHA WOO-SEOK
[Woo-seok] I found
where Lee Su-ho's ashes are.
If it's too much, I'll come with you.
THE LATE LEE SU-HO
MAY 7, 1991 - JUNE 14, 2018
[Kwang-jin] He was an orphan
with no family,
so I placed his ashes in a columbarium.
Seems like Mr. Paek
wanted me to come all the way here.
The truth is, I knew that Su-ho
decided to end his own life.
It was his choice.
Don't forget…
I'm…
[laughing]
You killed me.
[sighs]
I couldn't bring myself to tell you.
I was afraid you'd think
I was behind Su-ho's death too.
What do you mean?
I overheard what you said
to Detective Gong.
She's the type who could control
anyone she wanted to.
And there might be another person
involved too.
[sighs]
I guess you didn't hear
what I said after that.
I just meant that that's how the cops
might see it.
You're wrong.
I don't suspect you anymore, Seol-ah.
I trust you.
That's why I'm telling you
everything here.
He kept saying he was going to die,
like it was a habit,
so I told him to die
- and stop tormenting me.
- [sighs]
If only I hadn't said that
the last time we spoke…
Don't beat yourself up.
It's not your fault.
I think I know why he sent this now.
Mr. Paek is just getting revenge on me
in Su-ho's place instead.
He's using every means he can
in order to make me miserable.
They sent us a gift.
Why don't we return the favor?
DNA MATCH,
VEHICLE 4549, EVIDENCE IN ATTEMPTED MURDER
The same DNA was found in the
ghost vehicle and on the doctor's coat,
and it matched Kim Sung-hae,
age 34 who served time for manslaughter.
KIM SUNG-HAE
He's a former non-commissioned officer
with special training
and deployment experience in Syria.
You're saying he was in Syria
with Paek Jun-beom?
So, Paek's the torso
and Kim Sung-hae's just the tail.
We can't link him
just based on him going in
and out of the company building
unless we conduct a search and seizure.
Well, let's get him.
Catch Kim Sung-hae first
for attempted murder.
All right. [sighs]
Nice to see you, Ms. Han.
I'll take you to Mr. Paek's.
Mr. Paek will be here shortly.
Please have a seat
and make yourself comfortable.
Sure, no problem.
CEO PAEK JUN-BEOM
DELETING…
SELECTED FILES: 30
INTEGRATED CONTROL CENTER
CCTV SYSTEM
As instructed, we're deleting all the
footage that shows your movements, sir.
Delete the recent footage
from the parking lot entrance too.
[facility manager]
Will that be everything, sir?
No problem.
DELETING…
SELECTED FILES: 382
VEHICLE ACCESS LOG PROGRAM
WAITING FOR CONNECTION
The black sedan would've been caught
on the parking gate cameras
going in and out of the building.
THANK YOU
GOODBYE
Boss, take a look at this.
It's an automatic license plate
recognition system.
It captures the plates
and the person in the car too.
But nobody treats it like a big deal,
so the security is a total mess.
It's basically, "Come on in."
Look, see. It works on everything.
Then bring me everything.
Yes, sir.
Right to it.
Huh?
THIS FILE HAS BEEN DELETED
Hold on.
These bastards are deleting
everything in real time.
Damn it. They must have realized
the ghost car got flagged.
That's probably why Paek Jun-beom
isn't showing up right now.
[phone buzzes]
HAN SEOL-AH
Uh, I'm sorry. Something came up.
Have you been waiting long?
Not at all. I just got here too.
Have a seat.
[sighs]
First.
YOU ARE CORDIALLY INVITED TO ROYAL AUCTION
KOREA'S PREMIER FINE ART AUCTION HOUSE
An invitation?
Yes. It's for a preview event
we're holding for our VIP guests,
and it's also be the first public showing
of the Stiller piece.
Yes, I should be there.
That's my beloved child after all.
Everyone's been wondering
who the Stiller's owner is.
Are you sure you're okay with your
identity being revealed like this?
[thrilling music plays]
[inhales sharply]
I wanted to stay mysterious
but you kind of shattered that for me.
Oh, and about An Orphan from Syria…
It seems like a pretty meaningful piece
to you.
May I ask why you decided to consign it?
Hmm…
I wanted to show more of myself.
It feels like me without the mask.
[inhales sharply]
Truth is, I used to have nothing,
like an orphan in the middle of a war.
[inhales sharply] Honestly,
it's still strange
to see myself sitting here.
It takes a very thick mask to stand there
and pretend that everything is fine.
THIS FILE HAS BEEN DELETED
[gasps]
Found it. Wow, that was so close.
I barely got my hands on it.
If I had taken a bit longer,
this data would've been gone.
It was Paek Jun-beom.
[Jae-min] Man,
this is why he wiped everything.
Geez, this bastard is really meticulous.
One scary piece of work, huh?
What an evil bastard. Shit.
That mask…
how about you take it off now?
Who are you really?
Why did you approach me
when you already knew Su-ho?
Do you think I'm trying to blame you
for Su-ho's death?
Is that what you think?
[ominous music plays]
Or do you think…
I'm getting revenge on you?
No, that's dangerous.
Boss, wait up!
SPECIAL THANKS TO KIM DONGJUN
FOR HIS APPEARANCE
[Seol-ah] I don't get it.
Even if this is a revenge
on Su-ho's behalf,
this is way too extreme.
It's similar to my sister's accident.
Criminals stick to familiar tactics
and repeat what's worked before.
I'm also chasing the person
who ruined my life.
[Seol-ah] Then let's uncover them.
Let's uncover the hidden truth together.
So, isn't there something
you want to tell me?
[Woo-seok] We can finally find out
what Paek Jun-beom was trying to hide.
Let go!
[Jun-beom] I finally got it out there.