The restaurant CEO
who got into an accident on the river
also canceled his policy before he died.
The woman lost three men
but gained nothing.
But unlike her,
I gained something from these three cases.
If you love Han Seol-ah…
you die.
And that's a fact.
I'm sure those men wanted to save
the deeply hurt woman.
You see, men tend to go blind
once they fall in love.
That's why they gave their all to her,
even their lives.
She must've seemed like such a pitiful,
helpless woman.
You talk as if
you know everything about me.
Then tell me.
Who's next?
Next?
The next man who'll fall in love…
with Han Seol-ah.
You're right.
Su-ho, the first man you mentioned,
died in Syria seven years ago
in a terrorist bomb attack.
So, do you think
I was behind the attack as well?
All the policies were canceled,
and I didn't receive anything,
so why…
Those canceled policies…
could be a cover-up for something else.
Once or twice may be a coincidence,
but there's no such thing
as a third coincidence.
Lee Su-ho.
Choi Young-ho.
Yoon Seung-jae.
What did you gain
from the deaths of those men?
Good question.
What could it be?
Please leave now.
If you ever show up unannounced again,
I'll call the police.
I'll file an official complaint
with your company as well.
Be my guest.
The more you try to avoid me…
the more often our paths will cross.
EPISODE 3
REDEVELOPMENT THAT IGNORES
THE RESIDENTS MUST STOP!
ABSOLUTELY OPPOSED TO REDEVELOPMENT
WE'VE CLOSED DOWN FOR PERSONAL REASONS
THANK YOU FOR YOUR SUPPORT
He was up in arms
about the redevelopment issue,
but he took off
after receiving compensation.
Who else could've gotten
that old man to flip?
It's obvious.
HYUN-SU'S FRUIT
-Look.
-So it's true.
You're definitely a professional, Ms. Han.
-No way.
-Isn't wanting to die
-Yun-ji went straight at her.
-the normal response at this point?
Was it the booze talking?
What are you trying to say?
We shouldn't have
let her drink that night.
-I know.
-This is insane.
-What's going on?
-Oh, it's…
This was posted on the Allined App.
The main podium?
With your skills?
I won't hold back anymore.
Enjoy what time you have left.
Not that there's much of it.
Our weekly meeting starts at 11 a.m.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Ms. Kim Yun-ji.
-Man, that glare is no joke.
Let's behave like professionals.
You're definitely a professional, Ms. Han.
Isn't wanting to die
the normal response at this point?
What are you trying to say?
I'm curious to see the look on your face
when I take the main podium from you.
The main podium?
AUGUST 26TH, 21:02
Check out the time.
This was recorded right before
Kim Yun-ji called me.
What if the tip she was going to give you
was this secret she mentioned?
It's possible
Han Seol-ah got to her first.
No way.
Then who recorded this video?
Chair Kim.
Have you seen the video?
What are you going to do about this?
I found this on Ms. Kim's computer.
I'm having a really hard time
because of Ms. Han.
Just be patient.
You'll be on the main podium
at the next auction
as Chief Auctioneer Kim Yun-ji.
I can really trust you this time, right?
You're so pretty.
Oh, gosh. You need to delete that.
I guess she didn't trust you enough,
seeing how she saved these screenshots.
The pain of becoming a mistress.
The man who doesn't deliver
on his promise.
Aren't those the more plausible reasons
for her suicide?
What?
Are you seriously
trying to pin it on me?
If you feel wronged,
I can post this on the app for you.
One person is fanning the flames,
while the other is pouring fuel on it.
Good going, you two.
If you want to cover something up,
you need to put up a good distraction.
This piece by Stiller
was auctioned at Christie's Hong Kong.
Rumor has it that it's in the country.
All this petty gossip will get buried
if it sells for a record price
at our upcoming auction.
Go get the Stiller.
Whoever brings the painting…
will be first in line for succession.
You've really improved.
It seems like only yesterday
you were struggling as a contract intern.
But now you know how to play hardball.
You're the one who started it.
Where do you get off
trying to use my private life
to threaten me?
That's not the original.
What?
If this ever gets out,
I'll make sure you pay for it.
I have no plans to leak it right now.
This will come in handy for a long time.
All right.
Have at it.
But I'll be the one bringing the Stiller!
I only wish I could work
with such a competent superior.
MANAGING DIRECTOR JAE-UK
DO YOU WANT TO DELETE THIS FILE?
YES / NO
THERE ARE NO ITEMS TO DISPLAY
You know what, Artist Han?
Your daughter doesn't take after you.
That's why I like her.
21:58, KIM YUN-JI, ROOFTOP
Chew quietly.
ROYAL AUCTION
THE NIGHT OF THE CHOSEN FEW
22:02, HAN SEOL-AH
Let's take a look.
At 21:58,
Kim Yun-ji got off on the 12th floor
and went to the rooftop.
Then at 22:02,
Han Seol-ah got off on the 12th floor
and went somewhere.
About 9 minutes later, at 22:11,
Kim Yun-ji fell.
It looks like Han Seol-ah went after her
after having an argument.
If there had been a CCTV in the hallway,
we'd have caught the culprit.
That's why we need to find a witness.
A witness?
KIM YUN-JI CASE TIP CALLER.WAV
The woman who died at Royal Auction
didn't commit suicide.
She was murdered.
This wasn't a prank call.
You wouldn't use a pay phone
if you didn't see anything.
Find this person immediately.
By the end of the day.
Being told to find them
by the end of the day
doesn't mean the tip caller
will just fall into our lap.
I wish I were the tip caller
so I could go home.
WOO-SEOK
Hello?
Captain's been focused only on Han Seol-ah
since he came back
from Yoon Seung-jae's restaurant.
He's completely zeroed in on her.
Casually drop it during the meeting.
Drop what?
The fact that Choi Young-ho and Lee Su-ho
were also victims.
And that all three of these men
who were with Han Seol-ah
had taken out a policy before they died.
Do you want to see him lose it completely?
Tell him he can have
the insurance files too.
I'm the one who's going to suffer for it.
It's bad enough he's already on edge
and demanding that we find
the tip caller immediately.
Here.
Oh, man.
I feel better.
So, we need to bring in
the tip caller, right?
I knew it. Loyalty lives on.
I'm not doomed yet.
Over there.
Wait, 3386?
It's this pay phone.
Yeah, it is.
Hello, Grandma.
I'm a police officer.
Is there a CCTV nearby?
At a tiny hole-in-the-wall shop like this?
Grandma? Seriously?
I knew there wouldn't be any CCTVs.
This has been parked here
for at least a few days.
Get out of here!
Get out!
I told you that little bastard isn't here!
Please just leave!
Business is slow enough as it is!
It's okay.
Come on, pretty lady.
I don't know what's going on,
but we're not here to arrest your son.
We just need to see the dashcam footage
on that truck, pretty lady.
"Pretty lady"?
My goodness, you're such a smooth talker.
Oh, please.
He seems to be inside right now.
Can you please persuade him?
Here you go.
This is for the goods,
and this is for the dashcam memory card.
I wouldn't have to show my badge first
if I had operating funds to work with.
I'm telling you,
it's because you called her "grandma."
But "pretty lady" is a bit much,
don't you think?
You need to go all out
when flattering someone.
Now, go find the tip caller.
Will do.
I'll stay up all night again
and go through this.
RECORDING
The woman who died at Royal Auction
didn't commit suicide.
She was murdered.
YOON SEUNG-JAE
Let's see.
That's strange.
I don't see the name in the visitor's log.
Couriers generally sign in.
Can I check the CCTV footage, then?
You'll need to wait until tomorrow
for the manager to review it.
Then please check it and get back to me.
Okay, will do.
HAN SEOL-AH
YOON SEUNG-JAE, CHOI YOUNG-HO, LEE SU-HO
I'm sure those men wanted to save
the deeply hurt woman.
You see, men tend to go blind
once they fall in love.
That's why they gave their all to her,
even their lives.
HAN SEOL-AH
Then tell me.
Who's the next man who'll fall in love…
with Han Seol-ah?
YOON SEUNG-JAE, CHOI YOUNG-HO, LEE SU-HO
Lee Su-ho.
Choi Young-ho.
Yoon Seung-jae.
What did you gain
from the deaths of those men?
Once or twice may be a coincidence,
but there's no such thing
as a third coincidence.
Lee Su-ho.
Choi Young-ho.
Yoon Seung-jae.
So these three men dated the same woman
before they died?
Ms. Kim Yun-ji must've asked
for your number to tip you off about this.
Hold on a minute.
Why did you bring a life insurance case
to general insurance?
And to the sales teams, no less.
Could you make me
a general insurance business card?
A business card?
1 UNREAD MESSAGE
This is the management office.
Upon reviewing the CCTV footage,
the courier works for Dallyeo Quick.
Good morning.
You're here early, Ms. Han.
Sang-mi.
Which courier service do we use?
Dallyeo Quick.
Do you need to send something?
Can I get their phone number?
Seol-ah.
Did you send me that wine?
If you wanted it to be a secret,
you shouldn't have used the same courier
the company uses.
The pick-up location was your house.
What was your intention?
Did you want me to feel guilty?
Are you also trying to prove
that I killed Seung-jae?
Seung-jae asked me to do it.
I'm sorry.
I should've told you.
Eun-hyuk.
Forget it.
We'll talk about it some other time.
We should all have dinner together.
It's been a while.
It'd be even better with a glass of wine.
Did you like the gift?
You should've given it to me directly
instead of sneaking around like a rat.
You must've been pretty shocked.
But then again,
any normal person would react that way.
I sent it because Eun-hyuk couldn't do it.
If that makes you mad,
go complain to your dead fiancé.
Hey, Do Eun-hye!
Okay.
Thanks.
What did you do that for?
She probably came to check
because she's guilty of something.
-What?
-Be honest.
You're suspecting her too, aren't you?
Seung-jae asked me to do it.
If something happens to me,
can you give this to Seol-ah?
What are you talking about?
Not that I expect anything to happen.
Then why ask me to do it
instead of giving it to her yourself?
I heard something strange.
I could just ignore it,
but I can't get it out of my head.
I guess I still can't fully trust Seol-ah.
Pretty pathetic, huh?
-Wow, this looks delicious.
-This looks so good.
-Thank you.
-We'll enjoy them.
-Please do.
So you're our new account manager?
You're so cool.
Please come by often.
Sure thing.
Ms. Han, he's from the insurance company.
I'm the new fine art insurance
account manager,
Cha Woo-seok.
I look forward to working with you,
Chief Auctioneer Han Seol-ah.
Nice to meet you.
I've been put in charge of
the fine art insurance responsibilities.
I'll do it.
Okay.
This is your first day,
so I'll give you a tour
of the auction house.
Shall we?
Don't even think about
asking for a new account manager.
It doesn't matter to me
as long as you do your job well.
When it comes to risk management,
I like to handle it myself.
Each ID badge
has a different clearance level
depending on the holder's position.
The storage vault
that carries consigned artworks
is equipped
with the highest level of security,
which means
it's not a place anyone can enter.
I guess the chief auctioneer
has access to all areas
and knows the building layout
better than anyone.
For example, CCTV blind spots
or ways to get to the rooftop
without being seen.
The storage vault is maintained at 20°C
and 50% humidity at all times.
The stored artworks are protected against
flood, fire, and earthquake damage
by double exterior walls
and blast-resistant doors.
A few years ago, the Seoul Museum of Art
held a Renoir exhibition.
The total insured value
of the displayed artworks at the time
was one trillion won.
Likewise, the artworks
in this storage vault…
In the event of damage, destruction,
or theft,
we'd have to cover it.
I watched the video.
You're calmer than I expected.
What was Kim Yun-ji trying to reveal
before she was murdered?
Perhaps the secret behind the deaths
of Han Seol-ah's men?
You're convinced I killed them,
yet you have no evidence.
And you still want to know why they died.
Is that why you came all the way here
under the pretense of work?
I see you're well aware.
So?
Did you decide on your next man?
Step aside if you don't want to cause
any misunderstandings.
There are people in the monitoring room
watching us right now.
Moving forward,
meetings without prior notice
won't be allowed.
If things don't run smoothly,
it won't be the account manager
who gets replaced.
It'll be the company.
Goodbye, then.
CHARITY AUCTION TO SUPPORT EMERGING
ARTISTS IN PARTNERSHIP WITH TAEMYUNG
They got rid of everything,
including Kim Yun-ji's computer.
What about her car?
I looked everywhere near her place,
but I can't find it.
Her car insurance is still valid,
so I don't think they got rid of it yet.
I think I know where it is.
It's 132M 3925.
That's Kim Yun-ji's license plate number.
132M 3925
PARKING PASS
"Luen Palace"?
I can't believe you haven't eaten yet.
Come on, don't read too much into it.
I'm sure Seung-jae
just meant it as a surprise gift.
Eun-hye's just overreacting.
She's such a rude little brat.
She should be grateful to you.
Over here.
Well, look who it is.
What brings Mr. Cha from general insurance
to our life insurance team dinner?
-Have I been fired?
-You had your business card made,
so you might as well
just stay in general insurance.
Mr. Ahn will do everything from now on.
Hey, congratulations on passing the exam.
Thank you!
I'll do my best!
You know, a certificate alone
doesn't make you an SIU investigator.
You need to have Cha-cha's tenacity.
He dug into Han Seol-ah
and found a string of cases.
You have to be driven by curiosity
to be able to do this kind of work.
Mr. Cha, do you instinctively know
that a crime has taken place
just by looking at a case?
No, I don't.
It's just that if I miss anything,
there will be more victims,
like Chae-rin and my sister.
I don't want to make that mistake again.
Come on, have a drink.
This strong sense of duty
and responsibility
is the SIU's core principle, got it?
So do your best, okay?
-Will do, sir.
-Good.
Here.
Your first mission
as an official SIU investigator.
What is it?
"Luen Palace"?
You want to know who owns the Stiller?
I don't have all the answers, you know.
Oh, please.
Your husband is the vice president
of Christie's Hong Kong.
I'm sure you know.
A WALK
BLOOM
What do you think?
Must be an emerging artist.
Her pieces at our gallery exhibition
will sell out on the first day.
Granted, her father
will buy everything anonymously.
She's the daughter of the EN Group family.
Just make sure to feature her work
in your next major auction.
So you inflate
the prices of the paintings,
then sell the pieces you already own
at a higher value?
If you do this for me…
I'll return the favor.
THE LANGUAGE OF SILENCE,
BLOOMING THROUGH THE BRUSH
All I know is the English name
he used for the bid.
James Paek.
There's a rumor that he's the CEO
of a successful start-up company.
ENIGMATIC CEO OF 'YOUR HOME'…
AT THE CENTER OF RAMPANT RUMORS
RUMORS ABOUT 'YOUR HOME' CEO PAEK JUN-BEOM
HAVE BEEN SPREADING…
I'm Paek Jun-beom.
I'm Han Seol-ah.
CEO PAEK JUN-BEOM
NONGHYUP LIFE INSURANCE
Jeez, this hurts.
Oh, jeez.
Hold on a second.
Thank you.
Long time no see.
A torn ACL
resulting in lasting disability?
Gosh, how did this happen?
Well, I got hurt playing soccer.
Oh, boy.
Did you buy this secondhand too?
-Don't come near me!
-If you're going to pull a scam,
-That really hurts!
-at least put some effort into it, punk!
It's for real this time!
Hey.
Don't you remember what I said?
I said I'd make your diagnosis real
if you got caught again.
You little bastard.
-Hold on.
-Come here.
-Go away.
-Go away. Get away from me!
Don't come near me!
Allow me to escort you in.
This is our private viewing room.
Thank you for coming.
We prepared this just for you, Mr. Paek.
I'm rather excited.
This piece is praised
for its portrayal of human solitude
in a Baselitz-inspired style.
I see you've already figured out my taste
after just one auction.
To be honest,
I got a hint from a different piece.
Why is this here?
This is the first piece
you entrusted to me.
I thought you'd like one last look
before the auction.
I never thought I'd see it again.
Seeing it like this feels different.
I stopped by Hong Kong every vacation.
I happened upon an art gallery
and saw this painting.
Before I knew it,
I'd been standing in front of it
for an hour.
So it was destiny
that brought you to this piece.
It felt like I was falling in love.
Toward the end,
I even choked up a little.
It's called Stendhal syndrome.
This painting was the beginning.
I have a few more like this.
Would you like to come see them?
I'm curious to know which pieces
struck a chord with your soul.
Are you hungry?
In China,
they used to call this loach-tofu soup
"Diaochan tofu."
Is Diaochan a reference to
Romance of the Three Kingdoms?
Yes.
She was a beauty who shook the kingdom.
When loach and tofu are added to hot soup,
the loach burrows into the tofu
to find a place to hide.
In the end,
it slowly cooks to death
while trapped in the tofu.
So you're saying Diaochan
is like the tofu.
Then who was the loach
that died in her embrace?
I don't care who the loach was.
However, I find Diaochan quite pitiful.
Because that woman…
had nowhere to hide.
Just as I expected.
Oh, right.
Here you go.
Please enjoy.
There's something
I'd like to request of you.
What is it?
Two years ago at Christie's Hong Kong,
you successfully bid
on an Emil Stiller piece.
Please entrust it to me.
I'd like to feature it as the main lot
of our next auction.
I see.
You were interested in that piece,
and not me.
I'm sure you know
that there are many domestic collectors
eager to own a Stiller.
You'll receive at least 30%
more than your winning bid at Christie's.
You have my word.
It's a tempting offer.
But it's a piece I treasure.
Do you have…
any terms or conditions in mind?
People aren't driven by numbers alone.
I'm fairly certain
you already know what I want.
Since it's a piece you treasure so much,
it's only right
to give you more time to consider.
Once you decide on the terms,
please let me know.
They're intentionally taking alleyways.
ONDANG EXIT 2
Wait, I found them.
Nice, they tapped their card.
We'll find out who they are in no time.
This person was trying to
hide their identity at all costs.
There's a good chance
they know the suspect.
Luen Palace…
As you can see,
most of the hits are studio apartments.
I think it might be
a secret hideout or something.
Secret?
Like a secret rendezvous spot
for Kim Yun-ji and Yoon Seung-jae
to have a love affair.
There'd be too many eyes at hotels,
you see.
So? How are you going to find it?
I'll search on foot myself.
Seriously?
There are 70 Luen Palaces in Seoul alone,
and there are 30 just near Royal Auction.
Wait, you knew this whole time
and still made me do all that work?
Let's call in the experts.
Experts?
What experts?
BBALLAYU DELIVERY SERVICE
Damn it.
Boss!
Grim Reaper Cha is here!
Oh, damn it!
Hey, get rid of those papers!
MEDICAL CERTIFICATE
INSURANCE CLAIM FORM
Is it good?
Come on now. Eat slowly.
What, did you do something wrong?
Jeez, what do you take me for?
I'm done pulling wrist-bump scams!
See? My wrists are perfectly fine.
They'd better be fine,
after all the payouts they've cost us.
-Where are your guys lazing about?
-Lazing about?
They're out there,
running around and hustling.
Thanks to you for throwing us in jail,
we're living honest lives now.
Oh, is that so?
But you see, the world has changed a lot.
You can try hiding
or sitting on the mail all you want.
But the second you file a claim,
an AI program will let me know.
INSURANCE CLAIM DETAILS
DIAGNOSIS: RIGHT ANKLE JOINT FRACTURE
So you have ankle issues, huh?
I'll give you a chance.
A chance to run around
and hustle real hard.
CONFIRM FOLLOWING LUEN PALACE LOCATION
BBALLAYU
88-2, YEONDAM-DONG, SEODAEMUN-GU
198-12, WOLGYEON-DONG, NOWON-GU
JAMYUN-DONG, SONGPA-GU
512-74, WANGYUN-DONG, SEONGDONG-GU
GEUMHA-DONG, SEONGDONG-GU
SANGU-DONG, DONGJAK-GU
YEOKDAM-DONG, GANGNAM-GU
HANJAE-DONG, YONGSAN-GU
SEOYUN-DONG, JONGNO-GU
Hello, is this the key card that you use?
174-12, SANGYUN-DONG, MAPO-GU
-Okay, thank you.
-You're welcome.
The door is opening.
Found it.
BBALLAYU MR. YU
Did you find it?
Of course!
The client lives in Bangjae-dong.
All right, great job.
GANGHA POLICE STATION
-Is she the tip caller?
-Yes.
Do Eun-hye.
She's a graduate student
currently interning at Royal Auction.
Ms. Do Eun-hye.
Your identity and everything you say here
will be kept confidential.
Are you sure?
There's no need to worry.
I saw everything.
That woman killed her.
The door is opening.
WE HOPE YOU TRULY FEEL AT HOME HERE
Han Seol-ah?
It was Han Seol-ah.
She killed her.
Do you still think
I killed someone?
A spy app?
Didn't it ever occur to you
that Kim Yun-ji knew too much?
You'll end up dying at her hands too.
You knew Paek Jun-beom
was stalking you, right?
I don't have the right to fall apart.
Then you must know
what happened to Ms. Han Seol-ah's family.
Han Seol-ah was the only one who survived.
What if it was nothing more
than a string of bad luck for Han Seol-ah?
Is she a suspect now?
You're not getting out of this
unless you have a solid alibi.
Subtitle: Jenny Kiim