EPISODE 8
[Jun-beom] Hmm…
The truth is, I used to have nothing,
like an orphan in the middle of a war.
It takes a very thick mask to stand there
and pretend that everything is fine.
Who are you, really?
Why did you approach me
when you already knew Su-ho?
[intense music plays]
Do you think I'm trying to blame you
for Su-ho's death?
Is that what you think?
[dramatic music plays]
Do you think…
I'm getting revenge on you for him?
[scoffs]
I watching Su-ho be happy and sad.
Also tormented all because of
a woman named Han Seol-ah.
And I always wondered,
"What kind of person is she?"
The moment I saw you,
I understood everything.
She's the kind of woman
a man would risk his life for.
So then…
Are you saying you ended up falling for
the woman who caused your friend's death?
[Jun-beom] Hmm…
If Su-ho were still alive, I wouldn't
have dared to even think about it.
But my friend's no longer in this world,
and you and I are here,
under the same sky.
Anything else?
Do you need to hear another truth?
[fire alarm blaring]
[Jun-beom gasps]
J.B. PAEK
[breathing heavily, grunting]
Sir. Are you all right, sir?
[groans] What's going on?
The fire alarm went off.
We're checking on it.
Find out what's going on!
Yes, sir.
[door closes]
Let's finish this later.
[panting]
[person on PA]
Due to the fire alarm being activated,
all employees are requested
to evacuate the building.
Please avoid the elevators
and use the stairs
to find your nearest exit.
Get in, quick!
YOUR HOME
CONTROL CENTER
Stop right there.
[breathes shakily]
Next one.
Another angle.
Stop, right there.
Nice black cap…
103S 4549
So, it was Mr. Paek who…
He's the one who ordered the hit.
The alarm suddenly went off earlier,
so I couldn't press him for more, but…
I did that.
I was worried you'd be in danger.
[phone beeps]
[line ringing]
[Jun-beom] My office
will handle the arrangements.
Stay overseas for a while.
[phone beeps]
[sighs]
I didn't think this day
would come so soon.
If Mr. Paek tried to have
Mr. Lee Kwang-jin killed,
could it mean he's done this before?
Yeah, there's a good chance
that he might have.
I don't get it.
Even if this is revenge on Su-ho's behalf,
this is way too extreme.
I think Paek Jun-beom
already knows what information
was taken from the server,
and in that state, he'll do anything.
If we track his movements
after Syria and put pressure on him--
Then what if you become
his next target, Woo-seok?
It'd be even better.
His henchman's been exposed.
Paek Jun-beom will have to
trip himself up now.
Why are you being so reckless?
Are you worried about me?
Yes, of course.
Well, that's enough for me.
[Woo-seok chuckles]
AHN *****-SOO / M / 980205
Mr. Ahn, how long
do I have to keep hiding?
I'm tired of this.
We're just worried
you'll be in danger again.
My wife thinks I'm having an affair
because I won't even tell her where I am.
Mr. Ahn. Looks like you're out. [chuckles]
Want play poker now or what?
- Mr. Cha!
- Hey.
Feeling any better?
[chuckles] The doctor said
it'd be good to relieve some stress,
so I'm recovering
by emptying Mr. Ahn's wallet.
- [chuckles]
- He's a killer at cards.
Oh, man… [chuckles]
[Kwang-jin gasps]
Jun-beom…
Why would Jun-beom target me?
I just can't believe it.
He just didn't want the two of us to meet.
There's definitely more
to the relationship between
Lee Su-ho and Paek Jun-beom.
[sighs] The Jun-beom I know
has no reason to do this.
He's not the type
to do something like this.
A shameful secret
that shouldn't be known to the world.
Something no one should ever know.
[sighs] I can't think of anything.
[sighs]
[sighs] Well, if you happen to,
then please let me know.
I've almost got this puzzle solved…
but there's a piece missing.
The most important one.
GANGHA POLICE STATION
- [door opens]
- They've issued a travel ban
on Kim Sung-hae.
Hit-and-run, attempted murder.
There's more than enough evidence. [sighs]
The problem is Paek Jun-beom.
This illegal evidence from Woo-seok
isn't enough to charge him with murder.
Do you think that he also had
Kim Sung-hae kill Kim Yun-ji?
That doesn't explain
Paek Jun-beom's motive, though.
He's got a lot to lose. [sighs]
In cases like this,
isn't it love or a grudge?
[Seong-il inhales sharply]
Let's bring him in as a witness then,
and we'll see what kind of person he is.
All right.
- [knocks on door]
- [door opens]
Oh, hello there.
- You're here.
- What's up?
I called, but you didn't answer.
You called me?
Captain, why don't you just
head back home with your wife tonight?
Oh, I just wanted to drop off
some clothes for him
and some snacks for you guys.
You haven't had
a proper meal yet, have you?
Wow, this isn't just any midnight snack.
It's Chungmu gimbap.
Most people get bored of regular gimbap.
- [Gong] We will definitely enjoy this.
- [chuckles]
[Seong-il] Come on.
Let's sit down and eat.
[Eun-gyeom] Oh, this looks delicious.
[chuckles]
NONGHYUP LIFE INSURANCE
[employees chattering]
[Won-il] Taemyung Cultural
Foundation's accident?
FINE ART
INSURANCE CLAIM FORM
A cargo truck crashed into
the retaining wall and started a fire,
and five artworks were destroyed.
The insured amount alone is $7 million.
DRIVING RECORD CERTIFICATE
NAME: HAN SEO-YUL
The driver is only 23
and hasn't had his license a year.
When moving high-value paintings
like these, you never do it alone.
[machines whirring]
[Woo-seok]
A team of professionals is sent.
FROM ARTIST STUDIOS TO YOU
[engine starts]
[Woo-seok] They also send
the ones with the most experience.
There's no way that they would
handle this this carelessly.
[sighs]
It's possible this whole thing was staged.
- Anyway, get in touch with the GI's SIU.
- [sighs]
This case doesn't belong here. Not here.
We actually need some help
from an art expert,
and I hear you and Ms. Han
from Royal Auction
have gotten a bit closer.
Who said that?
[sighs]
I'll ask her.
[sighs] Thank you so much.
[sighs]
Can you tell me how many bidders
we've secured so far
for the Stiller piece?
Eleven so far,
both phone and written bids.
Only three are confirmed so far,
but we're still actively promoting it.
The price is so high, the hurdle is steep.
Same here.
Three people interested in the piece.
Early bids will determine
the momentum we have on this lot.
We need to make sure there's competition,
so please reach out to our VIPs again
and keep me updated.
Sure.
About the catalog…
Sang-mi, I'd like you
to complete the final review.
- Yes, Ms. Han.
- All right, that is it for today.
[inhales sharply] Oh, wait, wasn't that
something Yun-ji always handled?
Does that mean you might be going up
on the rostrum as an assistant this time?
Not sure. Who knows
what Ms. Han might be thinking?
Oh, man…
[dramatic music plays]
FINE ART
INSURANCE CLAIM FORM
[prosecutor] The defendant, Ju Hyun-su,
intentionally crashed
into a retaining wall on an entrance ramp,
causing the death of his passenger,
Cha Woo-hee.
The evidence at the scene,
and the defendant's insurance records,
demonstrate that he acted
with intent to kill.
The prosecution requests
the court sentence the defendant
to ten years' imprisonment.
[sighs]
- [phone beeps]
- [line rings]
[phone buzzing]
[colleague chuckles]
INCOMING CALL
WOO-SEOK
Wow, you're psychic.
I was just about to call you.
Anything on Ju Hyun-su?
So, someone signed up
for a food delivery app using his email.
About a month ago.
Get me the address. Fast!
[colleague] All right, got it.
[gate beeps]
[elevator bell dings]
[elevator doors shut]
ROYAL AUCTION
JU HYUN-SU
[elevator bell dings]
[ethereal music playing]
[door closes]
[ethereal music continues]
I thought I told you
to stay away from the auction house.
I'm family too.
I just wanted to see what it was like
to check in like everyone else.
Didn't I tell you not to act rashly?
The Taemyung deal has to wrap up smoothly.
No need to worry.
I've given it my all.
I mean, it is my comeback project.
I should at least get a taste of
one of your famous spreads, ma'am.
[scoffs]
Once the Taemyung deal's wrapped up,
hook me up with a stake too.
I won't be greedy.
How about 10%?
[scoffs]
You've grown a lot, Ju Hyun-su.
You've raised me well, ma'am.
[mysterious music plays]
[Seol-ah] I saw the accident on the news.
Is there a problem with the insurance?
The thing is…
It's similar to my sister's accident.
What do you mean?
The crash happened on the same curve
near Namcheonghyeon Interchange,
hitting the passenger side only.
Apart from the fire,
everything is the same.
Criminals stick to familiar tactics
and repeat methods that worked before.
I want to check if it was planned
by the same person.
I need your help, Seol-ah.
I handled the auctions
of all these pieces.
They were listed by an overseas gallery,
but when I looked into it,
it turned out to be a shell company.
And the real owner is our chairwoman.
Chair Kim?
She chooses artworks that will be
profitable for wealthy clients,
and takes a cut herself.
Taemyung bought this piece
for 1.05 million dollars,
but it was imported from overseas
for about 210,000.
Is that possible?
You see, paintings don't have set prices.
If someone pays 1.05 million for one,
that becomes the piece's real value.
Oh, I see.
So if the paintings were insured
and someone deliberately burned them,
they could collect the full 1.05 million?
People in the art world
would never do that though.
There's no way
they'd destroy an authentic artwork.
They'd sneak out the authentic piece.
And then burn the fake.
That is Chair Kim's way of doing things.
[Woo-seok sighs]
[scoffs]
A struggling artist was hired by Chair Kim
to create a replica of a particular piece.
But later, the work was passed off as
the original, and sparked a huge scandal.
[artist groans, yelps]
- [wails]
- [loan shark] Oh, no.
No, my hand! No! [screaming, sobbing]
[Han wails]
If you're going to be shameless,
at least own up to it.
Borrowing from loan sharks? Bold move.
Now look at the mess you're in, Mr. Han.
- Your hand…
- [Han screaming, sobbing]
- I'm begging you!
- How are you gonna hold a brush
with a hand like that?
That's the only thing about you
that still works.
If this ends up being a posthumous work,
I'll make sure it sells for a high price.
No! Please, I'm begging you.
Just let me keep it!
The naive artist thought he was just
painting a replica for an exhibition,
but he took the fall…
for everything.
Later, he was hounded by loan sharks
and died with his family.
Could the artist be…
He was my father.
I want to prove to the world
that my father wasn't that kind of person.
So, you joined Royal Auction--
[Seol-ah] Because I wanted revenge.
And now, it's become
the only reason I have to go on living.
I know how that feels.
I am also after the person
who ruined my life.
We need to find the paintings. [sighs]
The ones that were supposedly burned.
There's a secret vault
in Chair Kim's office.
I've been wanting to get in for
a long time but never had the opportunity.
You're going to need
someone like me for this.
And I need an art insider
to solve this fraud case.
Then let's uncover them.
Let's uncover the hidden truths together.
[exhales sharply]
Damn it, why's this office so soundproof?
Shit.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- [gasps]
Damn, you scared me. Geez…
- There's someone in there.
- Really?
Well, it was dead quiet.
I thought it was empty.
[clears throat, clicks tongue]
I'm off.
MEET CHA WOO-SEOK, THE GRIM
REAPER OF INSURANCE FRAUD!
He looks like an upright, dependable guy,
based on his features.
Is there anything else
you need me to do, ma'am?
You know I can be just as good as Yun-ji.
Do you know Ms. Kim's responsibilities?
I know, to some extent.
I may not be there yet,
but I'll learn step by step.
What I'm looking for
isn't someone at Ms. Kim's level,
but someone at Ms. Han's.
You should be aiming to reach
Han Seol-ah's level, at the very least.
For now,
just keep reporting to me like this.
Yes, ma'am. I'll make sure
to keep reporting like this from now on.
[Seol-ah] Mr. Paek sent me this painting.
There should be a clue in here.
"An Orphan from Syria."
Su-ho grew up in an orphanage.
His situation was a lot like mine.
[Woo-seok sighs]
[Seol-ah] Just how much did
Mr. Paek learn about me?
He seems to know
just as much about me as Su-ho.
Let's go over everything one by one
and figure out who he is.
[dramatic music plays]
Could you tell me the exact reason
you were fired from Your Home?
Until he left for Syria,
I managed his schedule every day
and took care
of just about everything for him.
But when he came back,
he suddenly told me to leave.
Everyone who had been there
from the beginning was let go as well.
[clicks tongue] Is there anything else
you remember from that time?
Hmm…
The security system in places like the
office and the lab kept malfunctioning.
It had been set up exclusively for
the CEO, but the errors kept happening,
and in the end he told them
to replace the entire system.
Errors?
The system was designed
to scan the iris and grant access,
but for some reason it kept failing
to recognize Mr. Paek.
So they brought in the security company
and they had to replace the whole system.
He wasn't recognized
even though it was him?
Right.
His iris is different?
Even with surgery, there's
no way to change your iris pattern.
He might be someone else
wearing Paek Jun-beom's face.
[Eun-hyuk] Here. What you asked for.
Oh, thanks.
Why did you ask me
to gather photos of this guy?
[chuckles] I promise I'll tell you later.
Where are you going?
Are you going around
investigating Paek Jun-beom?
Paek Jun-beom.
He was friends with Lee Su-ho?
Yes, and he approached me on purpose.
I need to find out exactly
what his real intentions are.
Are you saying that everything
that's happened to you
wasn't just a coincidence?
Mmm. That's exactly what I think.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
You should've come to me first
and not that insurance investigator.
He and I are just sharing information
because we need it.
Well, I'm kind of hurt.
Feels like you're relying
on him more than me.
It's not like that.
He's kind of like us, you know.
We just recognized that
in each other, like you and me.
[friend] Yeah, I know Paek Jun-beom well.
I heard you two were in a start-up club
together back in college.
He used to really take care
of everyone around him,
but a lot of people say
he's become a different person now.
So you're not in contact
with him at all now?
There were rumors that he'd hurt his face,
so I thought maybe that's why
he was avoiding people,
but I saw him at a conference
and he looked fine.
He even seemed
a bit more handsome. [chuckles]
But when I said hi,
he just treated me like I was a stranger.
I hear his other friends
also lost contact with him.
Do you happen to know why?
[inhales sharply]
I'm curious about that too.
How can someone change that much?
That bastard put the poison in, like this.
[exclaiming]
I watched, squinting.
And then I broke out in a cold sweat.
Cold sweat just kept dripping
down my back.
- And then?
- I just pretended to be asleep.
Yikes. If you'd actually had the IV in,
you could've ended up dead instead of me.
Yeah. I risked my life to pull this off.
I was ready to take that bastard on
in hand-to-hand combat
if he saw I was a fake.
Wow. You used
to be a detective too, right?
[smacks lips] Oh, no.
I'm more of the smart type.
I got in through the exam.
Well, anyway,
thank goodness we didn't get caught.
We even kind of look alike
with our faces covered, don't you think?
No, we don't.
[gasps] Can you call Mr. Cha, please?
[Kwang-jin] DNA.
Since we often go into conflict zones,
we keep DNA samples
for identification just in case.
OnWorld has Su-ho
and Jun-beom's DNA on file.
We can finally find out
what Paek Jun-beom wanted to hide.
KIM JOON-YOUNG
An invitation?
Yes, it's for a preview event
for our VIP guests.
And it's also the first public showing
of the Stiller piece.
Yes, I should be there.
That's my beloved child after all.
In 2013, Stiller sought
to visualize the "layers of memory."
The densely applied blue paint, along
with the repeating geometric patterns,
functioned as a metaphor
for the accumulation and erosion of time.
The red lines, reminiscent of frames,
were employed
to heighten a sense of disorientation.
Through this approach,
Stiller captured what he described as
"the moment when memory
consumes its own borders."
[whispers] Look, it's him.
[person 1] He's way better-looking
than the rumors said.
And he's still single.
Mr. Lee Kwang-jin says hello.
He's doing well,
and he misses you.
I'm glad to hear.
Mr. Lee is actually the only person
I really miss too.
Hmm, I see.
[scoffs, inhales sharply]
Do you usually act differently
from how you feel?
Why not make the wise choice this time?
Going to the police
voluntarily looks better.
It could get you a lighter sentence
instead of getting caught.
It sounds like it would be lost of fun,
but I doubt that I'll ever get the chance.
Our legal team works
way too hard these days.
[scoffs]
You must be very upset
about the whole accident, sir.
185TH MAJOR AUCTION
The paintings have appreciated several
times over, so the losses are huge.
And it's not just one.
You've got insurance
for exactly this kind of situation.
Ms. Han, I hear you know
the insurance account manager.
- [visitor] You do?
- Make sure that they take good care of it.
Yes. Of course, ma'am.
Put your worries to rest.
You know Ms. Han's great at what she does.
[chuckles]
Once you get the compensation,
you can buy even better paintings.
I'll pick out some good ones
for you again. [chuckles]
This here is a Stiller piece
coming up in the next auction.
Stiller works are rare,
and since this is the first time
going to auction in the country,
the competition will be fierce…
But I'm sure that you can…
Mr. Paek, Chair Kim would like
to meet with you privately.
Is that okay?
Sure, that's fine.
I guess I'm just not really
cut out for parties.
I feel uncomfortable.
[Seol-ah chuckles]
Times like these
call for a moment to relax.
[Jun-beom] Hmm.
[chuckles] You're working now.
Yes.
[coughing]
Is something wrong?
[Jun-beom chokes, groans]
- Mr. Paek!
- [crowd murmuring]
Mr. Paek Jun-beom, can you hear me?
[choking, straining]
What's wrong with him?
It looks like anaphylactic shock.
With this condition,
he should have an EpiPen.
[straining continues]
[panting]
[murmuring continues]
[breathes heavily]
[visitor 2] How come nobody's called
the ambulance yet?
- Oh, my God.
- [intense music plays]
[visitor 3] What's going on?
[crowd continues murmuring]
- [visitor 2] Is he breathing?
- [visitor 3] What's going on here?
What's wrong with him?
[line rings, clicks]
Where are you? Hurry.
[grunts]
Got the sample?
- Yeah.
- Huh?
[wheezing]
What exactly did you do?
We'll get totally accurate results.
- Step on it.
- Yes, sir.
[breathing shakily]
It looks like anaphylactic shock.
With this condition,
he should have an EpiPen.
[breathes shakily]
[Jun-beom] I watched Su-ho
be happy and sad,
also tormented all because of
a woman named Han Seol-ah.
And I always wondered,
- "What kind of person is she?"
- [breathes shakily]
If Su-ho were still alive, I wouldn't have
dared to even think about it.
But my friend's no longer in this world,
and you and I are here,
under the same sky.
[breathing shakily]
[sighs] What's all this commotion
at a VIP event?
Geez. [clicks tongue]
Mr. Song! Wait.
Hey, come here.
You were serving earlier.
What the hell happened?
[sighs] Mr. Paek suddenly collapsed
while drinking champagne.
But more importantly…
What's this?
LIST OF CHAIR KIM'S PROPERTIES
REGISTERED UNDER BORROWED NAMES
1 / JULIAN VANCE
2 / ELENA MONTGOMERY
What's all this?
It's from Han Seol-ah's desk.
I grabbed it
while all that commotion was going on.
You've got some nerve, huh?
You told me not to slack off.
Right.
Oh, man.
You see, people always
bite the hand that feeds them.
So she's been snooping around
behind Chair Kim's back?
110 over 70.
It's back to normal now.
But should we keep Dr. Jeong on standby?
It's fine.
Have a seat.
Is the event over?
Not yet.
Why are you here?
I don't think
I'll get another chance like today.
So isn't there something
that you want to tell me?
We finally ended up here.
There's somewhere I wanna take you.
I have something to show you.
[car door opens]
[dramatic music plays]
[Su-ho] Someday, later on,
I want us to build a house
somewhere in the woods.
- [Seol-ah] Hmm?
- A two-story house.
[chuckles]
[Su-ho] I want it to have a big yard,
big enough
for the kids to run around all day.
Along the path to the house,
I'll plant birch trees, which you love.
On the lawn, I'll set up a small swing,
so you can ride it with the kids anytime.
[phone buzzes]
SEOL-AH, WHERE ARE YOU?
[Woo-seok] Where are you, Seol-ah?
POWERING OFF…
The first year, I cleared the land.
The next year, I built the house.
From the stonework to the roof,
even every single tree,
my hand is in all of it.
I wanted you
to be the first to see it, Seol-ah.
Aren't you cold?
Just hold on.
Oh, right.
No fire.
Su-ho.
The blood in the syringe you brought
was compared against two samples,
Lee Su-ho and Paek Jun-beom.
We got the results, and the STR profile
is consistent with Lee Su-ho.
TEST RESULTS - SHARED ALLELES
OF SAMPLE 1 AND 2 - MATCH
SAMPLE 1 - LEE SU-HO
SAMPLE 2 - PAEK JUN-BEOM
MATCHES BETWEEN
SAMPLE 1 AND SAMPLE 2.
THEREFORE, SAMPLE 1 AND SAMPLE
2 ARE FROM THE SAME INDIVIDUAL.
So, he's not Paek Jun-beom.
That means he's Lee Su-ho.
Paek Jun-beom died in Syria.
[breathing heavily]
[automated voice] The phone you are trying
to reach is turned off.
You will be directed to voicemail after…
[colleague] Mr. Cha!
[interesting music plays]
It had started
to feel like someone else's name…
[sighs]
…but hearing you say it
feels like I'm back in the old days.
Honestly, I was worried.
"What if she recognizes me?" I thought.
But I was
Paek Jun-beom, the VIP.
You only looked at the painting I had.
Come on.
You were testing if it was me,
weren't you?
Didn't you put something in the champagne?
But how could you be…
Lee Su-ho?
[gate beeps]
Seol-ah.
[Chair Kim] He's at the TH Hotel.
Take good care of him.
[sighs] What's with you?
I'm late for my meeting.
Come on. I'm leaving for Syria tomorrow.
I already told you.
Work is more important to me.
So everything's different
now that you work here?
You think there's no future
with someone like me?
[Seol-ah grunts]
[sighs]
SEOL-AH
CALLING…
- [phone beeps]
- [line rings]
[phone buzzes]
[sighs]
I'm… [chuckles]
You killed me. [laughs]
[Jun-beom] Not anymore.
The idiot who chose death just so
Han Seol-ah would remember him forever…
is dead.
Funny how life works.
Of all days, Jun-beom and I happened
to be wearing each other's clothes.
- [people exclaiming]
- [Kwang-jin] Jun-beom, stay with me.
You're going to be okay, Jun-beom.
Just hang in there.
Jun-beom, you'll be okay. Stay with me.
- Excuse me, move!
- This way.
[Jun-beom] The friend
who came to save me died.
And I was the one who survived.
06 - PAEK JUN-**** - IN SURGERY
CENTRAL OPERATING ROOM
The medical staff thought I was
Paek Jun-beom.
I had to undergo reconstructive surgery
on my blown-out face and vocal cords.
After dozens of surgeries,
I took on my friend's face.
Along with my face and name…
even my voice changed.
And I had to live in the world again…
as Paek Jun-beom.
When I came back,
I realized how stupid it all was.
You didn't care at all
whether I lived or died.
[laughs]
Did you really like money that much?
Enough to go to a hotel with some old man?
That was work.
It wasn't anything like
what you're thinking… [sighs]
So what are you doing here now?
The Lee Su-ho you dumped
was utterly pathetic,
but Paek Jun-beom's life was different.
This is the private viewing room
of our auction house.
I'll escort you inside, sir.
[Seol-ah] Bidder number 86, 3.7 million.
Congratulations.
[Jun-beom] So this is how
sweet and comfortable success is.
It makes you confident.
I just didn't know that world.
And then
I started wondering…
"With this much money,
wouldn't I be able to tempt her?"
But part of me was hoping
you wouldn't fall for it.
[breathes shakily]
[breathing shakily]
You really are Lee Su-ho.
Lee Su-ho the fool.
When you have nothing, the only thing
you can throw away is yourself.
I hated you as much as I loved you.
I wanted revenge, even if
it meant dying. [breathing heavily]
[Woo-seok]
I'm at Paek Jun-beom's house. [grunts]
Shit. [breathes heavily]
I can't reach either of them.
Track their location.
You need to move now!
Don't you know Captain Pyo?
You know he won't roll out
for something like that.
What's going on?
I don't have time to explain.
[breathing heavily]
Then tell him to come
and arrest me in the act.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to kill Paek Jun-beom.
- [Gong] Hey, Cha Woo-seok!
- [phone beeps]
[sighs] Shit.
[alarm blaring]
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[grunting]
APPROACHED SEOL-AH
AFTER KIM YUN-JI CASE
FAINTED AT TAEMYUNG
ART CENTER
SUK-JI
OBSESSED WITH SEOL-AH
EUN-HYUK
MORE THAN A FRIEND?
YUN-JI - OWNED UNIT,
"ACROSS FROM SEOL-AH'S PLACE,"
CHA WOO-SEOK RESIGNED
2024 TO 2025
ROMANCE & PROPOSAL
DATED, THEN PROPOSED
YOON SEUNG-JAE
RAN GALLERY RESTAURANT
[breathes shakily]
HAN SEOL-AH
SEOL-AH AFTER WORK
NOT AS ME…
SEOL-AH
SEOL-AH RUNNING AN AUCTION
[breathing heavily]
And if I'd come back as Lee Su-ho,
would you have even noticed me?
[inhales sharply]
Only after I won that million-dollar bid
did you finally look at me.
And when you found out
I had that Stiller piece,
you came, wagging your tail!
[breathes heavily]
And like a moron,
I wavered again when I saw you like that.
[inhales sharply] I wanted
to make you my woman again!
[breathing heavily]
We can be happy, Seol-ah.
I'm Paek Jun-beom now, I can do anything.
I'll give you whatever you want, okay?
- You've completely lost it!
- Okay?
[laughing]
- Why not? Huh? [chuckles]
- [Seol-ah breathes shakily]
What?
Really? Because of Cha Woo-seok?
[breathes shakily]
You like that bastard?
[siren wailing]
[sighs]
DO EUN-HYUK
MORE THAN JUST A FRIEND?
DO EUN-HYE SEEMS TO
DISLIKE HAN SEOL-AH - HOSTILE
[sighs]
Hurry up and decide.
- [radio beeps]
- Get Paek Jun-beom's location now
and deploy all units.
[radio beeps]
Uncuff him.
[siren wailing]
Last ping before the signal dropped was
866, Jicheon-myeon, Yangpyeong-gun.
[gasps] No!
[whimpering] Get off me! Let go of me!
[breathing shakily]
Stay away.
[laughs]
Don't do this.
I already died once because of you.
Why not make it twice now?
In this life,
I'm not letting you go, Seol-ah.
[sobbing]
[both breathing heavily]
Huh? [breathes heavily]
CALLING…
HAN SEOL-AH
[automated voice] The phone you are
trying to reach is turned off.
You will be directed to voicemail
after the beep and charges will apply.
CALL ENDED
HAN SEOL-AH
Don't move.
[gasps]
[breathes shakily]
- Let go!
- This is a murder case!
Let me see her just once.
[Seol-ah] Everyone said
they just pitied me
that they'd do anything for me,
so I told them to do what my parents did,
to get insurance and die.
[Woo-seok] If someone else was involved…
Don't let your guard down. She's still
the prime suspect of the investigation.
Cha Woo-seok really cares.
[Seol-ah] Thank you so much
for helping me and trusting me.