EPISODE 2
TRANQUILIZER
DO EUN-HYUK
Hello?
Seol-ah.
Where are you right now?
Why?
Seung-jae…
was in an accident.
Can you come to the dock right now?
I think someone died.
Oh, no.
It's him.
He was my fiancé.
Did you already know?
That he canceled his policy
before he died?
Yes.
What a shame.
If he hadn't canceled it,
you could've held 700 million won
in your hands.
You must have a lot of time on your hands
to investigate a canceled policy.
You couldn't receive the death benefit,
but the 200 million won premium
was returned to Mr. Yoon's account.
And you're assuming
that money came my way?
You think I killed my fiancé
for a measly 200 million won?
Tell me.
What does his accident
have to do with what happened to Ms. Kim?
I can smell it.
The stench of someone…
trading human lives for money.
Seol-ah.
What are you doing?
Who are you?
You're the one who interrupted us.
Who do you think you are
to treat Seol-ah--
Don't.
Do you, by any chance,
know Mr. Yoon Seung-jae as well?
I'd like to talk to you.
Can I get your contact number?
I'll give you my business card, then.
I'll be waiting.
You didn't eat again, did you?
Give me a minute.
NONGHYUP LIFE INSURANCE
SIU SENIOR MANAGER CHA WOO-SEOK
Why did an SIU investigator
come to see you?
And what was all that about Seung-jae?
It seems Kim Yun-ji and Seung-jae
had insurance with that company.
Insurance?
"Seiren"?
You know, mermaids that lured sailors
with their singing.
Oh, I think I remember that
from Greek mythology.
I found that story amusing.
I wonder why those men
jumped into the water despite knowing
it'd lead to their deaths.
Is that why
you made it your restaurant logo?
Yeah.
Seol-ah doesn't fully open herself.
There are times when she feels unfamiliar,
as if I'm seeing her for the first time,
and as if she could vanish one day.
Seung-jae…
are you still worried
she won't accept your proposal?
Actually…
I took out a life insurance policy
with Seol-ah as the beneficiary.
EUN-HYE
KIM YUN-JI
AUCTIONEER AT ROYAL AUCTION
DATE OF DEATH: AUGUST 26, 2025
POLICY ISSUE DATE: AUGUST 10, 2023
PUSHED? ACCIDENT? SUICIDE?
TIP CALL BEFORE DEATH
What does his accident
have to do with what happened to Yun-ji?
YOON SEUNG-JAE, OWNER OF THE GALLERY
DATE OF DEATH: AUGUST 17, 2025
BENEFICIARY: HAN SEOL-AH
CHEONGYANG RIVER YACHT ACCIDENT: DROWNED?
And you're assuming
that money came my way?
You think I killed my fiancé
for a measly 200 million won?
These are the newly arrived pieces.
And the condition report for these?
I found the file on Ms. Kim's computer.
I'll take care of it.
I appreciate it, Sang-mi.
Of course.
Also,
about that…
What should we do with it?
COMMUNITY CHAT SEARCH
RISK LIFE FOR MONEY
Anyone willing to risk their life
for money?
Must be in Cheongun.
Recruiting a hitter
with a clean insurance record.
What's the rate?
If we go easy,
about three million won per person.
I'm in.
What car do you have?
It's less suspicious if it's expensive.
It's a foreign-made car, of course.
Yes, I'll get back to you shortly.
-Mr. Cha.
-Yeah?
Ms. Kim Yun-ji's family
had no idea about her insurance policy.
Take all the time you need.
Once you get in touch,
I'll make sure the insurance payout
is processed smoothly.
Thank you.
Thank you, but…
I'd pay a hundred times that amount
if it'd bring my child back.
My precious daughter is gone.
What's the point of any of this?
I'll take that.
It's heavy.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
Let me carry it for you.
He's from the insurance company.
Where should I put it?
This way, please.
It feels like she'll be back any moment,
so I left everything just as it is.
Over here, please.
There are a lot of company documents.
You can take them with you
if you need them.
Okay, I will.
All right, then.
Take a look around.
I'll prepare some tea for you
in the living room.
H2 2025 GLOBAL ART TRENDS REPORT
Can you step out for a bit?
Why?
Do you want to rummage on your own?
Didn't you hear what her mother said?
She told me to take the company documents.
HAN SEOL-AH BUSINESS TRIP
HAN SEOL-AH MEETING
WITH SU GALLERY MANAGER
HAN SEOL-AH ON LEAVE
OUT OF THE OFFICE ALL DAY
MAYBE A VIP CLIENT MEETING?
She didn't smile once
after joining Royal Auction.
I thought it was rather strange
when she left the TV station
and suddenly decided to work
at an auction house.
What kind of person
was Ms. Kim at work?
She was hard-working.
I heard she was about to get promoted.
I just don't understand.
When a suicide takes place at a company,
there's usually a message behind it.
For example, workplace bullying,
conflict between colleagues,
or being wronged.
But you're saying
it was none of these things.
Then I wonder what it was.
I don't know
everyone's personal matters at work.
Do you have any idea
what it could've been?
There's one thing…
that comes to mind.
Why are you out all night these days?
Get up and have a bite to eat
before you sleep.
Are you…
seeing that man again?
Were you with him?
What's wrong, Yun-ji?
Do you know the man Yun-ji was seeing?
A man?
I'm her mother, but I don't know anything.
I don't know why
she was suffering so much,
or why she chose to end things.
ASSOCIATE AUCTIONEER KIM YUN-JI
I'm her mother, but I don't know anything.
I'm sure you went through
everything at work.
Did you come to check
if she left something at home?
You came to check first,
but I guess you didn't find anything.
You want to know what I found?
I could tell you.
Keep it to yourself.
I don't care what you came here to do,
but I find it offensive to be questioned
before a mother who lost her daughter.
Shouldn't you be more cooperative
as her immediate supervisor?
I've already cooperated with the police.
And I have no interest
in prying into the private life
of the deceased.
I'm trying to find out
whether or not it was a wrongful death.
Wrongful death?
What about wrongful suspicion?
You never know
who the real victim might be.
VIOLENT CRIMES UNIT 1
CALL LOG
NAME: KIM YUN-JI
YOON SEUNG-JAE
Yoon Seung-jae.
Yoon Seung-jae again.
Hey, Ggong.
You've heard of Yoon Seung-jae, right?
Yes, I left the Cheongun Police Station
investigation report on your desk.
Investigation report?
GANGNAM "A CLUB" VIP NARCOTICS CASE
GANGHA POLICE STATION
YOON SEUNG-JAE DEATH CASE
BODY FOUND FLOATING IN WATER
BODY IDENTIFIED BY FIANCÉE (HAN SEOL-AH)
NONGHYUP LIFE INSURANCE
2025 CERTIFIED
INSURANCE FRAUD INVESTIGATOR
Don't tell me he hasn't come to work yet.
Does he not know the quarter-end
is right around the corner?
That little punk.
Hey, Cha.
Where the hell are you?!
Oh, I see.
Of course, you have to spend money.
Right, right. Be careful, okay?
What did he say?
He's bringing in a big one.
I'm so done being stuck in this office.
I'm getting out of here!
I can do this!
"The Purpose of Insurance."
CHEONGUN, WHERE LIFE IS GOOD
All right, the backers are here and ready.
Where are you, Mr. Hitter?
I'm 500 meters behind.
This is your first time, right?
I'll go straight,
then turn right, and brake hard,
so be bold and don't hold back.
Just ram into us, okay?
But you're in a compact car.
Just go for it. We won't die.
I'll hit you full force, then.
Okay.
What's your plate number again?
It's 7622.
Got it.
Follow us, but don't make it obvious.
Hey, let's go.
What's taking him so long?
Damn it, why isn't Cha Woo-seok here yet?
-Hey, move over, will you?
-Sit still, for crying out loud.
-Why isn't he coming?
-Why is it so tight in here?
Where is he?
Hey, where are you?
You said you had a foreign-made car.
I do.
It's just a bit big.
What the hell are you saying?
What the hell? It's 7622!
That's him!
-Hey, step on it!
-What the hell?
What the hell is with him?
-Just go!
-Go!
-Speed it up!
-Step on it!
Go faster!
Step on it already!
I told you to lose some weight!
-He's going to hit us!
-Go, go, go!
Hey, move to the side!
I told you to lose some weight, idiot!
Hey!
You crazy bastard! Stop right now!
-Hey!
-Step on it!
He's closing in!
-Go faster!
-He's going to hit us!
Go faster, come on!
Speed up!
Step on it!
-Go faster!
-He's coming!
Step on it!
This is my goddamn car!
-Watch it!
-Holy crap!
Oh, jeez.
Damn it.
Man, I feel like I'm going to die.
Oh, man.
What are you all looking at?
It's nothing. Go back inside.
Oh, dear.
I was going to hit you from behind,
but you crashed into the truck
in front of you.
Hey.
Were you trying to kill or something?
Yeah.
-How'd you know?
-Hey.
Hey.
Oh, let me introduce you to each other.
This is Detective Kim
from Cheongun Police Station.
And this is the Cheongun Family Gang,
an insurance fraud ring.
Oh, I see.
An insurance fraud ring, huh?
-Cops?
-Nice to meet you.
-All right, let's go.
-That hurts!
-Come on.
-See you.
-Go already.
No wonder you wanted to meet
at such a random place
instead of the station.
Here.
Files on all the scams
they've pulled off so far
and CCTV footage.
Man.
This is just what I needed.
A guy like you
should've stayed on as a detective.
Let me show you
what you asked me to look into.
When I got there, he was already dead.
It was an accidental death.
Are you sure Yoon Seung-jae
was alone on the yacht?
Yeah.
There were a lot of witnesses,
including the dock manager and fishermen.
-Then the autopsy results must also--
-Death by drowning.
I think he accidentally fell overboard
and struck the propellers.
The case itself isn't strange,
but that woman was a bit…
Here it is.
His family was overseas at the time,
so his fiancée came to identify the body.
I worried she might pass out
because the body was severely damaged,
but she didn't even bat an eye.
Here.
I canceled the insurance policy,
so don't worry.
CHAIR KIM
I always make sure
to include steamed sea bream
on my father's ancestral table.
He must've liked it.
He didn't because it was too fishy.
I only make it because I want to eat it.
Try some.
Are you sure you didn't make it for me?
Sharp as ever.
Back when I used to bring raw fish
to Artist Han's studio,
you were always the most excited.
Even at a young age, you ate everything,
including sea squirt and sea cucumber.
You seem to remember everything.
You made the right call
visiting Ms. Kim's family.
It takes that kind of thinking
to protect a company.
Workplace bullying
is such a big topic these days.
-How did you--
-They called to say thank you.
Did you know her father
works at the National Tax Service?
If he set his mind to it,
he could easily take down our company.
From what I've heard, her death seems to
have been caused by personal matters.
Her mother didn't harbor
any resentment toward us.
She appeared to be having
a hard time though.
You're having a hard time too.
I heard you lost your fiancé
in an accident.
If something like that happened,
you should've told me
and taken some time off.
It was better for me to focus on work.
You poor thing.
Here, eat up while it's still warm.
I called you earlier.
I'm Cha Woo-seok, an SIU investigator.
What is this about?
I'm investigating matters
involving Mr. Yoon Seung-jae's insurance.
I believe he had a fiancée?
Yes, I know her.
Seol-ah.
Do you happen to know
Ms. Kim Yun-ji as well?
Who?
This person.
Oh, I've seen her before.
I remember her
because she's been coming by often.
Ms. Kim Yun-ji has been here?
What for?
I wouldn't know.
What was her relationship with Mr. Yoon?
Did it look like
they'd known each other long?
They didn't seem close.
Mr. Yoon didn't seem that fond of her.
When was her last visit?
The day before Mr. Yoon's accident.
She came by again
and waited until we closed,
saying she had something to tell him.
She sat over there.
When I got there, he was already dead.
It was an accidental death.
Kim Yun-ji and Yoon Seung-jae met,
and they both died
in just ten days.
I didn't know you were so competent.
It's normal for the police
to have reasonable suspicions.
But why would an SIU investigator
chase after a case
where a payout was never made?
That's the problem with you, Seong-il.
You lack imagination.
You think this was the first time?
This is why you're always one step behind.
Ever thought that your imagination
might be the problem?
Like the delusion
about your sister's death
being a murder.
As the detective in charge,
you don't want to admit incompetence,
yet you want peace of mind.
Yeah.
I get it.
But are you really at peace?
What are you thinking about?
Stop worrying about me.
I'm not.
You are. It's written all over your face.
I didn't lie like my friends did
and was honest about
taking a trip with my boyfriend.
Jeez, when did you grow up?
I think I'll get married before you.
Ms. Cha Woo-hee.
Marriage already? Control yourself.
I'll have what she's having.
Did you know Kim Yun-ji went to see
Yoon Seung-jae at his restaurant?
On the day before the accident, at that.
So?
Why did those two meet?
You can't know everything about someone,
no matter how close you are to them.
So you have no idea?
Then what could it be?
What reason was there for your fiancé
and colleague to meet secretly?
It didn't seem like
they were just acquaintances.
Were they
involved or something?
You kill out of love,
you kill out of hate, and you want to kill
as much as you love.
The most common motive for murder
is love affairs.
Love affairs?
Not a fan of that theory?
Then what about
premeditated murder for money?
Do you know what insurance scammers
have in common?
Once they've had a taste of money,
they want more.
They want bigger money
through easier means.
Then things escalate, and they get bolder,
so bold that people start to notice.
-What does that have to do with--
-Ms. Han Seol-ah.
I'm investigating a tip I received.
A tip claiming that Yoon Seung-jae's death
was a case of murder-for-insurance.
I see Ms. Kim Yun-ji gave you the tip.
I was supposed to meet her that night.
But she goes and commits suicide?
That makes no sense at all.
Stop playing detective.
I never received any insurance payout,
which means
I'm not the subject of your investigation.
I guess I'll find the answer
if I dig deeper.
What is it that you really want to know?
Your fiancé and Kim Yun-ji.
Did you kill them?
HAN SEOL-AH IN CHEONGUN CITY
HAN SEOL-AH, KIM YUN-JI, YOON SEUNG-JAE
A love triangle?
I don't think Han Seol-ah knew.
Really?
Micro expressions.
No matter how good your poker face is,
you can't hide fleeting expressions.
She didn't know.
And there's no way to find out
since they're both dead.
What really happened?
But you know,
when I asked if she killed them,
she was surprisingly unshaken.
It's one or the other.
Either she's innocent,
or she's completely deceiving
even herself.
Either way, it was just
attempted insurance fraud, right?
Ju Hyun-su didn't start out
intending to commit murder either.
It started with the insurance payout
from the car accident.
His accident insurance got denied,
so he needed a scapegoat.
And that was my sister.
So you think Han Seol-ah likely received
a payout in the past as well?
Probably.
I heard Ms. Kim died
after an argument with Ms. Han.
Really?
I heard Ms. Han gave Ms. Kim
a really tough time.
I sensed something might happen
from the moment you tore that painting.
I can't blame her for wanting to die.
I've kept quiet about this,
but Ms. Kim often came to me in tears.
Because of you.
I see.
Then why didn't you do a better job
comforting her?
I guess she couldn't rely on you either.
Whatever.
What's important is public opinion.
The real reason Kim Yun-ji died…
Han Seol-ah constantly bullied Kim Yun-ji…
Rumors about the chief auctioneer
replacement have been floating around…
Ms. Han is Chair Kim's secret daughter?
There's no way.
If you want to sway public opinion,
you should at least use multiple accounts.
What?
What did you say?
Damn it.
She's too damn observant.
For goodness' sake.
A bit higher, please.
Okay.
Next piece.
That's good.
Set the lighting to 20.
Okay, next piece.
-Let's take a ten-minute break.
-Okay.
THE REAL REASON KIM YUN-JI DIED
RUMORS ABOUT CHIEF AUCTIONEER REPLACEMENT
IS IT TRUE THAT MS. HAN IS QUITTING?
What do you think?
About what?
I'm asking how much you can trust
your best friend, Han Seol-ah.
Go back to work.
She scares me now.
I'm worried about you.
Be honest.
You're suspecting her too, aren't you?
Eun-hye.
Seol-ah's the one
who got you this internship.
The scholarships
and training opportunities you got
didn't just happen on their own.
I never asked her for any of that.
Who does she think she is?
She considers us family.
Family?
She's just pretending to care about me
so she can use you.
She's just keeping you around
to make you take photos.
Watch what you say.
This tastes good.
You told me before
that my mom getting money
from me falling ill
wouldn't make her happy,
and that it'd just lead her
further down a bad path.
If I tell the truth,
what will happen to her?
Will she get taken away?
Chae-rin.
The only person who can stop your mom
is you.
And I want to protect you
so you won't hurt anymore.
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you sooner.
I'm fuming.
How much time do you think
Chae-rin's mom will serve?
Can't people like her
just be locked up for good?
What kind of mother is she?
I'm glad Chae-rin finally spoke up,
but I'm not sure about this.
No matter how terrible a mom is,
a child would still miss her.
But still,
we couldn't just leave her like that.
We had to save her.
Did we really save her though?
At least we saved her from the worst.
The world's a crazy place.
All this over money.
I've requested her foster care
and medical support,
so make sure to follow up on it.
I've already prepared
the necessary documents.
Hello, this is Cha Woo-seok.
Mr. Cha, this is the Insurance Fraud
Prevention Team at the KLIA.
It's about your inquiry on Han Seol-ah.
We found a policy
taken out with HA Life Insurance.
SHOCK AS DOCTOR IN 30S DIES
IN SUSPECTED PROPOFOL SELF-INJECTION
NFS REVEALS, "CAUSE OF DEATH WAS
PROPOFOL OVERDOSE, NO SIGNS OF FOUL PLAY"
The doctor's name was Choi Young-ho.
He had a whole life insurance policy
with HA Life Insurance,
and the policy was set to pay out
500 million won
to his then-partner, Han Seol-ah,
upon his death.
His policy was canceled
before he died too.
So she didn't
get this 500 million payout either?
What's up with this woman?
In any case, she didn't get the payout.
Two people died after taking out
huge life insurance policies,
and the beneficiary is the same person.
As a former police captain,
do you not find it suspicious?
That's why it's even less of our concern,
unless the police take an interest in it.
Jeez, you've become a corporate man
through and through.
Hand this over to Detective Gong.
Don't bother with things
that don't count for your performance.
Hey, Cha-cha.
Cha-cha!
I don't know why
this reminds me of that movie.
What are you doing?
Don't you know
Basic Instinct
, Mr. Koo?
Maybe Han Seol-ah is like Sharon Stone
in
Basic Instinct
.
She uses her incredible beauty
to seduce men
into taking out insurance policies
before killing them without mercy!
Should I just kill him?
An SIU investigator?
ION MENTAL CLINIC
I'm not sure why I need to disclose
a deceased person's personal life.
You're not even with the police.
Then do you know who Han Seol-ah is?
We have to maintain
doctor-patient confidentiality--
So she was a patient here.
In any case, I have nothing to tell you.
Hello.
Man, I'm hungry.
Ms. Kim Mi-yeon?
You know something about Ms. Han Seol-ah
and Dr. Choi Young-ho, don't you?
I need a few minutes of your time.
It'll cost you.
Depression?
I guess she was hurting badly
after breaking up with her boyfriend.
Are you saying
she dated someone before Mr. Choi?
Are you kidding me?
Of course, she dated someone before him.
She's gorgeous.
Dr. Choi was so head over heels for her
that he even dumped his girlfriend.
Anyway,
an old heartbreak
is healed through new love.
It's one of those cliché stories.
But I guess she failed at healing,
seeing how things turned out for Dr. Choi.
Then, by any chance,
do you know anything more
about Han Seol-ah's previous boyfriend?
He died.
I think it was somewhere
in the Middle East.
I heard he died in a terrorist attack.
Are you sure he's dead?
Yes.
I mean, it's uncommon.
A terrorist attack in the Middle East.
HAN SEOL-AH MEETING WITH CHAIR KIM,
AUCTION TEAM AFTERNOON MEETING
HAN SEOL-AH BUSINESS TRIP
LEASE SIGNING FOR LUEN PALACE UNIT 702
Did you know Kim Yun-ji went to see
Yoon Seung-jae at his restaurant?
On the day before the accident, at that.
Why did those two meet?
LEASE SIGNING FOR LUEN PALACE UNIT 702
You're still here?
Yeah.
What are you doing?
Oh, I was just organizing some files.
What brings you here at this hour?
I wanted to ask you something.
Seung-jae once mentioned
that he took out a life insurance policy…
and named you as the beneficiary.
By any chance…
did you receive the payout?
Why do you ask?
Tell me. I need to know.
Come on, not you too.
Did you…
really love…
Seung-jae?
Seol-ah.
What do you want me to say?
Don't you think
you're being too cruel to me?
No, I didn't mean--
Of all people,
I thought you were on my side.
This is all our friendship
amounts to, huh?
NONGHYUP LIFE INSURANCE
INSURANCE FOR THE ONES YOU LOVE
YOON SEUNG-JAE, CHOI YOUNG-HO,
A THIRD MAN?
HAN SEOL-AH
"TERRORIST BOMB ATTACK IN SYRIA
KILLS KOREAN MAN"
1 KOREAN AID WORKER KILLED
On the 14th in Raqqa, Syria,
a terrorist attack was carried out
by an armed group called IS,
claiming the life of a Korean aid worker
and adding to the grief of this tragedy.
The attack took place in an area
controlled by IS-affiliated militants,
and reports say a powerful explosion
killed dozens of people.
THE DECEASED WAS A KOREAN NGO WORKER
PROVIDING HUMANITARIAN AID…
They consigned it under my name?
Yes, they insisted
that it be delivered to you.
It's called…
An Orphan from Syria.
Nice painting.
Unauthorized personnel
aren't allowed in here.
Please leave.
Seven years ago,
there was a woman who had a boyfriend.
The man worked
for an international relief organization
that often went into
dangerous conflict zones.
He took out a life insurance policy
for the woman he loved.
The policy
was set to pay out 200 million won
upon his death.
He died in a terrorist attack in Syria.
But the woman
couldn't collect the payout. Why?
Because he suddenly canceled the policy.
She must've been devastated.
She lost her lover
and the payout.
Following the incident,
she became depressed and sought therapy.
But who knows if she was
actually depressed or just pretending?
And this is when
a certain psychiatrist
makes his appearance.
He fell in love with the woman
while trying to help her heal.
ION MENTAL CLINIC
DIRECTOR CHOI YOUNG-HO
He also took out a life insurance policy
and named her the beneficiary.
But a few days before his suicide,
he canceled the policy.
The restaurant CEO
who got into an accident on the river
also canceled his policy before he died.
The woman lost three men
but gained nothing.
But unlike her,
I gained something from these three cases.
If you love Han Seol-ah…
you die.
And that's a fact.
I'm sure those men wanted to save
the deeply hurt woman.
You see, men tend to go blind
once they fall in love.
That's why they gave their all to her,
even their lives.
In those men's eyes,
she must've seemed like such a pitiful,
helpless woman.
Then, in your eyes,
how does that woman appear right now?
I'm not sure.
I can't really see her.
Can you see her now?
That pitiful woman…
Does she look like the kind of woman
who wants to be saved by another man?
You said anyone who loves me ends up dead.
You talk as if
you know everything about me.
Then tell me.
Who's next?
Next?
The next man who'll fall in love…
with Han Seol-ah.
SPECIAL THANKS TO LEE ELIJAH
AND HA SEOKJIN FOR THEIR APPEARANCE
The pain of becoming a mistress.
The man who doesn't deliver
on his promise.
What did you gain
from the deaths of those men?
Does knowing that change anything?
I think I know where it is.
It felt like I was falling in love.
So? Did you decide on your next man?
Step aside if you don't want to cause
any misunderstandings.
Who exactly are you?
Why did you approach me?
Subtitle: Jenny Kim