STILL SHINING
MAY 2018
Well, you always came and did everything.
I felt troubled after getting discharged,
but working with wood eased my mind.
Gosh, I feel so relieved.
I'd accepted the job,
but Mr. Mo suddenly passed away,
and I couldn't reach his daughter.
I wasn't paid, but it still weighed on me.
I can sleep easy now.
-Want to try opening and closing it?
-Okay.
It works fine.
I'll go inside
and see if anything needs work.
Okay.
Just like in the photo,
she must be doing well, wherever she is.
That's what I thought.
STILL SHINING
I can just go from here.
I'll go with you.
Go with me where?
To where you're going.
I'll walk you there.
Where do you live?
Just somewhere temporary.
So, where?
I can't believe we met like this.
I just happened to be there,
but we kept running into each other.
It's funny.
Why did you happen to be there?
If you're out for a walk,
you could end up there.
Out for a walk on a subway platform?
It's that apartment.
Am I not supposed to go there?
What?
Would it put you in a bind
if someone saw you?
For example…
-Because you're married?
-No.
That's not why…
I'm not married.
That's so ridiculous I'm speechless.
I work there. "Empty home care."
I just made that term up, but…
I'm literally just watching the house
while the owner is away.
It's just homes of people I know
who have pets or houseplants.
I'm basically taking care of them.
How far are you planning to go?
I came to Seoul only a few days ago.
Did you come to Seoul
to do this kind of work?
I have a separate day job.
This is just temporary.
Then, where do you live?
I know you have a lot of questions,
but we're here.
It was nice to see you.
Tae-seo.
Is it okay
if I keep in touch?
Okay.
Rael?
What are you doing here?
You're Park So-hyeon's daughter?
After Ho-sik was torn up over her,
do you know how many years I spent
trying to comfort him?
Seriously, how could you?
-Na-yeong.
-You should've told me!
Ho-sik suddenly suggested we go camping.
He said we should ask you
to watch the house.
So-hyeon's daughter needs
a place to stay, so offer up our house?
He even reported back to her, you know.
I caught him on the phone with her.
I'm not her daughter.
Don't you ever say that again.
If she isn't your mom, then what?
Your dad's girlfriend?
What should I call her?
No matter how pissed you are,
parents are off limits.
In any case,
-because of Park So-hyeon…
-Don't you mention her name.
My dad died because of her.
What do you mean?
Hey.
Is that your only luggage?
Give it back.
Where do you live?
Give me my suitcase.
Is that so hard to answer?
You're in Seoul without a place to stay?
I told you I only got here a few days ago.
I'll be moving in somewhere in a week.
I had time, so I was going to stay here.
So you have nowhere to go tonight.
I do. Why wouldn't I?
Don't worry about me. Just go.
Let's part ways here.
This is so damn humiliating.
SEONG-CHAN
We're going to your place, right?
I'll just leave my bag with you.
If I take that,
my friend will ask questions.
-Just hold onto it for me.
-Your friend?
A friend from middle school.
You don't know her.
She went to high school in the city.
No matter who you stay with,
you're the one making this weird.
Like you said, I ran into
an old classmate in a bind.
How could I just walk away?
You would've done even more to help.
Wait.
I have someone in my life.
We're apart right now.
We decided to take a break.
Is he…
weighing on you a lot?
No.
It's because of you.
I'm telling you because I think
I should be honest with you.
Put these on.
Okay.
You can sleep there.
The bathroom's over there.
Get some rest.
Okay.
What's all that?
Wood from Yeonwoo.
I see. Are you making something?
Frames.
You should rest.
What about you?
I have something to do.
It's what I was planning to do.
Hey, Hui-seo.
Yeah, it's fine.
Yeah, I'll tell them myself.
He still looks out for Hui-seo.
Okay, bye.
He hasn't changed.
PLAYLIST
You can leave it on.
The other day,
I logged into your account
and listened to the music.
It was my second time.
I've only logged in twice in ten years.
Did you know?
What is it?
If you stay up all night, what about work?
Afternoon shift.
You can sleep a bit more.
No, I slept well.
I slept really well.
I haven't been able to sleep well
these past few days.
Can I come pick up my suitcase tomorrow?
Can you come by at lunchtime?
Of course. I'll make it work.
What time does your afternoon shift start?
-I leave at 1:30 p.m.
-I'll come before then.
I should go.
Come eat.
Eat what?
You really haven't changed.
What do you mean?
Soy milk.
I'm surprised you're a train operator,
but this is unexpected too.
Oh, that's right.
There was a woodworking shop
near your place.
I remember now.
After getting discharged,
I sometimes got firewood from there.
And I helped out every now and then.
That's how you got started?
Furniture gets too bulky,
but frames are small,
so it was more manageable.
You always find a way.
You might falter and stumble,
but you get there in the end.
That's what comes to mind
when I think of you.
You always find your way.
What about you?
You…
didn't think of me, did you?
No.
I tend not to look back.
It's better that way.
At your house…
I saw a new picture of you.
It was some time
after I'd left the military.
I saw it when I went there
to replace your door.
The photo itself…
just sparkled.
That's my last memory of you.
Looking happy and thriving.
I guess that shows even in photos.
I went to Hawaii as an intern then,
and everything was perfect for a moment.
Just for a brief while.
I've been well.
Just not recently.
I…
ran into you on my second day in Seoul.
I had hoped to see you at least once.
But after running into you like that,
I felt I needed to see you properly.
So I waited for you on purpose.
Who goes for a walk on a subway platform?
Why did you wait for me on purpose?
I had something to say to you.
Go ahead. Tell me now.
I don't think I need to anymore.
Let's say goodbye here.
Thanks.
I promise I'll repay you.
Follow me.
-Hello.
-Come on in.
I guess you still haven't had
a lot of bookings.
It seems that way these days.
I put in two extra.
Have a taste.
These are such rare treats… Thank you.
Hey, I saw you were running
the last trains tonight.
Do you mind swapping shifts with me?
Hello?
You just need to come in an hour earlier.
I'm the one who's thankful.
Okay, bye.
Water.
Tae-seo.
The sound of Tae-seo approaching.
-Here.
-What's that?
They're scones
that people line up early for.
This place only opens twice a week.
Our guesthouse does business with them,
and she gave me two extra today.
I saved them for you.
You run a guesthouse?
Where?
Just somewhere in a historic area.
Here.
Thank you.
Can we talk for a second?
First, what I want to know is…
You said you were on a break.
What exactly is going on?
Did you break up
and decide to take time to accept it?
Or are you taking time to work it out?
We both see it differently.
How you see it is what matters.
I don't care about who he is
or how he sees it.
Why do you want to know?
If you're trying to work things out,
as your once…
as your once close friend,
I was wondering if I was crossing a line.
Even just facing you right now
isn't easy for me.
For me, it's over.
But I did make the decision on my own.
I thought we both needed time
to come to terms with it.
But after hearing you now,
I was just putting it off.
But let's stop talking about this.
Talking about my breakup with you
just isn't right.
I've only shown you my worst,
so I feel really bad…
If you know where you stand,
I'll get to the point.
I have to go to work,
so I'll keep it short.
Stay here today and tomorrow.
I told you I have a place to stay.
After night shift tonight, I'll sleep
at the dorms for morning shift tomorrow.
Then, I'm off to Yeonwoo after work.
That's why I spoke to Hui-seo yesterday.
I have to go see my grandma.
Did something happen?
It's no big deal.
After I stay overnight in Yeonwoo,
I'm going straight to work.
You said you did empty house care?
It'll be empty for two days.
I only do it if they have companions
like plants or pets.
Don't make it empty for my sake.
The definition of "companion."
"A partner or a friend."
My companion being…
my friend, as in you.
Look after yourself.
Maybe sleep in all day while I'm not here.
You said you hadn't slept well these days.
I'm sure you've been
giving it your all in life.
And you're just at a brief standstill.
You'll find your way again.
As the next step,
just rest fully for two days,
and then go back
to living at your own pace.
I really did give it my all.
Like I told you,
I didn't waste a single moment of my time.
Well, it's no trouble for me at all,
so don't feel bad.
I bought plenty of water,
so don't bother bringing your own.
Thank you.
I'll try to get plenty of rest.
PHONE OFF
SAFETY ON
This is the passcode for the door.
It's 4675.
I bought some food and butane canisters.
Make sure you eat.
Let's air out the room.
These should fit you too. They're magic.
These are magic shorts.
They fit in middle school and as an adult.
They always fit perfectly. It's amazing.
Tae-seo's home.
I'm late.
I'll be back.
She's settled in.
-Granny.
-Yes?
This is serious.
When I saw you fall at the corner store,
it didn't look right.
Look here.
If it's like, bam!
If it's a fall like this,
you have bad knees.
But if you fall over like chopsticks,
you'll hurt your head.
That's really dangerous.
I just get these damn headaches.
Medicine doesn't even help.
A headache that bad at your age?
That calls for a checkup for sure.
Don't you want to see your grandson
get married and have kids?
Hui-seo already gives me
an earful about it.
I would've already gone
just to stop his nagging.
He nags nonstop.
It never ends with one comment.
He just goes on and on…
Goodness, Hyang-gi.
What are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be delivering the mail?
Are you out here working
or making social calls?
Are you threading needles
for every granny in this town?
A delivery should take seconds,
-not half an hour per house.
-I'm going.
Thank you, dear.
Pork belly?
-How did you know?
-Count me in next time.
Just go do your rounds.
Bye.
Could you check what dates
are available at the hospital?
What's gotten into you?
You always insisted you'd never go.
Hyang-gi explained it so well
that it was really easy to understand.
Hello!
You're having grilled pork belly
for dinner tonight!
Pork belly?
This is really good meat.
Today's meat is very good.
I bought it.
They always give me the best cuts.
That's our Hui-seo for you.
-Tae-seo, eat plenty of meat.
-Okay.
Let me go get some lettuce.
Grandpa.
Grandma needs to go to the hospital.
You said she's going?
She said she'd go.
Good.
There's this girl at the post office
called Hyang-gi who does deliveries.
She's the star of this town.
The grannies all love her.
I don't know what she said,
but it scared Grandma enough
to get an appointment.
She's a funny one.
Really funny.
She's something else.
Gosh.
Good night.
Tae-seo.
Yeah?
Do you have…
anything you're afraid of?
You know, for me…
it's our grandparents passing away.
I'm terrified of that.
Even while I'm working,
when I think of that,
it makes me tear up.
Every relationship
is lost at some point anyway.
There's always an end.
God, is that all you can say?
"They're both healthy. It'll be okay."
Can't you say that instead?
Yes, they are healthy.
Right? Especially at their age.
It'll be okay.
I wish…
I had a big family.
And a lot of nieces and nephews.
How about it?
I said three before,
but four might be better.
Let's make it four.
Four nieces and nephews total.
Evens are better than odds.
Not this again.
Come on.
The more the merrier, right?
Gosh, four nieces and nephews
would be perfect.
You've done great on your own.
Did you get some rest?
Take care.
To ensure your comfort inside the train,
we'll be adjusting the temperature.
Tae-seo, I got plenty of rest
thanks to you.
You helped me figure out
what I need to do.
I know I'm late, but congratulations
on becoming self-reliant.
I'll take that.
It's been well preserved.
You can leave margins like this.
Or if you make the frame thicker,
that makes it look embraced,
which is quite nice too.
Embraced… I like that.
All five are the same size,
so it should save time.
Then, can it be done quickly?
The reopening's next month.
But we still need to wait
three more times.
Three more times?
One day for gluing,
half a day for the edges,
and a day for oiling.
You have to wait for these three,
no matter what.
I see.
Three moments of waiting?
Why isn't this…
This is a bit hard to open.
Is this the wrong key?
Sorry.
It's going to be another hot day today.
I'm seeing the Hangang River
for the first time with Yeon Tae-seo.
Merry early Christmas.
Excuse me?
Sorry, just out of nowhere…
Unexpected memories
just suddenly hit you, didn't they?
Yes, they were just so vivid…
Old houses will do that to you.
Someone even remembered
the face of their mother,
who died when they were 3.
Good memories you had forgotten
suddenly come up to the surface again.
I didn't expect this.
Mi-ju…
She kept bailing on me,
so I thought it was weird.
But she was…
That horrible…
I was really serious this time.
Have you ever seen me
date someone for over three months?
I really liked her a lot.
Sorry.
How can you get over that?
I was so good to her.
God, this is driving me crazy.
Exactly.
I asked her to give me more time.
You can't just cut someone out
completely like that.
She wasn't having it.
Breaking up completely
without taking a break…
That's the best.
Go back inside.
Don't come out.
Go back in.
Eun-a…
I'll just take a quick look inside.
It's a good price,
and it's close to the guesthouse.
I can move in after two weeks, right?
Yeah, two weeks at the latest.
So you've made up your mind?
Yes.
When I first met you,
it felt like you'd come here on a whim,
so I wasn't expecting you to call.
It's this house right here.
-Just go further inside.
-Okay.
My goodness.
How could you leave like that?
Na-yeong, Eun-a's here.
Come in.
Cheers.
Gosh,
I feel so much better now.
It was nothing,
but it was made into something,
so imagine how upset I was.
I spun all kinds of stories
about how we met.
You should've told me.
I wouldn't have made such a fuss.
I'd only be a little mad.
Hey…
I'm more angry about you lying to me.
There's nothing worse
than lying to your spouse.
You lay it all out,
fight about it, and then make up.
That's how a marriage works, got it?
Hey, if I had told you,
you would've never met Eun-a.
-Just eat, okay?
-Thanks to me,
-you had a nice stay at our hotel.
-Exactly.
I admit it. I owe you big time.
We'd even taken Rael out with us.
How long should we be away for?
We'll do whatever you want.
How many days do you need?
-Let's go back!
-When?
Tomorrow.
We were headed to a campsite
that someone asked us to check out.
Stay as long as you want.
And Eun-a.
So…
What you said about your dad
dying because of So-hyeon…
Don't think like that.
I understand where you're coming from,
but it's wrong to say something like that.
I asked him about it.
What you said was so harsh.
I'll say what I want.
That's not right, Eun-a.
Yeah, it's not.
I don't like So-hyeon either,
but that's wrong.
It feels better to say that
than to blame myself.
There's no end to it
if I start blaming myself.
I'd have to go far into the past.
And I can't deal with that.
Hating that woman
makes it easier.
So I'll say what I want.
Goodness. You better go to bed, Ho-sik.
-Let's go.
-No, let's drink.
That's enough.
You can't even hold your liquor.
Get up.
Hey, I'm fine.
Sit down, Eun-a.
-Hey, just leave it.
-Don't clean up.
Where do you live?
Give me my suitcase.
Is that so hard to answer?
Now, I can give him a clear answer
about where I live in Seoul.
What else do I need to do?
What must I do so he won't…
do this to me?
I have to do it.
I can't put it off.
After that…
I should go pick up my bag
so I can look him in the eye…
and say a proper goodbye.
She left her bag behind,
but I'm not curious.
There can be only one reason.
Seong-chan, I need to talk to you.
Go ahead. What is it?
I'm going to settle down in Seoul.
I'm not going back.
I've had enough time to think.
This is my answer.
I know
you've thought about this for a while.
I'll do as you say, so let's meet up.
We can't break up over the phone.
It should be in person.
You had a really hard time
because of that.
Don't repeat that mistake.
Repeat…
I'll come to Seoul.
No, I'll come down.
See you at the bus terminal.
I only have 30 minutes.
I have work early in the morning,
so I need to get back to Seoul.
TONGYEONG BUS TERMINAL
You really came.
You seemed like a stranger in Seoul.
But here, you're the same person I know.
BYEONNWI
-Throw it away.
-You can't…
I know…
how you must've felt coming here,
but we barely even dated for a few months.
We're better as colleagues.
This whole breakup talk makes no sense.
You never had feelings for me.
It was just me.
It was only a one-sided thing,
so just stay in touch.
There needs to be some back and forth
so my mind will be at ease
and I'll know you're okay.
We go way back, you know.
It's been over ten years.
When you…
took care of everything
for my dad's funeral
and saw it all through
without me or So-hyeon there,
I had a feeling deep down
that I would fall for you someday.
You keep saying that it was one-sided,
but you're wrong.
I had feelings for you too.
You were always apologizing
and trying to do more for me.
You don't have to.
You were just trying to be nice.
I don't like someone just to be nice.
I had a reason.
Which was?
Let me at least know the reason.
I really…
depended on you.
Call me if you have any trouble in Seoul.
Let's stay friends at least.
Let's at least do that much.
I didn't come all this way
so we could stay friends.
I put you through a lot.
I'm sorry.
I've known you
since you were in high school.
Take care of yourself.
Never mind.
Just go.
I wouldn't be able to let go.
Not just for my dad…
but thank you for everything, Seong-chan.
That's what I came here to say.
-You're still here.
-Yeah.
By the way,
everyone in our office's photography club
wants you to do the job.
Then again, all we've done so far are
poetry and art exhibitions in the subway.
But everyone wants a good frame
now that it's a train operator
photo exhibition.
They all want the one you made for me.
-How many is that in total?
-Eleven, including mine.
It's at the end of next month.
I'll share your frame account
and tell them to refer to it.
Have them pick
the same size and wood type.
If they're the same,
can you do all 11?
Well, I'll give it a go.
But will everyone agree?
Of course.
Hey.
What's this?
A door.
It's the first thing I made.
What's with this photo?
Hey, you should've taken the picture
so it actually looks like a door.
This is just…
EDIT PROFILE
Tae-seo.
I'm back.
I left my suitcase here.
Eun-a…
Eun-a.
I knew you'd come back.
STILL SHINING
Subtitle translation by: Hyesoo Lee