You're part of a syndicate,
you bastard!
I don't care even if you
all gang up on me!
- Gio!
- You blame our family
as if  you didn't start
this mess.
Luna's right.
You started this mess.
No one wanted that
to happen.
You don't know
the whole story.
Right. You don't know
Someone gave Mom
waling-waling flowers.
I think I know this place.
Why? Have you been
here before?
This is our driver's house.
You won't get out of here.
Kiko! Kiko! Kiko!
- [GRUNTS]
- [THUDS]
Jade! Run! Hurry!
- Ah!
- Aah!
- [WHIMPERS]
- [THUDS]
Go! Run!
[PANTING]
- [GRUNTS]
- [GROANS]
[OBJECTS CLATTER]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [GROANS]
[PANTING]
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[COUGHS]
[GROANS, COUGHS]
[COUGHS, GROANS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[GRUNTS]
Jade?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[COUGHS]
Jade!
[KIKO GRUNTS]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING
IN BACKGROUND]
Oh, you're here,
Sir Martin.
A guest is looking
for you.
- Oh, okay. Where is he?
- He's over there.
He has some questions.
- Where's Kiko?
- I don't know.
He's not my brother.
Thank you.
I was just asking
if you saw him.
I don't know.
You came here first,
and you didn't see him?
I said I didn't see him.
Why would I look for him
when Jade is also missing?
Ah, Jade is also not here.
They're probably together.
They're together?
Why would they be together?
[PHONE RINGING]
[LUNA] Hey, I'm asking you why
they would be together.
Kiko.
Where are you?
We've been looking--
[KIKO] Gio! Gio, they took Jade!
What?
W-- Who? Jade?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Their driver...
Their driver took Jade.
Call the cops now.
I'm sure he had something
to do with Papa's death.
What makes you say that?
Just call the cops now, Gio.
He killed Papa.
- Wait, Kiko. Kiko.
- They took Jade.
- Calm down.
- What's going on?
Hey, what's going on?
He said someone took Jade.
What?!
Put him on speakerphone.
Who took Jade?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Their driver.
You mean Roi?
How did that happen?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [HANDBRAKE RATCHETS]
- [CAR DOOR OPENS]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
We were doing
an investigation,
and it led us
to his house.
Then he came
and caught us.
You were investigating? Why?
Luna, we're running
out of time.
Kiko, where are you?
Where did he take Jade?
I don't know.
I don't know where
he took Jade.
But I'm still here
at their driver's house.
Just stay there. We're going
there. Don't leave, okay?
Leon? Leon, where are you?
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
No one can know about this.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[THUDS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [CAR DOOR SLIDES]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ROI GRUNTING]
Coordinate with Coast Guard
Sector 4.
Secure the coast lines.
Go. Hurry up.
Roi Martinez. I have sent
you the suspect's profile.
Block all the exits.
Don't let him get out
of the island.
[MAN] Copy, ma'am.
[CHESKA] Martin, I couldn't
get a hold of Kiko.
I've been trying
to call him.
Martin, Gio, what's going on?
We're going to him.
Don't worry.
- I'll go with you.
- No need.
Just stay here.
We'll take care of Kiko.
We need you
and Trixie here.
This will be your way
of helping us.
Just make sure
everything runs smoothly.
- What about my brother?
- [GIO] We won't abandon Kiko.
He's also our brother, okay?
[HENRI] Martin, Gio,
are you coming with us?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- Martin, please be careful.
- I will.
- [LEON] Leave Jade to me.
- [JUSTIN] I'll go with you.
No! You and Luna check
on Mom at our house.
We'll handle this.
No matter what happens,
make sure that Mom
is safe, okay?
Edward and I
will look for Jade.
Leon, does Mom
know already?
Not yet. Just tell her when
you get home, okay?
Luna, Justin...
I know this isn't easy,
but you have to be
more brave.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Mom and Jade
both need our support.
Leon, let's go. Come on.
- Be careful. Please take care.
- Let's go.
Justin.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[PANTING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[ROI PANTING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KIKO GROANS]
Are you okay?
I know Roi.
He's the quiet type.
He doesn't have many
friends here,
but he'd never cause
trouble.
I guess you don't know him
that well.
Chairman, he kidnapped
my friend.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
I just can't believe
that he'd do that.
Chairman, I'm not lying.
How would you explain
what we saw inside?
There was underwear
and other stuff.
Don't worry.
The cops are on their way.
I had someone call them
earlier.
- Thank you.
- Don't mention it.
Are you sure you don't want us
to take you to the hospital?
No need, Chairman.
I'll be fine.
I'll just wait for my siblings.
Okay. Stay here.
Boys, come on.
Let's check the backyard.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Martin.
[MARTIN] Kiko, what happened
to you?
Are you hurt somewhere else?
- Martin.
- Wait.
I'm okay, Martin.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LEON]
What happened to Jade?!
Sorry. Sorry.
Sorry.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EDWARD] Jade!
[LEON] Jade!
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[LINE RINGING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello, Roi?
[ROI] Frida?
I--I'm sorry.
[CRYING] I'm sorry.
I... I didn't mean
to do it.
Huh? What do you mean?
- They already know.
- Huh?
They--
They all know.
Who knows?
[ROI SOBBING]
What do they know?
- [UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SOBBING]
They already know.
They know
how much I love you.
What?!
They know already.
[ROI SOBBING]
[ROI] They all know
how much I love you.
They all know.
- [UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [ROI SOBBING]
[ROI] Frida.
I love you so much.
I'd die if I didn't have you!
Do you understand?!
Roi, what are you talking
about?
Are you out of your mind?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ROI] I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to do it.
[ROI SOBBING]
[ROI] I didn't mean to.
Please forgive me.
Frida, I'm so sorry.
Frida... Frida...
I didn't mean to.
Roi, why? What did you do?!
- Tell me what's going on.
- Frida.
I swear I didn't mean to.
I didn't mean to.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[ROI] Frida.
[FRIDA] What are you
talking about?
Frida...
What is it? What did you
do, Roi?
- Tell me.
- I didn't mean to.
- [THWACKS]
- [GROANS]
[BUSY TONE]
- [THWACKING]
- [JADE GRUNTING]
[BREATH QUIVERING]
- [THWACKS]
- [GRUNTS]
Ah! Ah...
[LINE DROPS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [THWACKING]
- Ah! Jade! Ah...
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
- [THWACKING]
[PANICKED BREATHING]
- [YELLS]
- [LOUD THUD]
- [GROANING]
- [HIGH-PITCHED RINGING]
[PANICKED BREATHING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LINE RINGS]
[PANTING]
Ah! Ah...
[WHIMPERING]
Help!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GRUNTING]
Ugh...
[PANTING]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
We trusted him.
That animal...
- Animal!
- [LOUD BANG]
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
So that's why Kiko suspects Roi
was involved in Papa's death.
Sir, Kiko has a strong feeling
that Roi killed Papa.
There is a possibility.
But we can't be sure yet.
We have to follow due process.
[MARINA] He may be obsessed
with Mrs. Almazan
and he harbors a grudge
against your fathers,
but that doesn't mean
he's the killer.
So, what now?
You won't catch him
because of due process?
We're going to look for him,
Mr. Almazan.
And Roi will go to jail
for abducting your sister
and for what he did to Kiko,
not for the murder
of your fathers.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Justin, don't tell Mom yet.
- No. We should tell her.
- Wait, calm down.
Mom!
- [FRIDA] Yes?
- Mom! Mom...
Luna, why? What's wrong?
What happened?!
- Mom, it's Jade.
- What?
Roi kidnapped her.
What?! No!
No! Jade!
Oh, god... [BREATH QUIVERS]
No. No... We have to find her.
We... We have to find her.
No...
[BREATH SHAKES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS, YELPS]
[PANTING]
[PANICKED BREATHING]
[GRUNTS]
[YELLING, GRUNTING]
Please, please, please!
[PANTING]
Jade!
[PANICKED BREATHING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GRUNTING]
Jade!
Where are you going?
[GROANS]
[JADE GRUNTING]
[JADE PANTING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PANICKED BREATHING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Edward.
Dad.
Dad, please.
Please, I know you know
a lot of people.
Send people here.
We need to find Jade.
Uh-- O-Okay.
Alright. Don't worry, bud.
I'll make some calls.
Okay.
And Dad, I've sent you
the license plate number
of Aunt Frida's car, the one
their driver last drove.
- Okay?
- [ANDY] Okay.
Alright, alright.
I'll keep you posted.
I'll update you.
Okay, Dad.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
Jade.
Thank you so much
for helping us out.
It's a big help that more people
are looking for Jade.
You don't have to thank
me.
Because I'm not doing this
for you.
This is for Jade
and her family.
Right.
"Sorry."
That's what you should
be saying to the Almazans.
Because you...
You're the one
who brought Jade here.
I didn't bring her here.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[JADE WHIMPERING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[JADE GRUNTS]
[SOBBING]
Stop being stubborn, Jade.
You look like your mother,
you know.
[JADE SOBS]
Such a creep!
You're so shameless!
[JADE SOBBING]
[JADE SCREAMING]
[JADE SCREAMING, SOBBING]
Because of that flower.
They said that
the orchid was rare.
We didn't know things
would come to this.
You should've told us right away
so that you didn't have to deal
with it on your own.
Jade and I
had an agreement.
As long as we don't
have solid evidence,
we won't tell anyone.
Wait.
Does this mean that Papa
just got dragged into it
when Roi only wanted
to kill Uncle Fred?
But...
why did Papa's face
also get crossed out?
Sir Henry said it's
not right to conclude
that Roi is the killer.
What does your gut feeling
tell you, Martin?
I don't know.
And we don't know
what Roi is thinking.
He was obsessed
with Aunt Frida.
He's not in the
right state of mind.
You guys better go home.
Sir, what if Roi
comes back?
We'll handle it.
We'll station some men,
just in case.
But, sir, what about Jade?
Jade is still missing.
Kiko, Roi already has
a police blotter.
We also informed
the coast guard about him.
He won't be able
to leave the island.
So you guys better go home
and rest,
especially you, Kiko.
I'm fine.
- Maybe Jade--
- Kiko.
Let us do our job.
We won't stop
until we find Jade.
Come on.
You should go home.
I'm the one Roi needs,
- not Jade.
- Ma!
Mom! You can't leave.
- It's dangerous!
- Let me go!
A house in the middle
of the island,
surrounded by
two palm trees.
What about Trixie?
And Cheska?
They're not here yet?
It's payback time.
Jade is still in danger.
I love your mother.
I don't want to see her
get hurt.
I'm willing to die
and kill for her.
Hey! Hey! Hey!