You said that earring was yours
but it wasn't.
I didn't tell you
the truth  because
I know this would happen.
[JUSTIN] No matter how many
times  you file a report,
you won't know anything.
Mom had nothing to do with it,
nor any of us for that matter.
[MARTIN] Where's the signature
of the tourism officer?
[SARI] He hasn't signed it yet.
It's just one signature, Sari!
Look, just wait for three days
and Sari will resign then.
- Are you sure of that?
- Oh!
[GIO] I was in town earlier to
talk  with a possible sponsr
for the music festival.
They said they wanted to
talk with the general manager.
That's you, isn't it?
[JADE] We're talking about
my mother, okay?
[KIKO] But it's my father
being investigated  here.
So, just make me a promise.
[EDWARD] Oh, they're here, Jade.
Let's go?
I thought we had a meeting.
Why? Are we not allowed
to have a meeting on a boat?
[JADE INHALES DEEPLY]
["PANGHABANG IKAW" BY
DARREN ESPANTO PLAYS]
[EDWARD] I already talked with
a group of influencers.
They will arrive at the hotel
ahead of the music fest.
So, Jade...
let's make sure that they'll
have a good experience
at the hotel and
on the island, okay?
Really?
Is that why we'll be
island-hopping?
["PANGHABANG IKAW" CONTINUES]
Of course.
I also want to know how
island-hopping is with you.
Should it really just be me?
Why? Who's the Head
of Marketing here?
- Isn't it you?
- Yeah.
Don't tell me that you think...
I just want to be alone
with you?
["PANGHABANG IKAW" CONTINUES]
[EDWARD SCOFFS]
Do you think I just
want to be with you?
Hell no!
How delusional!
I never said anything like that.
You're the delusional one.
That's what you were
talking about, right?
[SCOFFS] Of course, not.
Of course.
Yes.
["PANGHABANG IKAW" CONTINUES]
Hey! Hey, hey, hey!
What are you doing?
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JADE] Hey!
Edward!
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Edward!
Hey! Edward! Edward!
Hey!
What are you doing?
We have a meeting, don't we?
- [WATER SPLASHING]
- [PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
We're in the sea!
There are no rules here!
Dive in, let's have
a meeting here instead.
I don't want to.
I'm not in the mood, okay?
Okay, fine.
But just like I said earlier,
I promised the influencers that
they'll get to dive
and island-hop too.
The hotel can do that, right?
But just so you know,
the influencers I contacted have
at least 500k followers, okay?
I can imagine it already.
Once they post...
Boom!
People will automatically
book a room in Hotel 88.
Isn't that right?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Jade! Were you listening to me?
[STUTTERS] Oh, yes. Yes.
[JADE] We'll still proceed
as planned.
Wait for me when we get back.
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
You don't have to open
the door for me.
It's fine, sir. Don't mind me.
- Gandara!
- Hey!
How are you doing?
You have a cool ride, huh?
It's just work.
- Gandara! Gandara!
- Send my regards to Julie!
Oh, hello!
How are you and
your grandfather?
We're doing fine.
Grandpa still looks great.
Of course! Who else are
you going to take after?
- Oh, that's a lot.
- Take some home.
- Oh, no, it's fine!
- Just take some.
- It's for you and your grandpa.
- Okay then.
Hey, how have you been?
Thank you so much!
Are you running for
a position here?
[SARI GIGGLES]
Sir, you're so funny!
I'm not kidding.
Well, sir, I'm a little...
Just a little, okay?
I'm a little bit popular
in our town.
I always win pageants here.
That's why they call me "Ganda."
[SARI] And, sir,
I'm not trying to brag but
I've never lost
a single pageant.
So, you know, sir, sometimes--
You're quite talkative,
aren't you?
[SARI CHUCKLES]
You're so-- [EXCLAIMS]
Sorry, sir.
- You're so funny, sir.
- Is the tourism officer inside?
- [STUTTERS] Uh, yes!
- We might wait too long.
I've spoken to his secretary.
I said we were already here.
Um...
Why did you choose
to have a music festival?
[LUNA CHUCKLES]
It's simple, ma'am.
A lot of money will come in
both for us and for you.
And your product, Planet Mobile,
will be promoted too.
Um, haven't a lot of people
done that already?
It's starting to feel like...
it's repetitive.
What's unique about this one?
And, uh, what does it mean
to you, personally?
Um...
Well, for me,
music is the only place where
people stop pretending.
[LUNA] There are
no titles nor status.
Whoever you are, you're all
equal at the music festival.
This is the kind of crowd
you'll want your brand
to be associated with.
Real people, real connections.
Hmm...
I don't know.
Also--
Ma'am.
Let me just add that
this music fest we're proposing
this not just about
music or headliners.
Personally, it's more
about memory.
So, this is the kind of night
that people will remember.
You may not know this but...
Luna was a DJ back then.
Oh, really?
She has always had
a unique energy that
can connect to people
through music.
And that's what we want to
happen with our music festival.
To connect with people,
whether or not they're locals.
Hm.
I like the way you see things,
Mr. Cabrera.
Just call me Gio.
[SPONSOR] Oh, sure. Gio.
Oh, by the way,
do you have a card?
Of course, I have.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[GIO] Here.
[SPONSOR] Okay.
Okay then.
I'll just get in touch
with you, okay?
[GIO] Okay, ma'am.
I still have a meeting
to attend to,
so I'll leave
the two of you alone.
Thank you, ma'am.
- Thank you.
I'll just give you a call then.
Thank you.
[LUNA EXHALES SHARPLY]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Wait a minute.
Why do you seem angry?
I got the sponsor
to say yes, didn't I?
Yeah. Thanks to you.
Are you angry because
you got overshadowed?
No.
What's wrong with what I did?
[LUNA] Nothing.
Nothing? Then why
do you seem angry?
I just don't like it when others
speak on my behalf, Gio.
About what?
Who are you to tell others
that I was a DJ?
Well, isn't it true?
Why don't you want her to know?
You know nothing!
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Luna!
[WAVES LAPPING]
[GROANS SLIGHTLY]
[JADE SQUEALS]
Seriously?!
Are you doing that
on purpose, huh?
Jade, when the influencers
arrive,
you can't be
acting like that, okay?
Why? What's wrong with me?
That! Exactly that.
You don't seem to know
how to have fun.
[JADE SNICKERS]
You probably don't even know
how to make a joke.
Oh yeah? Since when was
making jokes a requirement?
What about you?
Do you even know how to joke?
Ah...
Are you challenging me?
Fine.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Which fish is important?
I don't know.
You're not even going
to think about it?
Okay, fine!
You're the expert at jokes.
I just don't feel like thinking.
Then it's...
"Es-fish-cial."
Fish!
- "Fish-cial" "Es-fish-cial."
- That's so corny. So corny.
Cut it out, that's corny.
So corny.
Corny? You want another one?
No.
So grumpy!
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
Did anyone use this truck
after the owner died?
No, sir.
Even Sir Mike's children
never touched it.
Okay. Thank you.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
If there really was a folder,
where could it have gone?
We were at the
actual crime scene.
There was no folder.
Do you think
what I said helped?
It looks like it made them think
when you mentioned the folder.
That was new information
for them too.
It's a shame I really forgot
about it back then.
That folder just slipped
my mind.
Same here.
A lot of things were
happening at the time.
[PHONE CHIMES]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Who's that?
Uh, no one.
You're smiling. Let me see.
- It's nothing!
- Who is it?
- Monette, it's nothing.
[MONETTE] Congratulations,
Raphael Salcedo!
We are excited to inform you
that you have been
officially accepted
to the
University of the Arts Manila.
Your creative journey
starts here.
You applied?
Huh? Uh--
[CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
Well...
I just tried.
It's nothing serious.
And I don't even really
want to go there, okay?
I'll just stay here.
Always right beside you.
Besides, it's just the
two of us in this world.
Why would I choose
to move away, right?
Are you sure?
Uh. Monette, come on.
I told you, it was nothing.
You know, I just made
a bet with...
With Rona.
I told her I'd get accepted.
And I did.
But it's nothing.
Look, I'll delete it now.
Hmm. It's deleted.
- Raphie, if you want to--
- I don't.
Monette, let's not talk
about this anymore.
Oh, there you are.
Sir Justin!
Sir Justin, you were just there.
We've been looking for you.
Why?
Oh, we have a guest
who wants to go island hopping.
But aren't you from recreation?
[GAME SOUNDS FROM PHONE]
Damn!
Who even is that guest?
What a nuisance!
What?!
Why didn't you say
you weren't coming to work?
[SIGHS]
Fine. [SIGHS]
Fine, fine.
There's nothing I can do
about that.
- What did he say?
- So annoying.
We don't have a boatman!
He said he's sick,
so he can't come in.
I don't know about him!
Just cancel that island hopping.
That's a waste.
[RAPHIE] This way, ma'am.
Ma'am is here!
She's already excited.
- [GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [WIND CHIME RINGS]
[MONETTE] Oh my, ma'am.
The boatman isn't here.
They said it's canceled for now.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's fine now.
[MONETTE STAMMERS]
Huh? I thought--
It's fine, alright?
[MONETTE] Okay.
I'll take care of it.
Alright, I'll go get changed.
Okay.
[DOOR OPENS]
[SIGHS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
We didn't find anything
the first time.
But whatever was
inside that folder,
I'm sure it was important.
[SIGHS]
No matter how important
that folder is,
if we can't find it,
it doesn't matter.
It's not even in
Michael Fernandez's truck.
[EXHALES]
What if it got lost
at the crime scene?
So?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
That means...
It's possible someone else
was there.
[EXHALES]
Who could that be?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [WAVES CRASHING]
- [BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
Will we wait for a boat,
or will we ride this?
Nope.
No?
How are we going to leave?
This is the tour.
Welcome to Isla...
Solara!
It's beautiful, isn't it?
I booked for
an island-hopping experience.
That's what I paid for.
This is not it, okay?
- I want a refund.
- Hey!
This is more fun
than island hopping.
And look at the waves,
it's strong today.
That's why it's safer here.
And it's safe here,
as long as...
I am with you.
[WOMAN] Justin...
- [SLAPS]
- [GRUNTS]
[WOMAN] How dare you?
Are you dating Angel
and me at the same time?
Huh? Who's Angel?
Stop denying it.
You went out on Friday
after we went out on Thursday.
And now you're with someone new?
Uh, excuse me.
I'm a guest at Hotel 88.
I'm not one of his girls
for your information.
Are you sure?
My god, you're such a player!
Look.
I went out with you on
a Thursday
and went out on
a Friday with Angel.
If I wanted to date you both,
I would've asked you
both out on Thursday.
Besides, we're not
really exclusive, right?
You're so shameless!
Don't come near me again!
Step aside.
Woah!
Do you have a boyfriend?
- You are unbelievable!
- Oh!
Don't mind that girl.
Should we hang out after this?
[SARI] You told me earlier
she was there.
I still messaged you earlier,
remember?
[RECEPTIONIST] She left again.
[SIGHS] We've been here
for quite some time,
can we ask for
a follow-up, please?
- [SIGHS]
- [KEYBOARD CLACKING]
Do you see my handsome boss?
He's good-looking,
but he has a short temper.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [KEYBOARD CLACKING]
- [SIGHS]
He's already mad!
Oh my god!
I'll just check on him.
Hold on.
Sir...
[MARTIN] We've
been waiting here for hours.
Do you know how important
every minute is to me?
[CLICKS TONGUE] Sir, they told
me that she's there.
She's here?
Where?
Tell me, Sari, where is she?
Where is she?
Am I blind?
Are my glasses broken?
You told me she's here,
so where is she?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
You're just wasting my time.
How incompetent.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Sir Martin!
Could I please get
an update? Please?
Where are you going?
Our tour isn't over!
[WAVES CRASHING]
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
The foot traffic is strong...
and the demographics are right.
It just needs the right owner.
- [WAVES CRASHING]
- [BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
I like your smile.
I knew you liked me too.
[SCOFFS] Whatever.
[CHUCKLES]
Raphie, find me a new assistant.
Someone quiet, skilled and
knows what they're doing.
What's going on, sir?
What happened to Sari?
Did she resign?
Did I win the bet?
What are you talking about?
Just find me a new one, ASAP!
- Okay?
- [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Sir! Sir! Sir!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
I'm going home.
Do whatever you want.
Sir, wait! The tourism officer
will talk to you now.
She's already there. [PANTING]
[CURIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
It's chaotic. Noisy.
I'm sure only young people
will come here.
Alright, I still have somewhere
else to go.
[SIGHS] Ma'am.
For sure, most of them
will be young people.
But I'm also sure
they won't be the only ones
who'll be interested
in our music festival.
The last time something
like that happened
here on the island,
your father, Michael,
was the one leading it.
[OLD TOURISM OFFICER]
You know what happened?
Well, it even sparked trouble.
A lot of people fought.
Because they were drunk.
Ma'am, that was a long time ago.
And strict security
is already part of our plan.
[OLD TOURISM OFFICER]
Even so.
Change it.
Just hold a mass instead.
More people would be happy.
But, ma'am--
[OLD TOURISM OFFICER]
Your father just died,
and you're already doing
all sorts of things.
Ma'am, it's 2026!
Yet you still think so backward.
No wonder this island
is being left behind.
You may leave now.
I still have things to do.
Hilda...
- Let's go.
- Sir!
We won't get anything from here.
Sir, wait! Just stay put.
[SIGHS]
Ma'am! One moment, please!
Just a second.
Wait a minute, please.
I just remembered
what my grandfather said.
Why would I care about
what your grandfather said?
Uh! Ma'am! [PANTS]
My grandfather said,
if you fight with someone
or hurt someone's feelings
during festival week,
you'll have bad luck on
this island for the whole year.
Would you want that?
I've heard that saying too.
Is your grandfather, Botong?
Exactly! That's my grandfather!
Did you know he was
the one who predicted
that I would grow old here
at the municipal office,
serving our people?
Oh, really? Oh my, ma'am!
You're not the only one
my grandfather predicted
whose fortune came true.
There are many of you.
Now I remember!
- You were always with him!
- [SARI CHUCKLES]
You were still
so tiny back then.
[SARI That's what
I remember too.
You're still the same.
Nothing has changed.
You're still beautiful.
[OLD TOURISM OFFICER
CHUCKLES]
[SARI CHUCKLES]
Ma'am...
About our event at Hotel 88...
I promise, cross my heart!
[SARI] Our security
is really tight.
Sir Martin is from Manila.
He knows a lot
about these things.
All that security stuff.
It's on another level.
- They are like terminators.
- [TOURISM OFFICER LAUGHS]
Would you like that, ma'am?
So please, ma'am...
Go ahead and sign this permit.
[SIGHS] If it weren't
for your grandfather Botong.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[SARI] Thank you, ma'am.
[CHUCKLES]
Thank you, ma'am.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Don't follow me.
- Why would I even follow you?
- Let's split up first.
[GIO SCOFFS]
[BOAT ENGINE WHIRRING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
What are you doing here?
I'm just here to collect
the remaining  debt you owe.
We are going to make
a dance trend.
That way, they'll see us
having fun in Hotel 88.
- Oh, Jade!
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine, I'm fine.
Sir, I have good news for you.
You have a new candidate
to interview
for your future assistant!
I am Justin Almazan.
At your service.
So, you're an Almazan?
About the flowers,
who sent them?
Someone sent you flowers?
It's just like what
your dad used to give me.
Didn't the police return to you
your father's phone?
We might be able
to find something there.
I'll also check my dad's phone.
Are we still doing
the right thing?
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]