[LUNA] Everyone,
this is Edward Arellano.
[KIKO] Okay.
Welcome to Hotel 88.
[JADE] Don't you really
know anything?
[KIKO] Why?
What else don't I know
- about my family?
- Please, just don't bother me!
- Don't go after me!
- Jade!
Even when it comes to Edward,
she wants to get ahead.
Luna's really something,
isn't she?
[MARTIN] Wait.
Do you have a past?
We do.
What?
[GIO] Music festival.
They're right.
There are lots of returns.
I can make this event happen.
But, can you?
[LUNA] Are you kidding me?
If the hotel loses money,
I will make you pay.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
You want to open up
that family's case?
I just need solid evidence.
Sir Henri! Good morning.
Good morning, Leon,
Mrs. Almazan.
Good morning.
Is there a problem?
[HENRI] Oh, Leon!
As police officers,
we never run out of problems.
All the problems in
our town are also our burden.
Oh, sir.
If you burden yourself with
other people's problems...
doesn't that just mean
that you're a meddler?
But that's how the police are.
We meddle in things...
because we care.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Leon, can we go now?
We'll get going then.
Okay.
Take care.
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LUNA] No.
No...
No.
You're rejecting all
my suggestions for the DJ?
[LUNA] I'm rejecting them
because they're all expensive.
But we'll get that money back
with the ticket sales!
It's still expensive!
You'll have to pay for their
transportation from Manila!
There are a lot of
local artists here.
Why don't you get them instead?
I've included them there!
But the lineup has
to be balanced.
You don't even want
Echo Nova to come?
You like them, don't you?
It's expensive!
Do you want someone affordable?
Then go and perform yourself
so it'd be free.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
What's wrong with you, Gio?
I'm just trying to
be practical because
I want to please
my general manager.
And it's true that
you're really smart!
So you can go do it, DJ--
If you really want the people
on your list...
then negotiate again.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Fine!
I'll come back to you
for a second proposal!
[MUSIC TURNS UPBEAT]
[FEMALE EMCEE] Bringing sweet,
new energy to the floor...
DJ Solenn!
Good evening!
- [CROWD CHANTING]
- [UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's Luna.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Luna!
[LUNA] Oh, sure. Come on.
[MAN] Can we do the other side?
- Thank you. Thank you!
- Thank you.
[GIO] Luna!
- Luna!
It's Gio!
Gio!
- Gio?
- Gio!
Gio!
[LUNA] Hello! It's really you!
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[LUNA] Long time!
- I know.
- [LUNA CHUCKLES]
Hi, DJ!
- Hi! Hello!
- Hi, DJ!
["TADHANA" BY
SOFRONIO VASQUEZ PLAYING]
You're here again.
Are you going
to come here every night?
As long as you're here,
I'll be here.
["TADHANA" CONTINUES]
[GIO] Same spot.
[LUNA] Same spot!
["TADHANA" CONTINUES]
Wait!
What is it?
The club's dirty!
You should clean up first.
I'm already used to it.
[GIO] Even so.
You should still be clean.
- Okay?
- Okay.
[GIO] Eat up.
["TADHANA" CONTINUES]
I already told you that
we could eat somewhere else
after your gig.
I like it here.
It's already my ritual.
Cup noodles every day,
with you.
If only those who know you
from our town can see you now.
Mm!
They have no idea.
That's why
you should say nothing.
You haven't been there
for over a year!
Do they still know who
Luna Almazan is?
They know who Luna is.
But they don't know Solenn!
["TADHANA" CONTINUES]
I wish we could
always be like this.
["TADHANA" CONTINUES]
[GIO] We could do that.
Just say it.
["TADHANA" CONTINUES]
- Let's eat.
[LUNA CHUCKLES]
Alright. I've introduced you
to our clients, okay?
We're going to our
laundry supplier next.
Also, the, uh...
Can you put the coconut tree
at the entrance to the back?
- Got it?
- Yes.
Hey, Kiko.
I just asked you to move a tree
and you said yes.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Is it because of Jade
and the mysterious earring?
Give me a hip, a belly,
and a pork chop, please.
What really happened?
Why did you grow apart?
I don't know, either.
She just suddenly
stopped talking to me.
Did you ask why?
She said we're not kids anymore.
That a lot has changed.
Does that mean
we can't be friends anymore?
Well, it's not like that.
But right now, Jade is focused
on your family affairs.
You know what I think?
I think you should focus
on the music fest.
If it goes well,
the hotel will be successful.
And the hotel's success
will be a way for you
to make amends.
Okay?
- Is it done?
- [VENDOR] Yes, ma'am.
- [BOY 1] Miss Jade!
- [GIRL 1] Miss Jade!
Miss Jade!
Wow! You all look very excited.
Have you been waiting for me?
- Yes!
- [GIGGLES]
- Come on.
- Are we going to begin?
Yeah, I'm just going
to get our materials ready,
then we'll start right away.
Miss Jade, this is for you.
- It's a steamed bun.
- Wow! Steamed buns!
- Did you get my favorite?
- Yes.
Wow! Thank you, Boyet!
You're all so sweet!
Here, let's share.
- Thank you.
- [GIGGLES]
- Miss Jade...
- Mm?
Is Sir Edward coming, too?
Ah... [CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
I don't think he can come today.
Looks like he's busy
with other things right now.
- Let's go.
- Let's go!
Oh, Boyet!
Oh, no! You got the wrapper.
[LAUGHING] It's because
you're eating too fast.
Here, I'll take it off for you.
Now, open wide. Aah!
Mm!
- It looks so good.
- [LAUGHS]
Come on. Are you guys
excited to paint?
- Yes!
You don't sound like it.
[CHUCKLES]
Is that really
what you're going to eat?
Am I starving you here?
It's just good, Dad.
You want a bite?
All yours.
By the way,
do you have a schedule today
in the community or...
are you just not gonna go?
No, Dad. I have another meeting.
Okay. Is this for your
Hotel 88 promotions?
Yeah. Just an update meeting.
I've hired people
to handle the guestlist
for the festival.
Good.
I like that you're taking the
Hotel 88 promotion seriously.
It's just like you said.
If you choose to do the work,
then do it perfectly.
Correct.
Also...
This is important to Jade,
so might as well...
Mm, okay. [CHUCKLES]
Might as well because
it's important to Jade.
There it is.
There. I see it.
Do you see that?
I can see that Jade
is the real reason
why you're taking
this job seriously.
No way, Dad. Come on.
No way? Hm?
You sure it's all business?
Of course, it's just business.
What else?
And I know this is important
to you, too.
So, it's good that
I get to do this so, you know...
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYS]
Okay.
If it's really just business,
then, good job.
Keep it up.
And, uh...
Good job on your heart.
[SNICKERS]
Give me a break, Dad.
Excuse me. Has Jade come in?
I don't know, sir.
Alright, thank you.
[PHONE BLEEPS]
Huh?
She blocked me?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
You will need to check
with the tourism officer
if we need to register
with them
if people are going here
for the music festival.
You also need to
arrange a meeting with
the city hall if we need
security.
Sir?
Is your middle initial
the letter "U"?
No, "S" for Sandoval.
Do they need that in the permit?
I thought it was
the letter "U"...
U for... utusero (bossy)!
[RAPHIE] Sir! You've dropped
so many orders!
I did not sign up for this job!
You are a hotel staff.
I'm counting on you.
Uh, sir.
My job is in food
and beverage.
Sir, it's not you.
It's me!
You need to hire
an assistant.
Sir, I can walk away, right?
[SIGHS]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GLASS CLINKING]
[Trixie] Ma,
you're not listening to me.
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
I'm listening.
You said something about Miss...
- Mister... Diaz?
- Yes. Mister...
- Mister Diaz.
- And the boutique's design.
Mom, you're not listening to me.
- [GLASS CLATTERS]
- I'm sorry, Trixie.
[TRIXIE] You're thinking
about Martin, aren't you?
When he called, he
said he was fine.
He said the same
thing to me.
But I don't believe it.
I mean...
there's a lot of things
going on with your brother.
And now, he's
living on that island.
[GLASS CLATTERS]
You're worried he'll have
a hard time because
he didn't have a personal
assistant and
he's not used to living there.
- [EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SIGHS]
Yeah. It looks like
we're both worried about hum.
But I was thinking, Mom,
what if...
what if I go to the island?
But as a hotel guest...
No.
[LUNA] Justin, can we talk?
[JUSTIN] Sure,
but can we talk after I chill?
Justin, it's working hours!
I am working!
[SCOFFS] Do you really want
to call it work?
I'm in charge of the
events and recreation.
I'm just waiting for more work
for the music fest event.
And this...
is recreation!
Come on, Justin.
I don't Martin to think
that you're lazy.
That's enough.
We have guests who wants
to swim and chill because of me.
Right, girls?
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, yeah!
Before I forget...
I'm going
to take a day off, okay?
You're not working,
yet you dare to take a leave?
Jade's only here once a week
and that doesn't bother you.
Jade's in dad's
outreach program.
She's there right now.
What are you going to do?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you serious?
What do you mean?
Whatever.
I'll just keep it to myself.
[SIGHS]
- [MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
Your father will be furious if
he finds out I let you go there.
You're not making me go there,
this is my decision.
Trixie, can we not
argue about this.
Because?
You know your father
doesn't like that place.
[TENSE MUSIC SWELLS]
I want to go to my brother.
Ever since
his father died...
I want to do something
nice for him and this is it.
I going to Hotel 88.
Sir, are you all right?
Wait, is it your
birthday today, sir?
No, it's tomorrow.
But thank you.
You're the only one
who remembers.
All right, sir. Enjoy.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[GLASS CLATTERS]
[MELLOW MUSIC
PLAYING ON SPEAKERS]
[STAFF]
Sir, you need to go home.
You said you can only
drink eight...
No, no. Give me another one!
I'm not drunk! Hurry up!
Nah, man. He's drunk.
[MAN 1] He's passed out!
You heard about the idiots
who killed each other?
The other one was Michael,
a playboy.
He's so foul that he decided
to bed his friend's wife!
[MAN 2] They should've shared.
Hey, you.
What are you looking at?
You think it's funny?
You're laughing, huh?
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[BLOW LANDS]
[STAFF] Sir! Sir, that's enough!
[GRUNTS]
- [GLASS BREAKS]
- [GROANS]
Huh?!
Come on, keep laughing!
Your lives are a joke!
All you do are gossip
about other people's lives!
Huh?! Come on!
Come on!
Let me go!
- [STAFF] That's enough!
- Huh?!
Sir, the police are here.
Sir Henry.
We've been seeing each other
more often recently.
I wish we didn't see
each other so often.
Whenever we meet,
it means there's trouble.
[SCOFFS]
[FRIDA] What is this?
Justin!
Why do you have a black eye?
The usual, Mom.
He got into a fight at the bar.
- Is that right, sir?
- Sit down.
When they found out he's
an Almazan, they backed out.
[FRIDA] Get me a cold compress!
It's nothing new, sir.
We'll talk to our lawyers
about it.
Your brother
might still be mourning,
that's why he got into a fight.
I hope your family finds peace.
Thank you.
Justin,
what's going on with you?
Why do you always
get into fights?
Mom! It's nothing.
I'm gonna take a rest.
- Justin!
Justin, wait!
We're not done here!
What's going on, Ma?
The usual.
He got into a fight again.
[SIGHS]
Justin!
What?!
You're too old to be doing this.
Picking fights at bars?
[SCOFFS]
You act like you're still
in high school.
Why do you keep
worrying Mom so much?
You know what
she's going through.
This is the last time
that our lawyer
will take care of your problem.
Next time,
find someone else
to bail you out.
[DOOR SLAMS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYS]
[RAPHIE] Sir, would you like
some drinks?
Breakfast, sir?
You haven't eaten yet.
My sister's cooking
is really good.
[MARTIN] Raphie, I'm not hungry!
Ah...
Uh-- I got it!
English breakfast?
Or Tagalog...
- Or what--
- I don't want anything.
What I need to know
is where my applicants are.
- Raphie, did you post it?
- [SIGHS]
Sir, I really posted it,
I promise.
[MARTIN] Maybe--
Maybe what you said is wrong?
I posted the correct
time and place
so that many people would see
that you're looking
for an assistant.
So, why is it that until now,
none of them are here?
Uh...
Maybe they aren't
awake yet, sir?
Sir, not everyone
is an early bird
with the worm like you.
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
It's impossible.
It's possible, sir.
It's really, really,
really, really possible.
[SIGHS] Where are they?
[RAPHIE] He's really mad.
[SARI] Universe!
Please make it happen.
Universe, give this to me.
This is mine now, universe.
Universe!
Good morning, y'all!
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[HENRI] This case
isn't done yet, Marina.
I still need to know more about
Michael and Federico's deaths.
Looks like Gio's going
to make some money.
We can collect from that.
Solara island?
Here it is!
Huh? They got someone else
at Hotel 88?
You still have feelings
for me, huh?
Is this what you mean?
I need to see the beach.
That should be included in
what I promote for Hotel 88.