That means Dad just
got dragged into this mess?
So, how did he get involved
in RoI's obsession?
If Roy really is the killer,
then that means Dad and
Uncle Fred's friendship is real.
See? I told you
I was a good boy.
- Get out!
- It's payback time.
Mom, wait! Mom! Mom!
- Mom! You're not leaving.
- No.
- It's dangerous!
- Let me go!
I have to find my daughter!
- No, no, no, no, no...
- I have to find Jade!
Can you just shut up?  I'm
getting  anxious because of you!
Hey! Don't yell at me like that.
- [SCREAMING] Ah!
- Hey!
Who did you go to?
Sari's grandfather,
who happens to be a...
- Fortune Teller.
- What did he say?
There is an abandoned...
house...
in the island...
nestled between two palm trees
Jade's life is still in danger!
I have some good news.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARINA] Take a good look at
the back, side, and front.
- Sir Henri.
- Oh?
Sir Henri, is there
any news on Jade?
This is the car Roi used.
He could have hidden
in one of the islands here.
That's where he probably
took your sister.
We're also checking this area.
There might be witnesses
who saw them.
We'll come with you.
Whether it's here on
on another island
I'll look for Roi myself.
You can't come with us,
we might run into trouble.
[EDWARD] But what about Jade?
Don't worry about it, okay?
You'll be the first to see her
when we bring her back.
Leave it to us, okay?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
- [FIRE CRACKLING]
- [POTS CLATTERING]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[ROI] You should eat.
I don't want Frida to get mad
at me because I starved you.
You're sick.
You're sick in the head.
You are brave, Jade.
You got that from your mother.
That's why I'm slowly
starting to like you.
[ROI] Your personality.
You're just like your mother.
Don't compare me to her.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
That's what you think.
Eat.
I'll feed you.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
- Go ahead and starve then!
- [PLATES CLATTERING]
Can you get us something
to drink, please?
Has there been an update
on Jade's whereabouts?
- What did the police say?
- They haven't found her yet.
[MARTIN] What about Leon?
Leon went with Justin to see
where they found Roi's car.
So they found it?
Where's Jade?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Why don't we go there too?
Let's just go.
[SIGHS] Alright.
- Luna, we'll follow them.
- [FRIDA] No, don't.
Don't go. They're asking
us to stay here.
Leon will...
Leon will contact us if ever.
Let's just stay here, Kiko.
We don't know if Roi
has any accomplices.
[GIO] If someone does go here...
it would be better if
someone's with them.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Luna...
- Ma.
I hope Jade is okay.
I really want her to come home.
She is, Ma. She's okay.
Jade will come home,
don't worry.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SIGHS]
Were you aware that my parents
have been separated for ages?
[TENSE MUSIC SWELLS]
You were always
with my dad, right?
I'm sure you know that.
[JADE] That they were cold
to each other.
Why are you telling me this?
Mom wanted to leave him
for a long time now.
She wanted to leave.
To live her own life.
She doesn't seem
to be happy anymore.
She wanted to leave so badly
that she didn't tell us
that she was planning
to move to a different country.
Did you know about that, too?
[TENSE MUSIC SWELLS]
Where?
Which country?
Her residency has been approved.
I'm asking you where?!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
She told us we were
already grown-ups
and that she would rather leave.
Because she feels so alone.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
No.
She's not leaving.
- [THUDS]
- No one is leaving!
Because I never once
left her alone!
I don't want her
to leave, either, Roi.
So please...
I have to stop her.
Please, bring me to her Roi.
I just need to talk to her.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UTENSILS CLINKING]
- Have some drinks, boys.
- I'll carry it, Auntie.
Let me. I need a distraction.
[EXHALES DEEPLY] Okay.
- Thank you.
[FRIDA] You're welcome.
I keep thinking Roi might
be hurting Jade.
Mom, let's stay positive.
Jade will be safe.
You need a distraction, Auntie?
How about you tell us
how you met Papa?
Kiko, don't ask her that.
[FRIDA] It's okay.
Maybe it's time you know too.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Um...
Michael and Fred were already
friends when I met them.
They both studied business,
but they loved archaeology.
They loved antiques
and treasures.
[LUNA] Mom, I remember you said
Uncle Mike was your first crush.
- Yes.
- Because he was fun
and adventurous.
Yes, that's true. But...
your dad was the one
who pursued me.
And I appreciated him.
I appreciated everything
he did for me,
so we became a couple
and eventually got married.
I loved your dad.
Over time, however, we
had a lot of disagreements.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
But Mom, you never
showed us that.
[FRIDA] Yes, Luna. If there's
one thing we both agreed on,
it's that we love our children.
We didn't want you caught up
in our problems.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
But Michael...
He was there to listen
whenever I was sad
and frustrated because of Fred.
That's why I started to feel
that way about him again.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm sorry. I shouldn't
be telling you this.
But your father and I
didn't have an affair.
You don't need to explain.
[FRIDA] Mike was
a very caring person.
And I had feelings for him,
but he only saw me as a friend.
[FRIDA SOBS]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MICHAEL]
I'm your friend, Frida.
Frederico's also my friend.
[FRIDA] Fred didn't believe it.
But heaven knows
that he was just a good friend.
But he eventually
came to believe Papa.
I hope so.
Thank you for being honest.
You didn't have to do that
for Kiko, but you did.
It's up to you, Martin,
if you want to believe me.
But as Michael's sons,
I want you to know
that he was a good person
and that he was
good to my family.
He shouldn't have died.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Please, Roi.
I need to talk to Mom.
I have to stop her
before it's too late.
Please, Roi.
I thought you loved her.
- Why don't you just let me--
- Shut up!
You're getting
on my nerves, girl!
Be quiet.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CLANGING]
[SOBS, BREATHES HEAVILY]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE KEYPAD BEEPING]
[LINE RINGING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Roi?
[FRIDA] Roi?
Please say something.
I know you, right?
[WHISPERS] Mom...
Where's Jade?
Where's my daughter, Roi?
[WHISPERING] Mom...
Roi?
I wish you hadn't taken Jade.
I wish you had just
talked to me instead.
We would've been
together by now.
Mom--
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Roi, you know,
the flowers you gave me...
I loved them so much.
But I had to throw them away
in front of my kids
because I didn't want them
to know.
But now...
why would I need
to keep pretending?
I thought maybe we
should be together now.
Just let Jade go.
Take me instead.
Let's go somewhere far away.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're just saying that, Frida.
I'm not stupid.
You know, Roi,
before Fred died,
I really wanted to leave.
I wish you had just told me
so I'd know.
Because I really didn't
want to be alone.
I'd rather be with you.
Because...
who was always there
when I was sad?
Who was always there for me?
Isn't it you, Roi?
[SNIFFLES]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Fine.
You're really the one I need
anyway.
I'll send you the location
where we'll meet.
[WHISPERING] No, Mom. Mom. Mom.
Okay.
B-But what about Jade?
Where's my daughter?
But, Frida...
You better not fool me...
or I'll kill your daughter.
- [LINE DISCONNECTING]
- Roi.
Roi!
- [LUNA] Ma.
- Roi.
Mom, what are you doing?
I'm saving my daughter!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You shouldn't have put
yourself in danger, Mom!
If I hadn't done that,
we wouldn't be able
to track Jade!
But what if Roi
doesn't keep his word, huh?
What if he takes
both you and Jade?
That's why we should be there.
You can't go there alone,
Mrs. Almazan.
He'll kill my daughter
if he finds out
there are police involved.
That's why we need
to plan this carefully.
- [FRIDA EXHALES]
- When are you meeting?
[SIGHS]
He messaged me.
[EXHALES] He said it's later.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm coming with you.
I'm coming too!
[LEON] No, Justin.
Luna needs someone
with her here.
I'll talk to the team first.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
We already lost your father.
We can't lose another
member of this family.
That's why I'll do everything
just to bring your sister home.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Jade.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JADE EXHALES]
[ROI] I should have told Frida
right away how I felt.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Maybe it wouldn't
have come to this.
Look...
[BREATH QUIVERS]
You even got hurt.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You'll be free soon, Jade...
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Once I meet your mother.
But you won't be able
to be with her anymore.
Because I'll take her away
from all of you.
[WHIMPERS]
Anyway...
[SOBS QUIETLY]
I'm the only one
she wants to be with.
[BREATH QUIVERS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Do you want to say something?
Don't hurt my mother.
Please.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Come on, Jade.
I'm not going to hurt her.
[BREATH QUIVERS]
- I'll love her...
- [JADE EXHALES DEEPLY]
...every single day.
[JADE WHIMPERS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LUNA] Mom, Leon,
please be careful.
Wait!
I'm coming with you.
You can't, Edward.
You might just get hurt.
Your father will worry.
Auntie, you can't stop me.
Jade's life is already
in danger,
so just choose.
Are you taking me with you,
or should I just follow you?
[FRIDA] But what about Andy?
Auntie, I'm old enough.
I can decide for myself.
And this isn't
Dad's decision anymore.
I'll handle it, Mom.
Okay, fine.
Let's go.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARTIN EXHALES DEEPLY]
Okay, bro. Be careful.
[KIKO] What did he say?
Have they found Jade?
Not yet. But they know
where she is now.
Where?
Let's go there.
They might need help.
[MARTIN] He didn't say.
The police said
it's confidential.
What if we follow them?
Kiko, we can't.
It's a sensitive operation.
Let's let the police handle it
so Jade can get home safely.
So we'll just wait here?
Isn't it harder just
sitting around like this?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[JADE SOBS, SNIFFLES]
Don't cry, Jade.
Frida might get mad at me.
You should look okay
when she sees you.
So she won't feel sorry for you.
I don't want my love
to be sad.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
That's what I call her.
"My love."
Because I love her so much.
[JADE SOBS]
I'm already thinking
about where we'll go...
...where I'll take her.
I've saved up a bit.
We can finally leave
this island.
[JADE SOBBING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
But don't be sad, Jade.
I'll let her call you.
But only occasionally.
Of course, we'll be busy
with our new life.
Shh. There, there.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Come on.
So you can say goodbye
to my love properly.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Leon, please...
Leave now.
Roi might see you.
- Mom...
- [SIGHS]
Leon, promise me.
No matter what happens,
Jade is the priority.
- But--
- No, no, no, look.
[FRIDA] Leon, listen to me.
No matter what happens,
Jade is the priority.
[EXHALES]
[SNIFFLES, EXHALES]
Be careful.
I love you so much.
[FRIDA WHIMPERS]
Go, go, go, go!
Mom.
Leon.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Go.
[SIGHS]
Run, okay?
I'm the only one Bok is after.
We're not leaving you.
We're staying together!
One... Two... Three... Run!
- Chase them!
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [FRIDA SCREAMS]
- [GRUNTS]
- There he is!
- [GROANS IN PAIN]
[FRIDA SCREAMS]
Leon!
[GRUNTS]
- [THUDS]
- [GROANS]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GRUNTING, GROANING]
Jade! Jade!
- Like what happened to Jade--
- Shh!
No! As long as they
haven't said anything,
nothing bad has happened
to our sister.
[BLOWS LANDING]
Just take care of them, okay?
Go now, son.
- [BLOW LANDS]
- That's enough!
- Gio!
- [GUNSHOTS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
I won't be asking you
for money anymore, Gio.