Sari, the contract.
Sari, contract!
Sir, I caught it!
I have it here!
Raphie!
Sir!
Oh. Hello!
Welcome to Hotel 88!
Those jerk cops are here.
The Almazan siblings have been
staring at us since earlier.
- I noticed that too.
- They're getting paranoid.
Bro, is this yours?
Is this your missing car?
Bok asked my friend
to sell it.
Those bastards are
in a syndicate.
Damn that Bok!
I think this is where
we'll find
answers to our questions.
You know, I also almost got
caught last night.
OMG. Twins.
Where is Jade?
She still hasn't replied in our
family group chat.
Flowers!
Someone gave Mom
waling-waling flowers!
I know someone who
has that kind of flowers.
Anyone home?
I think I know this place.
Have you been here before?
This is our driver's house.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Roi?
[KNOCKING]
- Roi!
- Jade.
He's probably
at your house.
You said he's your
driver, right?
Let's go and check.
Over there. There's the door.
Come on, let's check.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's unlocked.
Let's go inside.
Come on, Kiko. It's open.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Is that the flower
you were talking about?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Check-- Check if there's
more inside.
Okay.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JADE EXHALES SHARPLY]
[DOOR LOCK CLICKS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[WATER BUBBLING]
- [WATER SPLASHES]
- [GASPS]
Damn you! You jerk!
You stole the car and you
want me to pay for it?!
You are so stupid,
aren't you?
You only found out now?
[BOK LAUGHING]
[WATER SPLASHES]
You jerk!
- [GRUNTING]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [WATER BUBBLING]
- [GRUNTING]
[WATER BUBBLING]
Gio!
- [MARTIN GRUNTS]
- [WATER SPLASHES]
- Stop it!
- You!
That's enough! Stop it!
- Gio, stop!
- Stop it!
I said stop it!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[JADE BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CABINET DOOR CREAKING]
[JADE BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JADE BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [JADE BREATHING HEAVILY]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Kiko!
[PANICKED BREATHING]
Jade?
Jade!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBBING] Kiko, please!
- Jade!
- Kiko!
- Jade! Why?
- Kiko.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
Look over there! Look!
Look! There! Look!
[JADE SOBBING]
[JADE] No...
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JADE WHIMPERING]
Jade!
Jade, let's go. Hurry up!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
He's making me pay 2 million
for debt that's not even mine!
You criminal bastard!
Should I really be the one
to go to jail here?
I am a guest here!
You're the one who
caused a ruckus here!
Do you see this?
This is a physical injury, Gio!
- What happened?
- [GIO] You're a criminal!
- Are they fighting?
- Looks like it.
- Should we just change resorts?
- [BOK SHOUTING]
- Let's go?
- Yeah.
Oh, sir! Sir! Sir!
Sir, sir! Wait a second.
Don't take them seriously.
They're just acting.
That's just for content.
Just look at them.
It can't be real.
Would you like a bigger room?
I can upgrade it, sir.
- Yes.
- Sir, I'll take care of it!
- Sir, come. I'll upgrade it.
- Okay then.
Come with me, sir.
You'll definitely love the room!
What about when
you deceived my brother?
Fraud, extortion!
You even dragged
his grandmother into this!
Gio.
Even if you all team up--
I don't care!
Okay, get moving.
Take him with you now.
Take me?
Your hotel is nothing but trash!
[BOK] You're all trash!
Just shut down your hotel!
All of your staff are idiots!
Let me go!
Your hotel is trash!
Just close this place!
[LUNA] What's going on here?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC TURNS SUSPENSEFUL]
Jade?
What are you doing here?
You can't get out
of here anymore.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
I will call the police.
Kiko! Kiko!
- [KIKO GRUNTS]
- [BLADE SWISHES]
Kiko, please! Don't!
- Please!
- [GRUNTS]
[KIKO] Jade!
- Get out of here! Hurry!
- [GRUNTING]
Hurry up!
- [GRUNTS]
- [JADE SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING, GROANING]
[KIKO] Run, Jade! Hurry!
Hurry up!
[GRUNTING]
[KIKO] Hurry up!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GROANS]
- [DOOR CRASHING]
- [KIKO GRUNTING]
- [KIKO YELPS]
- [GROANS]
- [KIKO GROANS]
- [TABLE CRASHES]
[JADE PANTING]
Kiko!
[JADE] Kiko!
[KIKO GROANS]
- [MOANS]
- [BODY THUDS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOBBING] Kiko!
[JADE PANTING]
My god, Gio!
You brought that guy here?!
No, I didn't.
He came here himself.
It's still your fault.
You're the one to be blamed.
I didn't even know he
was going to be here!
I'll tell everyone
how bad it is here!
- Oh, hello!
- Hello! Welcome to Hotel 88!
[GUEST 1] What's happening?
Is there a problem?
Oh, no. They were just making
a content for social media.
- Aren't they good?
- Yes, they're vloggers.
Come on. Let's go, ma'am.
- This way.
- Raphie, bring their bags.
- Help them.
- Thank you.
[RAPHIE] Such beautiful ladies!
Ma'am, you're so pretty.
[MONETTE]
Follow me. It's nice here.
You'll love it!
Didn't you think about the
trouble it will cause?
My brother explained
everything already.
- He didn't want that to happen.
- The same goes with you!
You're all the same!
You blame our family as if you
didn't start the mess.
Where is that coming
from, huh, Luna?
Why? It's true, isn't it?
Luna, that's enough.
[MARTIN] Nice! Good job!
Make your sister calm down.
She's always upset.
Well, isn't what you
did upsetting?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Luna's right.
You started this mess.
No one wanted that
to happen.
Besides, you don't know
the whole story.
Right.
You don't know the
whole story.
There's nothing we can do.
What happened has happened.
At least now that guy
is gone.
[JUSTIN CHUCKLES]
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Now, I know there's someone
worse than me.
- What did you say?
- What?
- Am I wrong?
Justin, let's go.
[SCOFFS, CHUCKLES]
[JUSTIN SIGHS LOUDLY]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
What's with them?
I don't know either.
Is it still because
of the earring?
[SIGHS SHARPLY]
I thought that was over.
They said they
don't want to talk about it.
Raphie, you're such
a slowpoke.
- Hurry.
- I'm coming.
This way.
- Uh, excuse me.
- Oh. Do you need anything, sir?
I'd just like to ask
if you know this person.
Uh... No, I don't, sir.
Are you sure?
I don't know
who that is, sir.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Alright. Excuse me.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
- Oh, shoot!
- I'll clean that up, sir.
- Sorry.
- Are you okay?
- Of course.
- Daryl.
Why wouldn't I be?
I'm just making sure.
I don't want us to face our
guests looking troubled.
I'm okay, Martin.
I'm sorry about what happened.
I wasn't able to control myself.
Well, a little self-control
might have worked,
but it wasn't your fault.
It was Bok who came here
and caused trouble.
As for you,
you did everything you could.
You made this event possible.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Even so.
This is what I've been
telling you, Martin.
Told me what?
That my life is a mess.
You shouldn't be
dragged into it.
We shouldn't be dragged
into it,
but we should always
help each other.
Thank you.
Wait.
Where's Kiko?
I haven't seen him
since earlier.
Maybe he's at the venue.
Why don't you call him?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[LINE RINGING]
- He's not picking up.
- He's not?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Thank you.
- Are you a local?
- Yes, sir.
Really?
- You grew up here?
- Yes, sir.
Do you know this person?
Um, no, sir.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, sir.
Okay. Thank you.
Enjoy, sir.
[UPBEAT MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Bro! Have fun, okay?
If you need anything,
I'm right here.
- Just one call away.
- Sure, bro.
This is so far, fun, Edward.
I got you, I got you.
It's gonna start in a minute.
- Hi!
Edward, can we take a selfie?
[LUNA] Yeah, that's good.
Also, can you fix the barricade
at the north entrance?
It's broken down.
We can't let that stay that way.
- Copy, ma'am.
- How about the wristbands?
We've fixed that issue, ma'am.
Yeah, make sure
everyone gets one.
Are you alright, Ma'am Luna?
Yeah. There's just so much
going on right now.
I had to deal with something
back at the hotel earlier.
Ma'am, why don't you
get some rest?
Not right now.
Go on now. And keep me updated.
Yes, ma'am.
She probably just went
to a supplier.
Who?
Jade.
You're looking for her, right?
She's on her way.
Yeah, I'm looking for her.
Where is she?
[PANTING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[COUGHS]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [JADE PANTING]
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
Someone took Jade.
No matter what happens,
Mom should be safe at home.
No, Jade!
- What about my brother?
- We won't abandon Kiko.
He's also our brother, okay?
Make sure everything
runs smoothly.
That monster!
It's possible he's obsessed
with Mrs. Almazan,
and he was mad
at your fathers.
Where's Trixie?
I saw her leave
with Miss Cheska and Sari.
- Hey!
- Aah!
I can't lose another member
of my family again.
- Mom! Mom!
- Mom!
We're also checking
this area.
We might find something that
could help us find them.
We'll go to whichever
island it is.
I'll confront Roi myself.
Police!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
I love your mother.
I'm willing to die
and kill for her.