[GRUNTS]
[BOTH GROANS]
Roi, don't hurt my son!
- Police!
- [GROANS]
[GROANING]
Where did you take Jade Almazan?
I won't tell you if you
don't let me and Frida go!
Get off!
- Run! After them!
- [GUNSHOTS]
[THUDS]
Hey!
- Gio!
- [GUNSHOTS]
I'm not after your money
anymore, Gio.
Just do it, Bok.
Don't drag my brothers
into this.
I'll kill you  if something
happens to them.
[GRUNTS]
How does it feel
to be unlucky, Gio?
- [GRUNTING]
- [SCREAMS IN PAIN]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GIO GROANS IN PAIN]
- [LAUGHS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [GIO GROANS]
- [LAUGHS]
- [GIO GRUNTS]
- [GROANS]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PANTING]
[GROANS]
[PHONE BEEPING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Just keep looking for Jade.
- Yes, ma'am.
- [PHONE BUZZING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Ma'am?
This is Edward Arellano.
Yes, ma'am. I just want
to ask for an update.
Mr. Arellano,
we've arrested Roi.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Okay.
How about Jade?
Where is she?
Has Roi told you
where she is?
Not yet.
Ma'am, we need
to find Jade.
Mr. Arellano, we know our job.
But for now,
you need to get out
of that place.
No.
Ma'am, we can't leave yet.
Roi must've hidden Jade
somewhere around here.
He's still using her
against her family.
That means Jade is here.
Mr. Arellano, our entire team
is still searching.
We'll update you.
Okay, ma'am. Thank you.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Jade. Jade.
Jade, where are you?
Jade!
Jade, please show yourself.
Jade. Jade!
Jade. Please show up.
Where are you, Jade?
Come on, Jade.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Jade. Jade, where are you?
Jade!
Jade, are you there?
Come on, Jade.
Jade. Jade...
Jade, please.
Jade!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUFFLED WAIL]
[JADE SOBS]
Jade.
Jade!
Jade...
[PANTING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[MUFFLED SOBBING]
[GRUNTING]
[BARRELS CLANK]
[EDWARD] Jade.
Jade. Jade.
Jade, Jade, Jade.
Can you hear me, Jade?
[JADE GROANING]
[EDWARD] Jade. Jade.
Jade, Jade.
Jade.
[GRUNTING]
[METAL CLANKS]
[METAL LID CLANKS]
Jade.
Jade, Jade, Jade,
Jade, Jade, Jade...
Come here.
[EDWARD GRUNTING]
Jade...
Jade, Jade.
Jade, wake up.
Jade, Jade, Jade.
[EDWARD] Jade. Wake up, Jade.
Jade, Jade, Jade!
Wake up! Jade!
Jade? Jade. Wake up, Jade.
[EDWARD] Jade, wake up...
Jade.
Wake up.
[WHIMPERS]
[SOBS]
You're safe. You're okay.
I'm here now.
I'm here, Jade.
- I'm here, okay?
- [CRIES]
Jade... It's okay. I'm here.
No... No. No.
Huh? Huh, Jade? Jade.
[SOBBING]
[EDWARD] I'm here, Jade.
I'm here.
Jade...
You're all right.
- Jade.
- [JADE SOBS]
[SOBBING]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
- [THUDS]
- [LEAVES RUSTLING]
[KIKO GRUNTS]
[KIKO] Gio!
[KIKO GRUNTING]
Gio!
Kiko!
[PANTS]
[GIO] Martin...
Gio, hold on tight!
- Hold on, please!
- Please!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTING]
[GIO GRUNTS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Bok...
We'll get away from them, okay?
- Just hang in there!
- Gio!
Gio! Gio, stay awake!
Stay awake, please!
We'll go to the hospital!
Promise!
Stay awake!
[KIKO] Gio!
[KIKO, MARTIN GRUNTING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KIKO GROANING]
Kiko, don't let go!
[GIO GRUNTING WITH STRAIN]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADING]
[ROI] I didn't do anything!
Why are you locking me up?
I'm innocent!
- [GATE BANGING]
- [LOCK CLANKING]
I didn't kill them!
I've never killed anybody!
Believe me!
- That's enough!
- [HEAVY BREATHS]
[ROI]
It wasn't me who killed them.
- [GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
Mrs. Almazan has
identified you.
She claimed you were there
at the time when both men died.
[ROI BREATHES DEEPLY]
I went there for Frida.
[BREATH QUIVERING]
For her safety!
And because you've long had
feelings for Mrs. Almazan,
you used the opportunity
to get Frederico
out of the picture.
Then you killed his friend too
so there would be no witness.
All of this, just to carry out
your plan with Mrs. Almazan.
[ROI CRYING]
I didn't do anything.
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
They were dead
by the time I saw them!
[JUSTIN] You're a liar.
You killed my dad!
We welcomed you!
My parents trusted you!
[ROI SNIFFLES]
[HANDCUFFS RATTLING]
Justin...
- Justin, I didn't kill anyone.
- [MOCKING TONE] Huh? Huh?
[JUSTIN] Crazy!
You're crazy!
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [LEON] Justin, let's go.
- Huh?!
You're going to rot in prison!
You murderer!
[SCOFFS]
Let's go!
[ROI]
The only crime I committed...
was loving Frida.
I swear to all of you,
my conscience is clean!
[PANTING]
I didn't kill Michael.
I didn't kill Frederico.
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ROI CRYING]
[PRESSURE CUFF UNFASTENS]
[SIREN WAILING
IN THE DISTANCE]
[FRIDA] Jade.
- Jade, my daughter.
- Mom?
- [SOFTLY] Jade.
- [VOICE BREAKING] Mom.
[SOBBING] Mom, Mom...
Mom... Mom...
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
[FRIDA] Thank God you're safe.
Thank you.
[FRIDA]
I'm so sorry, sweetheart.
My dear, I'm so sorry
I was late.
Your life should never
have been in danger.
[JADE SOBBING]
Mom, it's not your fault, okay?
- [MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [BOTH SNIFFLING]
Roi...
Mom, it was Roi's.
[BREATH QUIVERING,
EXHALES HEAVILY]
He's gone, sweetheart.
He's been caught.
No one will hurt you anymore.
- [FRIDA SNIFFLING, WHIMPERS]
- [JADE SOBBING]
[FRIDA] My baby...
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
- I'm sorry.
- I love you, Mom.
I love you.
[KISSES, CRIES]
Mom.
Let's go?
Let's go, Mom.
Let's go.
Slow and steady, alright?
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MARINA SIGHING]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'll get going.
The rest of us already
went ahead.
It's Michael Fernandez's
children who need help now.
What happened to them?
Bok ambushed them.
But don't worry,
I'll take care of it.
You should go ahead.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Okay.
[FOOTSTEPS RECEDING]
[SIREN WAILING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOORS OPEN]
[HURRIED FOOTSTEPS]
[REAR CAR DOOR OPENS]
[MARTIN] Doc, please hurry!
- Doc...
- Doc! Nurse, please!
Nurse, my brother! Save him!
- Please!
- [NURSE] Get checked, too!
[KIKO] No! Nurse, just focus
on our brother!
He's dying!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
What about Bok?
He might come back for us.
He won't. The cops are already
after him and his crew, okay?
This way, hurry!
Nurse, where's
the emergency room?
[NURSE] This way.
This way? Thank you.
[CHESKA] Kiko! Kiko!
- [TRIXIE] Oh my god, Martin!
- [CHESKA] Kiko!
- Ouch!
- What happened?
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
[CHESKA] What happened to you?
[CHESKA CRYING]
You're so reckless!
- What happened to you?
- That's enough, that's enough.
- I'm okay now.
- He has so many bruises
on his lips and nose.
- Why did you do that, Kiko?
- On the nose too?
Are you really okay?
Let's run some tests, please.
- You may be injured.
- [SIGHS] Trixie.
- [SNIFFLING]
- [MARTIN] I'm okay.
- [TRIXIE BREATHES OUT]
- Promise.
[SARI CRYING]
[CHESKA] Sari?
[VOICE SHAKING] Uh, don't worry
about me, sir.
I'm okay.
These are, uh. Happy tears!
I'm happy that you're okay.
Um--
Wait a sec. Where's Gio?
He's severely hurt.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
My god, Martin,
what even happened?
[BLOOD PRESSURE CUFF CRUNCHES]
I know you want
to go home already.
But we need to make sure
that you're okay.
[WHEELS RATTLING]
[SNIFFLES]
I'm sorry I couldn't help you.
I'm sorry I wasn't there
when you were alone.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
You don't have
to say that, Luna.
But I made a promise to Dad.
I told him I'd do anything
for our family.
And that includes
being a good sister to you.
[SNIFFLES]
I know you're trying
your best, Luna.
[JADE SNIFFLES]
You don't have to blame
yourself for everything
that's happening to us.
Okay?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SNIFFLES, SIGHS]
[LUNA SNIFFLING]
[LUNA] Oh, they're here.
[JADE] Leon!
- How are you?
- Leon.
[LEON EXHALES HEAVILY]
Leon, the doctor said
I can go home already.
Leon, any update?
What did the police say?
Roi is already jailed
for kidnapping Jade.
But for the murder of Dad
and Uncle Mike, uh...
Our lawyers will have
to look into it first.
What's up?
Hm?
[CHUCKLES]
I told you to be careful.
If it hurts somewhere,
tell us, okay?
[SNIFFLES]
What about Mom?
Where's Mom?
They're still checking up
with her.
- I need to talk to Mom.
- Jade, Jade.
- Just rest for now.
- I have to talk to Mom, please.
- You have to rest.
- Please, just for a moment.
[FRIDA] Jade.
[JADE CRYING]
Jade.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JADE SOBS]
Are you okay?
I'm so sorry, Mom.
I'm so sorry.
[CRYING] Jade, you don't
have to apologize.
It's Roi's fault, not yours.
No, Mom...
No apology would ever be enough
for all of the things I've done
and said to you.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
[SMOOCHES] It's okay, Jade.
It's not.
Jade, listen to me.
My dear,
I'm your mother.
There's nothing you can do
that I won't be able to forgive.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JADE SOBBING]
[SNIFFLES, SIGHS]
[FRIDA SOBBING]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Your Dad will never be able
to forgive me
if even one of you disappears.
And I will never be able
to forgive myself either.
Thank God we are all safe.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE RINGING]
- Luna.
- Kiko.
I was just trying to call you
to ask about Jade.
Ho-- How is she?
Wh-- Why are you here?
She's alright.
Ho-- How about your family?
That Roi is sick in the head.
He'll rot in jail.
What about Jade, is she okay?
How about Aunt Frida?
Jade is doing fine.
Mom was just checked recently
and she's fine too.
What about you? Your family?
What on earth happened?
[SIGHS]
Well... [INHALES SHARPLY]
Gio is the one
who got hurt really badly.
Why? What happened to Gio?
We were on the way
to your place.
But we were waylaid
by Bok and the others.
You remember that guest
who caused a mess at the hotel?
It was him?
He wanted
to exact revenge on Gio
so they chased one another,
hit each other,
and now he's all beat up.
How did he get beat up?
He got stabbed.
Where is Bok and the others now?
The police is currently
looking for them.
I hope he gets caught already
so him and Roi can rot together.
Are you okay, Luna?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Well then, you should head back
to your siblings, Kiko.
Get some rest yourself.
Let's keep in touch.
Alright.
[BREATHES DEEPLY] Thanks.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
- [KNOB CLICKS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I hope you get well soon.
[FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[KNOB CLICKS, DOOR CLOSES]
Get him!
Where's Bok?
I don't know!
- Bring him in.
- Come on.
- [FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [WAVES CRASHING]
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TWIG CRACKS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUN CLICKS]
[MAN] Hey!
I got this. Bring him in.
- Let's go.
- Hurry up!
[WATER SPLASHING]
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [LEAVES RUSTLING]
- [WAVES CRASHING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BOK SCREAMING IN DISTANCE] Aah!
[FOOTSTEPS RUNNING IN SAND]
[WATER SPLASHES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LIQUID TRICKLING]
Bok?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Welcome to Hotel 88!
The most awaited...
Gio's return!
Back to normal then?
No.
My siblings are in danger.
I need to protect them.
Why do you have
Dad's laptop, Leon?
I don't have reasons
to stay here anymore.
You should not
have been dragged.
If you think justice
has been served
for your father's death,
you're wrong.
The real killer
is still out and free.