Roi Martinez. I've sent you
the profile of the suspect.
Block all the exits.
That man can't leave
the island.
We trusted him.
That bastard!
Kiko has a strong feeling
that Roi killed Papa.
He may be obsessed
with Mrs. Almazan
and he harbors a grudge
against your fathers,
but that doesn't mean
he's the killer.
We're going to look for him,
Mr. Almazan.
And Roi will go to jail
for abducting your sister
and for what he did to Kiko.
- I'll go with you too!
- No!
You and Luna check
on Mom at our house.
No matter what happens,
make sure that Mom
is safe, okay?
Thank you so much
for helping us out.
You should be apologizing
to the Almazans.
Because you brought
Jade here.
Frida, I love you so much.
I'd die if I can't have you!
Help!
Stop being stubborn, Jade.
You look like your mother,
you know.
Such a creep!
You're so shameless!
[VOICE PROMPT] ...be reached.
Please try again later.
Roi... [SIGHS]
I can't get ahold of him.
[VOICE PROMPT] This subscriber
cannot be reached.
- Please try again later.
- [SIGHS]
- [MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [LUNA SNIFFLES, SOBS]
Why can't our family
ever catch a break?
Why are we being punished
like this?
Luna...
- That's enough.
- No.
Justin, are we bad people?
Have we done anything wrong?
- [PHONE BEEPING]
- Please pick up.
[PHONE RINGING]
Martin.
That's Martin?
Put him on speaker.
[MARTIN] Hello, Luna?
How are things there?
Martin, how about Jade?
Have you found her?
Not yet, Justin.
They're still searching.
- I'll go there.
- Me too. I'll go.
No need.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
The police
also sent me home.
That's it?
This is Jade we're
talking about here.
Our youngest.
I know, Luna.
I know.
But the police
won't stop searching.
And we won't stop either.
How about Mom? How is she?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Where's Mom?
- Mom?
[JUSTIN] Mom!
- Mom!
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
- Mom! Mom!
Mom, wait!
Mom!
Mom! Mom!
- Mom! Mom! Mom!
- No...
- You can't go. It's dangerous.
- Let me go.
- I have to go.
- Mom, listen. Mom!
- Mom, please listen!
- Let me go!
We haven't found Jade yet.
We don't want you
to get hurt too.
Please, Mom.
I'm the one Roi wants.
Not Jade.
I have to find my daughter!
- I have to find Jade.
- Mom, no.
- I have to find her.
- No, no, no.
- You can't.
- Mom, please. Please.
[FRIDA] It's my fault. [SOBS]
- I have to find her.
- Mom. Mom.
I'm the one Roi wants.
Not Jade.
- Mom, it's dangerous.
- Mom. Mom.
I wonder what happened to them.
I don't know.
What if something else
had happened?
What if the driver came back
and hurt them?
What's going to happen now?
What if--
Can you just shut up?!
You're making me more nervous.
Hey, hey, don't yell at me.
Who do you think you are?
Why? Aren't you worried?
Well, I'm worried
about my brother.
How dare you tell me
to shut up!
- Because you're so noisy!
- What? Bring it on!
- Whatever!
- I'm telling my brother!
- Do it then!
- You bet I will!
Please stop fighting.
- We're not fighting.
I'm not a warfreak, okay?
[SCOFFS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- This tension is killing me.
- [MIMICKING TRIXIE]
It's so hard not knowing
anything.
Martin still hasn't
texted me back.
They wouldn't have time
to text back.
- But... but...
- [CHESKA] What?
I know someone who might
know where Jade is.
- Who?
Then let's go see that person
so we can actually help.
- Where are they?
- But what about the event?
Sir Martin told us
to monitor it.
Monette and Raphie
are here.
They're used to this.
They know what they're
doing better than we do.
Come on. Where are they?
Come on.
Well? Should we go check?
Come on, let's go.
Let's go, Sari.
- You know where they are?
- Yeah.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTING]
We got along fine, you know.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Honestly,
out of all of you siblings,
I like you best.
You're nice and quiet.
Unlike your sister, Luna.
She's so arrogant.
Too bad.
If only you didn't snoop around.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
But don't worry.
I just need to talk to Frida.
She'll explain
everything to you.
So you'll understand
why I did this.
And I love your mother.
I don't like seeing her hurt.
I'd die...
and kill anyone...
...for her.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SARI] We're here.
[TRIXIE] Here? Are you sure?
Didn't you say you know someone
who can help us locate Jade?
Yes, that's why I brought you
to our house.
[CHESKA] Your house?
What are we doing here?
- [SHRIEKS, YELPS]
- Hey! Hey! Hey!
What's with the knife?
Give me that!
I was going to peel
some coconuts.
[SARI] You're doing that
at this hour?
[BOTONG] Is there a specified
time to peel coconuts?
Uh...
And who are these two?
Hey, careful.
Oh, these are Cheska
and Trixie, Grandpa.
You're too loud.
G-Good evening.
I'm Cheska.
Hello. Trixie here.
Good evening.
Uh, this is my grandpa.
He can tell us where Jade is.
How?
He's one of the most famous
and brilliant healers
and fortune tellers
on this island.
- Fortune teller?
- [CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
- [PHONE CAMERA CLICKS]
- Hey. What's that? Hm?
Thank goodness the music fest
ended without a hitch
and everyone had fun!
There's no doubt that
our event was a success,
so congratulations, sirs!
I'd like to thank you,
Raphie, and Monette.
We're extremely grateful
that we can rely on you.
Don't mention it, sir.
If only Monette and I could do
anything to ease your worries,
we'd have done it already
I wonder how Miss Jade is doing.
[PHONE CHIMES]
Come on, hurry up!
Get out of here.
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
Well? Didn't I tell you
I'm a good boy?
Shut up.
You should've believed me
when I said I was innocent.
You don't even have evidence
to prove I stole the car.
Yeah, yeah.
Just sign here.
After that, you can leave.
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'll get going now.
It's payback time.
No updates from the police yet,
but I know they're doing
everything they can.
You heard that, Kiko?
The police are doing their best.
They won't abandon Jade
so you can calm down now.
[KIKO] I can't do that, Gio.
I was with Jade
when she was abducted.
If only I had managed
to fight back--
[RAPHIE] Kiko, you were
knocked unconscious.
That isn't an excuse, Raphie.
Had I not been knocked out,
Roi couldn't have taken Jade.
This isn't your fault, Kiko.
Don't blame yourself.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
I think it's time to rest.
Maybe we should call it a night.
I'm sure Sir Henry will have
an update for us tomorrow.
Wait, where's Trixie? Has she
returned from the event?
Oh, I didn't get to
talk to her all night,
but I saw her leave
with Miss Cheska and Sari.
Cheska's not back either?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- What's he doing?
- Shh!
Just wait. Don't make a noise.
Yeah, shut up.
You might disturb him.
Let him do his thing.
I was just asking.
What's that candle for?
Shh!
[BOTONG] There is...
...a cool breeze.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
[WIND HOWLING]
You know what?
This is crazy. I'm going home.
Shh!
[INTRIGUING MUSIC CONTINUES]
There's an isolated house...
...on an island.
[CANDLE WAX
DRIPPING ON WATER]
[CHESKA WHISPERING]
Guys, what's going on?
The old house on that island...
...stands in the middle
of two palm trees.
That's where they took
the woman.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BLOWS]
- [BOTONG HUFFS]
- [SARI GASPS]
Grandpa, are you alright?
Y-Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Did you hear what Grandpa said?
Mm-hmm.
In a house...
in the middle of an island,
sandwiched between
two palm trees.
Nice one, Grandpa.
So cool
- Are you okay, Grandpa?
- Yeah.
Hey, they're here.
Would it kill you to update us?
You had us worried sick!
I'm sorry, Martin.
- [MARTIN HUFFS]
- There was no signal there.
Honestly, I shouldn't
have gone with them.
Yeah, right.
You believed it, too.
Excuse me?
Where were you anyway?
We went to Sari's house.
Sari's house?
Well, Sari said...
she knew someone who could
help us locate Jade.
I couldn't just pass that up.
I want to help too.
Who was it?
Sari's grandfather
happens to be...
- ...a fortune teller.
- What did he say?
He said there's a house
on an island...
...sandwiched between
two palm trees.
That's where Jade is.
But there's so many houses
like that on this island!
[CHESKA] Well...
Sari said her grandpa
is a famous fortune teller.
Look, don't just
believe Sari, okay?
Because if you...
If you disappear too,
I'm going to lose my mind!
- Martin...
- Go to sleep!
- Bro.
- What?
- I took a video. Look.
- Forget it. Get some rest.
Just look at it, bro.
You aren't curious?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Not too long after I was
hired as your driver,
my mother got sick.
Not one hospital
wanted to accept her.
But Frida...
She did everything...
to have my mother treated.
She wasn't just pretty.
She has a very good heart, too.
Mama eventually died.
But that only...
...revived my weary heart.
I fell in love with Frida.
I promised myself
that no matter what happens...
I will protect her.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
I never thought ill of Roi
because he's been with us
for many years!
[LUNA] Then why are you saying
he might've killed Dad?
Because he told me
to go home that day.
He said he'd
take care of things, so...
I didn't know what he'd do!
- Ma.
- Leon...
Are there any updates?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh my god...
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
Jade...
Where could Jade be?
Where is Jade?
"Sir, we're all still awake.
Just call if you have updates."
[PHONE CHIMES]
What did they say?
"We're still doing our rounds."
Still no update.
Tsk!
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
I'm sorry, Fred.
I'm so sorry.
Mom, go get some rest first.
We'll monitor the search.
As if I'd get a wink of sleep
in this situation.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[HENRI] With the new evidence
and with Mrs. Almazan's
new statement,
it's become clearer that Roi was
at the crime scene at that time.
That means he's now a suspect
in your fathers' deaths.
Will our fathers' case
be reopened?
That's right.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[DARK MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
It's devastating if it's true.
It would mean Papa
just got caught up
in that guy's obsession.
There's just one thing
that doesn't make sense.
What?
Why did Papa
bring a gun that day?
They said it was Papa's gun
that was used, right?
And according to
the witnesses' testimonies,
Papa was furious.
So how did he get caught up
in Roi's obsession?
We can't answer that.
We don't know
what really happened.
After being away from home
for so long,
there's so much about Papa and
Uncle Fred we no longer know.
But if Roi really
was the murderer...
that would mean Papa and
Uncle Fred's friendship
was real.
And this ongoing beef we have
with the Almazans...
I feel like we really
should end it.
Jade's life is still in danger.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Shouldn't we patch things up
with the Almazans for real?
The more time passes,
the more I can't stop thinking
about all sorts of things.
Stay strong, Mom.
Have they still not called
or sent any updates?
[FRIDA SIGHS]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Edward.
- Edward.
I have good news.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[KIKO] I hope Jade makes it
through all of this.
I hope we don't go through
any more pain.
[STIRRING MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Roi must've used the car to go
to one of the islands here.
We'll go with you,
wherever it is.
Did you know Mom and Dad
have already separated?
She wanted to leave.
No one's leaving!
Where's Jade?
Where's my daughter?
I'll send you the place
where we'll meet.
Don't try to fool me.
You can't go there alone,
Mrs. Almazan.
He'll kill my daughter
if he finds out I brought
cops with me.
How about we follow them?
Kiko, we can't.
So we'll just wait?
We can't just sit back
and do nothing.