I'm just here to collect the
rest of what you owe.
Do you own this hotel now?
Didn't I tell you to wait?
I'll pay you, Bok.
- [SCREAMS]
- Jade!
- Are you okay?
Sir, I have good news for you.
There's a new candidate
you'll be interviewing
to be your assistant.
It's fine.
I don't need a new assistant.
About the flowers,
who sent them?
What kind of flowers
were these again, Ma?
The same ones your dad
used to give.
Waling-waling.
Didn't the police return
your father's phone?
Maybe we can find
something there.
[DOOR OPENS]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[SIGHS]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC GROWS TENSE]
[FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
[DOOR SLAMS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC SWELLS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
There!
Finally, I found it.
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [OBJECT CLATTERING]
[DOOR OPENS]
Uh...
Martin.
You're still awake?
[MARTIN] I can't sleep.
What about you?
Same here.
Ah, do you want some...
milk?
Monette has milk there.
Wasn't that what Papa used
to give us to help us sleep?
Let's go.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh.
Gio.
You can't sleep either?
Do you have a minute?
I just wanted to tell you
something.
[MILK POURING]
That guy's crazy, huh!
He beat you up?
Was that the one from room 203?
- I'll take care of it.
- [GLASS THUDS]
[CHAIR SLIDES]
I just really wanted
to let you know.
I feel like...
he just wanted to make sure
I would really pay.
W-Wait.
You mean that's the Bok
you owe money to?
He followed you here?
Looks like he's still
not satisfied
with what I already paid.
[SIGHS]
W-Wait-- How did he know
you were here?
Martin, social media.
It's really easy, especially...
people recognize us
because of Edward,
and because of those
influencer friends of his.
Sorry about that.
[SIGHS]
I tried to drive him away,
but...
that bastard really
has some nerve.
It's a bit concerning,
but it's good that you told us.
At least we know
what to expect, right?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
If I could just drag him
out of here,
- I would've done it already.
- [CHUCKLING]
[MARTIN] Hey...
We'll have security
keep an eye on him, okay?
Thank you, Martin.
But Gio, if you ever
need backup,
I'm right here.
I may not have abs,
but I'm a strongman.
- [SCOFFS]
- [CHUCKLES]
Whatever you say.
Abs? Abs.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[VAN ENGINE RUNNING]
[ROI YAWNS]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Roi, are you sleepy?
Ma'am?
I'm asking if you're sleepy.
Because if yes, I'll drive.
It's dangerous if
you're driving while sleepy.
Uh... [CHUCKLES]
No, ma'am. I'm fine.
Uh... I just didn't
sleep well last night,
but...
I can manage.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What?
Suppliers, stage setup,
lights, sounds, permit,
- security--
- Sir!
Have you checked
the generator?
- Sir, breathe. Inhale, exhale.
- Sari!
It's all set, sir!
Look, check, check!
The artist contract,
did you get it signed?
- [SARI] Oh!
- Where is it?
Yes, Sir. It's here.
Wait a second.
[MARTIN] Let me see!
Wait, sir. It's right here.
Sari! Artist contract?!
Sari, the contract!
Sari, where's the contract?!
[SARI] Sir! I caught it!
Sir, here it is!
Here's the contract!
I did it, sir!
[SARI SQUEALS]
[SIGHS] Raphie!
Sir! Sir...
Sir!
[CHUCKLES]
[MAN GRUNTING]
[JADE] Let's go here.
Quick.
- Come on, come on.
- Jade...
my brothers might look
for me.
They won't. We'll be quick.
Promise.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [JADE] Kiko, Kiko.
- [KIKO] Oh?
You know, I have a
strong feeling about this.
I feel like this is also
where we'll find
the answers to our questions.
You know what? Me too.
I almost got caught last night.
OMG.
Twins.
Twins?
Us? [CHUCKLES]
What is that, like gecko twins
or something?
No! I mean, me too.
I almost got caught
last night too.
Oh! Twins!
Whatever, Kiko!
Let's just go.
Here, this way.
Let's go here.
Here, here.
There's a path here.
Let's pass here. There.
Just stay quiet, okay? Slowly.
Kiko, is there a path there?
- Let's check.
- Let's check. Come on.
There's no path here anymore.
Where are we?
Here, here.
Let's just stay here.
- Okay.
- Come on.
- Game.
- [THUDS]
- [CRACKS]
- [SCREAMS]
- Are you okay?
- Ow! Kiko!
You said we'd go slow?!
Oh my god! It's always like this
- when we're together,
- Ow, ow! My phone!
- something unlucky happens!
- My phone!
Excuse me?
Are you saying
I'm the unlucky one?
I didn't say that.
You just implied it, right?
What I'm saying is,
something unlucky happened,
I didn't say it's you.
You're always so paranoid.
Okay.
Okay, you have a point, that...
or maybe the universe
is trying to tell us something.
Like what? That we
shouldn't be doing this?
That we shouldn't
doubt your mom?
Kiko, I'll say it again.
I just want the truth.
And this time, hopefully, the
universe is on our side, right?
[KIKO] Universe, please, grant
us this one thing, please.
Where's the phone? Where is it?
Oh... never mind.
Here it is.
- Game?
- What? So? Should we open it?
Game. Three, two, one.
["PAANO KUNG TAYO NA LANG?"
BY ANGELA KEN PLAYING]
One, two, three, go!
["PAANO KUNG TAYO NA LANG?"
CONTINUES]
Yes! Oh my god!
- Yes! Ah!
- [LAUGHS]
Uh... wow...
Thank you, universe!
What? What? Thank you...
Thank you! Thank you, universe!
[SQUEALS] Yay!
[SIGH OF HAPPINESS]
[EDWARD] Bro, thank you.
Thank you for coming.
You think I'd ever say no, bro?
That's what I'm talking about.
But how are you guys?
I'm excited
for your event.
Bro, this is gonna be huge.
Believe me.
- Yeah, I got this.
- Hope you brought more guests.
I got this, bro.
More of our friends
are coming tomorrow.
- Really? Seriously?
- Yeah, seriously.
Nice one, nice one, nice one.
Let's go?
- Let's check your room.
- Let's go, let's go, let's go.
- Welcome to Hotel 88, sirs!
- Hello! Hello!
- Hi.
- For check-in?
This way.
Ma'am, get them room, please?
The bigger ones.
they are my friends.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
- You're welcome.
- [MONETTE] You're in room 307.
Wow... no "thank you,"
straight to "you're welcome"?
I already guessed
what you'd say.
I knew I made the right call
getting you.
I know, right?
So? Let's go.
- All set?
- Yeah, all set.
- Let's go, let's go.
- Let's go. Thanks!
- Thank you, sir!
- Thank you.
- Enjoy! Thank you.
- Thank you, thank you.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[RAPHIE]
Welcome, sir!
[RECEPTIONIST]
Good morning, sir.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Uh...
Hello, welcome to Hotel 88.
For check-in?
Good morning, sir.
Can I get your ID?
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sir Martin is here.
He's just talking
to the lighting crew.
There's a small problem,
you know?
But he's here.
We need to talk to them.
Oh, Sir Gio is here too.
But...
why are people wandering around?
Wait, I'll come back to you.
I just need to find him.
Hold on.
[TRIXIE] Are the voltages
and wires all good?
We can't afford
a glitch later, okay?
Okay. Alright, thank you.
I'll introduce you
to the band's vocalist.
He's my friend. We're close.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
I'm not interested, Justin.
- Then... shots?
- I don't drink.
B-But... Come on.
I'm just welcoming you.
Why? Because you found out
I'm Martin's sister?
No, I just want to give you
a proper welcome.
[SIGHS SHARPLY] If you're
the one doing it, I'd pass.
Oh man.
No... wait, wait, wait.
Can you stop doing that?
No.
The more you walk away,
the more
you'll see this face.
Oh god.
[CHUCKLES]
- Miss Trixie, Sir Justin.
- Yes?
- Have you seen Sir Martin?
- No, why?
The police are looking for him.
Police?
Yeah. Okay,
I'll find him and come back.
Done? Ma'am?
- Ma'am. Can you check--
- Huh?
Jean, we're over budget.
Their stage rig costs
way more than allocated.
That's what they gave me, sir.
Try talking to them.
Production expenses
are exploding.
I'll try, Sir Leon.
Thank you.
[PHONE RINGING]
Justin.
[PHONE CHIMES]
Hello.
Wait, I'll find them. Sorry.
Jade hasn't answered yet.
Where is she?
[LUNA] Justin, I'm busy
at the hotel. What now?
The stupid police are here.
What are they doing here?
[JUSTIN]
I don't know either.
But Sari's with them.
They're looking for Martin.
What do they want
with Martin now?
Will those cops ever stop?
For now, we don't know why.
They literally have
nothing better to do.
That's it.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[JADE]
Look at this.
[PHONE BUZZING]
- "I miss you."
[JADE CHUCKLING]
[KIKO]
You look really amused.
Those two are crazy
with their bromance.
But then again, they've always
been like that, even before.
[KIKO] Exactly. You know,
this is what really confuses me.
If they're that close,
would Papa really be able
to have a relationship
with your mom?
[SIGHS SHARPLY]
I don't know, Kiko.
I just have
this strange feeling.
But look at this.
Look.
Their calls are back to back.
What do you think
they're talking about?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[JUSTIN]
Luna said she's on her way.
Have they been here long?
[SHARPLY EXHALES]
Feels like they just got here.
You know, I really don't like
the look on his face.
Makes me want to punch him.
What do you think
they're talking about?
I thought the earring issue
was already settled.
So why are they here now?
Do you want me to go over
and approach them, Leon?
I'll deal with them directly
so we can get this over with.
Don't.
Don't?
What, we just stay here?
Just stare at them?
[SCOFFS]
Thank you for coming.
This means a lot, sir.
Thanks.
It's our job, after all
to make sure everyone is safe.
We'll be sending a few
more of our men.
They'll keep watch here
until tomorrow.
Will you be sending some
to Hotel 88 as well?
We also have guests
checked in there.
We'll check.
But the event is here.
So the security
should be here too.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
That makes sense...
Alright then, we'll handle
the security at Hotel 88.
But whatever happens,
you can still call us.
- We'll go now.
- Alright. Thank you again.
There, they left.
The Almazan brothers have been
staring at us for a while now.
Why do you think that is?
They're probably
just getting paranoid.
Good. I'm not letting them
off the hook.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh, looks like Martin's gone.
Oh, Luna!
What happened?
Did those police officers
talk to you?
What did Martin say?
Did they approach you?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
So, nothing happened?
Leon!
I was waiting for them
to call me over or something,
but... nothing.
They just talked
and then left right away.
What about Martin?
You didn't ask him?
They came up to us,
but they didn't say anything.
I thought they might get
the wrong idea
if I started asking questions.
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
Do you think this is still
about the earring?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
All I know is the four of us
have to stay united.
We can't fall apart.
Four?
But there are only three of us
right now.
Where's Jade?
Nothing.
She still hasn't replied
in the family group chat.
- Oh no...
- Where could she be?
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
Nothing. We're at a dead end.
I really thought
we'd find something out.
Isn't it better
that we didn't find anything?
Kiko...
No,
my gut just won't let it go.
I know it.
I can really feel it.
You're really holding on
to that hunch.
Kiko, I know what I saw
when we were kids.
I really saw Mom
and Uncle Mike together.
Right? I've told you
about that before.
Yeah, yeah.
You've said that before.
But what does that mean?
Papa pursued Aunt Frida
while she was
still married to Uncle Fred?
Gave her chocolates,
flowers, that kind of thing?
Flowers...
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Flowers!
Someone gave Mom flowers.
She said they were
waling-waling.
Wait, when...
when did this happen?
It was recent. She even thought
one of us gave them to her.
Oh... maybe Papa
wasn't really the one
she had a relationship with?
Maybe it was another man,
and he's still alive.
Who gave her the flowers?
Wait, is there a flower shop
near here?
Yes.
Two.
In town.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight.
- And right...
- Yes, right!
- Right.
- Oh, okay.
- Perfect!
- Okay.
- "Wow, Hotel 88 looks fun"
- [BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[BRY]
Bro, is this yours?
Is this your missing car?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
"THAT'S IT!
WHERE DID YOU SEE IT?"
[LINE RINGING]
Bro, where'd they find the car?
[BRY] Bok tried
to have my friend sell it.
He turned it down.
What? Sell what?
How did that happen?
[BRY] He knows
how Bok operates, Gio.
Those bastards are a syndicate.
What do you mean,
a syndicate?
[BRY]
They ask you to sell the car,
then they're the ones
who steal it too.
In the end,
you're the one who loses
because you end up
owing them.
Isn't that exactly what
Bok's been doing to you?
That bastard!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Uh... Miss?
Excuse me. Do you happen
to have waling-waling?
Like this.
[FLORIST]
Did you say waling-waling?
No one sells that.
What? Why not?
Because this flower is rare.
You can't just buy it anywhere.
You're right.
There are places where that
plant is already endangered.
Kiko...
I just remembered,
Dad told me
this flower is too delicate
and takes a long time to grow.
We're screwed.
What? How are we supposed
to find one now?
I don't know either, Kiko.
What do we do?
[FLORIST]
Wait.
I know someone
who grows that kind of plant.
Really?
Where?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- Where's the guest in room 203?
- Huh?
- This guest in room 203.
- [CHUCKLES]
Chill, why the face?
He's by the pool area.
He even had these drinks
sent over.
Gio, why?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey! Hey, Gio, what are you
going to do? Wait, Gio!
Why'd you point him there?
He asked.
Wasn't I supposed to say?
Did you see Gio's face?
Call Martin.
Right now, hurry!
[INAUDIBLE]
- Yes!
[LAUGHS]
[GRUNTS]
- Ahh, that hits the spot.
- [GRUNTS]
What, want to order more?
What?
Why don't we just buy
this resort?
- Whoo!
- You're just drunk, boss
Drunk? I'm not drunk.
You're crazy.
You know what?
This is mine!
I can easily buy this place,
man. Right?
What about you, man?
How much are you, huh?
Alright, alright.
- 5 million pesos.
- 5 million pesos?
- You're weak, man.
- You're ugly, man.
- What about you?
- That's cheap!
- You, how much? How much?
- 10 million pesos.
That's more like it.
10 million, huh?
10 million?
5 million?
I got you covered, guys.
[GRUNTS]
Dude! Hey!
I'll buy your property, okay?
[BLOW LANDS]
[BODY SPLASHES INTO WATER]
[WATER SPLASHING SOFTLY]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Is it here?
Yeah, I think.
It's what that old lady said.
Hello?
- Anybody there?
- Kiko-- Kiko, wait.
I think it's abandoned.
I think I know this place.
Why?
Have you been here before?
This is our driver's house.
[MUSIC BECOMES TENSE]
I'm not gonna pay
what you stole!
Gio! That's enough!
You judge our family so much,
as if you don't start
your own fights.
Why don't you manage
your brother's anger issues?
You're all the same!
I haven't seen Kiko all day.
Is that the flower
you were talking about?
- You're looking for her, right?
- Where is she?
Jade! Run! Go!
[PANTING]