Mom, it's Jade.
Roi kidnapped her.
- Aah!
- Ah!
Help!
[JADE YELPS]
Stop being stubborn, Jade.
We trusted him!
He's a monster!
If Roi is the murderer,
it means Papa and Uncle
Fred's friendship was real.
It's payback time.
I can't lose another member
of our family again.
That's why I'll do everything
to get your sister back home.
I'll send you the location.
But Frida, don't pull
a fast one on me,
or I'll kill your daughter.
Aren't we going
to do something?
We can't just sit here
and do nothing.
Leon, listen to me.
No matter what happens,
Jade should be the priority.
I love you all so much.
[BROODING MUSIC PLAYING]
I can't just wait here.
I'll go follow them.
Psst. Hey.
Look. We can't just
go there.
The police have a plan.
Earlier, you said
it was dangerous,
and now you want
to go there?
Yes.
But like I said,
you can't stop me.
I have to save Jade.
Hey.
If you'll only cause my mother
and sister to get hurt,
then don't help, Edward.
Just go home.
Follow me.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[BROODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello? Hello, Roi?
Where are you?
I'm here at our meeting place.
Are you alone?
Yes. That was our
agreement, right?
I brought my stuff
with me
so I can go with you
wherever you want to take me.
There's a path
on your right.
Go there.
Okay. Jade is with you,
right?
Just do as I say.
[BROODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CALL DROPS]
Roi!
[BROODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Go, hurry. Follow her.
Copy, sir.
[BROODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Leon should've taken me
with him.
I want to hurt Roi myself!
If there are many
of us there,
Roi might not believe Mom.
This isn't just about
Jade's safety, Justin,
but also Mom's safety.
All we can do
for now
is pray that nothing bad
happens to them.
I hope they call.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I hope Jade and Mom
are okay.
[FRIDA] Roi?
Jade?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[FRIDA GASPS]
- Wait. Where's Jade?
- Shh! Shh!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ROI BREATHING SHAKILY]
Wait. Roi, wait.
I'm going with you, right?
But first, tell me where
Jade is.
Where's my daughter?
- Would you like to see her?
- Yes, yes.
- Love?
- Yes.
Jade!
Jade, Mommy is here!
Where are you?
- Jade!
- Shh! Shh! Shh!
- Shh!
Roi, Jade isn't here.
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- Is the service boat ready?
- Yes.
You're leaving?
I knew it. You're leaving.
I was thinking,
if Leon went with Aunt Frida,
who was left
at their house?
Probably Luna.
Or maybe Justin.
We all know Justin.
He can be feisty.
I won't be surprised if
he went with Leon.
What's your point?
Luna might be alone.
But they have bodyguards,
remember?
It's still better if there are
other people aside from them.
You're worried about her?
You said it yourself we can't
just sit and do nothing.
I have to do something
and check on them.
Now you understand me when I
want to do something for Jade.
If you're going there,
I'm going too.
- Let's go.
- Me too.
I thought you just
wanted to wait.
[SCOFFS]
I won't be left alone here.
Come on, we're running
out of time.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
You said you'd take me
to Jade, but she's not here.
- Where is my daughter?!
- Love.
Love. Love, listen to me.
We don't need her anymore.
Once we get out
of here,
we'll have her siblings
pick her up.
No! That wasn't our agreement.
I want to see my daughter!
Where is Jade?!
- Love. Love.
- Where's Jade?
She's safe.
But you can't see her
anymore.
No! You didn't keep your word!
Where is Jade?!
Where is my daughter?!
Jade! Jade!
You're so stubborn!
Shh.
Love, shh.
Don't be stubborn, okay?
- Roi.
- Don't be stubborn.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Mom!
- Leon!
[ROI] I knew it!
- No.
- Love, you tricked me?
- You said you'd come with me.
Leon, just go.
Leave now, please.
I'll go with you.
Leon, please go.
Suit yourselves if you want
to delay things.
If you'll let Frida and I leave,
you might still find
Jade alive.
Roi, what did you do
to Jade?
What did you do
to my daughter?
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUFFLED GRUNTING]
[WHIMPERS]
[MUFFLED] Help!
- [MUFFLED SCREAMING]
- [THWACKING]
[MUFFLED] Help!
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
[MUFFLED SOBBING]
[JADE] Help!
[MUFFLED GASPING]
Help!
[FRIDA] What did you do
to my daughter?
[ROI] My love...
Explain it to them.
Tell them I'm innocent.
- Mom, no.
- Tell them.
- Please!
- [FRIDA] No.
- Don't do this, Mom.
Leon.
Our priority, remember?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
My love.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm coming with you.
- No--
- Huh?
They won't follow us.
I'm coming with you. Let's go.
Stay right there.
Please!
Don't you dare follow us!
Go!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [GRUNTS]
- [BLOW LANDS]
[LEON] Let her go!
[BOTH GROANING]
- Frida!
- Roi!
[GRUNTING]
[BOTH GROANING]
[BLOWS LAND]
[BLOW LANDS]
Roi!
Don't hurt my son!
Police!
[TENSE MUSIC SWELLS]
- Get up!
- [FRIDA] Leon!
Don't move!
Don't come any closer!
[LEON CHOKING]
Stay back.
[FRIDA] Roi!
Put your guns down
if you want to see Jade alive!
- Leon.
- Put them down!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
So? Has Leon replied?
Not yet.
Maybe we should stop
bothering him.
He'll update us
when something happens.
Oh God.
I hope nothing bad
happened to them.
Nothing's going to happen.
Okay?
Panicking won't help, Kiko.
Sorry, I'm just worried
about Jade.
We're all worried.
Maybe call Luna too?
So she knows we're
on the way.
[LINE BEEPING]
She's not answering.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
What the hell?!
[GUN COCKS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[KIKO] What's his problem?
Is that Bok?
That bastard!
It's Bok!
Gio!
If you want to see Jade alive,
let me go!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Fine!
[PANTING]
Put them down!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LEON GRUNTS]
Secure the area.
Come. Come...
Come on, Leon.
[KIKO BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BOK] Gio, get down here.
Let's settle this!
[KIKO BREATHING HEAVILY]
Get down.
Get down here, Gio!
Gio. Gio...
- Gio. Gio. Gio. Gio.
- [KIKO] Gio.
[MARTIN] Gio.
Gio!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Get down!
Gio.
[KIKO BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BOK] Get down!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Son, are you okay?
- The ambulance is on the way.
- Thank you.
Mom.
The ambulance is coming, okay?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PANTING]
[BOK] Get down!
- Gio.
- You should run.
- I'm the only one he's after.
- We're not leaving you!
We're sticking together.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Stop being stubborn.
One, two...
...three, run!
- [GUNSHOT]
- Go after them!
[GUNSHOTS]
You two take those two!
I'll go after Gio!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Come here!
Hey!
[MAN GRUNTING]
- Gio!
- [GUNSHOTS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm not after your money
anymore, Gio.
Just do it, Bok.
But don't drag my brothers
into this.
Bogs and the others
will take care of them.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THUDS]
[GROANING]
I'll kill you if anything
happens to them.
You're funny.
You think you can kill me?
Who's holding the gun here?
[GUNSHOT]
[BLOWS LAND]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
[BLOWS LAND]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[THUDS]
[BLOWS LAND]
[GRUNTS]
[HEAVY THUD]
[GROANING]
[COUGHS]
[ROI GROANING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROANING]
Frida!
Frida, help me!
Frida.
- [ROI PANTING]
- Cuff him.
Frida, help me!
- Frida!
- You're under arrest.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be used
against you in court.
Do you understand?
You don't understand me.
Frida... Frida's the only one
who understands me!
Frida!
[ROI PANTING]
Where did you take Jade Almazan?
Answer me!
Let me talk to Frida alone
before I tell you anything!
Go. Take him.
[ROI] Frida!
So what, we're not calling them?
Why is it taking so long?
This is so hard, not knowing
what's happening.
Did they find Roi?
Did they find Jade?
If we call, Justin,
we might ruin their plan.
- But what if...
- [SIGHS]
- ...something happened to Jade?
- Shh! No!
Don't even say that.
As long as they haven't said
anything,
nothing bad has happened
to our sister.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- Help!
- [THUDS]
[MUFFLED GASPING]
Help!
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
[JADE] Help!
[MUFFLED GASPING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[BLOWS LAND]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[BLOW LANDS]
[BLOWS LAND]
[GRUNTING]
You're still trying to run?
[BOTH GROANING]
[BLOW LANDS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[BLOWS LAND]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GROANING IN PAIN]
[GASPING]
[BLOWS LAND]
What? Let's take him
to the boss!
Wait! I'm not done yet!
[BLOWS LAND]
- [BLOWS LAND]
- [YELLING]
Kiko! Kiko, stand up!
Kiko! Kiko!
Can you still move?
Let's go!
- [BLOWS LAND]
- [MAN GRUNTS]
That's enough, Kiko!
We have to go back for Gio!
Kiko, come on!
Gio!
We have to find Gio!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BOK GRUNTS]
[GASPING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GRUNTS]
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS] Argh!
How does it feel
to be unlucky, Gio?
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
- [FLESH SQUELCHES]
[GIO GRUNTS IN PAIN] Agh!
[GRUNTING CONTINUES] Agh!
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
They were dead when I saw them!
Rot in jail, murderer!
I can tell you the truth
with my conscience clear!
[LEAVES RUSLTING]
Don't let go! Hold on tight!
Jade!
[MUFFLED WAIL]
Mom, we need to find Jade.
Did Roi tell you where she is?
Our entire team
is still searching for her.