[METAL GRINDING LOUDLY]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
I know you know where...
Tell me.
[PANTING]
I'd rather die
than tell you.
Tell me!
Where?
- [SCREAMS] Aah!
- Aah ! [THWACKS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- Mike! Mike!
- [GROANING]
Let's go!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
[MIKE SCREAMING]
- [OBJECTS CLATTER]
- [BODIES THUD]
- [GROANS]
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [KICKS LAND]
- [GROANING IN PAIN]
[SANDRO GRUNTING]
- [THWACKS]
- [WHIMPERS]
- [KICKS LAND]
- [GROANING IN PAIN]
[THWACKS]
Ah!
Hurry! He might get up!
Move! Come on!
[BOTH GROANING]
[PANTING]
[GASPS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SANDRO GRUNTING LOUDLY]
- [BLADE SWISHING]
- [GROANING]
- [FLESH SLICING]
- [YELPS] Ah!
[GRUNTING LOUDLY]
[KICK LANDS]
[BLADE SWISHING]
[GROANS IN PAIN]
[KICKS LAND]
[BODY THUDS]
- [GROANING]
- [OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROANING CONTINUES]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [BODY THUDS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[ENGINE RUMBLING, STOPS]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[PANTING]
Go! Go! Go! Go!
- Hurry!
- [MIKE GROANING]
Hurry!
[PANICKED BREATHING]
[GROANING]
- [BODY THUDS]
- Mike! Mike! Mike!
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GROANING IN PAIN]
- Come on!
Get up! I can't leave you.
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Come on! Hurry!
[LEAVES RUSTLING]
[BREATH QUIVERING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[GROANING IN PAIN]
[BOTH PANTING]
[GROANS]
I think we got away.
Yeah, I think so.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[YELLS]
Aah!
[BODY THUDS]
[CHOKING]
I know you know something.
Tell me!
[CHOKING]
Even if we both die, you're
not getting anything from me!
[BLOWS LAND]
[COUGHS]
[THWACKS]
[GRUNTS]
[COUGHING]
- [GRUNTING]
- [BLOWS LAND]
[THUDS]
[KICKS LAND]
GROANING LOUDLY]
[BODY THUDS]
[GRUNTS IN PAIN]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[GRUNTS]
Where's the golden egg?
It was right here.
- [YOUNG GIO] Hey! Kiko!
- [YOUNG MARTIN] Kiko!
- Martin! Gio!
- Oh.
- Did you guys find it?
- Negative, bro.
Nothing.
We haven't seen anything.
We're pretty far
from the hotel now.
Come on, let's move.
- Hey!
- Whoever gets there first!
Last one there
has poop in their butt!
- Race you!
- [GIGGLES]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Where do you think Papa
hid the Easter Egg?
Yeah...
Papa really made it hard
this year.
Probably,
it's somewhere in the hotel.
But where?
[YOUNG GIO] In the basement,
underneath.
Did you check there?
I don't wanna go there.
It's scary down there, Gio.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
Just kidding!
You're so annoying.
You're way too serious.
I'm not scared, okay?!
Only brave kids can find
the Easter Egg.
- I'm brave, okay!
- Yeah, right.
But can you beat us to it?
- Of course!
- Alright, come on. Hurry!
[LAUGHS]
Hurry!
- Pa! Pa!
- Pa!
So, did you find it?
We've gone everywhere, Pa.
But nothing.
You still haven't found it?
Come on, you guys.
Just be patient.
You'll find it eventually.
Just give us a clue, Pa,
please!
- Yeah, Pa.
- Please, Pa.
How are you gonna find it
if you keep asking
for clues?
- Come on, let's find it!
- That's not fair!
- You can do it!
- Yeah, sure.
We've gone really far, Pa.
[MIKE] Really?
How far did you go?
- Just... really far.
- [MIKE LAUGHS]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MIKE] Kids...
Are you enjoying your stay
at the hotel?
- Yes, Papa!
- Yes!
- And you, Kiko?
- Yeah, but...
But what?
It's just that...
when I think about...
how I'll have to go
home again... after summer.
It makes me sad.
After Holy Week,
school starts again.
You just don't want
to go to school.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
[MIKE]
Just remember, kids...
when you grow up,
you won't have to leave
right away.
You can stay here
as long as you want.
What if Mama
doesn't want us to?
If your mom doesn't want to?
You know...
when you grow up,
you'll be the ones deciding
what to do with your lives.
But I only have
one request.
What is it, Papa?
I hope...
you'll love each other
as brothers, okay?
Brothers should
love each other,
even if you have
different moms.
Hmm?
Look out for each other...
Take care of each other.
- Do you promise?
- I promise, Papa.
I promise.
Okay.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[BOAT ENGINE REVVING
IN THE DISTANCE]
Looks like your Uncle Freddie
is here.
Alright, fix yourselves up.
Hurry.
You look like a mess.
We'll look for the egg later.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[YOUNG JADE] Kiko! Have you
found the Easter Egg yet?
Not yet.
- Come on
- Come on!
Ma! Ma!
- Thank you, Monette. Raphie.
- Thank you.
- Hey, Luna, me next!
- What is it now?!
You know Leon? He wants to
go to high school in Manila.
Well, that's perfect.
Let's just put them
in the same school,
so they can be classmates too.
- Yes!
- Awesome!
[FRIDA] Hey!
Don't get too excited.
I still haven't agreed
to let you study in Manila.
[FEDERICO CHUCKLES]
[FEDERICO] Leon's grown up
so much, huh?
Mm-hmm. [CHUCKLES]
By the way,
how's that restaurant
you're planning to build
on the other island?
Well, I'm still thinking
about it.
[FEDERICO] But if you become
my business partner,
I'll push through with it.
Hm. Look!
Does everything really
have to include Mike?
I did it!
Mike's basically like
a brother to me.
You know, we share
a lot of things.
Whatever he likes,
I like too.
That's important in business.
[GLASSES CLINK]
Kiko, let's go back.
The Golden Egg might be there.
Come with me.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[YOUNG JADE]
What are we doing here?
[YOUNG KIKO]
The Easter Egg might be here.
Kiko, come on already!
Shh...
I'm looking for something.
Just follow me.
I don't think the Golden Egg
is here.
Come on!
Don't be scared.
There's two of us.
Just look around.
- [MOUSE SQUEAKS]
- [CAN CLANGING]
- [SCREAMS]
- [OBJECTS SHATTER]
Jade! That was just a rat!
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Why are your brothers not here?
It's your birthday.
I don't know.
I haven't seen them
for two years.
[MEN SHOUTING]
What's that?
Let's see what it is! Come on!
- [GRUNTS]
- That's enough!
Federico!
Stop it.
This is a problem between us.
Don't drag Michael into it!
Why shouldn't I?
You're both making a fool
out of me!
[MIKE] Believe me! We didn't
want it to happen either!
- Believe me!
- No!
You fooled me!
[FEDERICO] Since when?!
Answer me!
- [MIKE GRUNTS] Aah!
- That's enough!
Federico, stop it.
The kids will hear us.
Come on, let's go.
I'm begging you.
Let's leave.
I trusted you
more than a friend!
[HUFFING]
Federico, wait!
Jade, let's go!
Federico!
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Has he arrived?
Is that him?
- Oh.
- Kiko's here!
Oh. He's here. Kiko!
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Monette! Raphie!
[MONETTE] Come!
[RAPHIE] Is that him?
- [MONETTE] Yes.
- [RAPHIE] Monette.
Kiko!
Let me help you
with your things.
- My gosh.
- [KIKO] How are you?
Long time no see!
It has been five years.
I know. I'm glad you still
remember my brother.
He's all grown up now.
We already know that.
Here's the boat
going to Solara Island.
Your father has
been waiting for you there.
How's it going at the hotel?
Well, it's still the same.
It's still close.
It's still not operational.
Since the fire,
it hasn't been reopened yet.
I'm sure it'll feel different
because there are no people.
It's like it became
a haunted hotel.
No, it didn't.
- How's your trip?
- Sir, let's go!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[MONETTE] We're here!
[RAPHIE] This way.
[KIKO] Papa said we have
something important to discuss.
[RAPHIE] That's what he
told us, too.
He said his kids
are coming home.
Do you have any idea
what it is?
[MONETTE EXHALES HEAVILY]
He suddenly called us.
Even Raphie and I
were surprised.
But we'd be more surprised
if you
and your brothers reunite.
[KIKO] Have they arrived?
[RAPHIE] You're the first one
to arrive.
[SIGHS] Finally.
[RAPHIE] Sir's over there.
Pa.
Son.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
It's been a while
since I got my hands on these.
Perfect timing
for your brothers' arrival.
Do you remember, Kiko?
When you were kids,
we'd always hang out
during the summer.
I think this is the last photo
of us together.
It's been a long time,
hasn't it?
[MIKE GRUNTING]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[KIKO] Pa.
Why did you
ask us to come here?
What's the matter?
You said...
you have something
important to tell us.
[SIGHS]
Let's wait
for your brothers first.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Good morning, sir.
[EMPLOYEE]
Sir, sales keep dropping.
Chinese suppliers
are undercutting us online.
Almost half the price.
Plus free shipping.
Sir, instead of suffering
more loss,
- should we just...
- [MARTIN] Shut down?
Shut down?
Since when did you
become a coward, James?
We don't compete on price.
We compete by making
our competition irrelevant.
We pivot.
We turn our bookstores
into coffee shops.
We will be the new
hangout spot and creative hub.
A place where online shops
can't compete.
This company will not close
as long as I'm the one
running it.
Is that clear?
[JAMES] Yes, sir.
Get back to work.
[SOFT TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GIO WHISTLING]
[PHONE BUZZING]
Psh.
[GIO EXHALES DEEPLY]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Where's my money?
I'm going to pay you, Bok.
[SMACKS]
You want me to kill you,
don't you?
[BOK] Hmm?!
[GIO HUFFING]
If you kill me,
you'll never get
your money back.
I need my money, Gio.
You wouldn't want
my patience to run out!
Remember this.
If you still don't give me
my money back next time,
I'll kill you!
[GIO GRUNTS]
Thank you!
See you again next time!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIZZLING]
Oh, Is that pork belly?
Didn't the Doctor tell you
to take it easy on the fat?
Right, Grandma?
This is for you!
What are you blabbering about?
Isn't this your favorite?
Alright, let me eat now.
Hey, hey, hey!
You think I don't see
the wound on your lip, huh?
Hmmp!
- Where?
- Mm-hmm.
Who hit you this time?
It's nothing, Grandma.
Don't worry about it.
What would you do
without me, huh?
Come on, Grandma,
I'll die before you.
[GLASS THUDS]
I'm not kidding around. Want me
to hit you with a ladle?
Alright, alright,
let's just eat.
- Ouch, it's hot!
- Be careful!
This doesn't have any fat.
Oh my goodness!
I know that look.
How much?
Elena and I went to the salon
last week, remember?
- And then we went to--
- Grandma, just tell me.
Your dad messaged.
He wants you
to go to the hotel.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
I don't want to be involved
with Papa anymore.
Well, to be fair, you all
had different mothers...
That's why it's hard to bond.
Grandma, let's not talk
about that anymore.
I won't go there anymore.
I'm fine.
Rebranding?
Coffee shops? Creative hubs?
- Based on my projections...
- [CARLOS] Projections?
[CARLOS] You know what I see?
I only see a graph
that's going down.
And you want to borrow
a big amount of money...
just to turn it into a very
expensive hangout spot?
[PHONE BUZZING]
- I'll make it successful, Dad.
- [CARLOS] Enough!
You'll use my money, Martin.
And I make the decisions.
[FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
"PAPA: WHEN WILL
YOU COME HOME, SON?"
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC
PLAYING, FADES]
[MOMMYLA] I'm getting old.
When your mom died,
all I thought about was
me being here
to take care of you.
I forgot that
I'm actually getting old.
[MOMMYLA] You need to be
around someone.
They need you there.
And now he needs me?
Where was he when Mama died?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
He wasn't a good father,
grandma, and we both know it.
But still!
[SIGHS]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
I wonder what your brothers
look like now...
Who do you think is the most
handsome among you three?
[SCOFFS] Why are you even
asking, it's obviously me.
You're so full of yourself.
- Raphie?
- Hmm?
Does Papa still drink all day?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[RAPHIE] Hasn't your dad always
been a heavy drinker?
It only got worse
when the hotel closed.
But you know what,
we're also thinking
that Sir Michael might just
sell the whole property.
That could be the reason
why he called for you three.
Yeah, my mom and I
think so too.
If we had to split
our shares,
then I should take mine.
Splitting the money is easy,
but where will your dad live
if he loses the hotel?
- He could live in your place.
- [CHUCKLES]
Sure, he can sleep next
to Monette.
- [LAUGHS]
- Right?
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHESCA] What's up, bro?
Are you already rich?
- [GRUNTS]
- [REFRIGERATOR CLOSES]
Are you crazy? Of course not.
Come on, bro. I thought
you'd hit the jackpot.
[KIKO] How are all
the vegetables?
Do a good job there, you're the
only one helping Mama around.
Bro, you don't need
to remind me.
I got everything under control.
Besides...
you shouldn't be worrying
about the farm anymore.
Come on, man...
you're the heir now.
You'll inherit
everything there!
Hello!
Oh, shut up! [CHUCKLES]
By the way, mom said...
to give your dad a kiss
for her!
Hey, he might believe that!
He might fall in love
with me again!
I sure hope so.
What do you mean
you hope so?
- Mom likes the idea of it!
- [SCOFFS]
I was just joking, ma.
Just go with my dad.
You might have another chance.
[CHUCKLES] Well, alright now!
I'm going to sleep.
Give mom a kiss for me, okay?
Sleep?
Are you sure you
can sleep there, bro?
[SNEERS] You haven't been
there for a long time.
And...
I heard that place closed down,
and no one stayed there
for so long.
You never know, you might have
some unseen visitors there.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
You talk a lot,
I'm hanging up, bye.
[CHUCKLES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
What's that?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Who's there?
Kiko.
Uncle Federico.
[FEDERICO CHUCKLES]
Good evening, Uncle.
Good evening.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MIKE] Go back
to your room, Kiko.
Your uncle and I need
to talk about something.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I see your youngest
is already home.
Yes. I'm just waiting
for the other two.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's been months...
but no one's given birth yet.
Sandro is gone.
We already buried the bastard.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SIGHS]
We're safe.
Our whole family is safe.
We can finally carry out
the plans we've had.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
We no longer have any rivals
for the hidden treasure
in this hotel.
There's no turning
back now, Federico.
We already got what we wanted.
[FOREBODING MUSIC
CONTINUES, FADES]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAR DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Dad! Dad!
Thank you so much, Dad.
You made so many kids happy.
Thank you, Dad, for sponsoring
their painting sessions, huh?
- I'm so happy!
- That's good to hear.
You know, anything
for you, my princess.
Let me know if
you need anything.
Thank you, Dad.
You are the best dad
in the world. [SMOOCHES]
- Love you.
- I love you.
Jade, sit down.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Leon.
Dad.
Wow! That smells good.
Try this.
- New specialty, Luna?
- Yes.
Oh.
Mm!
It's really good, dear.
Thanks, Dad.
Dad, you said you have
something to tell us.
Well...
I just wanted
to tell you that, uh...
Michael and I...
We've reached an agreement.
Really?
Yeah.
But why?
I mean...
The last time we went
to the hotel was, like, what?
More than 10 years ago?
And now you're suddenly okay?
[LEON] Whatever the reason is,
what matters is
they're on good terms now.
Leon is right.
That said,
we will be having
a get-together at Hotel 88.
Just like the old times.
Exciting!
[CHUCKLING]
It's good with me.
When are we going?
[SMOOCHES]
Where were you?
I haven't seen you in days.
Justin...
Take a shower first.
Why?
Just go.
[SCOFFS]
I shall return.
Ready for a party.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
The world is healing,
don't you think?
Sir Michael and
Sir Frederico are talking again.
Right?
After a decade of them
being on bad terms,
What changed?
What happened?
You know,
let's stop overthinking.
Let's think of the menu
we'll have for Easter Sunday.
Because, like before,
the Almazans will be here.
- They're coming? Wait.
- Yes.
- Where is it?
- What are you looking for?
Oh, here it is.
I need to bring out
the big cauldron.
Cauldron? You're doing
too much.
Oh, come on.
I'm just excited, Monnette.
[MONETTE] You're so silly.
Isn't this too sudden?
What is?
Everything.
The...
reconciliation...
The announcement...
What needs to be announced?
Is there a problem if...
Michael and I are reconciling?
If that's true...
then no.
You know, more than anything...
that it's what I want.
I'm doing this for my kids.
That's what's important.
So...
What's the announcement?
Just wait for a few days.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[OBJECT RUSTLES]
W-Who's there?
Monette? Raphie?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Monette?
- Aah!
Wait! Wait! Wait, sir!
It's me, Raphie!
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
My gosh, Raphie!
What are you doing there?
I'm taking out the trash.
Why are you wearing a mask
while taking out the trash?
Why? Am I not allowed
to take care of my skin?
My gosh, sir.
Also, you shouldn't be out.
It's Good Friday.
God is dead.
It's not good to be out
late at night
so let's go.
- My gosh.
- I thought there was a thief.
Let's go, sir.
It's not safe out here.
Sir Kiko.
[RUSTLING]
Papa's still the same.
He'll welcome us
in his drunken state.
I'm here because he's going
to tell us something important.
It's probably
bout money, right?
- Get it out! Get it out!
- [CHOKES]
- Hey!
- [KIKO COUGHS]
Jade? I'm Kiko from Hotel 88.
The Almazans are here.
It's nice to see
the three of you again.
Just like before.
Aren't you going
to call your father?
Reconciliation...
Is there a problem if
Michael and I reconcile?
What happened?