Hello, Philippines!
And hello, world!
Alright! Welcome to Hotel 88!
Welcome, sir.
We only have one guest,
and you're suspecting him?
I wouldn't suspect him
if he wasn't trying
to open Papa's room.
The 50 million
is nowhere to be found
and the hotel owes the bank
money that you need to pay.
Papa agreed to give the Almazans
a share of this hotel for free?
That means he
was a generous friend.
So what?
Why would he shoot Uncle Fred
if he agreed to share the hotel
in the first place?
Where did you put
the money, huh?
We don't even know
he convinced Papa
to give him shares without
getting anything in return.
For sure Uncle Mike
had a reason to agree.
We need a general manager
to lead this hotel's operations.
We want things to be fair?
Let's vote on it.
There are four of them
and only three of us,
and you agreed to vote on it?
Are you sure
he'll take your side?
You shouldn't have agreed to it.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GIO] Aren't you worried?
Nope.
Jeez, Martin.
I'll say it again, okay?
There are four of them
and only three of us.
Leon will vote for me.
That's some intense
fighting spirit.
Are you sure
he'll take your side?
Our side.
He'll take our side.
Leon is my friend,
and I know him.
He wouldn't suggest
having a vote
if he wasn't going
to vote for me.
I don't know.
I still don't trust him.
I will be the GM of the hotel.
I'm better than Luna,
and running a business
is my strength.
So my friend
would vote for me.
[SCOFFS] I hope so.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Your brothers seem skeptical.
I can't blame them.
Don't worry, bro.
I've explained it to them.
I know you're
the best person for the job.
I know you.
I know your dedication
to these things.
You know, my siblings
are just worried.
Of course, they think
you'll vote for your sister.
She's your sister, after all.
You know the hotel
better than we do.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
I need this.
I know.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC FADES]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
Dad didn't give me
the opportunity
to save my business
in Manila.
I don't want to fail
with this hotel this time, Leon.
You want to show your stepfather
that you can do it
without his help?
I will do everything I can
to save the property
that our fathers left us.
And I know it
won't be easy.
But knowing you,
you'd never give up
no matter how hard it is.
Thank you for your trust, Leon.
Don't worry, bro.
Even though I'm busy with
the businesses Dad left behind,
I'll support you
with the help you need.
You have to be the GM.
Thank you.
[LUNA] Can we talk?
Nope.
Sell me your share.
Out of the three of you,
I know you're the one
who needs money the most.
Are you sure?
Why?
What do you know about me?
I know you.
You're practical.
[SCOFFS]
I'm practical?
You talk like we're close.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Why?
Are we close?
Gio, please.
This isn't the time.
When is the right time?
We'll both benefit
if you sell to me.
You only remember me when
it's convenient for you, huh?
You remember I exist
whenever you need me.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're right.
I need money.
But who said I want
to work with you?
Have some snacks.
Thank you, Monette, but you
really don't have to serve me.
[MONETTE]
Oh, please. It's okay.
I also gave your brothers
some drinks to cool down.
It seems seeing the Almazans
make their blood boil.
Here.
Oh.
Do they make your blood
boil now too?
[INHALES DEEPLY]
It's not like that.
I was just thinking
about my dad.
He and Uncle Fred were on good
terms before they died, right?
Yeah, but he was
angry when he left, wasn't he?
I was here.
Maybe he was just drunk
so you thought he was angry.
Possibly. Why?
Is something bothering you?
You see, Papa agreed to share
this hotel with Uncle Fred
without getting anything
in return.
Would you trust a friend
that much?
What's your point?
If you really
trusted each other,
would you kill each other?
So you think
they didn't kill each other?
Possibly.
What if they didn't?
Well, if that's the case,
someone else killed them.
Is that right?
I don't know, Monette.
But I still can't believe
they killed each other.
They've known each other
for years, so why now?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [WIND CHIMES CHIMING]
[LUNA]
Before we meet with them,
I want to have everything
in this memorized.
Luna.
You know I only want
what's best for you siblings.
[LUNA]
Of course, Ma.
Why?
Because, sweetheart,
if this partnership...
and running the hotel
is just going to cause problems,
it's okay if
you don't push yourselves.
It's okay if you choose
a quieter life.
Ma, we're used to
business stress.
I can handle this.
The real headache
is Uncle Mike's kids.
If I could just remove them
from their positions...
Don't say that.
But it's true, Ma.
Like,
do they have any misconduct
listed in this agreement?
Misconduct?
Theft.
Embezzlement of funds.
So we can strip them
of their ownership in the hotel.
Then that would be great.
It's just...
this might take a while, Ma.
Why?
I didn't expect...
there'd be complications
with the hotel Papa left behind.
So we're still working on it.
[LOUISE] Can you pause
for a while?
I mean...
So much has happened to you.
The bookstore closing...
Your father's death.
You need time
for yourself.
You haven't even had
the chance to grieve yet.
Martin, are you listening to me?
Yes, Ma.
I need to do this.
Son, we have a lawyer
who can act as
your representative there.
And the hotel
affairs can wait.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Come home first,
to your family.
No.
[LOUISE] No?
You don't want to come home?
I'll stay here for now, Ma.
I'll be fine.
[LOUISE]
Okay.
I'll let you be.
Just be safe.
Please?
Okay, Ma. Bye.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
It's my fault.
It's my fault they died.
[BREATH QUIVERS]
[BREATHING SHARPLY]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[MUSIC BECOMES DARK]
No!
Fred...
[PANICKED BREATHING]
Fred... Fred, no! No! No!
- Mama! Ma. Ma. Ma..
- No! [PANTING]
Are you okay?
You were having a nightmare.
You were calling their names.
Who?
Daddy and Uncle Mike.
Are you okay?
Go on, get some rest.
I'll follow in a bit.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Get some rest, Ma, okay?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES]
[RAPHIE HUMMING]
Good morning Philippines!
Good morning, Sir Jeff!
Sir Jeff?
[KNOCKING]
[MONETTE] What did he say?
Is he having breakfast?
He said to get
his breakfast ready.
He's not responding.
Maybe you're just
knocking too sweetly again.
[CLEARS THROAT, KNOCKS]
Good morning, Sir Jeff!
Breakfast is ready!
Still nothing.
Maybe Sir Jeff just
sleeps like a log.
Let's just leave him for now.
- [KNOCKING]
- [BOTH GIGGLING]
[CHAIR CREAKS]
This is really messed up!
Our dad gets killed,
they contributed nothing
to the hotel, and then what?
They're voting
on who gets to manage it.
From their POV,
Papa fired the first shot.
so they're furious too.
[MARTIN]
Don't worry.
I'll be the GM
(General Manager).
Oh, here we go again.
You really believe Leon?
That what? That Leon will
give his vote to Martin?
Yes!
That's a long shot.
Even if you're his friend,
your opponent is his sibling.
His own blood.
I trust Leon.
He knows how to honor a deal.
You're voting for me though,
right, Leon?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I know Martin's
your best friend.
But I'm your sister.
Luna.
If this were just
a simple family partnership,
I wouldn't want to be
the hotel's GM.
I'm doing this for Dad.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[LUNA]
For justice for his death.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FRIDA] Jade?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Jade, do you want to go with me
to your favorite bookstore?
[WATER RUSHING]
My siblings and I
are going to Hotel 88.
How about later?
We can go when you arrive home.
I just want us
to spend more time together.
- [PAINTBRUSH CLANGS]
- Well, I don't.
Jade.
Stop it, Mom.
What is this, huh? A bribe?
[FRIDA SIGHS]
No.
Can't I spend time
with my daughter?
I know what you did, Mom.
What did I do?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[JUSTIN] Jade!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Justin.
- You're rude now?
Why are you talking
to Mom like that?
Why? It's true!
Mom wasn't like this
when Dad was still alive!
When it mattered.
- Jade...
- I'll take care of this, Mom.
She just wants to spend time
with you!
You can't even accommodate that?
Why are you acting like that?!
Can't I say no?!
Don't reason
that you're like that
because you're grieving
over Dad.
Mom is also grieving,
but she's not rude.
- She's trying her best.
- [JADE] And it's too late!
[JUSTIN] What's wrong with you?!
[FRIDA SCOFFS]
You don't know anything.
- Are you crazy?!
- [LEON] What's with you?!
- It's Jade!
- That's enough!
Martin and the others
are waiting.
[FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
[LEON] Let's go!
[JUSTIN GRUNTS]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC SWELLS]
[LEON] You two have
to stop fighting.
- [JUSTIN] Tell that to Jade!
- [JADE] Wow!
[JUSTIN] There's something wrong
with her!
- So it's me again?!
- Shut up!
There's a voting
we have to deal with.
We're doing this for Dad.
Uncle Michael murdered Dad.
We should at least avenge him
through this.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Right, Leon?
[FOOTSTEPS]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Good day to us all.
How are you all doing?
For those of you
who don't know me,
I am Atty. Silvestre.
And across me is
Atty. De Castro.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Let's get this started,
Attorney.
So we could get it over with.
[SILVESTRE] Okay.
So, let's get down to business.
We are here today
to agree
on who will be
the general manager of Hotel 88.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SILVESTRE] Two names
have been nominated
for this position.
First, Martin Madrigal.
Who is one of the heirs
of Mr. Michael Fernandez.
Second, Ms. Luna Almazan.
One of the legal heirs
of Mr. Federico Almazan
[SILVESTRE] It has been decided
to have our vote face-to- face.
Let's start?
Francis Endaya.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I vote for Martin.
[SILVESTRE] One vote
for Mr. Madrigal.
Ms. Jade Almazan.
I vote for Luna.
[SILVESTRE] One vote
for Mr. Madrigal,
and one vote for Ms. Almazan.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mr. Gio Cabrera.
Martin.
[SILVESTRE]
Two votes for Mr. Madrigal
and one vote for Ms. Almazan.
Justin Almazan.
Of course,
I vote for Luna.
[SILVESTRE] So we have
two votes for Mr. Madrigal
and two votes for
Ms. Almazan.
- Martin Madrigal.
- Luna Almazan.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Three votes for
Mr. Madrigal
and three votes for
Ms. Almazan.
And so...
Mr. Leon Almazan,
Your vote will determine
who will be
the general manager of Hotel 88.
[STIRRING MUSING CONTINUES]
[SILVESTRE] Mr. Leon.
- [BIRDS CHIRPING]
- [PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Mr. Leon Almazan.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Luna.
Luna Almazan.
Yes!
Woo-hoo!
- Thank you, Leon.
- [JADE] Congratulations, Luna.
[ATTY. SILVESTRE] Okay.
So, we have three votes
for Mr. Madrigal,
and four votes for Ms. Almazan.
Our general manager
for Hotel 88
is Ms. Luna Almazan.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, Jade.
[SNICKERS] I told you, guys.
The new GM of Hotel 88, people!
[SNICKERS]
Oh.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Luna going to be our boss?
Housekeeping or security guard?
What the hell
is wrong with you?!
Is that Leon?
I don't want us
to resent each other.
Blood is thicker than water.
- E-Edward--
- You chose Edward to promote?
I have to tilt the power
back to us.
Are you crazy, Bok?
I told you I'll pay you,
didn't I?
Hurry up, Gio.
Don't wait for me
to go back to your grandma.