Aah!
[MOTORCYCLE HONKING]
[SQUEALS, GRUNTS]
Why do you have this?
- I saw it--
- This is ours!
We should protect each other,
and that includes Mom.
I'm sorry if I was the reason
they fought.
Does Martin know about this?
It's Kiko. He was the one
who found the earring.
We shouldn't let the police
know about this, okay?
Was this Mrs. Almazan?
It was recorded
from a car's dashcam
on the day Michael Fernandez
and Federico Almazan died.
- The earring?
- That's ours.
- We apologize because--
- Because I lost it.
The earring is mine.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I misplaced it near the place
where Dad died.
What were you doing there?
Am I not allowed to visit?
Why not at the cemetery
where your dad is buried?
What do you even care?
I wanted to go where my
Dad had last stepped in.
Do I seriously have to ask
your permission for that, Gio?
Gio.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
So, are we good?
Are things clear to you now?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Or maybe you still have
something to ask?
[LEON] I hope this will no
longer cause any issues at work.
[MARTIN] Of course.
Let's make it official then.
Welcome to Hotel 88.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
I'll see you around.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
So, the earring belongs to Luna?
Am I the only one
who doesn't believe
what those siblings said?
They had different reactions.
Justin acts off. He just goes
along with his sister.
Jade looked at Luna strangely.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
I just can't explain it.
All I know is that...
they are obviously
hiding something.
I will try to talk to Jade.
She might be able to tell me.
Do you think it's that easy?
Remember, she's an Almazan.
She'll protect her family
no matter what.
There's nothing wrong
with trying, right?
So, you guys
take care of the hotel.
I'll find out the truth
through Jade.
Okay.
So, you're going to use Jade?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[WAVES LAPPING, SPLASHING]
- [BATS SCREECHING]
- [BIRDS CHIRPING]
- [SHOVEL DIGGING]
- [OWL HOOTING]
[SLOW HEAVY FOOTSTEPS]
- [EERIE NOISE]
- [UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUN CLANKS]
- [BICYCLE WHEELS ROLLING]
- [GROUND SHAKING, CRUMBLING]
I won't use her.
Besides, we're not
that kind of people.
Jade and I used to be close.
We were friends
when we were kids.
I'll try to talk to her nicely.
[MARTIN HUFFS]
Okay.
If you think you can convince
her to speak the truth...
do it.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
I have a project in mind.
Let's see if Luna
can still say no.
Speaking of...
[LUNA] Everyone,
this is Edward Arellano.
He will help us
promote Hotel 88.
Edward, they're
Uncle Michael's children.
They are also co-owners
of Hotel 88.
- The Operations Manager...
- Martin Madrigal.
Of course.
We know each other.
[LUNA] Right.
He also reached out to you.
- Good to see you here.
- [EDWARD] Good to see you.
Gio...
Gio is in charge of sales.
Edward.
[GIO HUFFS]
Mm.
Kiko is in charge
of housekeeping,
including food and beverages.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
It's all good.
Welcome to Hotel 88.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
So, can we go back to work?
- Jade.
- [JADE] Mm?
Tour me around.
Let's go.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JADE] Excuse me.
[SIGHS IN RELIEF] Good thing
I was able to convince Edward.
It's a great help that he's
a family friend of ours.
[SLOW CLAPPING]
Impressive!
You're so great, Luna.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Martin...
Next time, inform me if you have
anything to do for the hotel.
- So, none of us gets surprised.
- [MARTIN SCOFFS]
Of course.
You are the GM after all.
I really need
to keep you updated.
[CLICKS MOUTH] Okay.
Thanks!
[KIKO] Jade.
- Kiko.
- [KIKO] Can I talk to you?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Once... Once you're done.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Let's go?
[WAVES LAPPING, SPLASHING]
Do you know that Edward?
Yes.
Actually, I was the one
who thought of hiring Edward
to boost the bookings
of the hotel.
But Luna didn't tell me
that she's long known him.
[CLEARS THROAT]
It's obvious.
That family's seriously
playing tricks against us.
They're even desperate
to get Edward first.
That Luna is really
something else, huh?
Goodness,
she's always been like that.
What do you know about Luna?
Never mind.
D-Do you guys have a past?
Yeah.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
What?!
And her demeanor?
She's not the Luna
I've known before.
Perhaps I should remind her
of who she truly is.
W-What do you mean?
Just think of this
as my way of helping you.
You want to be the GM,
don't you?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
You've seen all the rooms.
Luna said you can stay
in any of the rooms.
Just inform--
I'm okay with
the executive rooms.
We just need
additional services.
Cheaper rooms get booked fast.
The bigger rooms are the ones
that need to be promoted.
Okay. Copy. Noted.
The restaurant also serves
Western and local cuisines.
Why did you suddenly
leave me at the café?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Daily happy hour runs
from 3 to 5 p.m. for drinks.
That's fifty percent,
so it'll help promote the hotel.
Luna said you can also order
anything on the menu.
On the house.
Okay.
Copy.
Noted.
[SIGHS]
Jade, are you okay?
I've covered everything,
haven't I?
We're done.
Jade, you're not answering
my question.
Oh, wait. Jade.
Jade.
Yes.
Yes, I'm okay.
Let's continue our lunch here.
I don't have time for that.
As far as I know,
the tour ended early.
So, you still have time.
I'll repeat.
Just because there's more time
doesn't mean
it should be wasted.
We haven't even discussed
the social media plan yet.
You call that wasting time?
Lunch at the restaurant?
No.
What's wrong
with a music festival?
Big setup, big budget,
big overhead!
The hotel has just been opened.
[LUNA] We can't handle that.
[JUSTIN] Luna's right.
My suggestion--
[LUNA] We're not even done
with Edward's promotion yet.
[MARTIN] And so?
We're just going to rely
on one form of promotion?
[GIO] It's not just hotel guests
bringing money in.
When we have events like this,
we can generate income
from those checked in elsewhere.
Like a music festival!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Leon.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Say something?
[MARTIN SIGHS SHARPLY]
Yes. It needs a lot of money,
but the returns are high.
Revenue, hotel promotion...
partnerships we can use
in the future.
- Luna, can you hear them?
- I said no.
- Let's consider it, Luna.
- Leon!
They're right.
Lots of returns.
It's easier to sell tickets
because there are more tourists
during a festival
compared to the off-season.
I can push this event.
You?
Can you?
Are you kidding me?
But if the hotel loses money,
it's your fault,
and I'll make you pay for it!
[CHAIR THUDS, SCRAPES]
[FOOTSTEPS RECEDING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE RINGING]
Yo, bro.
Yeah. How are you?
No, no, no, no.
I'm not busy.
No, no, no.
What's up?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No problem, yeah. What's up?
[SIGHS SHARPLY]
Jade!
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
- Jade!
- [EDWARD SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
- [JADE HUFFS]
- [HEAVY FOOTSTEPS]
Jade!
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[KIKO] Jade?
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hello.
Did you really have
to say hello?
Can you please leave me alone?
Kiko, just go! [HUFFS]
I just said hello.
What's wrong with that?
- Hi.
- Please, Kiko.
Isn't it obvious
I don't want to talk to you?
Is this still about the earring?
Jade, I didn't know
it was yours.
[HUFFS]
Leave me alone, please!
[SIGHS SHARPLY]
Jade, we need
to talk about this.
- You know we need to.
- No, I don't want to!
It won't take long.
Kiko, can you please stop?!
[HUFFING]
[SOFT MUSIC FADING]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh, sir, drinks?
Did you see Jade?
Ah, Miss Jade?
She was-- I didn't see her.
But I can offer you--
Okay, one iced
Americano, please.
And if you see Jade,
tell her I'm here, okay?
Okay, sir. One iced
Americano coming up.
And I'll tell Miss Jade
you're looking for her.
Right away, sir.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
This guy is also
built different...
Miss Jade, wherever you are,
stay right there, don't show up.
[CRYING]
Things were better
back then, right?
When we were kids?
We were still friends under
this table.
But now...
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Jade...
I know we can't just
be friends again...
But we don't have
to fight, right?
We
We're not kids anymore.
A lot has changed.
Especially about our families.
We grew up, and our fathers
died, that's it, right?
Do you really not know anything?
Why? What else don't I know
about our families?
Please just leave me alone!
Don't follow me!
God!
- [EDWARD] What's...
- [JADE SIGHS]
going on...
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EDWARD] Jade?
[Edward] Jade! Jade!
Jade, you went missing again!
And what were you doing
under the table?
What? What else do you need?
I already did everything
you asked!
I toured you around, accompanied
you, what else do you need?
what's more?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
- Jade...
- Jade!
Everyone keeps calling my name!
Everyone keeps telling me
what to do but no one
listens to what I have to say!
Jade, what's the problem?
What do you want?
What I want...
is for everyone
to leave me alone.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Isn't that case already closed?
I just want to know
if my theory is possible.
That Mr. Michael Fernandez and
and Mr. Federico Almazan
didn't kill each other.
Sir, I stand by what
I wrote in that report.
Even if you
read it over and over again,
it won't change.
- Acevera.
- Oh?
A new case?
Nope. I just asked about the
Almazan and Fernandez case.
There is a problem with
the autopsy report, isn't there?
- Why?
- Study it carefully.
That pathogologists accepts
bribes and changes the report.
I don't know why that bastard
isn't fired yet.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[LIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
This thing?
You're still the same
with the hand sanitizer.
You still don't
want to get your hands dirty?
Here.
[LIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Get home safely.
You know, I feel guilty.
What?
Do you need to pee, bro?
Guilty!
What is it?
Can you hear me?
[CHESKA] Hello?
I can't understand you.
Try finding
a better signal first.
Hello?
This one?
Is this okay now?
Can you hear me now? Hello?
Hello!
- [KIKO] Hello?
- Chubby! You're chubby!
Hey! [CHUCKLES]
I heard that, okay?
[CHUCKLES]
What did you say?
You need to pee?
I said I feel guilty!
Guilty?
Well, as you should.
You really teased that person.
You even followed her
under the table.
That's childish, bro.
Well, we used
to do that all the time
when we were kids.
Oh, right!
Jade was your crush, right?
[CHESKA TEASING]
Childhood crush.
That was a long time ago.
[CHESKA] Well,
maybe that's something
you should start with first.
Try being friends again first.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHESKA] Hello?
Hello, bro?
Did you disappear?
No, I'm still here.
I'm just thinking about
what she told me
that I really don't know
anything about my family.
It feels like she's not
telling me something.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Maybe it's not really a secret.
Well, you were bothered too
when your Papa Mike died.
Maybe it's just
the same for her?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[MARTIN] Pa...
I know we have a lot
of unfinished business.
We were never given
a chance to really talk.
You asked me back then
if I had already forgiven you...
I didn't answer you.
Because I was still in pain
back then.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
It wasn't easy.
For someone whose only wish...
...was to be loved
by his father.
- [SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [THUNDER RUMBLING]
I had to fight battles alone.
Because you weren't there, Pa.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
But now, if you ask me again...
I can finally say,
"Yes, I've forgiven you."
And I'm sorry it took me
this long.
Don't you worry, Papa.
I'm finding a way
so that only your children
will manage the hotel
you left for us.
I know how important
this is to you.
I won't let you down.
I promise.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THUNDER ROARING]
[RAIN POURING]
- [MUSIC TURNS ROMANTIC]
- [RAIN POURING]
["SILONG KA MUNA"
BY BRYAN CHONG PLAYING]
- [RAIN POURING]
- [THUNDER ROARS]
["SILONG KA MUNA" CONTINUES]
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
[RAIN POURING]
["SILONG KA MUNA" CONTINUES]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Who are you waiting for
to come out there?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
That family again?
Does this have anything to do
with the dashcam footage?
Yes.
But you said
it was circumstantial.
From what I'm seeing
in you right now...
you want to reopen
that family's case.
[SIGHS]
I need a reason to do that.
And that's what you're doing.
You're looking for a reason.
[EXHALES]
It's exhausting, but I get you.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MARINA] People like us...
We won't stop, especially when
we know something's wrong.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I just need solid evidence.
Here they are.
Sir Henri! Good morning.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
If you worry about
other people's problems,
aren't you being nosy?
- Jade!
Where's Edward?
It's just business.
Good job. Keep it up.
Good job to your heart, too.
She blocked me?
Just focus on the music fest.
If it becomes successful,
it'll be the hotel's success.
It'll be a way to settle things
within your family.
- [BLOW LANDS]
- Ah!
Next time, find someone else
you can trick to bail you out!
You want it cheap?
Then do it for free!
What's your problem, Gio?!