I don't know anything
about Hotel 88.
Don't worry.
You'll work with someone.
Who?
Are you sure we're getting
Edward to promote the hotel?
We need Edward
so I can execute my plan
of kicking the brothers
out of Hotel 88.
Finders keepers, remember?
So, it should be mine.
Give it to me
if you don't like it.
I'll see if I like it.
But I'm gonna keep this.
There's a gun but no papers.
Just a gun?
Why? Should there be
something else?
It's my deposit.
I know it's not all of it,
but I'll still pay you back.
- We need to talk.
- About what?
Where's the guest's money?
Yeah, I took it.
Return the money
before the guest gets back!
That's enough!
What if word gets out
that there's a thief in here?
Please, stop it. Calm down.
Are you out of your mind, Gio?
Did you even read the fine print
on the partnership agreement?
[SCOFFS]
Obviously, not!
It's written on there
in black and white!
"If any of the partners engage
in activities
that compromise the hotel's
reputation or operations,
the other family will take away
our management authority!"
That's enough!
Please.
Enough? No, Kiko.
He needs to understand this.
Because one mistake...
is all it takes.
You know how they think.
Legally, they will take this all
away from us.
Stop being so selfish.
Then, I'm selfish!
I'd rather die being selfish,
than put my grandma's life
at risk!
You have the money to pay off
people who threaten your family.
But me...
I have nothing.
If I don't pay them back,
they'd come back for Mommyla.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
She's my only family, Martin.
I can't lose her.
So, you used the money
to pay off your debts?
Not yet.
I was thinking about it.
But it's all here.
I didn't use it at all!
There you go!
Choke yourself with it!
I don't care what you think.
But I won't commit a crime
just to save my grandma's life.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Luna.
Yes, I'm here.
I'm waiting for Edward.
Okay. Bye.
[SIGHS]
Excuse me?
Have you told Edward
that I'm here?
I've been waiting here
for 30 minutes.
Yes, ma'am.
He's almost done at the gym.
He asks you to wait for him.
Seriously?
He knows what time I'm coming
and he went to the gym?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYS]
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Did you really sell it?
I got around 600,000 out of it.
How did you even
get that deep in debt?
You worked so hard for that car,
and you just used it
to pay off a debt?
Well, I got this left.
See?
Gio...
Don't worry, Mommyla.
I can save up for another one.
I just made sure that Bok
won't come back for you.
[SIGHS] Okay.
I love you, dear.
- I love, love, love you.
- Love you.
It's just a car. Mm-mm.
Next time, I'll buy two.
Excuse me?
Is Edward ready yet?
- Oh, there he is.
- Sorry.
Why?
Sorry for being late?
[SNORTS]
Sorry, I didn't get to dress up.
[SCOFFS] So arrogant...
Whatev-- Let's just go.
Has Luna told you that you'll
tour me around Hotel 88?
I need to see and experience it
before I could
promote your hotel.
I don't just post stuff that...
[CHUCKLES]
...you know, I don't like.
Yes, yes, I know that.
Can we just get this over with?
Gosh.
Okay, but we need to go
somewhere first.
Where?
Come on. Just follow me.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYS]
[EDWARD] Jade!
[KIKO] Gio.
Here, I'll give you 5,000.
No, Kiko. Keep it.
Come on, it's yours.
It's for Mommyla, not you.
[SCOFFS]
And tell that person
that I won't
just give them 5,000.
I can give them 1,000
every month.
Sure, if you want us both
to get beaten up.
No, but seriously,
I can give you more.
And where will you
get the money?
I don't know.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Tell me.
Where did the debt
actually come from?
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
Aside from selling condos,
I have other side jobs.
I buy and sell cars.
I got a sports car.
It was a handsome one.
As sleek as it gets.
It's all set up and everything.
They wanted me to sell it.
And that's when
my bad luck started.
So, what happened?
It got stolen.
Didn't you report it?
I did.
But you know it's not that easy.
They never found it.
And so...
That person wants you
to pay it back?
Yeah.
Exactly that.
But where the hell
would I get 2 million?
Even if I work
all kinds of jobs,
I'd never have that much money.
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
If you're hungry,
there's a restaurant
in Hotel 88.
I want to eat here.
It's okay.
We still have
a lot of time, right?
But that doesn't mean
we should waste it.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
I'll make sure not
to waste your time, Jade.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- Welcome back, sir.
- Hi!
One buttered salmon,
garden salad,
and iced americano, please.
What about you, Jade?
Order anything you want.
No.
No? Not even coffee,
drinks? Anything?
I want to go back to Hotel 88.
One vegetarian quesadilla.
It's good.
Any additional, sir?
That's all. Thank you.
Do you know that our classmate,
Abigail, owns this place?
Anyway...
Do you remember
when she laughed at me
because I couldn't tie
my own shoes?
She said it was because
of my chubby tummy.
Well, guess what?
She approached me
a few years ago
to ask for business advice
for this place.
She couldn't recognize me
at all.
She couldn't believe that
the kid she used to bully...
is very different now.
You're right.
- You're different now.
- [CHUCKLES]
I know, right?
[PHONE CHIMES]
[LUNA] How are you and Edward?
[JADE CLEARS THROAT]
Wait, where are you going?
Ah. To the restroom.
Wanna tag along?
[SNORTS]
Why would I come with you
to the restroom?
[CHILL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS] Do we really
have to search here?
It's better to be sure.
We might catch someone
doing something suspicious.
I'm going to the communities
with CCTV cameras.
Along the direction Jeff took.
The guest of Hotel 88.
Okay.
It's good to know where he went
aside from the hotel.
Jeff has a criminal record.
He has charges
for theft and assault.
I'm pretty sure
he's gone into hiding now.
What's important is for us
to find out where he is.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
She's been gone for 30 minutes.
Sir, do you need anything?
No. I'm just gonna check in
with my friend.
The girl you came in with?
She already left.
No, she just went
to the restroom.
The toilet upstairs
isn't working, sir.
But the one here on the side
is okay.
Are you sure she left?
She left me?
[WAITRESS] Yes, sir.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes, ma'am. I was the one
you were talking to
about the earrings
I already have you check it.
Okay. I'm on my way there.
You deserve to be
left alone in that cafe.
Gosh, you're so arrogant!
[HUFFS]
Let's earn some money today.
[SCREAMS]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING,
HORN HONKS]
[screams]
Ow!
[GRUNTS] Aah.
- Ow!
- Aah!
- Ow.
- Ah!
[GRUNTS]
Are you okay?
[KIKO GRUNTS]
Does it hurt anywhere?
You again?!
[GRUNTS]
Are you my stalker?!
Stalker?!
[KIKO] Aah.
[JADE] Ow.
Oh, shocks.
[GRUNTS]
Are you okay?
Does it hurt anywhere?
Don't touch me.
[EARRING CLINKS]
It's still okay.
My god! You almost
broke my earring!
If it has a scratch,
its value will depreciate.
What are you so mad about?
I know that earring.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
I have a bad feeling about this.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Why do you have this?
- I saw it--
- This is ours!
There are only a few of them
in the Philippines,
and that's ours!
Are you really sure?
Why? Did you go to the area
where our fathers died?
That's where I found it.
I went to the area
where our fathers died.
Don't tell me you went there
and left that by accident?
[JADE] Wow. I...
This looks so nice, Dad.
Is it for your anniversary?
Yes.
There are only a few of them
in the Philippines.
So I want your mom
to have one, too.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey! Jade, that's mine!
[KIKO] Hey!
Hey, that's enough!
- What's your problem?
- Oh...
I think he thought
we were fighting.
I'm sorry, sorry.
I saw you kind of
hitting each other, so...
We're good.
Martin was actually helping me.
It's all good now, okay?
I already called the bank
so they can assist you
when you cash the check.
Thank you so much, Martin.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING,
THEN FADES]
[LUNA] I was thinking,
we should involve everyone.
[FRIDA]
Leon and Justin too.
[LUNA]
Yeah, both of them.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, there she is.
Jade, come here.
Perfect timing.
- Can you help us?
- Join us.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
Mom?
Uh...
Did you ask Jade
to go to your room?
Why?
I saw her go in there.
Is something wrong?
Nothing, sweetheart.
I'll check on her.
Just keep going.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Nice, Gio!
At least
you've got money now.
Your grandma won't be
bothered anymore.
Sorry I couldn't help you.
I was going to pawn some
earrings, but they went missing.
You have expensive earrings?
- You're joking.
- Where?
No, not mine.
I just found them.
I was walking by the beach,
near where Papa died.
Oh?
Where are they now?
Well...
Jade suddenly took them.
She said those belonged to them.
She said she was sure.
You know,
I was actually wondering
why she looked so shocked.
Scared?
Kind of.
It's like
they're hiding something.
But if those were theirs,
does that mean...
they went there?
I don't know.
But weren't we together
that day?
We all went together
when the police said
something bad happened.
But whose are they?
Jade's? Luna's?
Or their mom's?
I don't know.
All Jade told me was
that they're theirs.
I don't know, but I think
we should tell the police.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[MUSIC BECOMES TENDER]
[BREATH QUIVERS]
[TENDER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
A month before Dad died.
You were already
planning to leave us?
[FRIDA]
It's not what you think.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
But this?
This...
[JADE SOBBING SOFTLY]
You were applying
for residency in Spain!
What is this?!
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
You did all this
before Dad died?!
You planned all of this?!
Jade, no.
It wasn't like that.
Mom, please tell me the truth.
I have so many questions!
I feel like I'm going crazy
thinking about it!
Were you going to leave Dad?
Were you going to leave us?
Were you going to go with
Uncle Mike?!
No, sweetheart.
Mike has nothing
to do with this--
I know about the affair, Mom!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
No, what are you saying?
Jade...
- What--
- [JADE] But I kept it a secret.
I kept it a secret,
and I didn't tell
any of my siblings.
[SOBBING]
I was angry.
Yes!
But I wanted to protect you
because I don't want my siblings
to look at you
in a different way.
Why?
Because they love you so much.
Dear...
Jade.
That's not the only thing
you've kept from me, Mom.
[SNIFFLING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[JADE SOBS]
The other pair...
Where is it?
I don't know...
- Where?
- I... I misplaced it.
[JADE] Where is it?!
I don't know.
Where is it?
Is this it?
It is, right?
It's this, right?!
Yes...
You didn't misplace it, Mom.
You left it near the area
where Dad died.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[JADE] Why were you there?
What were you doing there, Ma?
When we went to Hotel 88,
what did you say?
You said you
were going somewhere.
Did you go there?
Were you there
where Dad died?
What were you doing there, Mom?!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
It was recorded
from a car's dash cam
on the day Michael Fernandez
and Federico Almazan died.
500 meters away
from the location.
You know my loyalty
lies with you.
And we're all just fishermen
waiting for the chance
to cap something good.
Why don't you just
tell the truth?!
Don't do anything that will
put our family at risk.
And that includes Mom.