Kiko's in charge
of housekeeping.
- Housekeeping?
- [BARKS MOCKINGLY]
- You've got some nerve!
- What are you even saying?!
We'll beat them to it.
We'll make them leave.
We're stronger than them.
- Okay, next, Jade will lead
- Hey!
- our next stretch.
- Edward.
What are you doing?
Past is past.
Bosses, we've got a problem.
Monette and I are worried
about our guest.
They haven't come out yet.
We can report it now.
Nobody's reporting this
to the police.
Are you crazy?
Don't let my grandma see you.
I said I'd pay you, right?
I'll head out first, Luna.
- See you--
- Yeah, yeah.
Go now.
I'll follow later.
Alright.
Take care, okay?
If you need daily updates
on hotel activities,
I'll just email you.
And I'll update you
if I've talked to Edward.
Where's Gio going?
Don't mind him.
He's always leaving.
During work hours?
Why?
You need him for something?
- I'll call him.
- No, no.
It's fine. It's fine.
Thank you.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
- So we're good?
- Mm-hmm. Yes.
Thank you.
Just send it to my email.
Sure.
[MARTIN BREATHES DEEPLY]
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Here.
That's an advance payment.
I shouldn't even be paying you
since I didn't sell the car.
But it got stolen
while it was with you, right?
So you're still paying for that.
I know it's not enough.
But I'll give the rest.
So leave my grandma alone.
If you don't hurry, I might
just date your grandma.
You ****!
[LAUGHS]
- Go ahead, do it!
- What?
Do it.
Your debt's just getting bigger.
Hope karma hits you,
you bastard.
Karma?
Who's the one
broke right now?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARTIN BREATHES SOFTLY]
[EXHALES SHARPLY, CLEARS THROAT]
[LINE RINGING]
Dad.
When were you
planning to tell me
you brought Ronald in
as an investor in your hotel?
I was going to tell you.
You just beat me to it.
What do you even know
about running a hotel?
You couldn't even keep
a simple bookstore afloat.
And now a hotel?
I will make this work.
That's what you said before
about that business in Manila
you wasted.
That's because you never
gave me a chance to save it.
Martin, there's nothing
you can do about that hotel.
You know what? Fine.
Since you're so confident,
go ahead.
Show me what you've got.
But don't you ever come
back to me asking for help.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'll prove to you
exactly what I'm capable of.
Oh, I know you.
What do you need?
Sir, we'd like
to report something.
Oh, Kiko.
Ah, Sir Henry.
I'll take this.
Uh...
How can I help you?
We'd like to report something.
One of our guests
hasn't come back yet.
We're getting worried.
Alright, you can file a blotter.
There's no mandatory
waiting time.
See? That's better, right?
Yes, sir.
We'll file the report.
Dela Paz?
Yes?
Assist them.
They have a missing guest.
Okay.
Ah, Raphie...
Is it okay if
you go with Ma'am?
You handled the check-in,
so you might be able
to answer more questions.
Sure!
This way.
- Thank you.
- So, ma'am, here are the...
Do you have something
to say, Kiko?
Yes, sir.
Since I'm already here...
I wanted to ask something.
About what?
About my father's death.
Let's talk inside.
You're asking if it's possible
your father
and Frederico Almazan
didn't kill each other?
I was just thinking...
Maybe someone else killed them?
Maybe, sir.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
But based on the autopsy report
and the witness statement,
that's what led to their deaths.
Someone saw them arguing.
And the gun
belonged to your father.
Is that so, sir?
I just really don't understand
how they could've
done that to each other.
They were friends.
They were so close, Papa even
gave Uncle Fred a share
in Hotel 88,
no strings attached.
No strings attached?
Sir, it's nothing.
Please don't think about it.
You're right. There's an autopsy
and there's a witness.
So don't worry about it, sir.
- Sorry for the trouble.
- [KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[DOOR OPENS]
I'm done.
Sir, thank you again
for your help.
Alright. Thank you, sir.
We'll go now.
If the guest isn't back
by tomorrow, call me.
- Okay, sir. Thank you again.
- Thank you, sir.
- Let's go.
- Coming!
Do you need to pee?
[RAPHIE GRUNTS]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
It's Edward...
Justin, Luna,
I'm sorry I'm late.
- It's okay.
- It's alright, bro.
My sister and I didn't
wait long.
Really?
Anyways...
Luna, is this about what
we talked about?
The one no one is supposed
to know?
No, Edward.
This is about
the hotel's promotion.
That was you?
Our secretary told me,
someone called
about Hotel 88's promotion.
And they said they want
to hire me.
Are you sure?
I know this wasn't part of what
we talked about,
but I need you for this.
Okay, so...
what about the other person
who called me?
[SCOFFS] Just forget about them.
Just talk to my sister instead.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay, then.
Tell me.
[LUNA] It's simple.
Like I said earlier, we need
a promo for Hotel 88.
Since you have
so many followers,
one post from you
would be a huge help.
- [SNAPS FINGERS]
- Piece of cake.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
But...
I don't know anything
about Hotel 88.
Don't worry,
someone will be joining you.
Who?
- Me.
- Jade.
Jade is in marketing.
It's Jade who should be
doing the work.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'll work with Jade.
[CHUCKLES]
- [JADE GROANS] Ouch!
- [LUNA] Here, use this.
Luna.
Will Edward really
promote the hotel?
Yes. And since
you're in marketing...
- I'll leave him to you, okay?
- [GROANS]
Is there a problem?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Nothing at all.
- Right there.
- Let's work on this, Jade.
We need Edward so I can
carry out my plan
to get those siblings
out of Hotel 88.
Huh? How?
Just trust me.
Just stick to the plan.
Please?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SIGHS] Fine.
- [CHUCKLES]
- [JADE] Ouch! Luna, it hurts!
- [LUNA GUSHES]
- Ouch! There, there.
- Sorry, sorry.
Please, I can't reach
this part here.
- Where did you get that from?
- Stretching.
Stretching? Why is your
whole back hurting?
[SIGHS]
- [THUD]
- Oh.
[HISSES]
[SIGHS]
[GROANS SLIGHTLY]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[EDWARD] You ran away
because you're
embarrassed of me
for what you did
to me at the--
[JADE] Really?
You really want to talk
about that here?
[EDWARD] But just so you know...
[JADE] Ouch!
[EDWARD] Past is past.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
["PANGHABANG IKAW"
BY DARREN PLAYING]
["PANGHABANG IKAW" CONTINUES]
Move back for a bit.
[JADE CHUCKLES]
You knew it was me right away?
Because you smell like
sour baby powder.
[CHUCKLES] Hey!
Hey, that's too much! No way!
Wait, what are you even doing?
- Wait, wait.
- What's with the candy?
- Huh?
- [JAR CLICKING]
[CHUCKLES]
- [LID CLICKS]
- [CHUCKLES] Hey.
[LAUGHING]
Are you done?
Ready.
You're ready? Can I sit now?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHAIR SLIDES]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EDWARD] For you.
Thank you.
[CHUCKLES]
[JADE] You did this?
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
What is this?
[EDWARD] Jade, sorry.
I don't know how to paint.
"Will you be my prom date?"
But you understand, right?
["PANGHABANG IKAW"
BY DARREN PLAYING]
[CHUCKLES]
Yes, Eddybear.
So, what's your answer?
Yes!
I said it's a yes!
Of course it's you!
[CHUCKLING]
- [EDWARD CLEARS THROAT]
- Wait, are all of these yours?
Why do you have more than I do?
Well, red is your
favorite color, right?
So I just chose what you like.
You're so sweet.
Thank you! [CHUCKLES]
[DISTANT STUDENT CHATTER]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[JADE CLEARS THROAT]
Uh...
I need to go now,
I still have something to do.
I'll get going.
Where are you going?
I need to go, Edward.
Thank you.
[EDWARD CLEARS THROAT]
[JADE] Hi!
Sorry... Sorry, I'm late.
[CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WOMAN] Hey!
Let's take a picture.
Uhm, excuse me?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[WOMAN] Sure, let's go.
[LINE RINGING]
[EDWARD] Dad...
Jade isn't here yet,
but the program
is about to start.
Alright, Dad,
I'll just wait for her here.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DISTANT LAUGHTER]
[FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
"Will you be my prom date?"
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Did you really only see that?
That was really all.
That's also what
I told the police.
Two men arrived...
and they got into a fight.
When I went inside my house,
I heard gunshots.
When I came out, the two men
were already lying
on the ground.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
That's also what
Sir Henri told me.
I'm sorry, boy...
but that's all I can do
for your father.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Ah, ma'am.
There's nothing.
Are you sure?
Did you check every corner
of the car?
Yes, ma'am. I really didn't see
any jewelry there.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SIGHS]
- But...
...if you'd like,
I can check again.
Yes, please.
Keep checking.
[LEON] Mom?
[FRIDA] Leon.
Are you having Roi
look for something?
Oh, it's...
It's nothing.
Just a small thing.
Nothing to worry about.
Where were you? At the hotel?
Ah.
Uh, no, Mom. Uh...
I just had something
to take care of.
- I'll go to my room.
- Okay. Sure.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CROW CAWS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC BECOMES SUSPENSEFUL]
[RAPHIE] Really? Is it true?
Yes! I even had it checked
at the pawnshop.
They said it's expensive.
Well then,
you should've pawned it.
Hey, why would I pawn it?
It's not mine.
Oh, I thought it was yours.
No.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[RAPHIE] So what are you
planning to do with it?
Are you going to return it?
Finders keepers, right?
- Just give it to me.
- Hey!
Give it to me
if you don't want it.
[KIKO] I'll feel things
out first.
This is mine, okay?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARTIN] Just handle
the matters here.
I've got an important
meeting so
just update me, okay?
[KIKO] Okay.
[MARTIN] Sir, Kiko will be
taking care of you.
Okay.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Mr. Madrigal.
Hi. You can just call me Martin.
Yes, I didn't expect you'd come.
I just wanted to pitch to you
to get you to promote our hotel.
It's all right.
You'll just say yes right away?
I haven't even--
Yes, I've talked to
Luna about it.
Did I hear it right?
You've talked... to Luna?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHUCKLES] Yes, it's Luna.
It's not easy
to reject her because
the Almazans are
friends of our family.
Okay.
Is there... a problem?
[MARTIN] No, no! Of course not.
There's probably just
some miscommunication.
But I'm sorry if
I've bothered you.
- No worries.
- I'll get going then.
[EDWARD] Take care.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Dela Paz.
There's a gun but
there's no papers.
That's already questionable.
There's only a gun?
Why? Is there something else
that should be here?
[KIKO STUTTERS]
No, sir. I just thought
there's something else there.
Okay, we'll include this
in our report.
But we still need
to check this gun.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PLASTIC CRINKLING]
- Martin.
- What?
Can I give you an update,
or you're in a bad mood?
Come on, tell me already.
The police have left.
They found a gun
in Jeff's possession.
They said
it has no legal papers.
Does it have anything to do
with his disappearance?
I don't know.
I don't know. But, Martin...
I've seen that gun before, too.
- But...
- But what?
Kiko, tell me!
It actually came with money,
bundled in one-thousand bills.
That much?
Yes, but they're all gone.
What if the guest came back
without us knowing?
I wish it were that simple.
[SIGHS SHARPLY] But have it
checked anyway, okay?
Check which staff came in,
just to be safe.
Our hotel's reputation
might be ruined.
But only Gio knew about that.
What? What did you say?
I mean, I was with Monette
in the room.
She didn't see the money.
But Gio did.
B-But I don't want
to assume anything bad about it.
But he'd always say
he needed money.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARTIN] He's here.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MARTIN] Let's talk!
About what?
It's about money.
What money?
The guest's money.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- One mistake...
- Martin.
Legally, they will take this
all away from us!
How are you and Edward?
Gosh, you're so full
of yourself!
Ah! Aah!
Goodness, you almost broke
my earring!
I know that.
Which one of them?
Jade, Luna, or their mother?
But I think we need
to report this to the police.
Something feels wrong.
[TENSE MUSIC SWELLS]
[GASPS]
[MUSIC FADING]