Mike is like a brother to me.
What he wants, I want too.
That's important in business.
I trusted you
more than a friend!
[SCREAMS]
[HITS]
I know you know something.
Just say it!
Even if we kill each other...
you still won't get
anything from me!
- [GRUNTS]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [SCREAMS]
- [THUDS]
- [LEAVES RUSTLE]
- We're safe now,
our whole family is safe.
We don't have
any rivals anymore
for the hidden treasure
in this hotel.
You said you have something
important to tell us.
Later, when your
two siblings arrive.
- [PHONE CHIMES]
- Your father sent a message.
He's asking you
to come to the hotel.
He's not a good father,
Mommyla.
We both know that.
We'll be having a get-together
at Hotel 88.
It feels just like before.
The last time
we went to the hotel
was more than ten years ago?
And now everything's okay?
What matters is that
they're getting along now.
[THWACK]
I'm surprised you came.
You haven't come home
for years.
And now you're finally
visiting your father?
I just want to find out
what's going on.
Aren't you curious?
Papa and Uncle Fred
suddenly made up.
I don't ask Papa about him
and Uncle Mike, but...
[THWACK]
You know...
Peace is good, right?
- Yes.
- [SIGHS]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Alright, I'll leave you here
for now.
I'm going to the market
and picking someone up.
There are restaurants
around here, but...
since you might be
saving money,
just do some
window shopping first, okay?
Bye-bye!
- Take care! [CLEARS THROAT]
- Bye! Take care!
Miss, how much is one bibingka?
Uhm, it's 3 for 100 pesos,
or 35 pesos each.
- The 35 pesos.
- Okay.
- Here, sir.
- Here's my payment.
Hmm!
[JADE] Paint whatever
makes you happy.
Okay?
["PAANO KUNG TAYO NA LANG"
BY ANGELA KEN PLAYING]
CONTINUES]
[CHOKES]
[COUGHS]
[COUGHING, CHOKING]
[KIKO COUGHING]
Oh my god!
Oh my god! Oh my god!
Sir?
Sir! Sir-- [SQUEALS]
- [COUGHING]
- Sir, I'll help you!
- I'll help you, spit it out!
- [COUGHING]
- Spit it out, sir!
Spit it out! [GRUNTS]
[COUGHING]
- Sir, are you o-okay?
- [COUGHING]
Do you need to go
to the hospital?
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
["PAANO KUNG TAYO NA LANG"
CONTINUES]
Jade?!
You know me?
Yes! It's me, Kiko!
- Kiko?
- Kiko from Hotel 88.
["PAANO KUNG TAYO NA LANG"
CONTINUES]
- [CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY] Ah...
- How are you?
I'm okay.
Actually, um...
I'm kind of in a hurry.
Bye.
["PAANO KUNG TAYO NA LANG"
CONTINUES]
You're in charge here, okay?
[RAPHIE] Sir Gio!
Uh, h-hello.
- Are you hotel staff?
- Uh, yes.
I'm Raphie, sir.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Raprap?
- Uh...
Raprap in the past,
Raphie in the present.
Very present!
I have two bags,
make sure nothing
gets left behind.
Okay, sir.
Where's the service?
We're all riding together
with Miss Monette and Sir Kiko
back to Isla Solara, sir.
Isn't there a welcome drink?
It's hot.
Uh, we're not at the
actual hotel yet, sir, but...
over there!
We can get some there.
Shall we get some drinks?
- Is it far?
- Oh, the basket.
[CHILL MUSIC PLAYING]
- How far is it?
- It's just right there, sir.
Gio! [CHUCKLES SLIGHTLY]
Gio!
How are you?
Uh bro, I'm okay, okay.
[KIKO] Sorry.
Sorry.
Martin is also coming here,
Raphie said.
He might already be there.
There! There he is!
[CLEARS THROAT]
Martin!
How are you?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
My children!
Oh! We finally see
each other again.
- Pa.
- Oh!
[CHUCKLES]
He's drunk again.
Hmm!
Oh, Gio.
Tuna! Your favorite.
Come on, eat!
- Go on, eat now!
- Come on.
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
- Sorry, excuse me.
- [CHAIR SLIDES]
I'm not really feeling well.
I'll be in my room
just in case.
Oh!
Come on, eat now!
- Let's celebrate!
- I'm still full.
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
Pa.
Wait a second.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Why did I even come?
[SIGHS]
Same question.
After all these years,
Papa hasn't changed a bit.
He still greets us drunk.
I'm just here because there's
something important to discuss.
It's probably
about money, right?
[EXHALES]
Let's go back.
I shouldn't have come.
Yeah, maybe.
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
But whatever the reason
you're here today...
You, Martin,
and you too, Gio,
you're both already here.
So let's go back,
please, and be with Papa.
[SIGHS]
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BOTTLE THUDS]
[MUSIC FADES]
[SIGHS]
Why did I expect something
different was going to happen?
Can you believe it,
after all this time,
they ended up falling out?
You know, those brothers
used to be so close and happy.
They got along even though
they had different mothers.
And they even had
their childhood friends,
the Almazans, right?
It's only the first day.
Doesn't they say
the world is healing?
Maybe it's just normal
to be like that at first.
Healing, my foot.
Get moving.
They'll be here any minute.
- We have to get changed.
- Oh, right.
It's so early in the morning.
Come on, Gio.
Please help me.
- Just get this.
- [GIO] Look how dirty that is.
Come on.
Thank you.
[KIKO] This one, too.
Kiko, all this stuff
is covered in dust.
Come on, please.
I swear, it's just these.
What are you doing?
- I have no idea with this guy.
- [KIKO] There it is!
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Whoa, it's heavy.
[STRAINING] Oops.
- This one's yours, right?
- Is that mine?
Yeah, look.
And this is Gio's.
Does it still work?
Let me see.
- Is it going to work?
- I don't know.
This is silly.
I kept them there.
[MUSIC FADES]
I always check on them.
I told myself,
when Martin and Gio come visit,
they'll have bikes
they can use.
But what if Kiko...
Anyway, you've grown up now.
You won't be able to use
those bikes anymore.
They're worn down.
You stopped coming home.
You stopped visiting.
Why is that?
It's just...
we've been busy, Pa.
Do you really want
to know why, Pa?
Martin.
He needs to know the truth.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYS]
It's you.
You're toxic.
Your drinking,
your being an
irresponsible father...
There are so many reasons
we stopped coming home.
What are the reasons you don't
come home anymore?
Tell me.
I'll listen. I have time.
What have I done?
[CLATTERS]
[GIO] Stop it.
Pa, is this what you want?
Is this why you
asked us to come?
That's what you want?
A blame game?
This is wasting my time.
I'm leaving.
Hold on.
I know I've done a lot
to hurt you.
I've failed you
in so many ways.
But that's why
I asked you here.
So we can make things right.
So we can talk about
these shortcomings.
Let's rebuild our family.
Even this hotel.
Let's bring it back
to how it used to be.
Let's start over.
I want us to run
this hotel together.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SIGHS]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BOTTLE THUDS]
[MUSIC BECOMES CURIOUS]
[CURIOUS MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
[MUSIC BECOMES UNSETTLING]
[KEYS JINGLE]
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TIRES SCRAPE]
- [ENGINE REVS]
- [TIRES SCREECH]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINE REVS]
Ma?
Let's go?
Um... [STAMMERS]
Alright.
Alright, go ahead.
Bring your siblings.
Your father and I will follow.
I think he went out.
Oh? Okay.
See you.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hello. What's up?
Kiko, let me do that!
- I'll be here a little longer.
- It's okay, Monette.
They'll be here any minute.
Fine, I'll make it up to you.
When I get home,
let's play golf.
Who were you with
last time?
- Monette?
- Yeah?
Isn't Papa coming out yet?
Oh, he left in a rush earlier.
He seemed upset.
But he'll come back.
He won't be gone for too long.
You should sort things out
with your brothers.
You seem to be living
in different worlds.
- [MARTIN] Okay.
- The Almazans are here.
[MARTIN]
Take care. I have to go.
[LEON] What's up?
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC BECOMES UNEASY]
[MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
[MIKE] How do you expect me
to believe a liar like you?
Our agreement
was crystal clear.
We agreed that...
[INAUDIBLE]
[INDISTINCT ARGUMENT]
I didn't betray
this friendship.
- You did!
- Me?!
[TENSE MUSIC STING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Point the gun at me!
[MUSIC FADES]
[LUNA]
Mama told us to go ahead.
[RAPHIE]
Sir Gio, drinks?
- [MONETTE] Here's the food.
- [KIKO] Let me get that.
Oh, okay.
Where's Uncle Michael?
Uh, he'll probably
be here soon.
I haven't heard from him.
[MARTIN] I don't know.
- [RAPHIE] Sir...
- [MARTIN] He'll be here.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARTIN] It's been so long
since we last got together.
- [LUNA] Ten years, actually.
- [MARTIN] Ten years?
Nothing's changed.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Um...
Have you been teaching painting
to kids for a long time?
[CLEARS THROAT]
Uh...
Yes.
It's an outreach program
Daddy and I created.
Oh.
Do you want this?
No, it's okay. I'm full.
Thanks.
- [GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [BIRDS CHIRP]
[LEON] We haven't seen
each other in ten years.
That's long.
[MARTIN]
But we still look the same.
We haven't changed a bit.
- Juice?
- We were so young.
All of us were so little.
No, I'm good. Thank you.
- It would be a waste.
- I'm not thirsty.
- [LEON]...every Easter.
- It tastes good.
But it's nice to see
the three of you again.
Feels like...
the old days.
All of us together...
here at the hotel.
[MUSIC FADES]
Aren't you going to
call your father?
I'm starving.
Uh, I'll check.
He might be here already.
Wait a minute.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYS]
- Uh...
- [OFFICER] Sir's gone, ma'am.
What?
[GASPS]
What happened?!
[TENSE MUSIC STING]
[MONETTE WAILS]
No!
[MONETTE CRIES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SIREN WAILING
- [FRIDA] No! No! No!
Sir, sir!
You're not allowed here!
- [FRIDA] No!
- Stop right there, ma'am!
Ma'am! Stop right there.
- [CRYING]
- [SIREN WAILING]
No!
- [CRYING]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
Fred!
[CRYING]
- [SIREN WAILING]
- [CRYING, WAILING]
[SCREAMING, WAILING]
- [CRYING]
- [FRIDA] No! No!
[FRIDA BREATHES HEAVILY]
Fred...
[CRYING]
- Wait!
- Papa!
[WAILING] Papa!
- Papa--
- [BAWLING, CRYING]
Pa! [WAILING]
- [CRYING, BAWLING]
- [SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[BAWLING]
Papa! [WAILS]
- [SKY RUMBLING]
- [CRYING, BAWLING]
We're asking politely,
all the family members need
to step aside first.
- [KIKO] No!
- Sorry.
Please, go ahead.
I'm sorry.
[CRIES, SOBS]
- [SKY RUMBLING]
- [SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BAWLING] Pa!
[SOBS]
Why did you leave us?!
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [CRYING, SOBBING]
- [SKY RUMBLING]
[CRYING, WHIMPERING]
I don't want to!
I don't want to,
Papa!
Mrs. Almazan, we're sorry.
We have to do our work first.
- [SOBS]
- Please.
[OFFICER] Sorry.
It's just our work.
- [RAIN POURING]
- [CRYING]
- [SKY RUMBLING, RAIN POURING]
- [BAWLING]
Daddy! No! No!
Dad!
Please.
Sorry, it's just work.
You're not allowed here.
Sir, sir!
- Miss, please!
- [SCREAMS]
- [STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [WAILING]
Sir, please.
[CRYING]
[CRYING, SOBBING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SKY RUMBLING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNIFFLES]
It's supposed to be
your reconciliation dinner.
But this is what happened.
Why were they together?
They even got to meet earlier.
And they didn't even tell you?
Ma! Why?
[INHALES SHARPLY]
I don't know.
[SOBS]
This shouldn't have
happened to Dad.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Right?
Mom?
[SNIFFLES]
That's why we'll do...
we'll do everything...
for the truth.
- [EXHALES SHARPLY]
- [MUSIC TURNS DRAMATIC]
We won't stop...
until someone has paid
for what happened to Dad.
- [SOBBING] Brother.
- It's okay. I'm right here.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WHIMPERS]
[SOBBING]
- [GUNSHOT]
- [GRUNTS]
The investigation has also
become faster because
of the strong testimony
from the witness.
So what?
Can't you show some concern?
No! That's not true!
That was self-defense!
There's no reason for me to
stay here anymore without him!
We'll do everything
for the truth.
We won't stop until someone has
paid for what happened to Dad.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]