- Hi, sissy!
- Oh!
I'm Sari!
Sir Martin's assistant.
Assistant...
This is Trixie. My sister.
- This is my sister, Cheska.
- Bro!
- Excuse me.
- Sorry.
- The earring...
- Jade.
It's not Luna's.
It's Mom's.
Do you think Aunt Frida
had something to do
with their deaths?
I'm sure they got something
to do with what happened to me.
Mrs. Almazan,
where were you
when Michael Fernandez
and Frederico Almazan died?
You have no right to accuse
my mother.
We know about the earring.
I'll only speak
in the presence of my lawyer.
I'm begging you.
Please, just leave.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[SIGHS]
Dear.
Your birthday is ruined
because of me.
I'm so sorry.
[JUSTIN]
No, of course not, Mom.
I'm glad to spend time
with you guys.
I've told you everything.
I'm not keeping anything
from you.
You believe me, right?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes, Ma.
Ma, you don't have
to explain yourself again.
[JUSTIN] Let's go, Mom.
I'll take you to your room.
Get some rest.
Okay.
[FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
Luna.
[EXHALES]
The question is,
how did the cops find out
about the earring?
[EXHALES]
I'm leaving.
Keep an eye on Mom.
[FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GLASS CLANKS]
[FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Alright.
Slowly.
Be sure to check the wiring.
There might be a short circuit.
I don't want any problems
on the day of the event.
Yes, sir.
Guys, be careful.
Is this all set?
What?
Did Sir Henri message already?
Not yet.
What happened there?
Have you talked to Jade?
Not yet.
But you're okay now?
Yes.
And you're right.
This is justice for Papa
and Uncle Fred.
So this is the only
right thing to do.
They better get ready
for their lies.
It's getting obvious.
Where are they?
They left early, right?
[SCOFFS]
It actually feels weird.
None of them are here.
No grumpy faces.
It just feels so nice to
have the hotel to ourselves,
even if it's just
for one day.
Feels good, right?
Just chill.
No annoying people.
Yes, Lord!
This is the life, Lord.
[CHUCKLES]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
You want some
real chill?
- Game?
- Come on.
Let's do it.
- You're the slow one, bro!
- I'm already ahead of you!
- Hurry up!
- Hey, Martin!
- What?
- Come on already!
- What's up, bro?
- [LAUGHS]
- You got nervous!
- You're blocking the way!
- Move it!
- You're all so slow!
- Come on!
- Hey!
Faster, faster, faster!
What?
You guys are so slow!
Hey!
Martin,
you're so slow!
All you do is complain!
What?
You thought I was still
the same guy, didn't you?
What? No way, bro!
You can't beat me now!
- What's up? Hey!
- Oh.
Here it comes!
- Goodbye!
- Hey!
[GRUNTS]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Is Frida hiding something?
Is she protecting someone?
Michael and Federico have
had bad blood for a long time.
No one knows why.
Then suddenly,
they made up.
They even became partners
in Hotel 88.
If they really
killed each other,
that means
they fought again.
But what could Frida possibly
have to do with all that?
That's the question
we need to answer.
Or maybe...
she's protecting someone?
Or maybe she really
is involved in the mess.
If my suspicion
turns out to be true,
what would be
Mrs. Almazan's motive?
What could two men
possibly fight about...
...that involves a woman?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
His hair was long.
About this long.
He had a sharp nose.
His eyes,
just average, but fierce.
Slim, but...
His face was long.
[PENCIL SCRIBBLING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Like this, sir?
That's the one.
Sir, who is he?
No one.
We never met.
I didn't avail
of your services.
- Do we understand each other?
- Yes, sir.
[JADE] Dad!
Dad, so many kids had fun.
Thank you, Dad, for sponsoring
their painting sessions.
I'm so happy!
That's good to hear.
You know anything for you,
my princess.
[CHUCKLES] Thank you, Dad.
You're the best
dad in the world! [SMOOCHES]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[JADE] It's been one month...
since dad died...
And you already have
plans to leave us?
[FRIDA] Jade, no.
That's not the case.
Are you going to leave us?!
Are you going with Uncle Mike?!
No, Jade... [INHALES SHARPLY]
- This has nothing--
- I know about the affair, Mom!
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
[FRIDA] Your uncle and I
are not having an affair.
[JADE CRYING] I saw you!
I saw you when I was a kid!
I saw you!
Why don't you just
tell the truth?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[OMINOUS TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[FRIDA SIGHS]
[SIGHS SHARPLY]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Mom had nothing to do with
Uncle Michael and Dad's deaths.
That is what I choose
to believe.
I don't want our mother
to go to jail, Jade.
And do you think...
that I want that to happen?
Do you really think
I want mom to go to jail?
I don't know, Jade.
I don't know what you want.
I want the truth, Luna.
[LUNA] The truth?
The truth is,
Uncle Michael killed our dad.
What was the reason?
Nobody knows why!
Do you want me to bring
them back to life
so they can answer
your question?
Luna, you know
what I'm talking about.
So, even if mom explained it,
you still think she's the reason
why they killed each other,
is that it, Jade?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay.
Why did the police
go here earlier?
Luna, I know where
you're getting at.
Just say it.
Did you report it
to the police?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Not to the police, Luna.
I told it to Kiko.
I told him that it was
Mom's earring, not yours.
Why did you do that?
Because I'm tired
of all the lies, Luna!
Because you don't want to
believe the truth.
The truth? You also lied!
You told them the earring
was yours, even if it wasn't!
I'm just trying to
protect our family, Jade.
You have nothing to hide if Mom
isn't doing anything wrong.
Fine!
Let's assume what
you're saying is true.
Dad's already dead, Jade.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Can't you forgive our mother?
Don't tell me you're planning
to accuse her
of something even
worse than that?
I don't know, Luna.
Then, tell me!
Tell me, what do I have to do
to get you to stop?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC
CONTINUES, SWELLS]
Nothing.
Jade...
But maybe I am the problem.
I can't keep my mouth shut.
That's why I'll find
the solution.
[JADE SIGHS SHARPLY]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE DINGS]
[WATER DRIPPING]
What are you doing?
Just ask someone
to fix that tomorrow.
And just let it drip all night?
Can you hand me the wrench?
The wrench, Justin.
[LEON GRUNTS]
[THUDS]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[LEON GRUNTS]
This is what we should be doing.
Working together.
We're the only men left here.
It's up to us
to protect our family.
This is what Dad wanted too.
That's why...
you should get your life
together, Justin.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CHESCA] Dude, what if I
feature your father's death
in my vlog?
It would make good content!
Now you want to use
my father?
Who knows? I might be
able to help you.
I mean, I might uncover
something you didn't know.
Stop with the nonsense,
will you?
- Come on, dude!
- Knock it off, Cheska.
What? Are you going to do it
here in the hotel?
Then that'll scare off
our guests.
But the murders didn't
happen here, did it?
I'll go to the crime scene.
- You have a point.
- See?
My idea's great.
Now give me some money
so I can get started.
Well, your channel doesn't
have any viewers,
so go for it.
You meanie.
- [CLEARS THROAT]
- [PHONE CHIMES]
[JADE] Let's meet up later.
Don't tell anyone.
What? Who was it?
Nothing. Just a spam text.
Yeah, right.
I know you're lying.
Your nostrils are flaring.
- Who was it?
- I said it's nothing.
"Spam."
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Luna?
Is that you?
Who is that?
[EERIE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Roy.
What are you doing there?
[EERIE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ma'am, I thought
you were inside.
Uh...
I'm just going to give
this to you because
the maid said...
you didn't want to eat.
Old people say that...
bananas help...
relax the body.
It'll help you sleep better.
I thought about
what happened earlier...
I thought you might need it.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Alright. Thank you, Roy.
You can go home now.
All right, ma'am.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
Is she joking with me?
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Hey!
- Shh! Shh!
- [MUFFLED SPEAKING]
I need to know everything
about Uncle Mike.
Why do you look like that?
I don't want anyone
to see us.
Do you really think
you won't be recognized?
You're wearing shades at night.
Will we talk, or will you keep
talking about my clothes.
Fine. We'll talk.
But first of all,
I just want to tell
you that--
That what?
That you told your siblings
about the earring?
And they called the police,
is that it?
How did you know that?
If I were you, I would do
the same.
Hmm. You're not mad?
I'm not angry.
But I wasn't happy either.
I understand you.
But that doesn't mean
what you did was right.
We're still talking
about my family.
Sorry.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
That's okay.
Just make it up to me.
How?
I'm sure you've been wondering
why Uncle Mike and my dad
killed each other,
because I'm wondering too.
That's why you'll help me
find out the truth.
Well, that's
exactly what I want.
- But, i don't--
- Do you remember
when I told the you
it was my mom's earring?
Mom said she and Dad
had a fight
before Uncle Mike picked her up.
That's when
she left the earring.
Your parents were fighting? Why?
My dad accused her of having an
affair with your dad.
What?!
You're so loud!
[CURIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
And you believe that?
[SIGHS] I don't know, Kiko.
I don't know! That's why
I need your help
because I'm going crazy
thinking about it!
What?
Will you help me or not?
[CURIOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
There are three of us siblings,
but we have different mothers.
But with Papa,
you can't really deny that--
He's a womanizer?
No, he's...
Uhm...
He has a big...
...heart.
That's why he has so much love
to give to different women.
Okay.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Looks like there's
no one here anymore.
You know, Papa isn't here either
to defend himself.
So you believe it now?
That our parents had an affair?
Not really.
Then what did I see?
So that was nothing?
I just imagined it?
Okay fine, let's say
we did find something out.
And let's assume that what
you're saying is actually true.
But Jade, what does that change?
What does that have to do
with Papa's death?
I don't know, Kiko.
Don't tell me
you're thinking your mother
killed your father so she and
my father could be together?
So that...
they could finally be free
to love each other,
but then something went wrong,
so Papa got involved?
- Kiko...
- Are you serious?!
I don't know, Kiko!
I really don't know!
That's why I need your help
to find out the truth!
So right now, tell me,
yes or no?
Will you help me?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
If they find out about this,
they're going to get mad.
We're talking about
my mother here, okay?
And we're investigating
my father too.
So just make a promise.
- We'll make a dance trend.
- Hey, Jade!
- Are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Almost everything here
on the island belongs to us.
Except for the Hotel 88.
Edward!
This is the sea!
There are no rules here!
Let's hold the meeting here.
I am Justin Almazan
at your service.
Oh, whatever.
In three days, Sari will resign.
How did they find out
that you were here?
What are you hiding?
Are you really that scared
that the truth might come out?
If there really is a folder,
then where would it go?
The four of us
should stay united.
We can't fall apart.
But there are only three
of us now.
So where is Jade?