[CHOKES] Jade? It's Kiko!
- Kiko?
- Kiko from Hotel 88.
You haven't been
coming home anymore.
Why is that?
Because you're toxic.
You're an
irresponsible drunk.
That's why I asked you
to come here, kids.
So we can fix this.
Even this hotel.
Let's restore it.
What happened?!
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
Pa!
Dad! [SOBS]
Dad!
- Fred!
- You can't come near.
[SOBBING]
This shouldn't have
happened to Dad.
We won't stop...
until someone pays for
what happened to Dad.
[SOBBING]
Are you going to the morgue?
No.
What's the point?
The police are already there.
Papa is dead!
I know.
So what am I supposed to do?
Go visit him.
Show that you care!
Why?
Will it make a difference?
[HUFFS] Wow.
You guys are unbelievable!
What? You can't even
show a little concern?
[GIO] The last time I saw Papa,
I was just a kid.
When my mother died
we lost contact after that.
So there's no reason
for me to stay
now that he's gone.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What, are you leaving too?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SIGHS]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, why are you back already?
You should've told me
you were coming home.
I haven't cooked yet.
What happened?
How did it go?
Papa's gone.
What?
He was found dead.
They still don't know why.
Uh, but...
W-Why are you here?
Shouldn't you be there?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SLAMS TABLE]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[YOUNG GIO] Grandma?
Did Papa not come?
Did he not come
to Mama's funeral?
No, sweetie.
No one saw him at the church...
or at the cemetery.
How could Papa do this?
Mama is already gone,
and he still didn't come!
[SOBBING]
Grandma's here, sweetie.
I'm not going to leave you.
I promise, I won't leave you.
[SNIFFLING, WHIMPERING]
Papa is a bad person.
I don't want him anymore.
I don't want him anymore!
I don't have
any parents anymore!
[YOUNG GIO SOBBING]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SNIFFLES]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Sir.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LINE RINGING]
Pa.
What did you do to my office?
I sold the bookstore
to GS Malls.
You didn't even tell me
before you did that?
[CARLOS] It's a
business decision, Martin.
Nothing personal.
[MUSIC TURNS MOROSE]
[MIKE] What exactly happened?
[YOUNG MARTIN] I don't want to
go home anymore.
Why? Are you having
problems with your mom?
Her husband.
He hates me, Papa.
He doesn't like me.
Can I just stay here with you,
Papa?
You need to understand, son.
You need to go back
to your mom's family.
It's time to go back to them.
Do you not want me
anymore either, Papa?
It's not like that.
It is like that, Papa!
You'd rather drink
than be a father to me!
No...
Martin!
Martin, son.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CRYING, SNIFFLING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Um, hon?
You want something?
Oh, no.
[TRIXIE] Hello, Mom, Dad!
I am so sorry I am late.
Oh! Hello, big brother.
I haven't seen you for days.
Hi.
Martin, you remember
Mr. Dy, right?
I was in a meeting with him
earlier,
and he finally agreed
to sell me the property.
We can now start
on the new project.
[LOUISE] Ah, that's nice.
[CARLOS]
That's great news, Trixie.
You know what?
You really take after me
when it comes to charm.
[TRIXIE CHUCKLES]
You got it, Dad.
And how about you, Martin?
How are you?
I don't know.
Why?
What's wrong?
I don't know either.
First,
I didn't know I wouldn't even
have an office to return to
after coming back
from Solara Island.
[LOUISE] Solara Island?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARTIN] Don't worry.
I'm not going back there
anymore.
Huh?
But didn't you just
reconnect with your dad?
Because he's dead.
[LOUISE] Huh?
Son, what happened?
- Excuse me.
- [CHAIR SCRAPES]
Martin.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
We keep delivering
vegetables to you
and you don't even know
how to pay?!
I promise to pay you
next time!
- I promise.
- I don't need your promises!
The first time you did that,
fine.
The second time,
I tried to understand.
But the third time?
Still the same thing?
Now you're just taking
advantage of my kindness!
- I'm sorry. I will pay.
- Too late!
No! Cheska, take that.
Hurry up!
- I have had enough already.
- Sorry...
Sorry.
Come on, come on.
This is ridiculous!
She's not the only one
with bills to pay!
- Yeah.
- Unbelievable.
- Geez.
- Ma!
- Oh.
- Kiko!
What are you doing here?
I saw the multicab parked.
So I got down here.
Why did you come home
all of a sudden?
Yeah.
Are you okay?
[GEORGIA SOBS]
[SOBBING CONTINUES]
Ma.
Ma!
- Ma, I thought...
- [WAILS]
Shouldn't Kiko
be the one crying?
What's it to you?!
Michael was a jerk,
but I loved him!
[ENGINE STARTS]
[GEORGIA WAILS]
- [CERAMIC BREAKS]
- [KIKO] Ma?
I might stay there for a while.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Ma, wasn't this supposed to be
for your dream phone?
It's okay.
This still isn't enough
to make up for everything.
Ma, I don't hold
anything against you.
Yes, because
you're a good son.
If I told you to
go there and demand money,
you would.
If I told you to stay here
so we could save money,
you would too.
Ma, this my choice.
Maybe I just use
being busy as an excuse...
because it's lonely now, right?
The hotel has really changed.
What if...
Michael and I
ended up together?
Then Cheska wouldn't exist.
He's right.
No one would inherit
your beauty, Ma.
[KIKO CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
That's true too.
It's just that
sometimes I think...
maybe things wouldn't have
been so complicated if...
Michael and I
worked things out.
But your father and I...
we were never really
compatible.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
But I love you.
And Michael,
may his soul rest in peace.
He loved you.
I know he did.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Alright.
Sir Michael was kind.
He was a jolly person.
He was a father to us.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh, that afternoon,
I saw him leave.
He was in a hurry.
But that was it.
Did you see him talking
to someone
who may have led him
to be in that disposition?
He was holding a phone.
But I didn't know
who he was talking to.
I saw a car coming,
and two men got out of it.
And then?
I think they seem
to have gotten physical.
Things got pretty heated.
After that,
I just ignored them.
I went inside my house.
Then I heard gunshots.
By the time I got out,
both of them were dead.
Is no one else living
around here?
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Son,
it's okay to cry, alright?
I already did, Ma.
Kiko...
you can cry again
if you need to.
Especially if you feel like it.
Oh!
Group hug! Group hug!
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- [WIND GUSHING]
- Kiko? Kiko!
- [PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Raphie... what is it?
Kiko, the cops are here.
[WIND CHIMES CLINKING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
U-Uncle Federico killed Papa?
The investigation
progressed quickly
because of the strong testimony
of the witness.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
A witness saw
Mr. Fernandez's car arriving,
and he was with Mr. Almazan.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
No one knows what
they could've fought about.
- [BOTH GRUNTING] Argh!
- [GUNSHOTS]
[GUNSHOT]
[GUN COCKS, GUNSHOT]
[HENRI] The bullets found
on the victims' bodies
were from
a murder weapon.
And the murder weapon
found at the crime scene
was registered to
Mr. Michael Fernandez.
Both of their fingerprints
were on the gun.
Both had gunpowder residue
on their hands.
Proof that both of them
fired the gun.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mr. Michael Fernandez and
Mr. Federico Almazan
killed each other.
N- No. [BREATHING HEAVILY]
No! That's not true!
My Daddy isn't a murderer!
- That was self-defense!
- [GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
- Leon... Leon...
- Sir.
What would happen to the case
if it's true
that they killed each other?
We no longer have
leading suspects to be charged.
This is now a case closed.
[JADE SOBBING] No...
That's it?
My Dad was killed then--
That's unfair!
[JADE SNIFFLES]
We'll get going.
[JADE SOBBING]
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
We've already cleared out
some of the clutter here
in your dad's library.
If you need anything
from his belongings,
it's all here.
Monette,
everything has to be in order
so Papa can have
a proper funeral.
Did Papa ever say
what he wanted when he dies?
[SIGHS]
No, but...
...I wish your brothers
were here.
[SCOFFS] Let's not get
our hopes up about that.
Still, let them know.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Alright, I'll leave you here
for now.
If you need anything,
just call me.
- Okay?
- Alright.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LINE RINGING]
[BEEPS]
[KEYPAD CLICKING]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE DINGS]
[KIKO] Papa's autopsy
results are out.
You might want to see him
before he's buried.
Grandma, I'm heading out!
I still have a viewing
with my client.
Oh, okay, sweetheart.
Be careful, alright?
I'll cook dinner later
when you get home.
Okay, Grandma.
I'm heading out.
- Okay, okay.
- [SMOOCHES]
- Take care, alright?
- Bye.
- Be careful!
- Yes!
"Papa's autopsy results
are out.
You might want to see him
before he's buried."
Oh, you're not going to work?
After they shut down
my business?
[TRIXIE SIGHS]
Martin, don't worry about it.
I'm sure you'll find
something new to keep you busy.
I should.
I don't want to just
do nothing.
You? Doing nothing?
You're even more of a
workaholic than Dad.
Here, just a suggestion.
What if you take a break
for now?
That's different from
doing nothing.
Nope.
Why would I take a break?
You're really something,
you know that?
Aren't you going to be late?
Huh? Why? What time is it?
Oh, you're right!
Okay, wait.
You can have my breakfast.
Eat well, brother.
I love you.
See you later, okay?
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
The police have left, ma'am.
They're done talking
to the kids.
Alright, Roy.
Thank you.
If we need to leave,
just let me know
so I can get the car ready.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[WOMAN]
We're sorry for your loss.
[KIKO] Thank you.
[KIKO EXHALES DEEPLY]
- We're sorry for your loss.
- Thank you.
[WOMAN] Oh, hi.
You're here.
[GUESTS CHATTERING]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I thought you weren't coming.
Come on.
Let's bury Papa.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Leon?
Uh...
Mind if I get some rest?
Sure, if you're tired.
Thank you, Leon.
[HEELS CLACKING]
[INDISTINCT CROWD CHATTER]
My friends have been
waiting for me.
Can I leave now?
No!
You stay.
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
- [GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
- [HEAVY FOOTSTEPS]
[FRIDA] Edward.
Auntie.
My sincerest condolences.
- Thank you.
- Leon.
Edward.
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
When did you get back
from Singapore?
Just today, Auntie.
Dad picked me up.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- Dad...
- Leon.
- Uncle.
- Frida.
[FRIDA SIGHS DEEPLY]
You have our
sincerest condolences.
We attended the burial earlier,
but we chose not to go near
when you were having your
final moments with your dad.
[LEON] I appreciate it, Uncle.
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC SWELLING]
Papa...
All of us are here.
We're finally complete.
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC INTENSIFYING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Gentlemen, I've prepared some
coffee and snacks for you.
[PLATE THUDS]
- I'll pass.
- Just coffee for me.
Goodness.
I still find it hard to believe
that Papa and Uncle Fred
went after each other.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
They were still with us
just the other day,
having a nice conversation.
It should've been
a memorable get-together
between two families.
We hadn't been with Papa
for a long time.
Honestly,
I can't say I really knew him.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Me too.
And we don't even know
what transpired
in their conversation.
There's so much
we don't know about them.
Personally, I'm choosing to
believe what the police said.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm here.
Ma?
This hotel holds
many cherished memories.
Please don't put Hotel 88
up for sale.
If we lose this hotel,
we'll never know what it is.
If we were to make
this hotel operational,
the three of us  could
earn some money.
We're expected to divide this?
We have guests.
Or should I say... co-owners?
We want to buy your share.
You can shove your money
down your throat!