No one has ever attacked me
like this before.
This case isn't over, Marina.
We still have to know more
about Michael and
Federico's deaths.
[GRUNTS]
I've done what you told me
to do, ma'am.
Are you sure?
Yes, ma'am.
Is it because of Jade
and the mysterious earrings?
She said we're not kids anymore.
That a lot has changed.
I know you feel at ease
around me.
Is this what you mean?
I know you're just passing by.
You're not really
going to work today.
Come on.
[SIGHS]
Okay, Miss Trixie,
please wait for your keys.
- I'll just get it.
- Alright. Thank you.
Okay. Thank you.
[LUGGAGE THUDS]
- [WHEELS RATTLING]
- [LIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
Ah, yes, ma'am.
Welcome to Hotel 88.
Do you have a reservation?
What? Reservation?
Is that necessary?
- [RAPHIE] Yes.
- I don't have one.
But, maybe you still have
vacant rooms?
Oh.
As of now, we still have
vacant rooms, but just the--
The VIP?
- Oh, yes, ma'am.
- Oh, the VIP. That's it.
Give me the VIP room.
Give me the nicest, the biggest,
and the most expensive room
you have.
[RAPHIE] Okay. Right away.
The VIP room,
our best and most expensive one.
- That's it, I like
- It'll be yours, ma'am.
Alright.
- Are my keys ready?
- Ah, yes, ma'am.
- Here, ma'am.
- Thank you.
This is also a VIP room,
isn't it?
Oh, yes.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, ma'am.
This way.
- Enjoy!
- [WHEELS RATTLING]
Okay. Let's process
your VIP room, ma'am.
What are you talking about?
No. Put it on my brother's tab.
Just a regular room
for me, please.
But you said--
I said a regular room. Zip it.
Alright.
I'm just going
to re-process it...
Do you need help?
- No, it's fine.
- I can write it myself.
I can do it, ma'am.
Thank you.
[LIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
- [PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Oh, Miss,
have you seen Luna?
I don't know
where she is, ma'am.
Okay, thank you.
[KIKO] Jade!
- Jade.
- What now?
Jade, hold on.
I wouldn't bother you
if it's not important to me.
I'm busy.
Jade, just one minute, please!
Okay, five seconds. Five.
- Yesterday, you asked
- Four.
- if I know something.
- Three. Two.
- What is it that I don't know?
- One. Time's up!
Jade, please!
That was nothing.
Don't worry about that.
I also don't know
the things you don't know.
Jade, don't be like this.
You wouldn't bring it up
if it's just nothing.
And I won't stop, Jade.
We can't be like this forever.
Just avoiding each other.
You know there are matters
we have to talk about.
Fine.
You want to know the truth?
Yes.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
There's a restaurant downstairs.
There's a bar here upstairs.
Both are managed by Monette.
Noted, sir.
[GASPS] Martin!
- [CHUCKLES]
- Trixie?
- [MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
- How are you?
What are you doing here?
Oh, of course, for you.
I felt that you needed me here,
so here I am.
Is she your sister, sir?
When did I make you feel that?
- Oh, Martin--
- That's a serious question.
Aren't you happy to see me?
I crossed the ocean for you.
Of course. Of course I'm happy.
That settles it.
- Hi, sissy!
- Oh!
I'm Sari!
I'm Sir Martin's assistant.
Just let me know
if you need anything
and I'll help you
with all my loving heart!
- [CHUCKLES]
- Yeah.
This is my assistant.
Oh... assistant.
So how long--
Don't ask.
Oh, okay.
It's nice to meet you, Sari.
I'll introduce you
to my brothers.
Oh, great. G, let's go.
At last,
I'll finally meet your brothers.
Let's go?
Let's go.
- [FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
- [MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
Jade, I'm begging you.
It's...
about the earring.
It isn't Luna's.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
It's-- It's Mom's.
It's hers.
[EXCLAIMS] Bro!
- Cheska.
- I missed you!
Wow. You said 'Cheska'
as if you didn't know me.
Hey! What's up!
Cheska, what are you doing here?
What's wrong?
Hey! Goodness.
- Excuse me.
- Sorry.
Jade.
Jade, wait.
Ahh.
So she's Jade.
Okay.
She's pretty. Great, great.
What are you doing here?
Why? Did I disturbing anything?
Was she about to say yes?
Whatever, Francheska.
I'm not courting her.
Why would she say yes?
You tell me.
You seem so mad.
Who knows where that was going.
Why are you really here?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why didn't you tell me
you were coming?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Mama and I wanted
to help you.
We had a family meeting
and we agreed...
that I will go here.
A family meeting?
Why wasn't I included?
And majority wins,
so you can't complain.
Hey, I'm doing you a favor.
Come to think of it.
I'll help you out here.
You don't need to give me
money or pay me.
You just have to feed me
and let me stay here
- ...for a few days.
- Exactly how many days?
Bro, I don't like your tone.
Don't you want me here?
[CHESKA] Honestly, it hurts
my feelings.
I'm upset, but I can just
go home.
- It's just one boat ride away.
- No.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, okay?
You know, if you weren't
my sister,
I would've hit you for coming
at the wrong time.
Oh, my timing is wrong.
So, how are things going, bro?
Have you confessed your
feelings?
Are you taking your relationship
to the next level?
You're being pesky. Stop it.
- Just shut it, Cheska.
- Someone's being cranky.
Come on, I'll introduce you
to my brothers.
Crankypants!
Nice meeting you, Gio!
This is nice.
Feel at home, okay?
There are many activities
you can do here.
Just order any food
you want.
Hey. That's--
Kiko and I will take
care of it.
Would you look at that?
It seems Gio is nicer
than you, bro.
- Is that so?
- [CHUCKLES] I'm just kidding.
[CHESKA] You know what?
I'm still not used to this.
What do you mean?
You see, he's the eldest child
in our house,
but here, he's the youngest.
- Aww, you're the baby boy here.
- [KIKO SCOFFS]
You know, you talk a lot.
[MARTIN] Gio. Kiko.
Hello.
- You again?
- Are you stalking me?
You know,
this hotel is huge.
We can choose not to
see each other.
You two know each other?
- Uh...No.
- No.
- I'm Gio.
- Trixie. Hello.
Uh... This is Trixie, my sister.
- Hi.
- Oh.
- Your sister?
- Mm-hmm.
This is my sister, Cheska.
- I'm Martin.
- Hi, Martin.
You acted like
a VIP guest earlier.
It turns out you're the sister
of Martin's brother.
[CHESKA] So what? It's true.
Right, Kiko?
I'm a VIP
in my brother's life.
You should go to your
rooms and rest.
- Let's check in.
- Yeah, go.
- See you brother. Bye.
- You got it. Bye.
- Bye, Gio!
- Look at them.
Bye, Martin!
Gio, Martin...
We need to talk about
something.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
I told you I'd deal
with Jade, remember?
Well? Did you find out
anything?
Yes, but it's still not clear.
What do you mean?
She said the earring
doesn't belong to Luna.
It's Aunt Frida's.
So that means
Luna lied.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
I don't know.
That's all Jade told me.
Did you find out
anything else?
No, I didn't.
Cheska came so our conversation
was cut short.
[MARTIN] Wait.
Aunt Frida was the only
one not with us
when we arrived
at the crime scene.
The four siblings were all
with us.
Could Aunt Frida have something
to do with Papa's death?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I guess now we can report this
to the cops.
But we're still not sure.
How can we be sure if we
don't tell them?
Gio's right, Kiko.
It's no longer in our hands.
Kiko found the earring
at the place where Papa died,
but Jade found out
and took it.
You gave it to her?
Huh?
She said it belongs
to them.
She took it,
and I didn't get it back.
[GIO] Not only that, sir.
When the Almazans
returned to the hotel,
Luna claimed it was hers,
and she lost it when she
last visited her father.
That's possible.
Sir.
But Jade herself said
that Luna is lying.
The earring really belongs
to their mother.
It was Mrs. Almazan's?
Her daughter confirmed it?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
S-- Sir, isn't this an
important lead?
It might help solve
Papa's case.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Slowly.
That's it, we're close.
- Ma, what are we doing?
- [LAUGHS]
Alright!
- Do I take it off?
- Yes, take it off.
[GRUNTS]
[ALL] Surprise!
- Surprise, Justin!
- Happy birthday!
Happy birthday, Justin.
[LUNA WHIMPERING] Aw!
Sorry, I forgot.
You know your sister
has so much to think
about the hotel, right?
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
Happy Birthday, Justin!
Even if...
We're always fighting.
[CHUCKLING]
You know I love you, don't you?
- [BOTH LAUGHING]
- Aw.
Wow!
It's been a while since we all
hanged out like this.
[FRIDA] And we should do this
more often.
You're all growing up so fast.
I don't know for how long
I'll still be able to do this.
For me to be with you all.
I thought you...
Forgot it was today.
[FRIDA] No way.
That's never going to happen.
Do you remember when
your father was still alive?
No matter how busy he was,
no matter how moody he was,
when one of us
is celebrating their birthday,
we have to be complete
no matter what.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Here.
- Time to blow your cake!
- [LUNA APPLAUDS]
- [JUSTIN CHUCKLES]
- [LIGHTER CLICKING]
- Not working?
- Uh-oh.
[JADE] Make a wish, Justin!
It's too windy.
Just imagine that the candles
are lit.
- [JUSTIN SIGHS]
- [JADE LAUGHING]
- [FRIDA] Wish! Wish!
- Make a wish, Justin!
Alright. [CLEARS THROAT]
[BLOWS]
[CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
- What did you wish for, Justin?
- Thank you! It's a secret!
- What was it?
- You'll know soon.
- More women!
- More women?!
- Uh-uh! Nope!
- That's what I want!
My wish is for you
to finally have a girlfriend!
- [LAUGHTER]
- Who could it be?
[ALL SINGING HAPPY BIRTHDAY]
[JADE] Dance, Justin! Let's go!
[SIGHS] Do you think
they'll do something
about what we reported?
They have to.
It's their job.
[BOTTLE HISSING, POPS]
Kiko, let me just remind you,
we're talking about Papa.
Don't you want justice
for him too?
I do but it might just cause
more tension
between our family
and the Almazan's.
But we're doing this
not just for Papa,
but also for their dad too.
[KIKO SIGHS]
Hey! Take a little break.
We brought snacks!
Oh, right. You guys disappeared.
Where did you all go?
Just hanging out.
- Let's eat!
- Perfect timing!
- I'm hungry!
- Yes!
Eat up, guys!
- Eat up!
- Palabok!
Ms. Trixie, are you here
for the music festival?
Yes, of course!
Wouldn't miss it for the world.
It's my brother's first event
here so I can't miss it.
Also, I heard that there are
a lot of business
opportunities here, so...
I'm hitting two birds
with one stone.
What about me?
Dude, I can help.
You can hire me as a staff!
Oh, perfect! We need a staff!
- Right, Sir Gio?
- Exactly.
I can help too.
Are you sure?
Don't you want
to relax while you're here?
Huh? When did I ever rest?
I want to help. Count me in.
Alright, let's all eat!
- [CHESKA] Aw!
- [TRIXIE] Aw!
Aw, Sis, did you miss me?
Well, our sirs all missed
their sister too.
How could I miss you
when we're together everyday?
I'm just happy
because you're all complete!
And because of that...
Let's take a picture!
- Come on!
- Let's take a picture!
We rarely do this. Come on!
- Martin!
- Sir Martin, come on!
Don't be a killjoy, join us!
- Okay. One, two, three, smile!
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
[RAPHIE] It got quiet
all of a sudden. [CHUCKLES]
Alright, one more!
- One, two, three, smile!
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
- Alright!
- That's enough.
- Yes. Go help yourselves!
- Thank you!
[MONETTE] The food's
gonna get cold.
[RAPHIE] I'm going
to post this, okay?
- [LAUGHTER]
- What's this?
Eat more, Justin!
- The pasta's good!
- Mmm!
- Leon, want some dip?
- Delicious! This is so good.
Mom, did you make the pasta?
No, it's from my favorite--
[WOMAN] The nerve to celebrate
when you just lost someone...
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[FRIDA EXHALES DEEPLY]
- Roi! Roi!
- [ROI] Yes, Ma'am?
Please take a picture
of us family.
- Yes, Ma'am.
- Okay.
- One, two, three!
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
- Wait, wait!
- Roi, include the entire table!
Include the background too!
One, two, three!
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
Let's take one more.
[ROI CLEARS THROAT]
One, two...
[ALL] Happy Birthday, Justin!
- Okay, come on.
- Thank you.
Can I see? Thank you.
- It's so hot!
- Let me see!
Wow, it's gorgeous.
It's beautiful!
Wow!
Aw!
[CHUCKLES]
I hope your dad could see this.
I'm sure he could see us, Mom.
[TOUCHING MUSIC]
Hello?
[INAUDIBLE]
Huh?
Dela Paz.
Okay, I'll
call you later.
Where are you going?
Karma will get
those Almazans someday.
I'm sure they're behind
what happened to me.
They want me to stop
going after them.
Well they've made a mistake.
The dash cam footage,
the earring, it's enough
for them to get questioned.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
I'll come with you.
[CAR DOORS OPENING]
[CAR DOORS CLOSING]
Justin, you're the most
troublesome,
right, Mom?
- He's the most annoying!
- [LAUGHING]
- How mean!
- No comment! [CHUCKLING]
- [INAUDIBLE]
- Right?
True. Remember during
my birthday?
It's my birthday but you're not
present. Why?
- Where were you?
- Sorry, I'm sorry.
He was following his teacher
that he used to have a crush on.
- [LAUGHING]
- Am I wrong?
It's why you had
high grades, isn't it?
Yeah.
Well, no. I mean...
What's going on?
Sir Henri.
We just want to invite
Mrs. Almazan
to the police station.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Why? What for?
For the case
of Michael Fernandez
and Federico Almazan.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
We'd just like to invite
Mrs. Almazan to the station.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Why? What for?
It's about the case of Michael
Fernandez and Federico Almazan.
Where's your warrant?
[MARINA] We don't have it but--
[LEON] Then she won't come
with you to the station.
We just have a question,
Mr. Almazan.
[LUNA] Whatever it is that
you want to ask,
ask her here.
[HENRI] Are you sure?
Alright then.
Mrs. Almazan,
where were you
when Michael Fernandez
and Federico Almazan died?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
What kind of question
is that?
Mrs. Almazan, is it hard
to answer my question?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Where were you
when your husband
and Michael Fernandez died?
Mom, don't answer that.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Did you have something to do
with their death, Mrs. Almazan?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mrs. Almazan.
No.
You better leave.
You have no right
to accuse my mother.
We know about the earring.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
We know about the earring.
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [WAVES CRASHING]
I need my lawyer.
I'll only speak
in the presence of my lawyer.
You're not deaf, right?
You heard her.
She's not going to speak
with you.
You're asking nonsense.
This is ridiculous.
I'm begging you,
Please, just leave.
I'm watching your every move.
[SOCFFS]
Watch as much as you want.
This is a family occasion.
I hope you respect that.
You may go.
Let's go.
[FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You want me to bring
them back to life
to answer all your questions?
You should not hide anything
if Mom didn't do anything bad.
It feels good to have the hotel
just for us, even for a day.
It's fun, right?
No one's prying. Yes, Lord!
We're the men of the house now.
We should protect our family.
We didn't meet up.
I did not avail your services.
You might scare our guests away.
Then I'll go to the crime scene.
- What's Mrs. Almazan's motive?
- Who is that?
What could two men fight about
involving a woman?
Hey!