Oh, wow! It looks like
Gio's earning money.
We're finally getting
our money.
It actually feels weird.
None of them are here.
Yes, Lord!
This is the life, Lord.
We just want to invite
Mrs. Almazan
to the police station.
We know about the earring.
I need my lawyer.
How did the cops find out
about the earring?
Why did you do that?
Because I'm tired
of all the lies, Luna!
Let's assume what
you're saying is true.
Can't you forgive our mom?
Don't tell me
you're thinking your mother
killed your father
so she and my father
could be together.
Are you serious?
I don't know, Kiko!
I really don't know!
That's why I need your help
to find out the truth!
So, tell me right now.
Yes or no?
Can you help me?
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[FOREBODING MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay.
Okay, okay.
- What are you doing here?
- Bye.
I've got to go.
We have work to do.
Hotel 88 has a big event
that we're preparing for.
[JUSTIN]
What if the cops show up again?
Or someone else bothers Mom?
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
[JUSTIN] You said so yourself.
We need to protect them.
[LUNA] Justin is right, Leon.
Hey, you can't put
your lives on hold
just because of
what's happening.
I can protect myself.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Roi, is the car ready?
Are you going somewhere, Mom?
Yes.
I need to go to our lawyer
so we can be ready
for anything.
[FRIDA] I'll be fine.
Anyway, thanks for the flowers.
I appreciate it.
Let's go, Roi.
I'll be off.
- [GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [FOOTSTEPS RECEDING]
Let's go.
[SIGHS]
[MUSIC BECOMES OMINOUS]
Do you know if the Almazans
are coming today?
I don't know.
But I'm excited to see them,
especially Luna.
I want to know why she lied.
We'll find out their answer
when they return.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Wait.
Where are you going?
Do you have somewhere to be?
I'm going to send money
to Grandma
and meet the sponsor
for the music fest.
Alright, go now.
I need you here later, okay?
Okay.
[FOOTSTEPS RECEDING]
Sari.
[MARTIN] Where are you going?
I'm just going to
drink some water, sir.
Have you gotten
the tourism officer's signature?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- Uh...
- Where is it?
I haven't gotten it yet.
It's just one signature, Sari!
Now, tell me
how we're going to start
the event without a permit.
The tourism officer will
be back tomorrow.
I'll get it in time.
So, just chill. Relax, sir.
- Do you want a massage?
- Hey.
I don't have time
to joke around with you.
Uh...
You see, sir...
I did my best to get
the signature today.
Unfortunately, I ended up there
during lunch break.
I tried to wait.
But it turns out
the person who was supposed
to sign it already went home.
I bet they were just
waiting for a bribe.
[LIGHTHEARTED MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, come on!
Seriously? A bribe?
[HUFFS]
Maybe they just wanted to rest.
Or maybe they just wanted
to lie down and relax.
Something like that.
They should've delegated it
to someone else
instead of just leaving,
knowing that they had left
some work undone.
[SIGHS]
You have a point.
I always have a point!
This is exactly what's
wrong with the system!
Those slowpokes don't have
any sense of urgency!
How will we have progress
if they can't even accomplish
something this small quickly?
[HUFFS]
[CLAPS]
What?
What do you mean
by "what," sir?
Raphie!
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[LIGHTHEARTED MUSIC CONTINUES]
Raphie!
Hey! What are you doing there?
- Sir Martin is calling for--
- Shh!
That's exactly why I'm hiding.
Whenever Sari messes up,
he always calls for me,
"Raphie! Raphie! Raphie!"
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Two weeks.
One day.
You're exaggerating!
One week.
- Two days.
- Five days.
Let's just go with three days.
No more, no less. Final answer.
That's my best bet.
Hey, this isn't some game.
[RAPHIE] But kidding aside,
look at Sir Martin.
See?
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
He's boiling with anger.
I bet Sari will resign
in three days.
- You sure about that?
- Oh!
You startled me!
What do you think you're doing?
Just stay with your boss,
or he'll get even angrier.
My goodness!
He's really one of a kind!
He's so handsome,
so responsible,
so smart...
He's so perfect!
My god! Is he even human?
Well...
Is she even human?
I don't think so.
[GIGGLES]
Grandma, I've sent the budget
for this week.
[PANTS]
What for?
I already told you
there's still a lot left.
Well, it's better
to have some extra.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
You know, grandson,
even though I miss you...
I'm happy because I know
you're enjoying your stay
at your father's hotel.
We're just here
to settle something.
That's basically the same!
I know you.
I know that you're enjoying
what you're doing.
Of course, Grandma.
If the hotel is
in a good state,
I can sell my shares faster.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
What?
You're still going to sell it?
But...
what about your siblings?
I'll only sell it
to a good person...
someone I know
they can get along with.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you expect me
to stay here forever?
No way!
I still want to go back there.
[GIO'S GRANDMOTHER SIGHS]
[EDWARD] Dad.
Hey, bud.
So...
Everything's good,
everything's good?
Tell me. How is it working
with the Almazans?
It's alright, Dad.
The event is coming up.
Oh, by the way if you want
to come,
you're very much welcome.
Me, go to the event?
I don't think so, man.
I have a lot of work
to finish here
and beside I don't fit in
with those things anymore,
you know I'm-- [CLICKS TONGUE]
I'm just meant to take it easy.
I get it. Understandable.
So, uh, on another note,
bud, you do realize that...
We own almost everything
on this island
except for Hotel 88.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Yeah...
Is this the reason
why you agreed to--
Look. Try to understand it.
First and foremost,
your dad's a business man,
you know?
Uh... I will do everything
I can in my power
to secure our legacy
on this island.
But I thought you'd just
give them a hand, Dad?
Yes.
I said it and I will.
Don't get me wrong,
of course I'll help them.
Okay.
But, Dad, they don't plan
on selling Hotel 88.
If it's what
you're thinking about.
The Almazan siblings,
or rather, Jade
and her siblings,
they don't have any plan
to do so
whatsoever.
[CHUCKLING] They don't have to.
They don't have to sell it.
If you and Jade get together
isn't it basically
the same thing?
I told you this
many times already.
I have no plans
to be serious with her.
Okay, then.
I'll uh,
I'll just have to find
another way.
[PHONE RINGING]
Excuse me, I have to take this.
Sure, sure, sure.
[PHONE RINGING CONTINUES]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Okay, Sir Henri, Thanks.
What did he say?
It's circumstantial.
Just because Aunt Frida
is the owner of the earring
doesn't mean she was there
during the murder.
They said she could have went
on a different day.
Seriously?
Or...
That family
is just really powerful.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
The Almazans are here, sir.
[GIO SCOFFS] Oh?
The powerful family is here.
I thought...
You'll all be absent again.
Why would we be absent?
I don't know.
Guilt trip?
What are you talking about,
Gio?
Why would we feel guilty?
Come on. [SCOFFS]
You don't know?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Aren't you the liar?
You said that the earring
was yours but it wasn't.
[SUSPENSEFUL STING]
[SCOFFS]
Oh, okay.
It all makes sense now.
Were you the ones
who reported to the police?
Yes.
Why? Is it wrong?
Without asking us first?
To know about our side
of the story?
Why?
So that you could cook up
another lie?
Why did you even lie, Luna?
What are you hiding?
Are you scared the truth
might get exposed?
- Hey watch your mouth, jerk!
- Shut your mouth, loser!
I lied because I know
it's going to end up like this.
I just don't want things
to get messy.
But because of what you did,
we got even more suspicious.
We were just trying
to protect our family.
How about us then?
Huh?
Don't we have the right
to know the truth?
Okay.
I understand.
But now that you've reported it
to the police,
What?
Found something?
[JUSTIN] See?
[SCOFFS]
No matter how many times
you file a report,
you won't find anything.
So from now on,
we'll forget
this ever happened.
We're sorry that Luna lied.
But I assure you
my mom, or anyone else
in our family, is innocent.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
This is okay
for the suppliers.
- Yes, ma'am, copy.
- Thank you.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
What are you doing here?
Are you still insisting we had
something to do with the case?
Your brother said to forget it.
But it seems like you're
the one who can't forget.
Come to think of it,
why are you the angry one?
When you're the one
who didn't tell the truth?
Wait.
I didn't come here
to start a fight.
I have something to say.
Make sure that's worth
my time.
I can't really talk nonsense
with you, can I?
But before...
Wait.
You've really done nothing
but irritate me, huh?
I was in town earlier today
to talk to a possible sponsor
for the music festival.
And?
And...
They don't want
to talk to me.
[LUNA SCOFFS]
What did you expect?
They said,
it's the General Manager
they want to speak with.
That's you, isn't it?
Or do you want me
to send Martin instead?
That's not a difficult thing
to do.
In fact, it would be easier.
After all, the sponsor may not
like liars.
Aren't you going to stop?
Fine, I'll stop.
What, will it be Martin or you?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[KIKO SIGHS]
What will I tell my brothers?
[CHESKA SCOFFS]
Look at this guy.
You really don't use your head.
Bro, what do you mean
what will you tell them?
Why will you say anything?
Because Jade wants to know
if Papa and Aunt Frida did have
an affair.
What's it to her
if she finds out the answer?
If we discover
that Jade is right,
there's a possibility
Aunt Frida had something to do
with Papa's death.
And then?
Bro, there's no "then" yet!
I want to know
if I should tell my brothers.
[CHESKA SIGHS]
If you tell them...
If they find out about it...
They're going to be angry.
They're going to be angry, bro.
I know. That's why I'm having
second thoughts as well.
Mm! And when they get angry...
You're finished.
You're finished!
Anger will control them.
How then will you get
the right answer,
and how will you know
what really happened
if you let anger sway
your decisions?
They'll go straight
to the police station.
It'll be a huge drama.
It'll be a huge mess.
And there's more. There's more!
Prepare yourself.
- You ready?
- What is it?
She'll get angry at you.
[CHESKA] See?
Bro...
She'll never, ever
trust you again.
That'll hurt!
She'll ignore you...
You'll become like a rat
in her eyes.
- A rat, really?
- Why?
Are you okay
with being a rat?
[KIKO SIGHS, GROANS]
You're just messing
with my brain.
Come on, bro,
just trust me.
- Your crush is right, okay?
- She's not my crush.
Oh, stop it.
You can't fool me, what do you
mean she's not your crush?
Anyway, Jade is right!
There might be a way
for you to know the truth...
...with just
the two of you knowing.
Right? And then once you
piece together everything,
you already collected
a lot of evidence...
Then go ahead
and tell your siblings.
Do you get it?
[KIKO SIGHS DEEPLY]
You really need me
in your life, bro.
I got you.
- Hurry.
- I'll help you.
We'll figure this out together.
Just promise me
no one else will know
until we find out the truth.
There's no need for promises.
That's what I want too.
We're talking about
my mother here.
We're investigating
my father, too.
Come on.
Just swear on it.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
- What?
- Look.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
They're here.
- They're here.
- Ow!
Let's go! We have to hide.
Over there! Hurry!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
They're here again.
Three days and
two nights, right?
Oh, the boys aren't here, sir.
They went to town.
How can we help you?
We just want to ask
about their father, Michael.
What about him?
Maybe Monette and I
can answer your question.
Did you notice anything unusual
on the day Mr. Michael Fernandez
and Mr. Federico Alamazan
killed each other?
Sir, you've already
asked me that before.
My answer's the same.
Have we mentioned the envelope
Sir Mike was carrying?
What envelope?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ah, sir?
Sir, have you seen the...
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Yes, I'm sure.
I was the one who put
the envelope on his table.
He had the envelope with him
when he left that day.
Do you know where it is now?
We didn't see any envelope
at the scene of the crime.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Ah!
- [METAL TRAY CLANGS]
Ow!
[BREATH SHAKES] Ow...
- [FRIDA] Aah...
- Ma'am?
Ah...
- Ow...
- What happened, ma'am?
I burned my fingers
on the hot tray.
I forgot to wear gloves.
[OBJECTS CLATTERING]
[FRIDA] There.
Right there.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[HISSES IN PAIN,
BREATHES DEEPLY]
Are you all right, ma'am?
Yeah, I'm good. Thank you.
[SUCKS TEETH,
BREATHES DEEPLY]
[FRIDA BREATHES DEEPLY]
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EDWARD] Jade.
So this is where you are.
I've been looking for you.
[EDWARD]
Where are you going?
We were supposed to meet,
remember?
[CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
Oh, right.
Sorry, is it okay if
we bring Kiko along?
Why?
- Why not?
- [EDWARD SCOFFS]
Are you in charge of marketing?
I heard you're on
housekeeping duties.
- Food and beverage.
- Food and beverage?
That's perfect.
Go to this address.
I know them personally.
They can supply the best wine
for the music fest.
I already called them.
All you have to do
is meet with them for formality.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Okay. Thank you.
No problem.
The boat's here, Jade.
Let's go?
Huh?
I thought we're having
a meeting.
Can't we do it on a boat?
Let's go?
Come on.
Let's go.
Hey! Edward! Edward!
What are you doing? We were
supposed to have a meeting!
We're in the sea!
There are no rules!
Join me! Let's talk here!
Cancel the island hopping!
Ma'am is here,
and she's excited!
Raphie, find me a new assistant.
Someone who isn't loud
and knows what they're doing.
What happened to Sari?
Has she resigned already?
It doesn't matter  how important
that envelope is
if we can't even find it.
If it disappeared
from the crime scene,
someone else
could've been there.