Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
What are you doing?
Hey, Edward!
- Hey, Edward! Edward!
- [WATER SPLASHES]
This is a meeting!
Let's do our meeting here!
You're angry because I
overshadowed you?
- No.
- No, you seem mad!
Who are you to reveal
that I used to be a DJ?
- It's true, isn't it?
- Welcome to Isla... Solara!
- [SLAPS]
- Do you have a boyfriend?
You are unbelievable!
Where are you going?
The tour isn't over yet!
Please sign the permit.
[SIGH] If it weren't
for your grandfather!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, long time no see.
It looks like you're here too.
You knew I'd be here.
[BOK CHUCKLES] No.
I was surprised
by your presence.
What are you doing here?
[BOK] I'm on a vacation!
Is that not allowed?
And there's a music fest, bro!
You know
that's my thing, right?
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[GIO] Let's talk there.
Fine.
Let's talk.
You look like you might cry.
I'll just get the money
you owe me.
Since someone told me
you're already rich.
Do you own this hotel?
Didn't I tell you to wait?
I'll pay you, Bok.
Chill.
Okay, fine.
I can wait.
But while I'm waiting...
why don't we stay at the hotel?
There's nothing wrong
with that, right?
There are other hotels here,
why don't you stay there?
[BOK] How will I keep an eye
on you if I'm far away?
C'mon? It's like
we don't have a history.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Get out of here.
[LUNA] Hi, Sir. Welcome to
Hotel 88. Have you checked in?
Oh, not yet.
- Shall we?
- [LUNA] Yes, sir. This way.
Alright.
[LUNA] How many guests
are there? Three?
[BOK] Yes, three.
Do you have a room with an
overlooking view?
[EDWARD] Okay guys,
this is our last hurrah
and we need
content for promotions.
[LUNA] Fine.
What content will you do?
[Edward] Me? We'll all do it.
We'll all do it.
[JADE] Wait.
Wait a minute.
What are we going to do?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
We'll dance.
We'll make a dance trend
so they can see how
happy we are at Hotel 88.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
[LEON] I'll pass on that.
Me too.
I'm sorry, Edward,
we're not yet complete
Justin's not here yet.
[KIKO] Martin isn't here yet,
either.
Okay, guys.
Let's practice first, okay?
Let's just talk about
the plan later, okay?
- [EDWARD] Jade.
- Yeah?
- Let's start.
- Alright.
[EDWARD] Three, two, one, go.
- One, two, three, four...
- five, six, seven, eight.
Okay, let's stop this,
Is everyone ready?
["PAANO KUNG TAYO NA LANG?"
BY ANGELA KEN PLAYING]
Energy. Okay, game!
Three, two, one...
Go!
- One, two, three, four...
- five, six, seven, eight.
- [ALL] Ha!
- [SCREAMING]
[LUNA] Jade!
Jade, are you alright?
Are you okay?
Uh...
I'm fine, I'm fine.
- I'm okay.
- [LUNA] Sorry, Jade.
- [LUNA] I thought--
- [JADE] Let's just start over.
- Let's do it again.
- Okay.
Are you sure?
Three, two, one... Go!
- One, two, three, four...
- five, six, seven, eight.
On right!
- Okay.
Oh, come on.
We have the same vibes.
That's why you gave
me your IG.
Will you just stop.
Do you not have
an Instagram account?
How about Messenger instead?
You don't get it, do you?
I don't want to!
[SCOFFS] You're hiding something
on social media, aren't you?
Interesting.
How about your phone
number instead?
No.
Raphie! Raphie! Raphie! Raphie!
Please tell my brother how
disrespectful his staff are!
- He's been...
- Staff?
You mean, Sir Justin? [CHUCKLES]
[RAPHIE] Before I forget,
they've been waiting
for you, sir.
What's going on?
[RAPHIE] Uh, I forgot
to tell you, Miss Trixie,
he's one of the
owners of the hotel.
Sir Justin, this is Miss Trixie.
Sir Martin's sister.
Ah! She's Martin's half-sister.
- So you're an Almazan?
- [JUSTIN CHUCKLES]
- Miss Trixie!
- What?
I am Justin Almazan. [SMOOCHES]
- At your service.
- What are you doing?!
[RAPHIE] I'll take my leave...
Whatever. [SCOFFS]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[JADE] I couldn't get
away from Edward earlier.
Where did you go?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Here and there...
- Like?
Fine, I was just asking.
If you don't want to
answer, then don't.
Enough.
We just went places.
- It's part of the job.
- Okay
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Wait a minute,
where are we going?
My dad likes to take videos.
Sometimes, videos of himself
or of his loved ones.
Who knows, maybe...
Okay, okay.
You're right.
Mom might be there.
That would be proof if they
had an affair.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES, SWELLS]
Here.
We're here.
Huh?
Uncle Mike's room?
[DOOR LOCK CLICKS]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
Thank you, sir, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
Please pay us a visit again!
Happy anniversary!
Take care.
What is this guy up to?
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MONETTE] Hey, Gio!
Did something happen to you?
Ah.
[MONETTE] Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Did the guest from 203
come out earlier?
Ah, the handsome guy.
He just ordered some food and
had it delivered to his room.
He even complimented
my cooking skills.
Okay.
Wait a second.
Why did you ask about him?
Do you know that guest?
I don't.
I don't know him.
How would I even know him?
I just asked.
Okay.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
By the way, congratulations!
It's only been a few days but
we're slowly filling up!
It seems your event
will be successful.
You know, if only
Sir Michael saw all of this,
I'm sure he'd be very excited.
- [MONETTE CLICKS TONGUE]
- I think so too.
Okay, I'll get going then.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What happened to that guy?
[MICHAEL] Hello, kids!
- Your uncle and I are here!
- [FEDERICO] Yes!
Look, this place is
so beautiful.
Look at that.
Can you see it? It's so vast.
We'll take you here
next time, right?
- [FEDRICO] Yes, sir!
- [MICHAEL] Oh, Frida!
I'll borrow him for now, okay?
[LAUGHS]
[FEDERICO] What can we do?
You don't have a wife!
[MICHAEL] I'll have him
to myself for a minute, okay?
- But I won't take long!
- Yes, we won't take long.
- Uncle Mike...
- Yes... Yes.
But for now, it'll just be us.
- Right? Oh.
- Cheers!
Next time, we'll be with
our families, right?
[MICHAEL] It's nice.
It's beautiful.
[KIDS GIGGLING]
Hey, knock him down.
Knock him down!
- Knock him down!
- I'll get back at you!
Ouch! Stop! Stop!
[MICHAEL] Ayan!
Go, wrestle with Gio!
Strengthen your bones!
Hey, it's Papa!
Make him join us!
- Come on, Dad!
- [MICHAEL CHUCKLES]
I'll leave all that to you.
- You three can handle it.
- [KIDS GIGGLING]
Don't ask me to join you.
I'll just be your videographer.
[KIDS GIGGLING]
- Come on, Pa!
- Go on.
Just keep having fun here
at the hotel.
- Pa, come on!
- Come join us, Pa!
Hey, hurry up!
[MICHAEL] Kiko, are you happy?
Would you like some
more banana chips?
Pa, come on! Let's play here!
Right, Pa. Come join us.
- Come on!
- Join us!
Look, it's all done.
I built it myself.
Hey, that's crazy!
[MICHAEL] I love you so much,
my sons.
Should we make that one again?
- Sure!
- Okay then!
Hey, Pa!
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Uncle Mike loves you very much.
Jade.
Are we still doing
the right thing?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Yes?
No, it's just that...
Your mother's not in
the video anyway.
Maybe that means she really
has nothing to do with it.
Or maybe, we're the only ones
who have doubts?
Didn't...
the police return
your father's phone to you?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes, because that case
was closed. Why?
[JADE] We might be able
to find something there.
There could be something in
his messages or photo gallery.
I'll also check out
my dad's phone.
Jade, I thought we were only
investigating your mother here.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's just that we might be able
to find something, right?
I mean, there's no harm
in trying.
Okay.
Okay, let's go with your way.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FRIDA EXHALES] What is this?
[FEDERICO] Don't peek.
- Federico, what is this?
- Just a little bit more.
[FEDERICO] Just don't peek,
please?
- Okay.
- Oh, close your eyes.
[FEDERICO] I need to
let you go now, okay?
[FRIDA] Alright.
Just a little bit more.
Five seconds.
Four...
Three...
Two...
Don't open it.
And one, surprise.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- For me?
- Yes.
- I hope you like it.
- Mm!
I love it!
You know what they say
about that flower?
It only blooms when
it feels truly cared for.
Delicate...
Rare...
Just like you, Frida.
You can't be bought.
You can't be owned.
But...
the only thing I can do is...
take care of it.
Take care of you.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
My beloved is so sweet.
Thanks, my love.
I hope you like it.
I love it.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[FRIDA] I love you.
I...
I love you so much.
[MUSIC TURNS MELANCHOLIC]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[HUMMING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Hi, Sir Martin.
Good evening.
You're still so noisy
even though it's late.
- Sir, I have good news.
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Make sure it's good.
I was tired the whole day.
It's really good news, sir!
What is it? Tell me.
Because tomorrow...
you'll be interviewing
a new candidate
for your future assistant!
I'm really awesome!
I'm amazing, I did all that!
Cancel it.
Everything's fine now.
What do you mean?
I don't need
a new assistant.
- But you said to--
- I changed my mind.
Everything's fine.
Cancel the interview tomorrow.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Good night, Raphie.
You asked me to do that,
just to cancel it?!
[MARTIN] Thanks, Raphie!
You're so confusing!
[SIGHS]
This isn't mine...
[SARI] You know what, Grandpa,
I thought I'd lose my job.
Sir Martin is truly
something else,
his determination is unmatched.
And he's so handsome.
He looks like an angel.
Yuck!
- What do you mean, yuck?
- You said anghit (body odor).
Are you saying it's annoying?
Grandpa.
I said he looks like an angel.
Hmm, an angel.
[UTENSILS CLATTERING]
Didn't you say he has a temper?
- And?
- Are there angels like that?
Yes.
Sir Martin.
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
- Hey, Sari.
- Oh...
Snap out of it.
We're about to eat dinner. Hmm.
- Grandpa...
- Hmm?
I will never forget the moment
he saved me from that rain.
Sari...
It was just rain...
it wan't a disaster.
He gave you an umbrella, and
you're already acting like that.
Grandpa, men like that are
hard to come by nowadays.
The type who'll let strangers
borrow their umbrella
and don't care if they get wet.
- Oh, before I forget, Sari...
- Yeah?
I'm curious.
How's the event
you're planning?
Oh, he's G for the music fest.
- Hmm?
- It's like he'll die
It felt like he was going
to die if he didn't continue.
What do you mean by "G"?
- Game!
- Oh!
[CHUCKLES]
I mean, Hotel 88 is known
for being a lively place.
- Mhmm.
- And the dad!
The dad of the guy
who gave you the umbrella,
he was such a nice guy!
But then...
tragedy struck between
him and his bestfriend.
[CLICKS TONGUE] It's
devastating, isn't it?
They were friends who ended
up killing each other.
- They didn't kill each other.
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING, SWELLS]
What? But that's what
the police said!
Did they tell you
something else?
I knew both of them.
They were good people.
They wouldn't kill each other.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Leon.
Earlier, after the dance video
Edward made us do,
you just disappeared.
I just went somewhere.
Actually, you always disappear.
- [JUSTIN] Who wants dinner?
- Me, please.
Dad has other businesses
that also need attention.
[FRIDA] Oh, hello, everyone.
Oh, Mom, you're still awake.
[FRIDA] Of course.
[LEON] Hi, Mom.
[LUNA] Hi, Ma.
[EXHALES] I really waited
for you to come back.
About the flowers,
who sent them?
Someone sent you flowers?
Yes, this morning.
I thought it was from Leon?
Hmm?
Justin, wasn't it from you?
No.
What kind of flowers
were these again, Ma?
Like the ones your Dad
used to give.
Before.
[LUNA] Waling-waling?
[FRIDA] Yes.
[LEON CLEARS THROAT]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Well, it's okay.
Maybe one of the helpers.
I'll ask them tomorrow.
Go ahead. Have dinner first.
I just have something
to do in my room.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
- [DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
- [CROW CAWING]
[SPRAY HISSING]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [EXHALES]
- [DRAWER OPENS]
[EXHALES]
Dad.
If you're going
to make yourself felt, please...
do it now.
Show me where Mom
hid your phone.
[EXHALES]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [OBJECT CLATTERING]
[DRAWER CLOSES]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Oh!
- [THUDS]
[OBJECT CLATTER]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THUDS]
- [CLATTERING]
- [BREATHES HEAVILY]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[DOOR OPENS]
Sari, the contract!
- Oh!
- Where is it?!
Wait, sir, it's just here.
The more you
walk away from me...
the more you'll see this face.
Oh god.
Bro, is this yours?
Is this your missing car?
Huh--
[BLOW LANDS]
[WATER SPLASHES]
- Welcome to Hotel 88, sir!
- Here comes Edward Arellano!
The four of us should be united.
We can't fall apart.
But now,
there's only three of us.
Where is Jade anyway?
Flowers!
Someone gave Mom flowers!
It's waling-waling.
I know someone who takes care
of that kind of plant.
Is anyone there?
- Hello?!
- Kiko-- Kiko, wait.
I think I know this place.