You used the money.
I thought of it.
The money is all there.
I can't bear saving my grandma
through wrong means.
Let's earn some money today.
Aah!
[SHRIEKS]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING]
My goodness! You almost
broke my earring.
- Why do you have this?!
- I saw it--
This is ours!
If that belongs to them,
does  that mean they were there?
I don't know, but I think we
should tell the cops about this.
I know about the affair, Mom!
Were you there
when Dad died?
Are you accusing me?
[SOBBING]
I don't know, Mom.
[SIGHS SHARPLY]
All I know is that...
you lied.
You have been lying
for a long time.
You're a liar!
No, dear.
Please.
Jade, listen to me.
I'm tired.
I'm sick and tired
of your lies!
Dear, please listen to me.
Jade, please.
Jade, Mom, what's going on?
[JADE] Listen to you?
- [MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [JADE SOBBING]
Are you going to tell everyone
here the whole truth?
[JADE] Okay, fine.
Fine, Mom.
Let's get the truth out.
What do you mean?
What truth?
Come on, Mom.
Tell them.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
What were you doing at the
place where Dad died?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[JADE BREATHES SHARPLY]
Why are you suddenly
quiet, huh, Mom?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay, okay. Then let me tell you
what I think.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Half of this earring
was found
where Dad died.
This belongs to Mom.
Dad gave it to her.
Jade, what are you trying
to say?
Mom was there, and she kept
it from us all this time.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you accusing Mom...
- that she knows something--
- Stop it.
Jade.
Enough with those thoughts.
Aren't you getting tired
of all this mess?
[JADE SOBS]
[SOBBING]
It's not just that, Leon.
While I was looking for the
other half of that earring,
I found out that Mom was
going to leave us
before Dad died.
No.
That's not true.
Mom.
Tell us it's not true.
Mom?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
No.
We can't report that
to the cops.
Why?
Because we'll look dumb
if we report this
without enough
information.
We don't even know
who owns it.
All we have are theories.
Well, even if your suspicions
are right,
I don't have the
earring anymore.
But that earring will open a new
lead in Papa's case.
Let's just forget it.
It'll only cause trouble.
Suit yourselves.
I already made my point.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[JADE] Come on, Mom.
Tell them.
That's true.
[LUNA] What?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Why, Mom?
[SOBS]
Come on, Mom. Tell them.
What is it exactly?
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
That she and Uncle Michael
had an affair.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
And maybe that was the reason
he and Dad killed each other.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Well, Mom?
Are you trying to come up
with an excuse again?
Why don't we just
tell them everything, Mom?
The earring.
The affair.
The plane ticket.
The approval for residency!
What the heck, Jade?!
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Come on, Mom.
Tell them!
Tell them, Mom, please!
Y-Your Uncle Mike and I
didn't have an affair.
You are mistaken.
[SOBS] But, Mom, I saw you!
I saw you when I was
just a kid! I saw you!
Why don't you just tell
the truth?!
[SOBS]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm sorry...
Maybe... maybe I had feelings
for him.
Maybe I... I needed a man.
'Cause I was miserable.
Your dad and I,
we were miserable.
Your dad and I
had fallen out of love.
The ticket's real.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Yes, I wanted to go. Alone.
Just like I've always wanted.
And maybe...
Maybe I'm a bad mother.
But...
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
But if you want me to confess
that I was the reason
they killed each other,
I can't do that.
If you want me to
tell you that I don't love you,
it's not true, because I...
[SOBS]
I love you so much.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FRIDA] I love you so much.
[FRIDA SOBBING]
But, yes.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
I was there
the day your dad and Mike
got into a fight.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
- I told you about this before.
- The night before he died,
Fred and I fought.
I told him I wanted to leave,
hence the ticket.
- It's because of Mike, huh?
- He thought I wanted to do so
- because of Mike.
- No!
- Mike has nothing to do...
- Oh, come on!
...with what I want to do
with my life!
[FRIDA] I knew Fred was furious.
So when I saw Mike
pick up your father that day,
I followed them.
Careful, ma'am.
[FRIDA] I asked Roi to drive.
We followed Mike's truck.
Roi, hurry! We need to
catch up to them!
Yes, ma'am.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Where did they go?
Drive faster, Roi!
Yes, ma'am.
[ROI] Ma'am, it's a dead end.
Ma'am! Wait, ma'am!
Fred!
- Ma'am!
- Fred!
[GASPS]
- Ma'am!
Roi, find Fred.
Ma'am, just go to the hotel.
I'll go find Sir Fred.
Your children
are waiting for you.
Promise me, Roi, that you'll
take Fred and Mike back.
[FRIDA PANTING]
That's the truth, kids.
Why didn't you tell the police
about this, Ma?
I'm not as strong
as you think I am.
And I'm worried about you.
I don't want you
to think of me differently.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNIFFLES] I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I was
the reason they fought.
I'm sorry that I'm the reason
your daddy is gone now.
[SIGHS SHARPLY]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SNIFFLES]
[SNIFFLES, SOBS]
Mom's resting in her room.
Then, I'll leave.
You stay there.
Do Martin and his brothers
know about it?
It's Kiko.
He was the one
who found the earring.
We shouldn't let this
reach the police.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you still not okay?
[SCOFFS]
That's the problem with you.
You are such a Daddy's girl.
What about your mother?
You want me to stand by her?!
Seriously?
You're so quick to believe her.
Why can't you understand
that she's protecting
Uncle Mike?
You have to see this.
What is this?
Is this Mrs. Almazan?
That was recorded from
a car's dashcam.
On the day Michael Fernandez
and Federico Almazan died.
500 meters away
from the location.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[JUSTIN] What are you
trying to imply?
Mom had something to do
with Dad's death?
Jade, do you even
hear yourself, huh?!
You want your mother
to go to jail?!
I just want the truth!
[LUNA] Jade, come on!
What truth do you want?!
Do you want Mom to say
that she killed Dad
- for you to stop?!
- [LEON] That's enough!
[THUDS]
I believe
that Mom and Uncle Mike
don't have a relationship.
And Mom had nothing to do
with Dad's death.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Our family won't be ruined
just because of this.
We should protect each other.
And we will do it
for Dad.
Jade.
All I'm asking you
is not to do anything
to hurt our family.
And that includes Mom.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Where did you get this video?
That copy has
been requested before.
But the owner of the car,
where the dashcam is,
was out of the country.
They just got back,
so we only got this today.
Mrs. Almazan didn't include
in her statement
that she was in the area
that day.
This will greatly help our case.
Still, circumstantial.
You know that.
But why didn't she tell us
about it before?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[INHALES DEEPLY, SIGHS LOUDLY]
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
[GLASS THUDS]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Ma'am.
That's enough.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
The kids already know
that I followed Fred.
Would you like me to
tell them that I was with you?
No, no.
No need.
[SIGHS]
I already told them
everything.
I'm just hoping that we'll patch
things up after this.
I hope so too.
Just remember, ma'am...
You can tell me if there's
anything I can do to help.
You know you have
my loyalty.
I'm loyal to you... and sir.
As well as your
whole family.
Yes, I know that, and I
appreciate that, Roi.
Thank you.
[INHALES DEEPLY, SIGHS]
You should go
and take a rest.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Okay, ma'am.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WAVES CRASHING]
Dad.
You're late.
- I prepared that for you.
- Thanks, Dad.
Isn't it still too early, Dad?
Can't we just hang out
after lunch?
[EDWARD GRUNTS]
Son, you know in life,
just like with
everything else,
preparation is key.
If you're not prepared,
you won't catch any fish.
Got it, Dad.
So, uh...
Grace from reception mentioned
that Jade arrived at the resort.
Yeah.
Actually, they're asking for
help to promote Hotel 88.
That's okay, right, Dad?
Why not?
Well, technically, they're
our competitor.
We also have
a hotel and resort.
- So...
- You know...
I don't see it that way.
Her parents are my friends.
It's you I'm confused about.
Why?
You agreed to help?
I mean, you cried back
in high school
when Jade didn't show up
for prom.
[SCOFFS]
It's all in the past
and I've moved on from it.
Or maybe...
you agreed because
of Jade.
Dad.
You know what I see?
It's that up to this day,
you're still hoping...
that she'll like you.
- [MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [WAVES CRASHING]
Dad, if she ends up
liking me,
then that's her problem.
As for me, I don't have plans
to get serious.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
Son, you know...
life is just like
the wide ocean.
And we're all
just fishermen
waiting for the right chances
to catch something good.
If you just keep playing
around and don't get serious...
you won't get
a good catch.
You know, some fish
are worth keeping.
Just saying.
Come on, Dad.
It's just Jade.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Dad, Dad, Dad! I caught it!
- Okay. Pull.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
What if Michael and Federico
didn't kill each other?
Someone could've planted
the gun,
- and fired it...
- [GUNSHOTS]
...to make it look like
they killed each other.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
You mean they were
already dead
when someone
planted the gun?
There were no other
fingerprints found
because the killer
is an expert.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
What if...
Frida Almazan had really
something to do with this?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm sure they've already talked
about that earring.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay.
This is our official first day.
But before anything,
I know there's something
you want to ask us.
The earring.
As Jade said...
it belongs to us.
We won't deny it.
Actually, we'd like to
apologize because...
Because I lost it.
[TENSE MUSIC RISES]
The earring belongs to me.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES,
THEN FADES]
That family is really trying
to outsmart us.
It's obvious that they're
covering up for someone.
Just take care of
the hotel for now,
and I'll find out the truth
from Jade.
So, you're going
to use Jade?
We can't keep
avoiding each other.
Are you really that clueless?
A lot has changed,
especially in our families.
This case isn't over yet,
Marina.
- I need solid evidence.
- [GRUNTING]
We won't stop,
especially if we know
something's wrong.
[THUDS]
Next time,
find someone else
you can trick into
bailing you out!
I've been waiting a long time!
Until when will I be alone?
If the hotel loses money,
it'll be your fault,
and I'll charge you for it.
I can push through
with this event.
Can you?
I can.