It'll benefit us both
if you sell it to me.
You just remember me
when it's convenient to you.
I only exist when you need me.
I know what you did, Mom.
What did I do?
Fred... Fred, no!
No! No!
Mom is also mourning,
but we know
she's trying her best!
- Well, it's too late!
- What's wrong with you?!
You have no idea.
That's enough!
[LUNA] I know you're
best friends with Martin.
But I'm your sister.
I'm only doing this for Dad.
I'm voting for Martin.
I vote for my sister, Luna.
- Martin.
- Luna.
- Martin Madrigal.
- Luna Almazan.
- Luna.
- Yes!
Our new general manager
for Hotel 88
is Miss Luna Almazan.
Congratulations.
As the general manager,
I'm responsible
for the assignments.
Martin.
Leon suggested that
you be the Operations Manager.
Is that okay with you?
Leon will be in charge
of Finance.
- And Gio...
- Sales.
That's his expertise.
Yes.
Sales.
- Justin...
- I'd take anything.
But I don't like paper works.
Fine. Events and Recreation.
Jade...
You're responsible
for Marketing and Promotions.
You can't not be a part of this.
Mm.
Kiko will be in charge
of the Housekeeping.
Housekeeping?
Why? What's wrong
with Housekeeping?
You didn't even ask
if he wants to do that.
But that's what's left for him!
Okay, I'll give you a choice.
Housekeeping or the
guard house outside?
What is he, a dog?
[IMITATES BARKING]
- What's your problem?!
- Don't test my patience!
- [SNICKERING]
- Justin.
Oh, am I testing you?
- Let's go outside, then.
- You're on!
- Justin!
- Come on!
That's enough!
I'm fine with my assignment.
You guys don't have to fight.
[LUNA] See? Housekeeping.
It includes food and beverages.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I thought you were sure
of Leon's vote?
He said he's going
to vote for you, then what?
He betrayed you!
I knew this would happen!
Please! That's enough!
It's Martin's fault!
Didn't I tell you?
That's his sister.
You're just his friend!
Or... are you really his friend?
Martin, Leon betrayed you.
- They betrayed us.
- That's enough.
They want the hotel
all for themselves.
Wow! You just realized that now?
Isn't that obvious
from the start?
It just got a lot clearer now.
Hm?
We'll take it before they do.
Huh?
We'll make them leave.
[LINE RINGING]
Gio, you lying bastard...
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
What's up?
Who are you?
I've been seeing you
standing out here.
What do you need?
Wait. How is that possible?
Attorney said it's to be
shared between us.
It's on paper.
Papa said that one day,
the hotel will be ours.
Us, brothers,
and not just whoever.
I'll think of a way.
What's important
is that the three of us...
We are stronger than them.
Boss, chief, sir!
We have a problem.
What is it?
We're getting worried
about our guest.
They haven't
come out of their room.
They're probably asleep.
They've been sleeping
since yesterday.
Or maybe they just
want to be alone.
We're worried that something
bad might've happened.
Do you have the key?
She's on her way to the room.
We've got this.
I know you still feel bad--
That's enough.
[RAPHIE] This way, please.
Good day, Ma'am.
Uh, is Gio at home?
We're his friends.
He's not here.
What's your name again?
Bok, Ma'am.
Do you know where he is?
He's not replying to us.
Uh... he just left.
That's it.
Just try calling him again.
Maybe he's just hiding
inside, boss.
The car's there, you see.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCOFFS] Ma'am...
Can my friend use the bathroom?
He's been needing to pee
but's too shy to say.
Well, sorry about that.
Our toilet's broken,
but there are plenty of posts
over there, you see.
Alright.
I'll just tell Gio
you dropped by, okay?
Okay? Okay.
Alright.
Just let him know, okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
See? I told you.
When this hotel reopens,
you'll be the ones they hire.
Thanks, Monette.
I can finally get back to work.
[CHUCKLES] Sure.
Oh, please tell Jenny
I contacted her, okay?
- They can come back too.
- Okay, okay.
Hey, I'm really sorry
about this.
If I could handle this alone,
I would,
so I won't bother you anymore.
It's fine, Monette.
We'll carry the load
if something really happens.
[SIGHS]
Do you think he's in there?
[KNOCKS]
Anyone there?
- Sir Jeff!
- [KNOCKS]
Hello?
Hey, Gio.
We need to be sure.
I've seen so many cases
like this.
It's risky. What if...
Sir Jeff!
Hello?
Where could that be?
Monette, stay here.
Keep watch.
Maybe Sir Jeff's outside.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[RAPHIE] Sir Jeff?
Sir Jeff?
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE] The subscriber
cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
[BEEPS]
[PHONE] The subscriber
cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
Come on!
Why aren't you answering, Gio?
[KEYPAD CLICKING]
Gio, your friend came by.
He's looking for you.
His name's Bok.
Where are you?
[KIKO] What, Gio?
Are his things still there?
Yes.
Yes, they're still here.
Maybe he slept in another room.
Maybe he met some locals.
You know?
Possible.
Is he checking out today?
No.
Then let's wait until tomorrow.
Alright, we'll just keep watch.
Let's go.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE BUZZING]
What?
What do you mean, what?
After you didn't answer
my calls, what?
Sorry, Trixie.
I'm just not in the mood.
That's not fair!
I've been waiting so long
for you to answer.
[MARTIN] The signal here
is too slow too.
[MUMBLING]
Fine.
But don't you have any time
for your favorite sister?
I miss you.
Trixie.
You're my only sister.
Exactly.
All your time is spent
with your...
- ...brothers.
- It's not them.
It's the hotel.
It's super stressful here.
- How stressful?
- Trixie, please.
Just kidding.
[CHUCKLING]
What? I'm just asking.
Let me see your surroundings.
Why?
Come on!
Fine.
Hey.
Is that Leon?
Hi, Leon!
How are you?
He's too far.
He didn't hear you.
Alright, I'll just call again.
Okay. Bye, Martin.
Love you.
Martin.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you crazy, Bok?
Don't show up at my grandma's!
You know, you wouldn't
have a problem
if you were paying me.
I told you I'd pay you,
didn't I?
I'll pay you!
Hurry up, Gio.
Don't wait for us to go back
to your grandma's.
[GIO]
Don't you dare touch her.
- Don't you dare--
- [BEEPS]
Hello?
Bok!
Hello?!
Tch.
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
[HUFFS]
I know you asked for my vote.
But I had to make a decision.
[SIGHS DEEPLY] Of course.
That's your sibling.
I understand.
Blood is thicker than water.
I just want a peaceful life.
I also don't want us
to hold grudges.
Is that all?
My friend's coming.
I have to take care of him.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC BECOMES UNEASY]
I think a little
improvement here
could convince Papa to invest.
Seriously?
Have you already told him?
Yes, I've already told him.
Just assure him that our
investment will bring returns.
All the more reason to turn
this place around.
Bro, just give me
a few months.
We'll improve this.
I promise. I hope Uncle Ronald
can wait for it.
But why are you looking
for an investor?
The truth is...
I want my siblings and I to have
the upper hand
here at the hotel.
And an investor can
help us.
So, you are in a deadlock
with the other family?
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
I have to tilt the power
back to us.
And the family we share it with
won't back down.
You know they don't
easily give in, right?
[CLICKS TONGUE]
I hope you could get this.
If that's what you really want.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JUSTIN] Mom!
- Yes?
- Luna is now
the general manager of Hotel 88.
Wow! That's great!
I'll ask our nanny to prepare
a special dinner for us.
Yes.
- Let's celebrate!
- [FRIDA] Yes.
[JUSTIN CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC SWELLS]
[RAPHIE] The Almazans
might secure
being the General Manager.
So that means...
That Luna girl
will be our boss?!
- [GROANS]
- Well, it looks like it.
Monette, we should've voted
so Sir Martin won.
This is so unfair!
[MONETTE] What do you mean
by unfair? It was fair.
The voting already took place
with the lawyer present.
Plus, both sides agreed to it.
They didn't cheat, Raphie.
[SCOFFS] Whatever, Sir Michael
did all the work in this hotel.
[RAPHIE SIGHS] He built it
from the ground up.
Meanwhile, Sir Fred
just appeared out of nowhere!
We didn't even know
that he was involved, right?
[MONETTE] Shut up, Raphie!
Someone might here you!
I don't care!
I'm telling the truth!
I've been wondering
about that for ages!
- Like, why? Why?
- That's enough!
Even Kiko's confused
because of you.
[CHUCKLES] It's fine, Monette.
See? He's not bothered
because...
I'm telling the truth.
[SIGHS] Sir Jeff is becoming
an issue too...
Why don't we check his things?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
PLAYING, SWELLS]
- [DOOR OPENS]
- Gio.
[GIO] Kiko.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MONETTE] It's nowhere
to be found.
Everything is exactly
how we left it yesterday.
I think we should report it.
[RAPHIE] You're right.
Let's just report it.
- Raphie, talk to the police.
- [GIO] No.
No one report it to the police.
- But what about the--
- Don't say anything to them.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
That might make them panic more.
Let's get out of here.
- Let's go.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why did you bring Justin?
[LUNA SIGHS] I don't think
there's anything wrong
if he hears our conversation.
And he has a share
in this hotel.
Fine.
Might as well bring your sister
and I a cup of coffee.
- What?
- [MARTIN] I mean...
all you have to do
is call Monette,
and she'll bring it here.
Or you could bring
it here yourself.
[WHISPERS] Just do it.
- [CLICKS TONGUE] Tsk.
- [FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
[MARTIN] Here are
the hotel's files.
I already studied that.
And I can suggest...
- so the guests increase...
- Martin.
As an operations manager,
I think you should
focus on
the hotel's
day-to-day activities.
The hotel activities were
manageable
because we only had one guest.
[MARTIN] We should work on
increasing the guests.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[JUSTIN] I passed by Raphie.
He said he'd just
bring it here.
Fine.
Hotel 88 needs some promotion.
We've already set up a website.
And across all social media
platforms,
the hotel's accounts are active.
You? What's your suggestion
to boost our promotions?
- Well, I think we should--
- Actually, it would help
it would be helpful if
we got an influencer from
the island to promote.
I have done some research.
There's Edward Arellano.
Edward--
You got Edward
to promote for us?
[MARTIN] Yes.
Yes.
I tried to call him
to set up a meeting.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CROWD CHATTER]
[INHALES]
[EXHALES]
Jade?
It's Jade!
- Hi, Jade!
Come here, Jade!
- Let's draw!
- Right!
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[JADE] You're probably just
making me ugly, huh?
You turned my face into
your canvas. [GIGGLES]
No way!
You actually look so pretty.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
That's a promise, okay?
I wonder what I look like now.
- There he is!
- Oh!
- Who are you talking about?
- [EDWARD] Jade?
Edward.
Oh my God, it's really Edward.
[KIDS] Good morning, Sir Edward!
Good morning.
- [JADE CLEARS THROAT]
- Jade.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
What are you doing here?
[EDWARD SCOFFS]
[SIGHS]
You might be forgetting that...
we own this land.
I mean, we gave it to the people
so they could have
a place to live in.
I know that, but...
you don't really come here,
do you?
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why, Jade?
What do you know about me?
[JADE CLEARS THROAT]
But to answer your question,
I'm here because...
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Because I've chosen to hold
an outreach program here
since I came back.
What if we include Jade
in our activities today?
- Yes!
- No.
- Would you like that?
- Yes!
No.
Can you really turn them down?
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EDWARD] Stretch those legs!
[AMBIENT MUSIC PLAYING]
It might hurt now.
But always remember...
That in any sport,
stretching is important.
- [JADE PANTS]
- Sir Edward.
Sir.
Thank you.
[AMBIENT MUSIC CONTINUES]
You know, Edward,
why didn't you join us?
I'm good. I already
worked out earlier.
Okay! Six, seven, eight!
Okay, other arm!
EDWRD] Very good, kids!
- Jade, come on.
- You know what?
- I'm done.
- Okay, next!
- Jade will teach the next...
- Hey!
- ...stretching routine, okay?
- Edward!
What are you doing?
["PANGHABANG IKAW"
BY DARREN PLAYING]
Hold it.
Hey, kids, let's count.
- One, two...
- [KIDS] One, two, three...
Why did you run away
from me?
- ...five, six...
- What?
...seven, eight.
You gave me a flower.
Then you suddenly left me.
Edward, can we--
Can we...
...finish this first, okay?
[SIGHS]
Is it because you're
embarrassed of me
for what you did
to me at the--
Huh?
Really?
You really want to talk
about that here?
["PANGHABANG IKAW" CONTINUES]
Okay.
But just so you know,
I'm okay with it now.
Past is past.
[SIGHS]
Edward, we've been done
counting for a while.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- Very good! [CHUCKLES]
You're actually good
at stretching,
you never told me.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- Okay, next!
Just watch Jade, okay?
I need to take this.
- What?!
- Boys!
Edward!
Okay, kids. Next stretching.
[MAN] One... Two... Three...
- Four... Five...
Kids, hands on your waist!
Rotate!
- Seven...
- Eight...
- Okay!
[MOMMYLA]
Gio, your friend came here.
He's looking for you.
He said he's Bok.
Where are you right now?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
That's questionable in itself.
Only Gio knows about that.
Where's the guest's money?
I know this wasn't part
of our deal,
but I need you for this.
I don't know anything
about Hotel 88.
- You'll work with someone.
- Who?
- Me.
- Jade.
We need Edward
to execute my plan
of kicking the brothers
out of Hotel 88.
I really couldn't find
any jewelry.
[RAPHIE] What are you gonna do?
Return that?
Finders keepers, remember?