Michael owns
only 50 percent of Hotel 88.
We share ownership of this?
We want to buy your share.
You're full of yourself!
Who do you think you are?
- Martin, please.
- What?
Can't you hear
what your sister is saying?
I'll talk to my siblings.
I'll also talk to my siblings.
This is not just any hotel.
Don't sell Hotel 88.
Because this is your home.
And I want you to know...
If we lose this hotel,
we won't know what it is.
I'm here.
Oh, I'm sorry, sir.
We're not accepting guests yet
because the hotel
is still closed.
Yes, sir. My sister is right.
We're really sorry.
But your website says
the hotel is now open.
- Website?
- Huh?
Do we have a website?
All we have here
are spider webs, sir.
If you want,
I'll refer you to another hotel.
No. No need.
He can stay here.
Sir, our hotel's open.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, I wasn't informed.
Since when?
Now.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Hello, Philippines!
- And hello, world!
Alright! Welcome to Hotel 88!
The hotel that was once evicted.
Now, it's...
- ...back!
- Back!
Welcome, sir.
Welcome.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR CLICKS OPEN]
[DOOR SQUEAKS SHUT]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UNZIPPING]
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[WATER SLOSHING, SPLASHING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[WIND CHIMES TINKLING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FRED] Are you just
saying this after I told you
that Mike and I chose
to patch things up?
Fred, I told you a long time ago
that I wanted to leave.
It has nothing to do with that.
And then,
where are you going?
I applied as an immigrant.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS EXASPERATEDLY] What?!
You really want
to leave me, don't you?
I just want to live on my own.
[FRED SCOFFS]
- Please!
- Frida!
We're too old for that, Frida!
- Are you dead serious?!
- Exactly, Fred!
Our kids are all grown up now!
They can take care
of themselves.
I'm just thinking
this is the perfect time.
You are selfish!
You are being selfish!
Fred, you know we've had
an unhappy marriage for years.
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
Mike's the reason, isn't he?
After all these years,
- it's still Mike!
- No!
Mike has nothing to do with...
- what I want to happen...
- Oh, come on!
...with my life!
I give up!
Whatever happened
between Mike and me
is in the past.
I just want to move on!
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
[SNIFFLES, BREATHES SHAKILY]
[SNIFFLING, SOBBING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC BECOMES UNSETTLING]
[WATER SLOSHING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [CELLPHONE RINGING]
- [TAPPING]
Hello?
Have you read my e-mails?
[SIGHS] So, I'm right?
- [UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SIGHS DEEPLY]
These are the things that need
to be fixed at the hotel.
That's just my estimate, but...
It's not okay, is it?
[SIGHS] Alright.
Thank you again
for the consultation, bro.
I'll let you know
if we need a new accountant.
Okay. Thanks again.
- [SIGHS]
- [CELLPHONE THUDS]
- [UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SIGHS EXASPERATEDLY]
- [WAVES CRASHING]
- [WIND BLOWING]
- [OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BIRDS CHIRPING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [WIND CHIMES TINKLING]
[CELLPHONE BUZZING]
Hello?
Most probably,
it's in Mike's room.
I just don't know
where exactly it is.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
[DOOR CREAKS SHUT]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOORKNOB CLANKING]
[MUSIC SWELLS]
[DOORKNOB RATTLING, CLICKING]
[DOOR CLICKS OPEN]
[KIKO] Sir.
[DOOR CLICKS SHUT]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC BECOMES TENSE]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you need anything?
Ah, nothing.
Nothing.
Um...
I was just looking at the places
here in the hotel because...
this is different from the
places I've vacationed at.
Ah.
Well, this area is off-limits.
This is private.
Let's stay here instead.
Ah, really?
This is off-limits?
Why?
Is this the owners' room?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHUCKLES SLIGHTLY]
You know what,
just give me a tour.
So I'll know which areas here
are off-limits and which aren't.
Okay.
Alright, let's go.
This way, sir.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[RAPHIE] We only have one guest,
and you're still
overthinking like that?
I wouldn't overthink it
if he wasn't trying
to open Papa's room.
Maybe he just got lost?
Maybe there was traffic
on his way back to his room,
so he was just too
embarrassed to admit it.
Oh my god, Raphie! What?
Are you joking again?
Okay, what if...
What if he has other plans?
What if he's a thief?
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, Raphie.
- Are you okay?
- Huh?
I just have a feeling.
[KIKO] Really?
What is it?
Do you believe me now?
I can feel it now.
[EERIE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WIND CHIMES TINKLING]
[WIND BLOWING]
[WIND CHIME TINKLING DISTANTLY]
[EERIE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Leon?
[FOOTSTEPS]
[LUNA] Jade?
[EERIE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Jade?
Justin?
[EERIE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Who is that?
[CHIMES]
[GASPS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Mom!
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[RAPHIE] I have a feeling...
that something's coming.
Which one?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[RAPHIE] It's coming.
The festival is coming up!
- Oh my god.
- The festival's coming up!
I thought it was something else!
Isn't that a big deal
to you, Kiko?
When there's a festival,
there are many tourists.
When there are many tourists,
there's a lot of bookings!
[STUTTERS] Booking of guests!
Many guests will
book at our hotel.
Don't you want a lot of guests
to check-in at the hotel?
So just do your job properly
because that's for
our future guests.
Take this.
- [PILLS RATTLING]
- It'll help you fall asleep.
That's a strong dosage.
Thank you, dear.
You know, ever since Dad died...
I couldn't sleep either.
It was all so sudden.
I'm still in shock.
It hurts too much, Luna.
[SNIFFLES]
I know that I shouldn't be
thinking about this,
that I should be
thinking about you.
[FRIDA] About you, my children.
No, Mom.
Grieve.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
I'll stay here until
you fall asleep.
Do you know what's
on my mind, Mom?
What could they really
have fought about?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FREDERICO] Was Mike
responsible for this?
Mike is still the reason.
After all these years,
- it's still Mike!
- Wait, no!
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[LUNA] How did they get
to that point?
Of killing.
Isn't it connected to
their previous fight before?
They hadn't spoken for
more than 10 years.
That means it runs deep,
doesn't it?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Luna, let's not think
about those things.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Whatever the reason was...
it mattered so much that
they'd kill over it.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[GIO] Bro.
You just got
your commission, right?
Can you lend me some cash?
[MAN]
You're borrowing money again?
You know I won't ask you
if it isn't important.
I just need to pay Bok
so he'd leave me alone.
Bok? Don't you owe him
almost two million pesos?
Yes, that's why...
I'm asking for your help.
It doesn't have to be full.
Just half will do.
I'm also expecting money
from my father.
As soon as I get it,
I'll pay you.
With interest.
Bro, wherever you are,
just stay there for now.
Why?
Just lay low  while you still
don't have  the money to pay Bo.
Good luck.
Gio.
I'll call you later, bro.
What?
Martin's calling
for a family meeting.
"Family meeting?"
How formal.
Fine, I'll be there.
Martin and his brothers
aren't selling.
Aren't they just waiting
for us to raise our offer?
As of the moment,
we need to accept the fact
that we are co-owners.
And we have to work with them?
To reopen the hotel.
That's our best option
right now.
And we will cooperate.
No!
We can manage it without them.
[MARTIN] Yes.
But Luna won't just
let us call the shots.
As long as the division
of work is clear,
I'm fine with that.
It might even benefit us
to work with them.
Why would I want to work
with that Luna,
let alone the rest of
her siblings?
We have no choice.
It's official.
We have equal shares.
Do what you want!
I just need my money!
Why am I not surprised?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Can I...
...have the guest's deposit?
Huh?
What, you already want
an advance?
You know I badly need it
right now, don't you?
Yes, but we also need the money
to keep the hotel running.
The guest's payment
isn't even enough
to cover our expenses.
I won't gain anything
from this meeting.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You heard him loud and clear.
We can do what we want.
He didn't oppose us
working with the Almazans.
Leon, can I just work from home?
We'll see.
But when we're there, please...
Let's be civil with them.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What?
Why are you looking at me?
I'm saying this to everyone.
[SCOFFS]
You're right, Leon.
Be civil.
[JUSTIN SCOFFS]
Civil?
We don't want to
make things worse, do we?
You guys are good kids.
You, Leon...
Luna...
Justin...
Jade.
Maintain civility.
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
- Grandma?
- Hey, my dear grandson!
I'm glad you picked up.
I thought you had
forgotten about me.
Sorry, Grandma.
I missed your message last night
because I fell asleep early.
Have you taken your meds?
Of course. How could I forget?
Our neighbor, Preska,
kept coming here
to remind me to take
my meds
and check my blood pressure.
She's so fussy!
Well, I told her
to look after you.
I can take care of myself.
How about you?
How are you?
I'm fine, Grandma.
We're actually attending
to our first guest.
Oh!
You reopened the hotel?
That's great news! Really?!
It's just one person, Grandma.
I'm sure you'll have
a fully-booked  hotel in no tim!
Oh, I'm so happy for you!
But I also miss you so bad.
When are you coming home?
Don't worry. When I earn enough
I'll go home right away.
That's a promise.
Okay. Take care, alright?
[SULLEN MUSIC PLAYING]
What do you mean
we don't have money?
- Good day, sir.
- You're not bankrupt.
But the cash equivalents
of your business
is only enough to keep the
hotel running for six months.
Six months?
Hold on, Attorney.
I read the partnership contract.
It's right here.
The money Uncle Fred invested is
more than enough for six months.
[ATTORNEY] Yes.
The agreement states
that Mr. Almazan contributed
50 million in cash...
...on behalf and in trust
for his four children.
So, where is the 50 million?
I don't know.
It was just on paper.
Don't we have
any acknowledgment receipt,
deposit slip,
or anything that can prove
that Uncle Fred invested
that money?
What does that mean, Attorney?
Papa agreed to give the Almazans
a share of this hotel for free?
[ATTORNEY] Look, I'm just
telling you what I know.
The 50 million
is nowhere to be found
and the hotel owes the bank
money that you need to pay.
We have to pay off
the hotel's debts?
Yes. And if you fail to do so...
We'll lose the hotel.
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
[RAPHIE]
Here's your order, sir.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[GIO] Our father
really is
the best, huh?
He made us inherit a hotel
with a mountain of problems!
Blaming Papa
won't do us any good.
What we should focus on
is generating money
so we don't lose the hotel
in six months.
Don't you think it's odd?
If Papa agreed to share
the hotel with Uncle Fred,
it would mean he's
a generous friend.
So what?
Why would he shoot Uncle Fred
if he agreed to share the hotel
in the first place?
Maybe Uncle Fred triggered him
by asking for a bigger share.
They might've been drunk
when they made that agreement.
I don't know what to think.
Only Papa and Uncle Fred
could answer that.
but they're gone.
So, if I were you,
I'd just focus on
making the hotel profitable.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Our guest does look suspicious.
He almost went
into Sir Mike's room
and now he's listening in
on the brothers' conversation.
I believe Kiko now.
What are we going to do?
For now, we stay put.
I thought you believed Kiko.
Yeah, but he hasn't done
anything to harm us.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'd better go back to work.
We also need to hire
additional staff.
Monette and Raphie
can't do all the work here.
[MARTIN] We'll get there.
They can't make decisions
without consulting us.
What do they think of us?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You accepted a guest
and you didn't tell us?
It was all so sudden.
But we did inform you.
Just admit you want this hotel
all for yourselves.
You should thank us
for accepting guests.
That way, we can earn money
to pay off this hotel's debts.
[MARTIN] A loan was taken out
under the hotel's name.
The hotel was signed off
as collateral.
Why don't you use Dad's
contribution to pay it off?
Your Dad didn't
contribute a penny!
Our attorney checked everything.
We received nothing.
That's a lie.
Where did you put
the money, huh?
We wouldn't be in debt
if we have the 50 million.
The agreement shouldn't be valid
because your father
didn't do his end of the deal.
We don't even know
he convinced Papa
to give him shares without
getting anything in return.
For sure Uncle Mike
had a reason to agree.
No matter what you say,
the agreement is legal.
Why don't we focus
on the hotel?
Our funds are only good
for six months.
And if we don't make this
hotel operational,
we'd end up with nothing.
We won't be able
to pay the bank.
Okay, fine!
Let's reopen the hotel.
We'll use whatever money
it'll make to pay the bank.
It's not going to be that easy.
What we need is structure.
We need a general manager
to lead this hotel's operations.
And I think that's me.
[LUNA LAUGHS IN DISDAIN]
Oh, no, no, no, no.
You are not the only one who
knows how to run a business.
[JADE] Right.
You can do it.
Right, Leon?
I can do it!
You already kept your shares.
Leave the leadership to us.
We want things to be fair?
Let's vote on it.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
There's four of them
and only three of us.
Leon will vote for me.
What confidence you have.
Martin is your best friend,
but I am your sister.
- I have your vote, right?
- Even if you're his friend,
you're going against
his sister!
Your vote will determine who
will be the general manager
of Hotel 88.
Bok, you're crazy!
I told you I pay, didn't I?!
Don't wait until I give
your grandma another visit.
If only I could
revoke their shares.
Have they done any misconduct
that goes against the agreement?
Just one mistake, and they can
legally take this away from us.
- This looks bad.
- If you trust each other,
would you kill each other?
Are you saying
someone else killed them?
No!
- Aah!
- Watch out!
You almost broke  my earring!
I know that earring.