It was supposed to be
your reconciliation dinner.
But this is what happened.
What? Can't show any concern?
When my mother died,
we lost touch.
There's no more point for me to
stay here now that he's gone!
Son, it's okay to cry, okay?
Uncle Frederico killed Papa?
No! That's not true!
- My daddy is not a murderer!
- [GUNSHOTS]
Mr. Michael Fernandez and
Mr. Frederico Almazan
killed each other.
This case is closed.
Papa, we're here now.
And we're complete.
Mr. Fernandez has long
since settled his will.
He left all his possessions
to his three children.
To you, Gio Cabrera,
Martin Madrigal,
and Francis Endaya.
All of his properties will be
divided equally among us three,
Including this hotel?
Michael only owns
50 percent of Hotel 88.
What? Someone else
owns shares of this hotel?
[ATTORNEY]
A recent agreement was made...
...that 50 percent is owned
by Michael,
while the other 50 percent
goes directly to the
Almazan family.
What?! That family?!
According to investigations,
Attorney,
Uncle Frederico killed
our father.
Investigations show
that they killed each other.
That's the same thing, Kiko!
Uncle Fred killed Papa!
And they have a share
in this hotel that Papa built?
That's unfair to us!
The merger happened
before the tragedy.
To be specific,
the other 50 percent
mentioned in the agreement
will go only to Frederico
Almazan's children.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
You heard our lawyer.
You all have a share
in Hotel 88.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Is that the reason
Uncle Michael and Dad made up?
So we can be part-owners
of the hotel?
Your dad didn't mention
anything about that.
Maybe that's the reason
Uncle Michael killed Dad.
Jade, the cops said
they killed each other.
Leon, investigations show
Uncle Michael fired first.
It means he was the one
with the intent to kill.
My point is,
we don't know how they
ended up in that situation.
And my point is,
whatever their reason is,
Dad is gone.
The issue now is...
our stakes at the hotel.
Okay?
What are we going to do
about our shares?
Can't we just leave
the hotel to them?
Dad had other businesses
he left behind.
I need your help with them.
I agree.
You know what? I don't want
to be a part of anything
related to Uncle Michael.
But Dad wanted this for us.
That's why he gave us
50 percent shares.
I just want a
peaceful life, Luna.
And I want justice for Dad!
Luna, Leon...
Now is not the time to argue.
All I'm saying is this is
what Dad wanted for us.
Can't we do this for him?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KIKO]
You want to sell it?
Yes.
You can't.
This is Papa's legacy.
I have the right to do
what I want with my shares.
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
Papa left the hotel
with all three of us.
We must decide together.
What do you think, Martin?
How about I sell you my shares?
Do you have the funds?
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
Well, Martin?
I still have to look at the
pros and cons.
At the end of the day,
this is still a promising
business opportunity.
If you can't afford it,
I'll sell it to someone else.
Can you not be in such
a hurry to sell the hotel?
Papa just died
and you already want to
dispose of his legacy?
He wanted us to keep
the hotel running, remember?
All of us three, together.
He wanted us to start again.
Shouldn't we at least try?
All I'm saying is,
I need money.
Money, not a pain
in the neck, Kiko.
[SCOFFS]
[MUSIC BOX PLAYING "FUR ELISE"
BY LUDWIG VAN BEETHOVEN]
[FREDERICO]
The mistakes we make...
...are what makes us
stronger in life.
So no matter what happened,
I want you to remember
that I accept you, dear.
I accept you.
[VOICE SHAKING]
Dad...
Dad. [SNIFFLES]
Dad, I'm sorry.
[WHIMPERS]
Dad... [SNIFFLES]
[BREATH QUIVERS]
[SOBBING] I'm sorry, Dad!
Dear...
Dear, it's okay.
I'm scared. I'm scared, Dad.
Daddy's here. Okay?
[CRIES]
You don't have to worry
about anything anymore.
I'll take care of it.
Just leave everything
you've done here, okay?
And you're coming home with me.
I'll fix everything
for you, okay?
- [SOBS]
- Stop crying.
[CRANKS]
- I kept this in the car.
- [MUSIC BOX PLAYING]
I've been hoping
you'd come home to us.
[MUSIC BOX CONTINUES PLAYING]
[LUNA] I promise, Dad.
I will do everything for you.
For our family.
No matter what it takes.
What's the emergency?
We have guests.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Or should I say...
...co-owners.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What are you doing here?
We have a right to this place.
We know.
But you shouldn't have
come unannounced.
I'll go straight to the point.
We want to buy your shares.
Who told you we're selling?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Buy us out?
Are you joking?
Do I look like I'm joking?
I think it's better
if you just leave
because we're not selling
this place.
Are you seriously
kicking us out?
Technically, this place
belongs to us too, doesn't it?
It's not like that, I just--
That's exactly what
you wanted to say, right, Kiko?
Which is funny.
- Coming from you?
- [MARTIN] Coming from you?
What does that even mean?
You're talking like
you're somebody.
What?
I know you, Luna.
I know everything you've done.
- Martin, please.
- What?
Can't you hear
what your sister's saying?
I'm sure she means
nothing by it.
- Yeah, sure, sure.
- Right, Luna?
Leon, please.
- Don't take their side!
- [GIO] Fine, fine!
Take my share.
Let's just finish this!
How much?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Two million.
You can take it now, cash.
Same goes for everyone.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
No.
Shove that money in your chest!
Hey, don't talk
to her like that!
Hey!
That's enough! Enough!
Can we stop? Enough!
Come on!
We're not kids anymore.
[HUFFS] Your sister's
the one losing it.
Let's talk this out calmly.
You're the ones
who just barged in!
- Just leave already!
- [LUNA] No, no!
We have a stake here too,
right?
This conversation's
going nowhere!
This one's going
to go somewhere!
- Go on, try me!
- Let go of me!
Enough! Enough!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Jade, Luna, let's go!
- No, Leon, no!
- We do have a stake here!
- I said let's go!
Let's go!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LEON] Come on!
Justin!
- Let's go, Justin.
- Let's go.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
You shouldn't have said
you'd sell the shares.
I need the money, okay!
Hey, hey, hey, eat first.
Bro, didn't you think about
whether they can be trusted?
Why did our fathers
even end up like that?
It means he was furious
at Uncle Fed,
and you still want
to sell to them?
[MONETTE] Wait, remember, okay?
There are only three of you,
there are four of them.
- So?
- You're clearly outnumbered.
So you should stick together,
not fight.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
Ma?
Ma, Ma, Ma!
Ma! Ma, no--
Ma!
- Oh my God, Ma!
- [GROANS]
Ma...
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
You scared me, Ma.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I fell asleep.
I was waiting for you.
[PILLS RATTLING]
Tell me, what happened?
[SIGHS]
They don't want to sell, Ma.
But I'll do everything
to get it from them.
Are you sure
that's what your Dad wanted?
[SIGHS]
I don't know, Ma.
All I know is Dad
needs justice.
And this is the only way
I can give it to him.
This is what you want too
for him, right, Ma?
[SOBBING SOFTLY]
Of course.
Of course, dear.
Yes.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
Draw something
that makes you happy.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Ugh.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Dad...
This is so hard, Dad.
I miss you.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
But I'll try.
I'll try because I know
this is what you'd want for me.
- [EDWARD PANTING]
- [SIGHS] Okay, Jade.
Okay, Jade.
Let's find something
that makes you happy.
["PANGHABANG IKAW"
BY DARREN PLAYING]
CONTINUES PLAYING]
["PANGHABANG IKAW"
- Hey!
- Oh!
What is that?
You're giving it to me?
- Jade!
- [JADE CHUCKLING]
I'm sorry for what I said
to Luna.
I just got carried away.
I know.
What are you planning
to do with the hotel?
Honestly...
...I don't know yet.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Our dads killed each other!
Did you ever think
that would happen?
No.
Not ever.
[SNIFFLING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Can we...
...not fight over the hotel?
I'll talk to my siblings.
I'll talk to my brothers too.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
It would be a shame if you'd
just abandon the hotel.
We can still
continue operating.
You're good at this.
You can get it
back on its feet.
[SIGHS] What choice do we have?
- [FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
[KIKO] Let's go downstairs.
So, we won't be selling it
anymore, right?
That means we can
open the hotel for business.
Whether we'll be selling it
or not,
we need to know its status.
What needs replacing
or repairing.
[OBJECTS THUD]
[CLICKING]
Looks like
a lot needs replacing.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR OPENS, CREAKS]
Papa's room
still looks the same.
[DOOR CLOSES]
But there are
a lot more things here now.
- [PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [OBJECT CLINKS]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh, Martin.
Do you remember this drawer?
There would always be
chips here for us.
[MARTIN]
That drawer looks worn out.
We may need to replace it, too.
This used to be my favorite.
Papa used to be fond
of recording, right?
[OBJECT RUSTLES]
Chips and a videocam?
What a way to chill.
Oh, maybe we still have
a video here
while we were swimming.
[CAMERA CLICKS, CHIMES]
[STATIC NOISE]
[MICHAEL BREATHES DEEPLY]
Kids.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GIO] Do you really want
to watch that?
Don't play it.
If you don't want it,
that's fine.
I'll just tell you
all about it later.
[MICHAEL] Kids.
If you're watching this
right now,
I probably didn't have
the chance
to say it to you in person.
I had my fair share
of shortcomings as a dad.
Moments when I fell short.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
I've failed you
in so many ways.
Many of them I might not
be able to make it up to.
When weakness....
got the better of me.
Moments where
I wish I had more courage so...
I could've fought harder
for what's yours.
What's for us.
[MICHAEL SIGHS] Unfortunately,
your father is weak.
I just let destiny
decide for me.
Kids,
if you're ever unable
to forgive me,
I'll understand.
I guess I don't deserve it.
But Gio,
Martin, Kiko...
[TONGUE CLICKS]
I love you all so much.
In fact,
everything I did,
every decision I made,
even the wrong decisions,
I did all of it to protect you.
I want your future
to be secured.
[TONGUE CLICKS] Here.
Here at this hotel.
Hotel 88.
This place is filled
with beautiful memories.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
That's why
I'm sincerely asking you,
please don't sell Hotel 88.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Because this is your home.
And I want you to know,
- [STATIC NOISE]
- that there's a hidden--
Oh... what happened?
The file is likely
to be corrupted.
Forget it.
He's saying nonsense.
[KIKO] Didn't you hear him?
He said there's something
we need to know.
And I think
that if we lose this hotel,
we'll never be able to find out
what that is.
I just need money, ASAP.
[MARTIN] It's not easy to sell
a property of this size.
Okay?
It will take time.
You know that.
You're in real estate.
So I don't think that's
the solution to your problem.
What are you trying to say?
What I'm trying to say is that
if we make this hotel
operational,
you'll be able to earn extra.
The three of us will be able
to profit from it.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC TURNS FOREBODING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
I'm here.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
The re-opening of the hotel
will push through.
We have to treat them kindly.
Was that meant for me?
There's no 50 million pesos
and the hotel owes money
to the bank.
If it doesn't get settled...
We'll lose the hotel.
They left a hotel
and tons of problems.
We only have one guest,
and now you think ill of him.
Do you need anything?
Who knows
what he could be up to?
What if he's a thief?
[WIND CHIMES CLINKING]