You rejected all of
my suggestions for a DJ?
- It's expensive!
- You want something cheap?
Then you do it yourself
so it's free!
You've been gone from there
for more than a year.
Will they still recognize
Luna Almazan?
They know Luna,
but they don't know Solenn.
[CHUCKLES]
I hope we're always like this.
I want to visit my brother.
Since his Papa Mike
passed away...
I want to do something
nice for him, and this is it.
"U" for...
"Utusero!" (Bossy!)
Sir!
You gave me
so many orders!
You really need to hire
an assistant.
Raphie, did you post it?
I posted the correct
time and place
so that many people would see
that you're looking
for an assistant.
So why is it that until now
not one of them is here?
Where are they?!
[SARI] Universe!
Please make it happen!
Universe, give this to me.
This is mine now, universe.
Universe...
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
Good morning, y'all!
- [CHUCKLES]
- [PHONE RINGING]
Oh!
- [PHONE CHIMES]
- Hello, Grandpa?
Hello, Sari?
Where are you now?
I'm already here.
I'm just waiting for the boat.
Well of course, Grandpa!
Who else would
they pick but me?
Just me and no one else.
What?
Someone else already got hired?
Huh?!
They already hired someone
from Hotel 88?
They hired someone else?
[WOMAN 1] Miss, did they hire
someone already?
Then why are we still
going there?
Someone else already got hired?
- Let's just leave.
- Let's go.
- Hello, Grandpa!
- Sari?
- Grandpa, I can't understand.
- Who's the deaf one here?
- You or me?
- What are you saying, Grandpa?
No, I'm asking you
if someone else already got it.
Universe, this is mine!
[CHUCKLES SLIGHTLY]
I'll just call you later, okay?
- I'll update you.
- [MAN] Oh, Solara island!
- Solara island!
- Okay, Grandpa! Bye!
Me! Me! Me!
Where are the others?
Oh, I don't know.
They suddenly left.
Maybe they got tired of waiting.
I thought they were going
to apply at Hotel 88?
That's what I thought too.
But it turns out
I'm the one and only
future assistant of Hotel 88!
[CHUCKLES]
- Let's go! Let's go!
- Let's go!
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Raphie.
Are we expecting a guest?
What's Martin doing there?
[GIO] He's hiring
an executive assistant.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Assistant?
I don't even have an assistant,
and he's getting one?
Relax. Don't worry.
He's the one paying the salary.
It won't come out of the
hotel's magical budget.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CUP CLINKS]
[SIGHS]
[GIO] Cup noodles?
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CUP CLINKS]
[CUP NOODLES CLINKS]
[SIGHS]
[CHUCKLES SLIGHTLY]
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Bro, uh...
Do you have
any recommendations
for an assistant?
I would greatly appreciate it.
If I don't find anyone here,
maybe you might know
someone.
Goodness! Sir really can't wait.
[BOAT ENGINE HUMMING]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh, are they here?
[STAMMERS] T-There!
There they are! Sir! Sir Martin!
Sir Martin, they're here!
They're here! They're here!
- [BOAT ENGINE HUMMING]
- [SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Just one?
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SARI] Ma! Pa!
I've been waiting for so long.
How long will I be alone?
Grandpa said I would meet
my soulmate.
Because one day,
the sky will cry...
...and its tears
will fall to the ground.
- But when will that happen?
- [THUNDER RUMBLING]
- [RAIN POURING]
["SILONG KA MUNA"
BY BRYAN CHONG PLAYING]
[SARI] Back then, I asked
the universe for signs
that I would meet
my soulmate...
That one day...
the sky would cry
and its tears would fall
to the ground.
["SILONG KA MUNA" CONTINUES]
They say...
just because you want something
doesn't mean you'll get it.
But I say,
if it's truly meant for me,
then it's something
worth fighting for, sis!
["SILONG KA MUNA" CONTINUES]
You're so good, universe!
Just you?
Yes, sir.
Just me.
All yours, completely.
["SILONG KA MUNA" CONTINUES]
I need someone
who's good with scheduling.
I'm the class secretary
since fifth grade.
I even record the boatman's
schedule as a hobby.
Can you work under pressure?
Sir, even if you put me
in a pressure cooker,
I'll never be soft nor weak.
I don't want an employee
who chooses her tasks.
I'll shine your shoes,
I'll make you fried water,
and even if you make me count
all the tiles in this hotel,
I won't complain.
Sir?
Flower?
Or would you like a heart?
I can do that, too.
Am I hired?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYS]
[XANDER]
Alright, pose. Nice one.
Okay, one more.
- Alright.
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
Now, move closer.
Alright.
After this, let's do
a photoshoot in the rooms.
Aren't we going to the beach?
I was looking forward to it.
So, do I just have to wear
a bathrobe now?
Bathrobe?
Come on, Jade.
I need to see the beach.
It's part of my promotion
for Hotel 88.
[SIGHS]
Okay, fine. Fine.
Let's go to the beach
after this, okay?
[LIGHTHEARTED MUSIC PLAYING]
Excuse me.
["PANGHABANG IKAW"
BY DARREN PLAYING]
[WATER SPLASHES]
Mister Xander,
can we go over here by the pool?
[STAMMERING] Let's take photos.
Take many photos.
One wide shot, and...
[JADE] Yeah, that's good.
And hurry up,
we're going to the beach next.
Also, take a close-up shot.
A bit closer...
Yeah, that's perfect.
That's perfect.
[JADE] Excuse me,
you're kind of in the frame.
C-Can you move a bit?
A bit-- Alright. Sorry,
we're just doing promos.
Keep clicking, go on.
Can you up the brightness
a bit, too?
Okay. Thank you.
Remember, okay?
Don't take a bath
for three weeks.
- A sponge bath will do.
- Yes, sir.
- Go on now.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, sir.
- Alright.
Grandpa! Grandpa!
Grandpa!
- Oh?
- Oh...
Blessings, Grandpa.
- What is it?
- It's a success!
- What?
- A success, Grandpa!
- Grandpa!
- Yes?
I just got hired at Hotel 88!
What?! You got fired?
- Now, why did you--
- No, Grandpa!
Hired! I got hired!
- H-hired?
- I got hired!
At the Hotel 88?
[BOTH CHEERING]
Who wouldn't want you
as their employee?
No one, of course!
- But, Grandpa...
- Oh?
The boss is so handsome!
He cheeks are so rosy,
I want to bite into them!
Hey, Sari! That's bad.
Uh... [CHUCKLES]
- I'm just kidding.
- Mm?
I'm probably just hungry.
That's why I want
to bite into something.
Hmm?
- But, Grandpa...
- What?
- You know...
- What's this?
Tell me what the future holds
for me and Sir Martin!
Not right now!
Yes, why not?
- Starting tomorrow...
- Mm.
[SIGHS]
Tomorrow will be my first day
as an executive assistant
at Hotel 88.
[SQUEALS]
[BOTH CHEER]
Grandpa!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC TURNS SINISTER]
[GRUNTS, GROANS]
[GROANING, CHOKES]
[GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[PANTING]
[BLOWS LAND]
[GROANS]
[KICK LANDS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Diana, don't forget
about tomorrow.
Get all the things I ordered
from the Italian restaurant
in town.
It's for Justin's birthday
tomorrow.
Thank you.
Jade.
Should I make you some dinner?
I'm still full.
Then maybe you can help me.
It's Justin's birthday tomorrow.
Can you help me plan
a surprise for him?
I'll do it if that's
what you want to hear.
Jade...
I'm gonna take a rest, Mom.
I've told you the truth.
I hope you believe me.
[SIGHS]
What I believe right now,
is that you want
to be out of our lives.
Good night, Mom.
Jade...
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYS]
[PANTING]
[GROANING IN PAIN]
[GROANS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYS]
Who knew my clients
could actually be useful?
They're all increasing
the likes on the post.
[PHONE DINGS]
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[SCOFFS]
Well, look at that, it looks
like Gio's earning money.
We're finally getting our money.
Good thing we pulled
a fast one on Gio.
That item you made him sell
was so easy to steal.
Once he pays me 400,000,
we'll keep milking Gio
for more money.
- [LAUGHTER]
- This fool is so easy to scam.
A lot of people are interested
in our hotel.
Martin mentioned that...
a lot of people are booking us.
That's because
of Edward's efforts.
He made one post...
and the feedback was great.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
People are also booking
for the music fest.
It's thanks to Edward that we're
getting all these reservations.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Gio, what are you doing?
Gio...
Tell me the truth.
You still have feelings
for me, don't you?
You're pretty shameless,
aren't you?
You're being
so snappy with me.
If you really don't have
any feelings...
you should be indifferent.
You're overthinking this again.
Do you want to know
what I'm thinking of?
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
If you have
nothing more to say...
What?
Are you going
to kick me out again?
You're not really
over me yet.
Is this what
you're talking about?
I can do it.
Can you?
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
You just dropped by, right?
You're not working today.
- Go ahead.
- Okay.
[MARTIN] This house
is off limits to the guests.
My brothers
and I lived here.
How about me, sir?
Can I stay here too?
Only if I'm there,
Understood?
Copy. Noted. Got it.
I can handle it. [GIGGLES]
[SIGHS] We'll go up
to the hotel.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm in charge today because
the GM isn't there right now.
Actually, all the Almazans.
Call the supplier of toiletries,
we need more stocks.
Then call the technician,
we need the rooms checked.
- Are you listing this?
- Yes, sir.
Here, and in here.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GROANS]
Is that it? This is it!
It's beautiful! I've only
seen this in pictures.
It's beautiful!
Look-- Oh! I'm sorry!
- Excuse me.
- I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
Hey, I'm sorry!
[SCOFFS] Her head is hotter than
the sun here on the island.
[MAN] Island Solara?
Right here!
- Let me carry those, ma'am.
- Are you going to Hotel 88?
- Yes.
- Are you a guest there?
Obviously. And you?
I'm a guest there too!
There is no CCTV
in the area you mentioned.
I knew it.
Have the other CCTVs
in that town checked.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you really sure that...
you didn't see
that person's face?
Just to be sure.
It's been a long time since
someone attacked me like that.
It started when I drabbled with
the Almazan and Fernandez case.
Which one of them do
you suspect?
[HENRI] I don't know.
But I'm sure someone
wants to keep me quiet.
So I don't have to look
into that case.
This case
isn't over yet, Marina.
I need to know more about
Michael and Federico's deaths.
[HENRI EXHALES]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
When you get to Mr. Felipe
tell him to get
my usual order cheese
and cold cuts.
Tell him to add more
salted pork belly, alright?
Remember my instructions.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
I've done what
you told me to do, ma'am.
[MUSIC SWELLS]
Are you sure?
Yes, ma'am.
Alright. Thank you.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Give me the VIP room!
The most expensive one!
- This is the VIP, right?
- Uh, yes.
We can't just avoid
each other all the time!
Do you want to know the truth?
If you weren't my sister,
I would've punched you
because of how wrong
your timing is!
- [SQUEALS] Hi, sissy!
- [GASPS] Oh.
- She's my assistant.
- Ah... assistant.
- Surprise!
- Aren't they mourning?
Aunt Frida wasn't there when we
went to the crime scene, right?
Could she have something
to do with their deaths?
Mrs. Almazan, where were you
when Michael Fernandez
and Federico Almazan died?