[GRUNTS]
Jade. [GRUNTS]
Jade.
[SOBS]
I'm so sorry I was too late.
Mom, it's not your fault.
Okay?
Michael Fernandez's sons
need help.
They were attacked.
- Gio!
- Don't let go!
Hold on, please!
Nurse,
please save my brother!
- We need to check you.
- No!
Prioritize our brother.
His condition is critical.
What do we do, Martin?
Bok will come after us.
No. The police are
looking for him, okay?
Even his accomplices.
Bok?
[HOTEL STAFF]
You're not coming, sir?
Yes.
Just tell them.
[UTENSILS CLINKING]
[ROI] I didn't kill them!
I didn't kill Michael!
And I didn't kill Federico!
They were already dead
when I found them!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm glad you're going
back to the office, Leon.
You know...
Dad wouldn't be happy if
you neglected his businesses.
I want to make sure
you and Mom are okay
before I go back
to work on-site.
Thank you, Leon.
I already prepared
Mom's stuff for Spain, Leon.
[JOSH]
Even though I'll miss Mom...
I agree that
she should stay there,
especially after what happened.
What if...
I go with her?
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
That won't be necessary,
Justin.
Aunt Yayo will keep
Mom company.
[LEON] Mom's better off
with Aunt Yayo.
If one of us went with her,
she wouldn't be able to rest
because she would be
taking care of us.
So, this is it?
Life goes on for Mom.
Everything's back to normal?
No.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Is there something wrong,
Leon?
Uh...
No.
Nothing's wrong.
But I think
we should talk to
Martin and his brothers.
Something bad
happened to them too.
We need to
check on them also.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
That's all, sir.
Thank you
for your cooperation.
Good thing
you can go home now.
Sir, has Bok been found?
Did you catch him?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes.
Including his accomplices.
But Bok is dead already.
[MARTIN] Dead?
How? Did he fight back?
We found him
in the location you provided.
He tried to escape,
but by the time we found him,
he was already dead.
Jeez.
All we wanted was for him to
stay away from Gio,
not for him to die.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TAPPING]
[STIRRING MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[LAPTOP WHIRS]
[CLACKS]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[BEEP]
[CLACKING CONTINUES]
[LEON] Jade's birthday?
[CHIMES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[LEON] Dad dealt with
a lot of people
in his business transactions.
Which one of them has  motive
to kill him and Uncle Mike?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CLACKS]
"Dear Mr. Almazan,
Thank you for your payment
of 322,475.01..."
[LEON] This was just
a few days before he died.
But no package for him
was delivered.
What is this expensive purchase?
[CAMERA CLICKS]
[DOOR OPENS, SLAMS]
[JUSTIN] Leon?
What are you doing here?
I'm just checking some
of Dad's transactions.
- I can help you find it.
- No.
I've found it.
Do you need anything?
Ah, no.
Luna's looking for you.
It's time to eat.
I'm not eating.
I'm leaving.
I have something
to take care of.
- At the hotel? Because--
- No.
At the office.
At Dad's office?
Yes.
There's an emergency.
So I have to leave.
Could you give me a ride?
I don't want to eat lunch here.
No.
I mean...
Luna cooked lunch already.
Eat here so her
efforts don't go to waste.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[JUSTIN] Why do you have
Dad's laptop, Leon?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [RAPHIE] Hello, Philippines!
- [SARI] And hello world!
[CHESKA] Welcome to Hotel 88!
[RAPHIE] The hotel
that's waiting...
...for Gio who has returned!
- Yeah!
- Welcome back, Sir Gio!
- Welcome, Sir Gio!
- Ah!
- [TRIXIE] Welcome back!
- [CHESKA] Oh!
[TRIXIE] I'm sorry, this is all
I could make.
Welcome back
to my brother's brother!
[TRIXIE CHUCKLES]
[MONETTE] Come, let's stay
where you're safe,
and away
from a dangerous life!
[CHESKA CHUCKLES]
Thank you.
Thank you to all of you.
[RAPHIE] Aww, let's go, sir!
[MONETTE] And, since the
brothers are complete again...
Dinner will be special!
[ALL] Yay!
[RAPHIE] My sister's so great!
Come on!
[SARI] Sir, welcome back
as well.
Sari, I'm not the one
you should be welcoming back.
Sir, I welcome you into my life
every single day.
That's my job
as your one and only assistant.
Your one and only assistant.
Sari.
I want to tell you something.
Then just say it, Sari.
I just wanted to say that...
If Sir Gio returned today,
tomorrow, it'll be Ma'am Luna.
She called to say
she'll return tomorrow.
- I thought it's something else.
- That's all, sir!
You're going back to Manila?
Is there an emergency
with your grandmother?
Grandma's fine.
I just feel like I have
no more reason to stay here.
What do you mean no reason?
You are a part of this hotel.
You are one of the owners.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
A co-owner who brought trouble.
I know how Bok thinks.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I should've known he was
going to cause trouble here.
You shouldn't have
been involved.
If we really didn't want
to get involved,
then we should've left you
right when he was chasing you.
Or we should've made you leave
during the music fest.
[KIKO] But we didn't.
Because we want you here.
No matter if there's chaos
or not.
[MARTIN] If you're worried
about your grandma,
you can just bring her here.
Or I can arrange something
in Manila,
so that someone can look
after her.
Didn't I tell you
from the beginning?
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I needed the money,
that's why I went here.
But Bok's gone now.
I don't owe a debt anymore,
I shouldn't--
[KIKO] What about us?
Can't we be a reason
for you not to leave?
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I don't want you to get
in trouble because of me.
Are we really going
to separate now?
After everything
that has happened?
No one is leaving this family.
[KIKO SCOFFS] Unfortunately,
we're your brothers.
We won't let you
out of our lives.
And this?
I'll bring this to my room.
Or maybe I should put all
of your things there,
so you won't leave.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
I want to know the truth.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
I told you, didn't I?
Yes, I did kidnap Jade.
I'm not denying that.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
But no matter what you do,
you can't accuse me
for your father's death.
If you didn't kill them,
then what do you know?
What did you see?
- [SLAMS]
- For God's sake, Roi!
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Yes, I was there.
I was at the place
where sir died.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
I accompanied Frida.
[FRIDA] Roi, hurry up.
We need to catch them.
Yes, ma'am.
[ROI] Ma'am, the road ends here.
Ma'am! Wait, ma'am!
- Fred!
- [ROI] Ma'am!
Fred! [BREATHING RAPIDLY]
- Fred! Roi!
- [ROI] Ma'am!
Ma'am, you should return
to the hotel.
I'll take care of this.
Your kids are waiting for you.
Promise me, Roi,
you'll bring home Fred and Mike.
[ROI] Frida is important to m.
I don't want her hurt.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
That's why I'm the one
who went looking for them.
I have nothing
to do with it!
[FEDERICO] What do you mean
nothing?!
You know that...
[ROI] I could hear them.
[MICHAEL] He just wanted me
to be his business partner!
[ROI] I was close.
[MICHAEL] But I didn't
accept it!
[ROI] But I was distracted
for just a while...
when...
Bang!
A gun went off.
[ROI] And when I looked
at them...
They were already dead
on the ground.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
[GULPS]
Who shot them?
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
I don't know, Leon.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
I don't know.
But I'm sure...
It's not me.
[HANDCUFFS CLANGING]
They didn't kill each other.
There was someone else.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LAUGHING MANIACALLY]
What's so funny? Huh?
There's someone else.
No...
I just realized something.
How easy it is for you...
to pin your father's death
on me.
Because you're the only one
with a motive.
If I wanted your father dead,
I would've done it
a long time ago!
So I could've had Frida
all to myself.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Your mother is miserable
because of her husband.
And I'm the only one, Leon...
[HANDCUFFS RATTLE]
I'm the only one
who can make her happy.
But you ruined it.
You ruined everything!
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
I love Frida.
- I love her so much--
- [SLAMS TABLE]
[LEON]
You've really lost it.
Four times.
I heard the gun go off
four times.
But what does
the police report say?
Just two?
That's not true.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I heard it clearly.
Four.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Bang! Bang!
They altered
the police report.
Four.
So don't trust them.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
And if you think
that locking me up in here...
means you've given justice
for your father's death,
you're wrong.
Because the real killer...
is still out there.
[MUSIC BECOMES GRIM]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[FEDERICO] Leon.
Please remember...
This never happened.
Okay?
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE CHIMES]
Where are you?
I'm already here at Hotel 88.
[ENGINE REVVING]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [GRUNTING]
- [GROANING]
- [BLADE STRIKES]
- [YELLS IN PAIN]
- [BLOWS LAND]
- [GROANING]
[KICK LANDS]
Dad?
[GROANING]
[GROANING CONTINUES]
[HANDBRAKE CLICKS]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[BODY SLAMS INTO CAR]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Dad?
Who was that?
Son.
You need to leave, please.
Uncle Mike?
He's dead.
He's dead, Dad.
- He's dead, Dad.
- Leon.
- Leon. Leon.
- He's dead, Dad. He's dead.
You have to go.
Come on. Please?
- Come on, Dad. Let's go!
- No.
No. You go ahead.
Son, you need to go, please.
Go now.
- Dad, come on! Let's go!
- No.
No, you go first. Go on.
- Come on. You go first.
- But--
We've got this.
Go.
- Dad, come on!
- Be careful, please.
Go.
- Go ahead. [CAR DOOR CLOSES]
- Dad!
Go home!
[ENGINE STARTS]
Come on.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNIFFLES, BREATHES DEEPLY]
[CAR ENGINE HUMMING IN DISTANCE]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Dad.
Who was that?
Dad!
Dad, who was that?
Is he an enemy of
you and Uncle Mike?
Why did he hurt you?
Dad.
- Dad, talk to me!
- Look.
You don't have to worry
about anything.
Uncle Mike and I
have everything sorted out.
Leon.
Please remember,
this never happened.
Okay? This never happened.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Never happened?
Dad, I killed someone!
No, you didn't!
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
I saw him.
Look. Look. Look.
Leon.
Listen to me.
This can ruin you.
If you let your emotions
take over,
your mom will be affected,
as well as your siblings.
We're doing this for them.
I'm doing this for you.
You didn't kill him.
You didn't kill anyone.
That's on me.
Uncle Mike and I got this.
This is on us.
Can you please promise me?
Leon, please?
Can you promise me?
Please?
This didn't happen.
Okay? This didn't happen.
Let's just talk
about it again later, okay?
Please?
Dad.
[FEDERICO] Promise me.
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
Is he dead?
[SNIFFLES]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Look.
I'll be gone for a few days.
Your mommy and siblings
can't see me like this.
You know,
just tell them I have a...
I have an
emergency business meeting.
Look after them, okay?
Come on, son.
I'll be back soon.
Okay?
I love you, son.
[LEON SNIFFLES]
Take care.
I love you, Dad.
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's impossible that
what happened has nothing to do
with Dad and Uncle Mike's death.
But the man is dead.
I've killed him.
Did anyone know that
we were responsible for it?
Does he have an accomplice?
Does he have family
who wants to avenge him?
If what Roi says is true...
Bang! Bang!
[LEON] That someone else
murdered them,
and that person is still free...
They didn't kill each other.
There's someone else.
My siblings could be in danger.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I need to protect them.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
"Papa: I'll go to Belina.
I have a meeting there."
"Like I told you, anything for
our mission. Take care always."
"Juan: Okay, Pa.
For our mission."
"Pa, pick up the phone.
Did you see something?"
"Papa? Where are you, Pa?"
Where are you, Pa?
I hope nothing bad
happened to you.
But while I'm waiting,
I will continue our mission.
I'll search for the treasure.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- I didn't mean it.
- I'm sorry, sir.
A knife?
Why does he have a knife?
Now that the truth is out,
how will it be
with the Almazans?
We need
to reconcile with them.
Propose to me first.
- Propose?
- Yes.
It's not like everything's okay
once we're at the hotel.
As if they didn't say
anything bad about us.
I'm hoping that before I leave,
our families reconcile.
Maybe it's time to revive
the annual Hotel 88
team building!
- Team building! Team--
- Sari.
You are invited to join.
Will Kiko be there?